<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370150188258-1</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too many manager skirt chasers at Boeing.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370150188258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370150564821-2</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get off of welfare and foods stamps and get a job for a change! Another black man deadbeat. Pay your child support deadbeat.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370150564821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370150959745-3</Id><Title>Who posts to themselves the most on this board.and why? -EOM Vote now.</Title><Msg>EOM</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1370150959745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370150994505-4</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phil C and Harry S both were too busy chasing Boeing employee women because both were ugly old fat men and could not get any outside Boeing . Phil had his secretary , and Harry got a gold digger Boeing women . Phil and Harry are like the trolls here on the Boeing message board, just worthless to humanity so they come here to pay Texas holdem with their short stacks all of them are male pigs no ethics , greedy short sighted and failures for Boeing and failures to society like the Boeing trolls worthless #$%$</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370150994505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370151036034-5</Id><Title>#$%$ and thier handouts coming to an end. Thanks Obumer high gas prices and no handouts and of course no jobs,</Title><Msg>great future for America. All on your watch, and stop blaming Bush, he was five years ago.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370151036034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370151440772-6</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well you're the one who posted some weeks ago that 55 was the low. Learn how to use the historical price tab on Yahoo. I just stated facts about the low from March 2009 til today. Don't get your panties all in a bind over it. Not everyone gets in on the anniversary years of 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 etc. Those that bought near the low in spring 2009 and held have made a nice profit. Trying to make your point by using the 5 year number is just as bad and misleading.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370151440772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370151624612-7</Id><Topic><Title>787 fundamental cost saving</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370093338880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"no response means I'm right" as someone posted recently. HarHarHar</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370151624612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370152293233-8</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The world's largest hedge funds have bolstered their equity holding so far this year, increasing their exposure by over 5 percent and adding more to Boeing than any other stock, according to financial research firm FactSet." How about those hedge funds? Did they have any effect on Boeing's stock price? More than the buyback?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370152293233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 01:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370163535394-9</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hedge funds and Boeing stock . hummm, The price of the stock reflects the demand, period. . So since the Boeing stock is not doing as good as Airbus your argument is moot. Boeing has publically stated how much Boeing stock Boeing will buyback. I could find that Hedge fund information as a trailing fundamental after the fact by 3 months , I am a chart based stock trader. What a hedge fund does, is reflected in the stock price today. and over time. So your new argument is Boeing stock price is based on real hedge fund money instead of using shareholder money. Right. that would make your argument better then, how ?Since Boeing stock is poor compared to Airbus over time no matter who is not too interested in buying it. Remember supply and demand set the stock price. ? In other words the stock price sucks , So once more your point is? If you want to stipulate that hedge funds are buying Boeing and not the public information that Boeing is buying their shares back to inflate teh stock price go ahead. In any event Boeing stock price over time is very poor compared to Airbus Fundamentals do not mean much since popcorn Ben, turned the Fed into a stock market bubble gum machine. you need to watch stock charts now as the stock market is rigged . However if you still want to . go with fundamentals then you have to ignore foulmouthharbor, as his delivery advertisement does not consider the 4 year late , hugely discounted 787 original price , then further discounted with late delivery penalty, compounded by lack of use penalty for the cost to the airlines of the 3 month grounding Next extra rework cost to fix many 787 still on the tarmac that have to be reworked or scrapped, Then add the 30 billion extra cost to build over the original outsourcing estimate of 5 billion. Faoulmouthharbor is strictly acting as a advertising agent for Boeing all his delivery is gibberish posts are gibberish</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370163535394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 04:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370165354166-10</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FOAD, facehole.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1370165354166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 05:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370182548382-11</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer Americans Call Themselves Economic Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130222046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual the mentally deficient and mathematically challenged hooz omits all the facts, possibly driven by desperation in Obonz's falling ratings. The % of people identifying themselves as economic conservatives was below the 2013 level in both 2007 and 2008. Economic liberals were also lower in 2013 compared to 2012. The bottom line is that 81% of the country does not accept economic liberal thinking.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370182548382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 10:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370182665110-12</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AlQaeda is at the top of your list as Adversaries. If that is true and you are never wrong ANSWER THE QUESTION...WHY ARE MULTIPLE MAINSTREAM NEWS SOURCES REPORTING THAT OBAMA IS ARMING MUSLIM BROTHERHOOD AND ALQAEDA TERRORISTS ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370182665110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 10:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370182989550-13</Id><Topic><Title>Va. school board member asked to resign over racist Michelle Obama emails</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045437149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apropo given the subject matter. As your bosom buddy genna would so eloquently chortle "har har har har".</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370182989550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 10:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370183010316-14</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look...Ventura is quick to point out that he ALWAYS goes into each of his programs with an open mind. In some cases he debunks the conspiracy...the faked Moon Landings and the other where the Illuminati are acutally Lizard people are among them........Your sentence on the Pentagon plane "It had to go somewhere" answers it self. Ventura was asking QUESTIONS ...I</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370183010316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 10:23:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370184735783-15</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow Wayneker you really have lost it. Listen, I don't hate you. I suppose you should be pitied but I can't even muster that emotion because you are such a schlimazel. You just go ahead and live in your la-la land thinking that Boeing is an evil empire and with your after the fact made stock fortunes The board knows the score.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370184735783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 10:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370186352816-16</Id><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Msg>...but as we now know, what the Arms dealers and the New World Order want...they get !! Sixty-eight percent of Americans say the United States should not use military action in Syria to attempt to end the civil war there if diplomatic and economic efforts fail, while 24% would favor U.S. military involvement.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370186485085-17</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty opposed any opposition to m uslim made disasters,. huh spart</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370186485085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370186549860-18</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whoops, typo, s/b past, current, and future tense sparty opposeS any opposition to m uslim made disasters,. huh spart</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370186549860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370187449865-19</Id><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Msg>New problem, seems the sensors that alert all that the battery/AP is on fire, they are also subject to failure. Well if your feet start to feel hot its either on fire or you have a medical condition that makes them feel hot. Stop and think about it. Why should the passengers need to know if that explosive and fire prone battery is on fire. What good will it do, won't get you to your destination any faster, won't put out the fire. Keep em in the dark its better for everyone if they don't know their ride is making smoke. Good morning Boeing, and good morning to that particular group, you know the ones that are such a drag on you.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370188875368-20</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JAL grounded again Boeing 787!</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1370188875368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 12:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370190261123-21</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now why is it that you fail to mention, as the headline reads, "NO RISK TO SAFETY"? Evidently you don't realize that practically every flight, no matter how makes the plane, has some kind of anomaly but your on it like stink on #$%$ when it involves a Boeing plane.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370190261123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 12:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370191880336-22</Id><Topic><Title>The Latest Fatwa</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370139149409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 22:12:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now Sunni freedom fighters are not only battling Hizboolah terrorists in Syria but also in Lebanon. It will be also a hot time in Lebanon and Syria tonight</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370191880336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 12:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370192026792-23</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeveritass, I have a better question for you! Freveritass, since I had nothing to do with this report, how is it that you can't let a accurate public report by any users on the public Yahoo finance blog, go by you without making it a plot against you and Boeing ? You are not the Yahoo message board administrator, are you learning yet? freeveritass , you should change your name to communistveritass. Mrs. Communistass, there is nothing wrong with this news item, it is a important factual report on a outsourced plane with a 4 year history of delays, 30 billion over cost and a 3 month grounding caused by poor management . What is new here ? Let me tell you , MrsCommunistass, this news is the type of real fundamental news that can over time lead to lower stock price for Boeing . Like the Boeing Company advising that the 747 profitability going forward is limited and not as expected . Mrs Communistass, stock value can be hurt so your angry instead of smart enough to move to Airbus up who has an ascending stock price over time. As a matter of fact Airbus shareholders have made 146% gain in stock price value in the past 5 years compared with your stock Boeing up only 21%! So 100k then is now 120k or 100K in Airbus is now 246K now are you learning that your being angry does not make you any money, yet ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370192026792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 12:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370192272270-24</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats one of the drawbacks to Yahoo mb's, no review before posting. It happens frequently afte posting corrections needs to be made.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370192272270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 12:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370192428386-25</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing is moving engineering out of Seattle , the Governor and the Senators of Washington after spending 3 billion to keep the 787 in Everett , now that they understand the ethics of Boeing Chicago are we learning yet. Politicians , you need to keep the tax base up so are you listening now? Washington State politicians remember to advertise "Hey Airbus! We have some highly skilled engineers and empty hangers here in Seattle. Come on over!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370192428386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370192519372-26</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any news ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370192519372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370193020771-27</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try not to confuse badmouthing the union with criticizing and calling out the SPEEA leadership. Shuper is right - Goforth and his cronies are lunatic fringe that have no sense of balance as it pertains to reasonable discourse and negotiation with Boeing mgmt. The Eng/Tech's got an unprecedented salary increase and he still recommended voting down the offer - that's absurd. He made the pension issue a make or break deal when, in fact, it didn't pertain to anyone already in the union! All he succeeded in doing was kicking the hornets nest. Now look what's happening to Puget Sound engineering org's - they're moving out of town - and I don't blame mgmt. one bit for doing it. SPEEA needs to wake up and get rid of this guy.</Msg><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370193020771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370193024144-28</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The article you are discussing contained the statement, 'No Risk To Safety'. The flight was temporarily delayed, and has long since left the ground.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370193024144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370193213829-29</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I correct myself. The passengers left in another plane.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370193213829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370194740920-30</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, good to know the plane was held for inspection or at least the passengers all went home alive ! That is good, all Boeing needs now is a 787 airplane crash and all aboard dead to seal the fate of the 787.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370194740920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370195082723-31</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you ba nonsense- FYI- a decade ago, another person posting here had similar comments Re: Say WHAT ?? by: migit_minded_managers 08/02/02 11:36 am Msg: 172570 of 426164 Tincanguy, Your assessment of SPEEA is based on a false premise. That makes it difficult to understand why Shuper is opposed to its current structure. The confusion can be found in how you characterized what is happening. You stated that Day and Dunn and their small group of malcontents are hell-bent on destroying the substantial power that SPEEA has acquired in the past few years. Later in your statement you give credit to the leaders of the union for being responsible for turning SPEEA into a real union. That is the key to your misunderstanding. It was the members as well as the non-members who made this a union with teeth. Bofferding has never done anything for the union. He has worked for himself. It was those that SPEEA was supposed to represent that made this a real union. Everybody else just jumped on the bandwagon and have taken credit for what the members and non-members did, in opposition to what the leadership recommended we do. It achieved quite the opposite of what the leadership thought we could do. Remember that Bofferding recommended both contracts that the company offered last time. The membership rejected both. Bofferding said we had to accept the offer because a strike would fail. He said there were all the non-members who would not join in a strike. He was wrong. He was way out of touch with the membership because he only cares about himself. Those who voted for Day did so because they wanted Bofferding out. That was the first step. Day was known to oppose Bofferding.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370195082723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370195125646-32</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of those I spoke to on the strike lines had no affection for Bofferding. Those who did surprised me with their naivety. They pointed to his bringing in the big boys as key to our building strength. That isn't what happened. The big boys didn't want to look foolish for ignoring this little band of engineers who were bringing a DOW 30 company to its knees without their assistance. The big boys didn't want to be relegated to a role of being insignificant. They HAD to join in to keep themselves viable. While there are many examples of how Bofferding has manipulated the union and its staff to meet his needs, the real key to his disservice to the membership is that he was surprised by the membership's rebuke of his lackeys in the last vote and felt threatened - as well he should be. Then, rather than consider the needs of the many, and the negotiations soon to take place. he orchestrated the most devisive action he could, solely to eliminate the competition which threatened his dictatorship. Regardless of what you hear, Bofferding is behind the recall. Thr result of these actions is to split the membership. The turnout for the recall vote was larger than the initial vote. While the recall effort was a success it may well prove to be a failure. The vote was close and many of those who opposed the recall have stated their willingness to sign for decertification, should the opportunity present itself. How much more destructive can one be?</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370195125646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370195177736-33</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thr result of these actions is to split the membership. The turnout for the recall vote was larger than the initial vote. While the recall effort was a success it may well prove to be a failure. The vote was close and many of those who opposed the recall have stated their willingness to sign for decertification, should the opportunity present itself. How much more destructive can one be? This doesn't do much more than scratch the surface, but it should give you some basic understanding of what is going on among the active membership and why those who support the basic concept of union representation and strong unions would oppose their own union. Shuper doesn't oppose SPEEA. Shuper opposes the way SPEEA is controlled and manipulated for the benefit of one, in the guise of being good for everyone else. Millions and millions of people have been duped by that argument before and no doubt will be in the future. People are basically sheep. They follow the leader and refuse to acknowledge the shortcomings of those leaders until they discover too late the truth. The current stock market is a good example of the masses buying into what the leaders proclaim - not dicsovering the truth until it cost them more than they would have been willing to pay if the facts were clearly laid out.. Posted as a reply to: Msg 172533 by tincanguy</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370195177736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 13:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370196028675-34</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>during the time I had lunch at the Plant II Cafeteria and once in awhile in the executive dinning room. The rumors ran rampent, even while they were present. For a while I worked in the PP&amp;C organization Darrel E. was caught promising promotions to willing beautiful women for sex. Gerry Mathews was another. I guess my point, high level management playing the field instead of Working. The company protects these managers.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370196028675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370196597489-35</Id><Title>787 outlook for June</Title><Msg>From NYC787 site: I am expecting deliveries for June to be higher than May with at least 14 if not more 787s being delivered to customers. Here's my prediction for June: Aeromexico (ILFC)* - 1 Air India - 1 ANA - 2 British Airways* - 2 China Southern - 1 Hainan Airlines* - 2 LOT Polish - 1 Japan Airlines - 1 Norwegian (ILFC)* - 1 Qatar Airways - 1 Thomson Airways - 1 Many of the airplanes that would be slated for delivery in June already have had their B-1 flight or more. 4 customers will be receiving their first 787s this month as well.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370196597489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370196816081-36</Id><Title>Blame Boeing CEO phil C, he purchased a bankrupt Md not SPEEA</Title><Msg>Die was cast” Analyst Hamilton said “the ink was barely dry on the paper when the first layoffs were announced for SPEEA and the first jobs were moved elsewhere.” Yet he said the union’s stance in those negotiations probably wasn’t decisive. He thinks Boeing Chairman Jim McNerney was already determined to transfer work. “That die was cast,” Hamilton said. “Jim McNerney does not like Washington state. He doesn’t like unions. SPEEA could have got down on its knees and genuflected to Chicago, and they would still have moved jobs out.” Once Boeing moved to Chicago, it was so obvious . I retired and moved. Attention Washington State governor and lawmakers, are we learning yet? Its time to tax Boeing out of Washington State, to recoup the 3 billion in tax breaks you gave Boeing. Remember that done Boeing in return for the 100% production of the 787 in Everett. What happened to that deal ? Now, get busy lawmakers its yoru turn to get out of bed with Boeing and start the reality check! Washington lawmakers, you need to hang up the sign to Airbus ! Washington State has 100k of skilled and motivated engineers and workers who will to accept better wages and benefits and retirement and medical that Airbus pay right now . Finally to Boeing Chicago please get out of Washington State now . Washington State needs the space for Airbus Thanks for the old school memories , you know the designed and made in the USA 737, 747, 767, and the designed in the USA 777 . Please take the 787 and get out of Washington State now and take the 737 with you to the slave state , just get out of here your not wanted. Washington State will watch your new plane the 787 flying firebox failure, 30 billion over cost and 4 year delayed and grounded for 3 month with yet another new problem, over the next 15 years fail! We will watch Airbus pull away in the lead and china take over second place in 15 years .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370196816081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370197007222-37</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thje 787 is grounded!</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1370197007222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:16:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370197563416-38</Id><Title>outlook for June</Title><Msg>Airbus stock trend up in price! from up 146% for 5 years and Boeing trend in price down from 5 years trend only up 21% so BHT see you on June 30 ! freeeveritass, foulmoutharbor, joedokes45 sparticas91111 the facts will tell if trolling and BHT work for stock price appreciation or if stock chart reading makes money any bets ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370197563416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370199698971-39</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes...that's why I oppose Obama giving arms and material support to Bin Ladin Brigade, AlQaeda and Mu slim Brotherhood.....Sorry I am not on AlQaedas side...even if you are</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370199698971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 15:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370199929102-40</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty is not the person to attempt to influence anyone. He's the dude that supports Jesse Ventura for Pres. for Gawd's Sake.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370199929102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 15:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370199939989-41</Id><Topic><Title>787 outlook for June</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370196597489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:09:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be surprised if some extra inspections are scheduled to insure some ducts were not inadvertently sealed during upgrade.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370199939989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 15:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370200749232-42</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer Americans Call Themselves Economic Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130222046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More correctly stated, chemical_ali_infested is a climate change denying freak doofus.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1370200749232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 15:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370203158472-43</Id><Title>Don, it's sad that you blame the union and not the current Boeing Management</Title><Msg>You know, Don, I find it amusing that you badmouth the union that made it possible for you to have a good retirement. What you should be doing is to post on the poor management that the company has. Most who work there would be able to identify with that</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370203158472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 15:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370203264347-44</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it for Wayne not knowing how to find the low of BA in the last 5 years.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370203264347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370203503294-45</Id><Topic><Title>Blame Boeing CEO phil C, he purchased a bankrupt Md not SPEEA</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370196816081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:13:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don shuper if you want to assign blame , how is the union to fault for anything / they negotiated your pension and wages for the 30 years you worked for Boeing . If not for the union your could have been fired at will for anything or northing at any time. if you made it for 30 years in Carolina you would still be living in a trailer. Don, your set for life , you have a great pension and Social Security check , are you such a loser, you don't know you won? Your retired take the money and enjoy yourself the current Boeing workers get less and will not have a pension and the work will be gone from Washington state in the next 30 years</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370203503294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370203770448-46</Id><Title>JAL Dreamliner Grounded After Sensor Glitch, Kyodo News Says</Title><Msg>A problem with an air-pressure sensor on a battery container in a Japan Airlines Co. (9201) 787 Dreamliner made by Boeing (BA) Co. caused the airline to use another plane for a Tokyo-to-Beijing flight, according to Kyodo News. Japan Airlines said the sensor showed a difference in air pressure between the outside and inside of the container during a safety check before the departure of Flight 21 from Tokyo’s Haneda airport, the news network reported. Yesterday, Japan Airlines and ANA Holdings Inc. (9202) restarted Dreamliner flights. The twin-engine jetliner, the first built chiefly of composite materials, was grounded for more than four months because of battery malfunctions. Susan Bradley, a spokeswoman for Chicago-based Boeing, said that the company was aware of the issue and was working on it with the airline. So Boeing admits the 787 is still a failure or laugh now still teething after 4 year delay and 3 month more to fix the problem laugh now , it has been a few days of resumption of 787 flights . As I have said numerous times, the 787 is not , any time soon done teething, because the engineering control for the plane was not done by Boeing Seattle USA engineers .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370203770448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370203775269-47</Id><Topic><Title>Don, it's sad that you blame the union and not the current Boeing Management</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370203158472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 15:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking back on all the big unions and what they've done to the industtry doesn't speak volumes for you?...the auto industry, the commercial air industry? It is management's fault?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370203775269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370204647872-48</Id><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Msg>Joe Dokes 25 your a fool, You are not close enough; if you were working for Boeing then you would understand the problem. . If I were sitting in your house and watching the ocean I would be a lot more civil. I have been on the wrong end of Boeing Executives, they are like slave masters in the way they treat workers. And they are ignorant. I agree they should be in China not Carolina right now if they want cheap labor. Probably know that China would just kick them out after they set it up and run it with Cheap Executives too! Sad to say the 2010 version of Socialism, versus Capitalism versus Communism means Communism wins! Trust me you are better off just skipping the BA message board. if joe dokes 25 is the average moron</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370205938955-49</Id><Topic><Title>outlook for June</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370197563416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:26:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is a time capsule that I said when the 787 was only 3 years late , how am I doing !"The urgent need is to keep China out and build a better plane than Airbus. So Boeing with the 3 year 787 delay, has allowed the both the new Airbus plane and the Chinese with their C919 airplane to catch up and is going to be able to compete with the 737. The new 737 ( MAX) cannot be built until the 787 is working. Much of the technology of the 787 will be used on the 737 if it works. I think the sizzle of composite, especially for the wing is not ready and Boeing has blown a huge lead to nothing. Frankly, the 787 concept was flawed with a 100% integrator model at the same time as Boeing went from aluminum to composite, and also allowed too much engineering to be done by the contractors, with a final shot in the head by not keeping tight control over their contractor progress, a perfect failure on the heads of risk taking Executives. So if the gamble worked Airbus and China would have copied it. There was no need to get risky; Boeing should have made the other players take the gamble and watch. Now the program is in dire straits and the opportunity to be conservative and use 100 years of skill, knowledge and ability of the IAM and SPEEA workers is only now being deployed like it should have been in the start. The 787 is a 10 year project and is 3 years behind schedule or 2WWII time periods. The Sonic Cruiser project was finally abandoned by December 2002 in favor of the slower but more fuel-efficient 7E7 (later renamed Boeing 787 Dreamliner).[8] Much of the research from the Sonic Cruiser was applied to the 787, including carbon fiber reinforced plastic for the fuselage and wings, bleedless engines, cockpit and avionics design.[9]</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370205938955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370207778419-50</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tend to be able to connect the dots. When major unions take down their companies time, and time again, I tned to get it. When the national economic picture is very bleak, and big unions don't care they are willing to go out on strike anyway, I tend to get it. You don't have to be smarter than a 5th grader.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370207778419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370208483557-51</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Japan Airlines Co. said it had to replace a Boeing Co. 787 with another plane after a sensor indicated a problem with the Dreamliner’s battery box. Tape covering two holes used to regulate airflow in case of a battery fault in the auxiliary power unit was not removed after testing, triggering the alert, JAL said in a statement today. “The battery showed no abnormality,” it added. ... it looks like the sensors do work - perhaps a bit sensitive But that is GOOD news ! \</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370208483557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370209039233-52</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who do you support? More of the SAME insanity that has brought America down ? I don't think youre a control freak liberal..that leaves a war mongering bankrupting Neo Con......Give me a break</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370209039233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370210417556-53</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i've often thought sparty is a m uslim made disaster just like our occupier n chief...one things certain, he's their useful idiot just like our occupier n chief</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370210417556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370210751079-54</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In other words, AIRBUS RULES.</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1370210751079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370210786114-55</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"i've often thought" Come on... nobody believes that.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370210786114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370210829106-56</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And I use to be an OWNER of the Boeing Co. When people invest their hard earned money, and buy co. stock they are OWNERS fot he co. I take that very seriously. Most of you union dudes don't see it that way. And all the damaging strikes the union went on I sure didn't blame Boeing's poor stock performance on Management.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370210829106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:07:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370210891909-57</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate women?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1370210891909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370211277571-58</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer Americans Call Themselves Economic Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130222046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like an insurgent.......or a collaborator.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370211277571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370211314816-59</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big surprise, the moore-ons helped put a m uslim made disaster in our highest office. i've often though sparty is a m uslim made disaster, certain he's one of their useful idiots.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370211314816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370211511098-60</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big surprise, the moore-ons helped put a m u s l i m made disaster in our highest office. i've often though sparty is a m u s l i m made disaster, certain he's one of their useful idiots. funny the way dem board moderators, err community dope peddlers, i mean sparty, picks and chooses the responses he wants on topic page</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370211511098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:18:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370212632213-61</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As an OWNER of the company, you NEVER had a snowflake's chance in he11 of telling anyone in the company to try something your way. In the real world, shareholder initiatives, if they can be passed at all, are only ADVISORY to the board and execs. That makes shareholders more like bag-holders.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370212632213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370213465017-62</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, and it wasn't easy. I worked countless hours to help elect Barack Obama... twice.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370213465017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370213743007-63</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne thinks the communism works best, like sparty, equal pay regardless of output, their warped vision comes from experience wayne and sparty contribute nothing, the commune pays their bills</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370213743007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370213899196-64</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep - ben there done that !!! got the T-shirt ! Four times BA gets very nervous when challenged by formal shareholder proposals and proponents At Chicago- wife and I had an escort assigned to get water- keep me from press, but very polite and following me to the mens room. It was the two security people sitting in front of our reserved seats that gave us that warm fuzzy feeling. One with a buzz cut carrying heat and with SS style earphones and head on a swivel, the other one having the stature of a NFL line backer who was partly asleep, but left the impression that he understood perhaps 3 commands Sic em being the primary two - and maybe stop being the third. Looking across the isle and sitting in front of two IAM types was a duplicate pair</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370213899196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370214195096-65</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, we know, day in day out peddling dope on the BA board...while the commune pays your bills</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370214195096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370214284847-66</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer Americans Call Themselves Economic Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130222046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I include myself among a group of scientists that are considered "lukewarmers" with respect to climate change. I once was a warmist but the science now only supports a transient climate response of 1.3 degreesC for a doubling of CO2. The Paleocllimate records show short term warming periods where temperatures rose 10 degreesC in as little as 50 years prior to the industrial age. Do you think you will die from a 0.5 degreeC temperature increase over the next 70 years? What is it actually that you fear about climate change?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370214284847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:04:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370214294521-67</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the union goons don't have any enforcers, do they shupe</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370214294521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370214616482-68</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as a Teamster working on the Seattle waterfront we went out on strike for just over a month. The president and other officers brought represented workings to the tabled and cheered victory we got what we demanded. Then we listened to the cheering and howling for several minutes then we got around the the numbers. No change on medical or dental, we did get an hourly wasge raise of .05. We figured we would have to work for 100 years to get the money back.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370214616482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370215059190-69</Id><Title>Obonzo administration accused of torturing a Mus lim American abroad</Title><Msg>Mother Jones reports that a law suit has been filed.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370215059190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370215608676-70</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unions are a microcosm of communism, they're unfair AND unsustainable. the impact of collective extortion can be seen in gov't and education, at a state n local level, wa, california, detroit...why the IRS is even under the influence</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370215608676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370215723311-71</Id><Title>88 IRS agents should be prosecuted to the full extent of the law all doing major time</Title><Msg>until the president is impeached</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370215723311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370216048262-72</Id><Title>Fewer and fewer Americans call themselves economic Liberals</Title><Msg>maxing out the credit cards has never made sense. Spending money you don't have never has made sense. Stabbing the next two generations in the back, so I, you and me can have what others can't have never made sense. Liberal spending ideology is a lose lose proposition</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370216048262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:34:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370216132805-73</Id><Topic><Title>88 IRS agents should be prosecuted to the full extent of the law all doing major time</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370215723311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:28:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make the connection. The agents were IRS UNION MEMBERS, that hated the conservative TEA PARTY folks, and were in the pocket of Obama. He meets with them on Mar. 31st (the union President), and the next day choose their conservative Tea Party target.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370216132805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370216252281-74</Id><Topic><Title>88 IRS agents should be prosecuted to the full extent of the law all doing major time</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370215723311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:28:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tea Party.. Isn't that the Koch bros. #$%$ party..</Msg><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370216252281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370216387961-75</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Way to go dufussjoe.. Let's get some non union minimum wage earners to built our planes.. hat make you happy Doink head.</Msg><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370216387961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370216473404-76</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well There you are Uselessjoe.. It helps when you are..</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1370216473404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370216537234-77</Id><Topic><Title>Don, it's sad that you blame the union and not the current Boeing Management</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370203158472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 15:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's always managements fault.. They usually screw the shareholders with big payoffs.</Msg><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370216537234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370216611612-78</Id><Topic><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now you want government help.. You're such a loser.</Msg><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370216611612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370216672193-79</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bishop Romney was, and is a joke. get your head out of your rear end..</Msg><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370216672193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370217301160-80</Id><Topic><Title>HOLDER downgraded to MOSES !!</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370127238025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 18:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holder is supposed to ENFORCE the lay ...not GIVE the law....he does neither in the most LAWLESS administration of all time...PS...In addition to Fast and Furious Benghazi and the latest IRS gate...you can go back to the False Flag at Oklahoma City where he covered up the biggest FBI black op.of all time (until 9-11 of course).</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370217301160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370217374303-81</Id><Topic><Title>88 IRS agents should be prosecuted to the full extent of the law all doing major time</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370215723311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:28:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to interviews by the House Oversight and Government Reform Committee. orders came from Washinton DC. I would look to grant immunity to the agents for testimony against the Obonzo administration. Agents were just doing what they were told to do. The higher ups need to be punished.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370217374303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370217609983-82</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not with guns and brute force - neither IAM or SPEEA AFIK- Instead the Officers that do not kiss ED behind get recalled or verbally disparaged or ignored !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370217609983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 20:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370218059681-83</Id><Title>Yahoo Email ..We will read your email and Tuff Toe Nails if you dont like it !</Title><Msg>As of June 1, all Yahoo email users are required to upgrade to the company’s newest platform, which allows Yahoo to scan and analyze every email they write or receive. According to Yahoo’s help page, all users who make the transition agree to let the company perform “content scanning and analyzing of your communications content” to target ads, offer products, and perform “abuse protection.” Concerned..You should be.....Get Startmail which is completely protected...(Google Start mail home for more details) If you are reading this..you are the resistence</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370218059681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 20:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370218232475-84</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Email ..We will read your email and Tuff Toe Nails if you dont like it !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370218059681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 20:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Emailing through Yahoo means surrendering your privacy, whether it’s your own account or your friend’s,” says Harvard-trained privacy expert Katherine Albrecht, who is helping to develop StartMail, an upcoming email service that will not scan its users’ correspondence. “It’s time we start paying attention to these policies, because they’re growing more shockingly abusive every day,” she added.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370218232475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 20:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370221106070-85</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus 99991 you buy Boeing then ha ha , the rest of the world in June of 2013, is with Airbus up 146%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370221106070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 20:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370221210791-86</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored50 then move to China since you want to get away from Communism and go with the new Democracy its called work you to death and get rid of CEO's too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370221210791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370221267599-87</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored 50 your not qualified to state what any one thinks but your self ,and that is up to question</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370221267599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370221360758-88</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joedokes45 you still play with dots? Well that explains it then grow up move out of your mother's house and start drawing pictures freehand and keep your hand off your short stack too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370221360758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370221444588-89</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joedokes you take it seriously and then you call people dudes? really dude , really</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370221444588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370221572868-90</Id><Title>joedokes takes it seriously about stock ownership ,then calls union workers, dudes , really? seriously wow</Title><Msg>Joe Dokes , move out of your mothers house, stop connecting the dots and get a job</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370221572868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370221637416-91</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep the stock chart says so and the number one plane maker for 11 years is the Airbus company</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370221637416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370221826070-92</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freevertass another question ,why would you own Boeing up a pathetic 21% in 5 years, if you are a stock trader, you should be in Airbus up 146%in 5 years look it up on CNN money hummm</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370221826070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370222518817-93</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer Americans Call Themselves Economic Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130222046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suuuuuure you're a scientist. So is my golden retriever. She's good at the "science" of retrieving stuff. With education, luck, work, and some brains, you might achieve this level of science expertise. So far 0-fer-everything for chemical ali infested.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1370222518817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370223222401-94</Id><Topic><Title>HOLDER downgraded to MOSES !!</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370127238025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 18:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, I imagine that some folks simply do not understand what they are saying. And in the case of MSNBC's equation between Holder and Moses, it is just such an example of that. So, I will grant pure ignorance in their case. But, to be equated with Moses is in the extreme that should invoke much scorn. There are only a small number, less than a handful, of persons in the Old and New Testaments whose death and transition to Heaven were heralded: Enoch (great grand father of Noah, Genesis 5); Moses (Deuteronomy 34); Elijah (2 Kings 2); and Jesus (Acts 1). Except for Moses, the others were translated directly to Heaven from their earthly domain. In the case of Moses, he was lovingly and carefully buried by the Lord Himself (Deuteronomy 34:6). Moses had spent so much time with the Lord directly that he had taken on such a radiance, a glow, that people could not stand it. Thus, Moses had to wear a veil (Exodus 34) when he was among the people. I guess I do not see any resemblance between Moses and Holder. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1370223222401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370223504954-95</Id><Topic><Title>HOLDER downgraded to MOSES !!</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370127238025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 18:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only resemblance is both were/are male. But what else would you expect from msDNC ?</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370223504954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370224140286-96</Id><Title>No battery problem--tape mistakening left on 2 vent holes. Nothing is grounded at all</Title><Msg>Need to improve their check-off list----that about it.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370224140286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370224210138-97</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true--tape left on 2 vent holes by error. No grounding. No remaining problem. Short at it again</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370224210138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370224314186-98</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Totally lie. Tape was on 2 vent holes by error. They replaced the plane for the flight and there is now no remaining problem. JAL didn't ground anything. Tell the truth if you can on these boards</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370224314186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 21:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370225198906-99</Id><Topic><Title>HOLDER downgraded to MOSES !!</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370127238025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 18:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, There is a great proliferation of irreverence these days. And this MSNBC person is just such an example of that. Years ago, folks would never say something like this. It is very disturbing. I tried to imagine that it was simply ignorance, but I wonder. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1370225198906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 22:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370225440000-100</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings batteries</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370187449865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank-you.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370225440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 22:10:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370226021396-101</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the union works for underperformers like yourself huh wayne, those worth their weight (though they may be compelled to join a union) don't need unions, they're able to compete, function, and prosper as individuals on their own merits.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370226021396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 22:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370231087449-102</Id><Topic><Title>JoeDokes25 hates unions, blames them, not boeing mangment</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370204647872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The companies greatest asset is people. It is also their greatest liability. The IAM and SPEEA do whatever it takes to do the bare minimum. There are some very good employees, however it is the many that suppresses the few that actually want to work and perform admirally in terms of FOD, cleaniness and overall care for the quality. Wonder why the company is moving out? All one has to do is look inward and decide if what you bring to the table each and everyday is enough...</Msg><Username>trujrnyfan</Username><Timestamp>1370231087449</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 23:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370231251207-103</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I currently don't own or buy individual stocks, but those who bought BA in Spring 2009 have made over 200 percent. Just facts.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370231251207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 23:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370231771983-104</Id><Topic><Title>Polls show Americans oppose military involvement in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370186352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 11:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much oil does Syria have.......isn't that the only reason we care???</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1370231771983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 23:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370231921188-105</Id><Topic><Title>88 IRS agents should be prosecuted to the full extent of the law all doing major time</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370215723311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:28:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only regret I have is they were discovered.....Tea Party ain't done nothing but complain.....when do they construct......something</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1370231921188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 23:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370231986359-106</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better choice than Mitt or Rick Santorum or Bachman or......</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1370231986359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 23:59:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>