<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370493845497-1</Id><Topic><Title>“SHE GOT IN MY FACE”</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1370467066461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's really funny is that she was heckled by a LWNJ lezzie.</Msg><Username>db0865</Username><Timestamp>1370493845497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 00:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370495317848-2</Id><Title>The Audacity of Aho1es</Title><Msg>barack appoints useless nations liar head of the nsa and moochelle reminds donors she doesn't care what they think</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370495317848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 01:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370503512398-3</Id><Topic><Title>what is better ACAD,TSLA or Boeing and being competive in pay at Carolina compared to China hype or real?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370467848273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:30:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing said," we will create engineering centers for future work in South Carolina and possibly in Kiev, Ukraine." That is just another example of cheap outsourcing, the story, hiding the fact that the CEO hates unions, and he wants to be able to make sure Boeing employee's have no job rights. McTurdy thinks, that way he can be king , not an employer, a absolute ruler, and that is how companies fail like kingdoms fail. With no unions the company success is all based on the intelligence of the leader. With Boeing past and present leaders Phil C , H. Stonechipher and now James McTurdy, the CEO's ability has never been in dispute, just ask none other than the famous , Jack Welch , he told McTurdy to get lost If Boeing had a aerospace version leader of Steve Jobs or Elon Musk caliber , then it would be a different story. .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370503512398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 03:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370509894060-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Audacity of Aho1es</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370495317848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 01:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sick... sicker... censored50 The last is as sick as it gets.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1370509894060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 05:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370510454194-5</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's in their DFC manifesto. The DFC Little Red Book.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370510454194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 05:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370510528834-6</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you trying to change the subject, like a DFC would?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370510528834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 05:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370511277942-7</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Dipstick! Why don't you want states? Are you some sort of pathetic DFC?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370511277942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 05:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370512689003-8</Id><Topic><Title>what is better ACAD,TSLA or Boeing and being competive in pay at Carolina compared to China hype or real?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370467848273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:30:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>say hows that EADS Rafael aircraft sale to Brazil working out for you dell george?? Looks like the A350 is going to crash on its first flight any day now eh? What about that A400M- is somebody going to ever take delivery or have there been too many insurmountable obstacles in that fly by wire software????????? HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370512689003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 05:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370518696919-9</Id><Topic><Title>what is better ACAD,TSLA or Boeing and being competive in pay at Carolina compared to China hype or real?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370467848273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:30:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My son can't help the fact that he won't get over his termination from Boeing. But his resent desire to steal his mothers panties has us beside ourselves. I wish he would start taking his medication seriously.</Msg><Username>dellgeorgesr</Username><Timestamp>1370518696919</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370523057264-10</Id><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Msg>'Report: NSA Secretly Collecting Phone Records Of All U.S. Verizon Calls' The National Security Administration is secretly collecting phone record information for all U.S. calls on the Verizon network. “Under the terms of the blanket order, the numbers of both parties on a call are handed over, as is location data, call duration, unique identifiers, and the time and duration of all calls,” reports The Guardian, which broke the story of the top-secret project after it obtained record of a court order mandating Verizon hand over the information. The contents of the call are not recorded and it is also not known whether Verizon is the only cell-phone carrier complying with the massive spying project. The court order concerns all calls to, from, and within the United States. The Senate’s tech-savviest member, Ron Wyden (CrunchGov Grade: A), has been discretely warning citizens of these kinds of secretive government projects. “There is now a significant gap between what most Americans think the law allows and what the government secretly claims the law allows,” wrote Wyden and Senator Mark Udall to embattled Attorney Eric Holder. http://techcrunch.com/2013/06/05/report-nsa-secretly-collecting-phone-records-of-all-verizon-calls/?icid=maing-grid7%7Chp-laptop%7Cdl1%7Csec1_lnk3%26pLid%3D323987</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370523753636-11</Id><Title>Wells Fargo raised the price target $115-120$$$</Title><Msg>Go Boeing$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1370523753636</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370524213121-12</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does the first gay DFC worship uncle Ho?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370524213121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370525101105-13</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only reason the Federal Government exists is to facilitate the tyranny of special interests.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370525101105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370525683559-14</Id><Title>Has Obammy fundamentally transformed America into a Socialist Welfare state</Title><Msg>Or is he still working on it.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370525683559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370525952876-15</Id><Topic><Title>Has Obammy fundamentally transformed America into a Socialist Welfare state</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370525683559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's tryin desperately hard. Success, or failure will depend on the point in time the govt goes bankrupt like Russia did. At that point if the socialists can convince the voting public that it wasn't their fault, that those evil Tea Party folks wouldn't allow them to fully impliment their recovery effort, then yes, BO, and the pinko left will have been successful.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370525952876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370525991354-16</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ONLY? Care to elaborate?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1370525991354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:39:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370527312415-17</Id><Topic><Title>Has Obammy fundamentally transformed America into a Socialist Welfare state</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370525683559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dopey joe you still here - we thought you had bailed out of here and moved to Mogadishu by now- they haint got no soshulism in Mogadishu- you could even be your own tax collector there if you could achieve warlord status- and you can have all the guns you want so what are you waitin for</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370527312415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370527543016-18</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that would be health insurance for one thing- something even ignorant rednekks need- especially when they come down with dread diseases like cancer and diabetes which the private ins companys wont insure - but then your kind would never come down with anything like that would you econquack BTW I have told you several times that you don't know squat about economics so why don't you change your 'nym?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370527543016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370527737950-19</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we need the feds to keep an eye on the kind of crooks that want to amass all the guns in world, reinstitute slavery, end Roe Wade protection for women, protect womens right to vote and a lot of other crimes that you rednekks like to commit and prosecute you if necessary</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370527737950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370527808626-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Audacity of Aho1es</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370495317848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 01:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cliberg one of sparty's EU costume supports aho1es sparty's dependent on crooks</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370527808626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370528466367-21</Id><Topic><Title>Has Obammy fundamentally transformed America into a Socialist Welfare state</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370525683559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A druglord in Chicago can do the same.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370528466367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370529941697-22</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More from Huffington post: The order was granted by the secret Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court on April 25 and is good until July 19, Britain's Guardian newspaper reported Wednesday. The order requires Verizon, one of the nation's largest telecommunications companies, on an "ongoing, daily basis" to give the NSA information on all telephone calls in its systems, both within the U.S. and between the U.S. and other countries. The newspaper said the document, a copy of which it had obtained, shows for the first time that under the Obama administration the communication records of millions of U.S. citizens were being collected indiscriminately and in bulk, regardless of whether they were suspected of any wrongdoing. _____________________________________________ It is hard to find any justification for of spying on people not suspected of any wrongdoing. Is this the USA or the USSR? In the seventies the left called for a revolution to overthrow a government they felt was abusive and lying to its citizens. Now the left is in power and they are the source of lies and abuse and consider any suggestion of 'revolution' against them as treason. The liberal left currently in power has become far worse than the government of the 1970s and is on the pathway to becoming a power hungry totalitarian regime.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370529941697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:45:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370530600115-23</Id><Title>The Obamy Police State</Title><Msg>Despite his clear and popular promises to the contrary, President Obama has not shifted the balance between security and freedom to a more natural state—one not blinded by worst fears and tarred by power grabs. If anything, things have gotten worse. Killing civilians and U.S. citizens via drone. Seizing telephone records at the Associated Press in violation of Justice Department guidelines. Accusing a respected Fox News reporter of engaging in a conspiracy to commit treason for doing his job. Detaining terrorist suspects at Guantanamo Bay, despite promises to end the ill-considered Bush policy. Even the IRS scandal, while not a matter of foreign policy, strikes at the heart of growing concerns among Americans that their privacy is government's playpen. And now this: The Guardian newspaper reports that the National Security Agency is collecting telephone records of tens of millions of customers of one of the nation's largest phone companies, Verizon. If the story is accurate, the action appears to be legal. The order was signed by a judge from a secret court that oversees domestic surveillance. It may also be necessary; U.S. intelligence needs every advantage it can get over the nation's enemies. But for several reasons the news is chilling. Verizon probably isn't the only company coughing up its documents. Odds are incredibly strong that the government is prying into your telephone records today. Issued in April, the NSA order "could represent the broadest surveillance order known to have been issued," according to The Washington Post. "It also would confirm long-standing suspicions of civil liberties advocates about the sweeping nature of U.S. surveillance through commercial carries under laws passed after the Sept. 11, 2001, terrorist attacks." This appears to be a "rubber stamp," order, reissued every few months since 2001. As is the case with all government programs, the systematic snooping into your telephone records is unlikely to ever expire without public outcry. Congress is full of hypocrites. Liberals who criticized Bush are less incensed with Obama. Republicans who bowed to Bush are now blasting Obama. The next time your congressional representative criticizes Obama for curbing civil liberties, ask if he or she would vote to repeal the Patriot Act, the post-911 law that handed unfettered power to the intelligence and military bureaucracies. Most won't. The Bush-Obama White House hates transparency. President George W. Bush and his vice president, #$%$ Cheney, were justifiably criticized by Democrats (none more successfully so than Obama himself) for their penchant for secrecy. Obama promised that he would run history's most transparent administration. By almost any measure, on domestic and well as foreign policies, Obama has broken that promise. It is the lack of transparency that is most galling about the security versus civil liberties debate under Obama, because it shows his lack of faith in the public. Americans know a high level of secrecy and dirty work is needed to keep them safe. Most trust their president. Many approve of his job performance. Still, they expect and deserve an open discussion about how to fight terrorism without undermining the Constitution.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370530600115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370530960662-24</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't like or approve, but it is all part of the Patriot Act, demanded, created, and supported during the GOP administration. I don't remember you complaining when the GWB administration was using it, I do remember you cheering and disparaging anyone who was objecting to it. Your lack of consistency and morality is the heart of your hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1370530960662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370531682091-25</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Occasionally get failure to post, but trying 2 or 3 times to post the same thing usually gets it. Had a few things, like about Strategic Reserve never post or get deleted.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370531682091</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370531838133-26</Id><Topic><Title>The Audacity of Aho1es</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370495317848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 01:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>susan rice will now oversee the dnc campaign functions at the nsa, gathering records, spying, intel gathering to augment the dnc's already massive government arsenal. how does the thumb in your eye feel America</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370531838133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532176483-27</Id><Title>Employers Firing Less but also Hiring Less.</Title><Msg>For you victims of socialized government education that means unemployment may be dropping but so is the number of available jobs. It is poverty and economic depression by attrition.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370532176483</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370532970591-28</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna is a prime example of the federal government wasting taxpayer's money producing utterly ignorant victims of socialized government education. He is a real putz.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370532970591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370533447211-29</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima wants a communist state with the right to kill innocent babies. He also is in favor of slavery to the state. He is a well programed victim of socialized government education with a deep hatred of liberty. Does CDS ring a bell?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370533447211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370533596135-30</Id><Topic><Title>The Audacity of Aho1es</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370495317848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 01:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty err EU err spaz err censored deluded soul</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1370533596135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370534883095-31</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rover wants a communist totalitarian nazzie state with the right to kill innocent people of color. He also is in favor of slavery to the state or anybody else. He is a well programed victim of extreme right wing as well as totalitarian communist hate culture with a deep hatred of other peoples liberty. Does CDS ring a bell</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370534883095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370535003841-32</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>without the Federal Government the tyranny of special interests such as the Kochs, Mellons, Olins, Duponts, Waltons would reign supreme</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370535003841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370535104524-33</Id><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Msg>5 years age Einstein's peer and successor at Princeton, Freeman Dyson, went public that in his discussions with other top physicists, the physics foundation for the modeling of global warming was not complete nor accurate. I've been called a climate change denier on the BA board for offering scientific data and evidence that climate models are problematic and that modeled CO2 feedback effects have been exaggerated. Now James Hansen has admitted in British press the following. "The climate models often get criticised-and it is a valid criticism-that there is a lot of physics that we may not even have in the models, and that which we do have in may be inaccurate." - James Hansen Those with engineering degrees on this board who have worked with models realize GIGO does not make for good models. All future claims of disaster are based on these climate models as they are 'tuned' to less than robust data from the past. That tuning has caused the model estimates of warming to diverge to almost 2 standard deviations from measured temperature data. I knew Hansen would cave after reading one of his Physics Arxiv papers 3 years ago. I'm surprised it took him so long but politics always clouds scientific judgement with activist scientists.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370535134985-34</Id><Title>WSJ article Weak Signs For U S Output. Factories Suffer Worst Slump Since End of Recession</Title><Msg>Had an idea falling Unemployment was due to benefits running out. More on Food Stamps even in Mexico. 8% payroll tax can't be helping either. Three + years ago read an article going back to George Washinton about Cabinet and appointee experience in field. Kennedy had a 23% rating but this Obama looks like his criteria was something other then experience he got a 13% rating. Like no experience needed to apply. This just might be the start of the fall.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370535134985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370535317877-35</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One guy out of thousands of scientists- this is what is meant by consensus--now who you gonna believe thousands of scientists or a maverick scientist who is in the pay of the Mellon Bank and his rednekk booster named infestid</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370535317877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370535808557-36</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post Ali......the problem with any modeling is you can't take a minute amount of time in the scope of billions of years and establish a meaningful trend. It's like watching what you wife did the last two minutes and predicting what she will do the next 40 years. Most of the rabid warmers are academics, those who work in the real world dismiss it as folly.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370535808557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370536029004-37</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's nice to see that not everyone is OK with trashing human rights to privacy. Correct me if I'm am wrong but GWB didn't spy on every US citizen that was a Verizon customer. As I recall (again correct me if I have it wrong) GWB monitored only cell phone activity with overseas countries suspected of supporting terrorism. I don't mind and in fact support Obama in monitoring 'suspects' of terrorist engagement both overseas and domestically, but monitoring 100 million American citizens is an abuse of the patriot act in my view.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370536029004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370536222788-38</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pssssst........zosima.....consensus is not science.......most likely they never told you that while you were becoming a victim of socialized government education. Most major scientific discoveries occur contrary to the current consensus of accecademics.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370536222788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370536301983-39</Id><Topic><Title>WSJ article Weak Signs For U S Output. Factories Suffer Worst Slump Since End of Recession</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370535134985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WSJ statement reveals the numbers are screwy. "Weekly initial claims fell by 11,000 to 346,000, slightly higher than had been expected. The data was the last read on the labor market ahead of Friday's payroll report, which is expected to show 170,000 jobs added in May, a modestly higher rate than April." This falling rate due to running out of benefits.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370536301983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370536671284-40</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Verizon is probably not the only cell phone company that the government is leaning on. It's the only one we know about, and that is thanks to an English newspaper. The US media is in O's pocket. The stone walling continues and the leftist media aids in all the cover-ups. Makes you proud to be an american! NOT</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370536671284</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370536937591-41</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consensus? When has consensus been the basis of science? Consensus is meaningless. "No amount of experimentation can ever prove me right; a single experiment can prove me wrong." - Albert Einstein "Science is the belief in the ignorance of experts." - Richard Feynman</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370536937591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370537905649-42</Id><Topic><Title>Topping?</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1370448330518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Popped again at the open, didn't make it to 100, and is dropping fast.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1370537905649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:58:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370537966151-43</Id><Topic><Title>what is better ACAD,TSLA or Boeing and being competive in pay at Carolina compared to China hype or real?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370467848273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:30:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so for you BHT, today my stock ACAD is up another 5% and your stock Boeing is up .53% which is better? as I pointed out TSLA , after the 100% gain in a 16 day run, the day the short squeeze took place I said to sell and b e ready for a stock market pullback . I was right, it is so simple I read s stock chart not listen to the BHT people. Or if your a day trader watch TSLA for day trades as it goes sideways in a pattern you can day trade it. until it breaks out of the Bollinger band , hopefully up , but it does not matter you would have made 100% in 16 days I do this on a regular basis. Just think spartacus9991, a retired MD engineer, if he had followed me in Apple until a great leader died , Steve jobs, died and been with me since I called ACAD and since I called TSLA instead of being a BHT , he would have made a lot more money than the 5 years run on Boeing .spartacus99991 has suggested so many forms of misinformation over the years , Spartacus99991 claims he owns no Boeing stock and yet he is a BHT that means he has no purpose here, if you buy that then buy Boeing ha ha ACAD up 8.5% for 5 days ACAD up 235% year to date , ACAD up 1065% for one year Boeing down 1.87 for 5 days and up 31%for ytd and for one year up 43% which is better ? You should have booked your 100% profit on TSLA on the short squeeze and be out now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370537966151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370538276458-44</Id><Title>ACAD or Boeing which is better? ACAD up 1065% for one year and Boeing up 43% for one year !</Title><Msg>ACAD up 5% today, 6.5% for the 5 days , up 235% for the year to date and for one year up 1065% boeing not so good, down for five days 1.87% minus, for the year to date 31% up for one full year from today up 43%. After the 16 days 1005 gain on TSLA , then as I stated you should be out until TSLA breaks above the Bollinger band or day trade it if you know how as long as it has a range. BHT, good morning , how is your day going? mine is great up 5% on top of a 1060% year gain on ACAD ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370538276458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370538318028-45</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it when di*does liked rover have to use my words to bi*ch about me.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370538318028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370538402440-46</Id><Topic><Title>ACAD or Boeing which is better? ACAD up 1065% for one year and Boeing up 43% for one year !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370538276458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:04:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ACAD for 5 days should be 8.5% not 6.5% and TSLA should be a gain of 100% not 1005 thanks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370538402440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370538679496-47</Id><Title>Republicans hate free market competion !!</Title><Msg>A republican proposal, backed by the N.C. Automobile Dealers Association, would make it illegal for Tesla, or any other car maker, to bypass dealerships and sell directly in the state. The proposal cuts at the heart of Tesla’s business model: selling luxury cars over the phone or Internet and then delivering them to the front door of high-net-worth customers. Still, the proposal was unanimously approved by the state Senate’s Commerce Committee on Thursday, despite concerns about the state dictating who should be allowed to sell an automobile. North Carolina is the latest forum for the clash as auto dealers around the country have mobilized, mostly without success, in legislatures and in the courts to block Tesla’s direct car sales. “They’re trying to insulate the dealer franchise model from any competition,” said Diarmuid O’Connell.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370538679496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:11:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370538949671-48</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans hate free market competion !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370538679496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:11:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Competition !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370538949671</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370539067386-49</Id><Title>Airbus gives a clue on business plan going forward , what? no firebox needed?</Title><Msg>Europe's Airbus could increase narrowbody aircraft production once a revamped version of its A320 medium-haul jet enters service in late 2015, a senior executive said. "After we introduce the A320neo we could easily imagine going to rates like 44 per month, and in fact as we go towards the end of the decade, 50 a month," said Tom Williams, executive vice-president of programmes at Airbus, in a media briefing. "We don't need to make decisions on these things today. We want a sustainable industrial model," he added. Despite high orders for the latest fuel-saving models, last year Airbus suspended plans to go beyond a targeted production level of 42 a month for current A320s, which it has now reached.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370539067386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370539294194-50</Id><Topic><Title>what is better ACAD,TSLA or Boeing and being competive in pay at Carolina compared to China hype or real?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370467848273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:30:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that means he has no purpose here" Wayne, trying to say who should be able to post here? Mostly what I do is quote your disinformation and correct it. Just trying to help you. I've done very nicely, thank you, without following your advice.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370539294194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370539720138-51</Id><Topic><Title>ACAD or Boeing which is better? ACAD up 1065% for one year and Boeing up 43% for one year !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370538276458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:04:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about that BHT still trying after all these years first he lost on Apple next he lost on ACAD and recently he missed 100% on TSLA in just 16 days spartacus99991 could have doubled his investment portfolio so sad being a BHT !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370539720138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370540117956-52</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worse than a " climate change denier", you've been called a LIAR because you misrepresented the data at the U of I website, comparing late-spring pack ice this year to late-summer pack ice in the past.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370540117956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370540220061-53</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right, Rover. There's no such thing as a Bear Market because you have to normalize all the data in the context of the entire history of securities exchanges. Is that an unfair characterization of your claim?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370540220061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370540316960-54</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Discoveries occur contrary to Current Dogma, but when they are validated they become part of the consensus.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370540316960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370540611141-55</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US media won't criticize Obama or Holder 'cause they're afraid someone will call them racist.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370540611141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370540647778-56</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahahahah, this #$%$ ran his election off getting rid of these policies. YOUDUMBF--KS VOTED FOR CHANGE I THOUGHT?.............HAHAHAHAHAHA LIBDEM MORONS</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1370540647778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370540793586-57</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obots are just mirror images of the Bushbots of years past, and they can't see it. "Who needs rights?" they ask. "We can trust the President." It was stupid under Bush and it's stupid now.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370540793586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370541043145-58</Id><Title>spartacus99991 and IGZ and ACAD which is better? well IGZ is not a real stock so spartacus99991 any points?</Title><Msg>ACAD compared to IGZ by waynedickenson961 • Mar 21, 2013 3:57 PM Flag a well known Boeing hack attempted to keep up with me on my stock picks after I answered his debate style with a demonstration, not with words but in the few days it took me to make that gain on ACAD. I have been in ACAD for over a year anyway. I made 26% on ACAD this morning and am out. added today fyi-( not really just did not want spartacus9991 to get a great stock on my back until it is run up to the body of the trade gone- like now probably) This certain Boeing hack goes by the name spartacus99991, he claimed a stock IGZ was up 144% so what was my point. har har har ?a certain Boeing hack, spartacus9991, without knowing how to trade stocks, picked the wrong stock. Reason , IGZ , is not a stock , never was a stock, and never will be a stock it is a symbol used to test the trading platform, So a certain person who is a Boeing hack, named spartacus99991, should probably use one of his other avatar names now as he has just fooled himself sorry Less Less so spartacus99991, in just 19 days I made over 60% on ACAD while you pretended to show me up with a stock you thought was a real stock and it is a symbol used to check out the trade platform. Once more I remind you BA is not a buy or sell short, it is a poor stock investment compared to Airbus better stocks and the Boeing business plan and the Boeing mismanagement is the reason Boeing is always going to be a stay out stock.... More</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370541043145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370541086819-59</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a federal gov't can establish and maintain 800 military bases around the world. Does anybody know why we need 800 military bases around the world? How many foreign bases do the Chinese have? The Russians? If we don't need a federal gov't, then we don't need 800 military bases.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370541086819</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370541191526-60</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 and IGZ and ACAD which is better? well IGZ is not a real stock so spartacus99991 any points?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370541043145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>har har har B HT get over it your not making the money and I am your a hack and that is all you know how to do !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370541191526</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370541214265-61</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voted for change, got more of the same (and some of it worse)--and now they're in denial, unwilling to admit their mistake.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370541214265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370541968691-62</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are in error. Look at my comment again as here is the exact quote: "Polar ice extent is currently higher than 1986 Based on University of Illinois Cryosphere data." Polar ice means both poles and current means that day as in I was comparing the sea ice extent for that day with past sea ice extent for the same day. I DID NOT COMPARE MAY SEA ICE EXTENT TO AUGUST SEA ICE EXTENT AS YOU SUGGEST. You are usually more accurate than this. http://finance.yahoo.com/mb/BA/#mbt=How%2520Come%2520Dims%2520%25u2026&amp;mbl=http%253A%2F%2Ffinance.yahoo.com%2Fmbview%2Fthreadview%2F%253B_ylt%253DAs03xHttGD2te3Jlxs3hSO3eAohG%253B_ylu%253DX3oDMTB2OHBjOG42BHBvcwMyMgRzZWMDTWVkaWFNc2dCb2FyZHNYSFJVbHQ-%253B_ylg%253DX3oDMTBhYWM1a2sxBGxhbmcDZW4tVVM-%253B_ylv%253D3%253F%2526bn%253D7d8d92d6-c287-340e-8126-be6d06b3eecf%2526tid%253D1369881109294-1e1710fa-0454-42d0-83cd-b00f0f68bb75&amp;mbtc=mb-tab-topic</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370541968691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:06:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370542152138-63</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad for this country, they voted for this. But of course everything will be blamed as racist. The future looks very bleak.........god help our kids........</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1370542152138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370542199177-64</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I posted this with a kink to the message and in case it gets removed I'm posting it without the link. You can find my exact words in my history by cutting and pasting my quote into the Boeing search box. You are in error. Look at my comment again as here is the exact quote: "Polar ice extent is currently higher than 1986 Based on University of Illinois Cryosphere data." Polar ice means both poles and current means that day as in I was comparing the sea ice extent for that day with past sea ice extent for the same day. I DID NOT COMPARE MAY SEA ICE EXTENT TO AUGUST SEA ICE EXTENT AS YOU SUGGEST. You are usually more accurate than this.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370542199177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370542267012-65</Id><Title>which is better TSLA leeadership or Boeing leadership/</Title><Msg>It is real easy to figure out, tesla leader Elon Musk is a serial success read up on him and Boeings CEO is s serial mediocre performer at best, or as jack Welch told the Boeing CEO time to get out of GE your not good enough to stay here . Tesla’s highly efficient designs aren’t just being used in-house anymore.Toyota (NYSE: TM) is using power trains created by Tesla to power its recent electric RAV4. Deals like this help Tesla diversify its revenue streams and increase its volumes to gain bigger supplier discounts. Toyota recognizes that it can either spend thousands of man hours designing and creating its own power trains, or it can license out the leading technology. Toyota can still utilize its sales network and gain volume discounts from suppliers; this sales network is one of Toyota's strongest moats against up-and-comers like Tesla. Lets not forget even a BHT attempted to stop the Wayne train by pointing out that the CEO of Boeing consulted Elon Musk about the Boeing lithium battery failures. My answer is I have been a holder of TSLA and recently pulled out on the short squeeze gain and am eager to get back in at a lower price and am taking positions on low points as the stock trades into the Bollinger band. If you followed me, you would have made 100% on TSLA in just 16 days if you follow BHT the c-men group, your making less than you should. Especially if you own any Boeing. stock as a long time holder your not doing as well as those that own Airbus . Airbus will be flying high in stock value when their new 787 -777x killer comes online . wait and see or better yet buy Airbus now while you can get a great price . Airbus for 5 years is up 150% from today, not some low low point that you can not get today as spartacus99991 has been peddling ! Boeing today is up only 35% going back five years . Airbus ,long term is a gain on 100k investment now is worth $250,000 and a Boeing five year investment is now worth $135,000 which is better</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370542267012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370542342377-66</Id><Topic><Title>which is better TSLA leeadership or Boeing leadership/</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370542267012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let me give a thumbs down for the BHT , oh sorry , I can't do that to my own user comment , please help me out BHT ha ha !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370542342377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370542650115-67</Id><Title>which plane is better the 787 boeing or the new airbus plane a look at leaders business risk answered the question</Title><Msg>European planemaker Airbus has vowed to avoid the problems which led to the grounding of Boeing's 787 Dreamliner as the clock ticks towards a maiden flight seen as barely one week away. Chief Executive Fabrice Bregier said Airbus had focused on reducing technical risk in its costliest ever development project, drawing an implicit contrast with battery problems that led to the 787's three-month grounding earlier this year. "This aircraft is mature with limited technology risks ... and I have no appetite at all to launch a grounded aircraft," Bregier said in a major annual briefing at Toulouse, France.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370542650115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370542778521-68</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not much of a fan of this either, but, did anyone watch the interview with Holder? There is a strange way of getting those warrants. That system needs to be reworked. Also, did anyone notice in the Verizon case that they are not collecting listening to or recording the conversations: just gathering data on from location to location. This should tell you already that they have something in mind and that it has to do with a certain overseas location. And lastly, if this were more of the same, which it's not, why was it so much better under any other administration?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370542778521</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370542892845-69</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Touché.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1370542892845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370543816918-70</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instead of documenting your silly claim, why don't you back it up? When I went to the U of I website, the prominently-featured chart on the front page showed that your claim was not true. Where do you get your information? Why do you uncritically allow propagandists to make you lie?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370543816918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370543974223-71</Id><Topic><Title>which is better TSLA leeadership or Boeing leadership/</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370542267012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Airbus for 5 years is up 150% from today, not some low low point that you can not get today" So, Great Stock Trader (G.S.T., or is that F.E.B.), how would one buy Airbus today at the price of 5 years ago? It's so easy to point out the flaws in your arguements. HarHarHar</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370543974223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370544157003-72</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 and IGZ and ACAD which is better? well IGZ is not a real stock so spartacus99991 any points?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370541043145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much di you make on SSN or SLW or FFIV from 2 years ago? LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370544157003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370544264349-73</Id><Title>Twin Engine Large A/.C.</Title><Msg>Do I not remember ads many years ago statine twin engine were unsafe for polar flying by Airbus? Now they are trying to close the gap in large aircraft with a twin engine A-350. Go figure.</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1370544264349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370544398543-74</Id><Topic><Title>ACAD or Boeing which is better? ACAD up 1065% for one year and Boeing up 43% for one year !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370538276458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:04:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, I've more than doubled my total investments from 2 years ago, just not in individual stocks, but mutuals and Orange County real estate. Thank you for asking.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370544398543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:46:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370544543940-75</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We've got Senators such as Wyden and Udall warning us about it, now. You make comforting assumptions based on no evidence. The NSA's new $2 billion data center in Utah will open in a few months. See the article by James Bamford in Wired Magazine "The NSA Is Building the Country’s Biggest Spy Center (Watch What You Say)". Bamford says " Flowing through its servers and routers and stored in near-bottomless databases will be all forms of communication, including the complete contents of private emails, cell phone calls, and Google searches, as well as all sorts of personal data trails—parking receipts, travel itineraries, bookstore purchases, and other digital 'pocket litter.' It is, in some measure, the realization of the ;total information awareness' program created during the first term of the Bush administration—an effort that was killed by Congress in 2003 after it caused an outcry over its potential for invading Americans’ privacy."</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370544543940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370545101743-76</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He and Ho had a thing going on.........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370545101743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370545249725-77</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!!!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370545249725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370545473743-78</Id><Title>ACADIA. and Thomas Wie and up 1065% year to date and spartacus9991 who do you go with ? humm tuff decision</Title><Msg>ACADIA PHARMACEUTICALS INC, $15.65, up 6.3 pct (1348 ET) Jefferies analyst Thomas Wei expects the company to file for approval for its experimental Parkinson's disease drug in the first half of 2014, saying the company's timeline of filing in the second half is a conservative estim</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370545473743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370545852088-79</Id><Topic><Title>ACADIA. and Thomas Wie and up 1065% year to date and spartacus9991 who do you go with ? humm tuff decision</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370545473743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh wait, wait , that is for one year from today going back , I am sorry spartacus99991, the correct year to date is only 250% , spartacus9991 , watch out he might take acceptation on the minutia, and split a groin muscle, har har spartacus99991 still kent understand, that like spaeling, its not important making money is what counts disinformation by spartacus99991 ios not going to change the facts Boeing is far inferior to Airbus and is about to get a lesson in conservative shareholder protectionof asset new plane flying right the first time every time not the borne daed on the flight line 787 ha ha ha Aribus up 150% for 5 years Boeing forget it a loser stock for long term investment</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370545852088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370545908311-80</Id><Topic><Title>which is better TSLA leeadership or Boeing leadership/</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370542267012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>har har har not worth a comeback</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370545908311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370545951369-81</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 and IGZ and ACAD which is better? well IGZ is not a real stock so spartacus99991 any points?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370541043145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 so how is that IGZ doing har har har</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370545951369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370547004929-82</Id><Topic><Title>Topping?</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1370448330518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing dropping are your pants for cleaning purposes</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1370547004929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:30:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370547151306-83</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ali infested is imitating a former cigarette company doctor still claiming smoking isn't bad.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1370547151306</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370548089738-84</Id><Title>Verizon; " we have an exclusive calling plan for you "</Title><Msg>I received an email from Verizon stating; " we have an exclusive calling plan for you " and im thinking; does it come with or with out NSA spying device !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370548089738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370548262421-85</Id><Title>so one last shot ACAD is up 12% today and over 1065% for one year al all of spartacus9991 BS is not the facts</Title><Msg>so if you started today, ACAD would have make you 12% , or as a day trade still 12%/ I have been in ACAD for over a year and if you read my posts, as listed today I have included the date stamp as user id on the Boeing page to prove it. then read up an Spartacus 9991, look at his IGZ I reference with my reply on ACAD that ACAD report is several months ago just scroll down and look at it today . several months ago I pointed out to spartacus9991 that I was making 60% then on ACAD ina few days, so this Spartacus 9991 is a BHT and a loser big time end of the story. it is clear, I if spartacus99991 had been in with me on AAPL until Steve Jobs died, then ACAD and then TSLA he would be making money instead of flapping his lips and wasting his time spartacus99991 are you learning yet ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370548262421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370548547420-86</Id><Topic><Title>so one last shot ACAD is up 12% today and over 1065% for one year al all of spartacus9991 BS is not the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370548262421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 you just missed 12% gain today on ACAD after several days of up and a great new report are you listening now ? Remember Boeing is down .91% for 5 trade days , ACAD is up 12% today figure it out spartacus9991 your a fool BHT</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370548547420</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370548771765-87</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...“For sure” would mean p</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1370548771765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370549069629-88</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo doesn’t seem to allow “greater than” or “less than” signs, pretty stupid. In my first paragraph I meant to say “..in highly respected medical journals with impact factors of greater than 4.500,...” and I closed out with ““For sure” would mean p _LESS THAN_ 0.01 or something like that. By the time we know “for sure,” it will probably be too late to do anything about it. But hey, “I got mine” and to hell with the rest of the world, right? That’s what being a 21st century conservative is all about.”</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1370549069629</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370549282481-89</Id><Topic><Title>so one last shot ACAD is up 12% today and over 1065% for one year al all of spartacus9991 BS is not the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370548262421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correction ACAD is up 12.61% not 12 for the day spartacus99991 are you listening now you could have been in when I told you moths ago and istead you attempted to show me up with a stock you didn;t even know was a testing tool IGZ what a fool you are spartacus9991 ego over making money stupid person spartacus9991 like all the BHT you cant win and you cant compete with facts and a good stock chart man! your all done, you were done before you started Boeing is not a good stock the chart tells me that compared to so may other stock and yes on the Down jones two are much better than Boeing so why sell Boeing is a failure and will be dead in 10 years on the basis of bad leadership</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370549282481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370549333263-90</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 and IGZ and ACAD which is better? well IGZ is not a real stock so spartacus99991 any points?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370541043145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 ACAD is up 12.6% today how am I doing now eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370549333263</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370549354923-91</Id><Topic><Title>Verizon; " we have an exclusive calling plan for you "</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370548089738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to WaPo, "The order appears to require a Verizon subsidiary to provide the NSA with daily information on all telephone calls by its customers within the United States and from foreign locations into the United States." So the NSA spying is mandatory, not an option.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370549354923</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370549428041-92</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...By the time we know “for sure,” it will probably be too late to do anything about it. But hey, “I got mine” and to hell with the rest of the world, right? That’s what being a 21st century conservative is all about.</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1370549428041</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370549574410-93</Id><Topic><Title>“SHE GOT IN MY FACE”</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1370467066461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would think that at least one of her 20 or so "assistants" could help her with handlijg herself with more poise. There has never been anyone in the White House at any time that has created such an army of staffers whose sole duties are the facilitation of just the First Lady’s social life. One wonders why she needs so much help, especially at taxpayers’ expense, when even Hillary had only three, Jackie Kennedy one, Laura Bush one and prior to Mamie Eisenhower such assistants, if any, were paid from the President’s own pocket. They sure got the CHANGE part of H&amp;C down pat.</Msg><Username>dmib60010</Username><Timestamp>1370549574410</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:12:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370550407577-94</Id><Topic><Title>Verizon; " we have an exclusive calling plan for you "</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370548089738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Update--according to USA Today, the subsidiary subject to the order is Verizon Business Network Services. ("Verizon stock unaffected by news of NSA data collection") According to the NYT, Senate Intelligence Committee members said the program of compiling a huge database of calling logs of Americans’ domestic communications has been going on for at least seven years. (" Verizon Case Offers Glimpse of Vast N.S.A. Surveillance")</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370550407577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370550701947-95</Id><Topic><Title>Verizon; " we have an exclusive calling plan for you "</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370548089738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:48:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.. yea and ?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370550701947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370552637832-96</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 and IGZ and ACAD which is better? well IGZ is not a real stock so spartacus99991 any points?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370541043145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"no response means I'm right" as someone posted recently. HarHarHar</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370552637832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370552716927-97</Id><Topic><Title>which is better TSLA leeadership or Boeing leadership/</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370542267012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you got a laugh out of your flawed logic.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370552716927</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370552972254-98</Id><Title>Well - its off to the Bilderberg congress again tsk tsk Id invite Spartacus but he would try to smuggle a 500 lb bomb or sumthin</Title><Msg>onto the 747 to off all those Bilderbergers when he got there- Gee I bet you will be lucky to get a couple handfuls of goobers and a coke on the upper deck. Ah for the good old days with Braniff and Pan Am- we had good chow- then there was Air France and the SST and French food- Tough titty there Spartacus</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370552972254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370553172280-99</Id><Topic><Title>so one last shot ACAD is up 12% today and over 1065% for one year al all of spartacus9991 BS is not the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370548262421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, why does it always seem that you're so angry with posters on this board? No one signed up to be your student. Get over yourself. It's just a message board for passing the time of day and getting a few laughs now and then. Those that want to take your advice will and others won't. No more, no less.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370553172280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370553231361-100</Id><Title>The Tea Party hates Jan Brewer now</Title><Msg>The Tea Party hates Jan Brewer now "She is George Bush in a skirt!" a top Arizona Republican angrily declares. How it all went downhill so suddenly By Alex Seitz-Wald In Arizona this week, black is white, up is down, left is right and Gov. Jan Brewer is getting praised by gay Democrats and slammed by Tea Party conservatives. The governor made a name for herself on Fox News and at national gatherings of conservatives like CPAC as a kind of uber-Tea Partyer, who eats scorpions for breakfast, wags her finger in the president’s face at lunchtime, signs strict anti-immigration bills into law in the afternoon, and gives the Tea Party flag the same legal protections as the Star-Spangled Banner by bedtime. But this conservative edifice has come crashing down since she announced in her State of the State address this year, to the shock of everyone, that Arizona would accept Obamacare and expand its Medicaid coverage whether her Republican allies in the state liked it or not. Needless to say, they did not like it. But Brewer’s newfound love of Obamacare was so strong that she vowed to veto every single bill the Legislature sent to her office until they caved on Obamacare. Soon, this one-time darling of the right was getting eviscerated in National Review editorials, yelled at — to her face — by conservative talk radio hosts, and being called “Judas” from the chambers of the state House of Representatives. But Brewer stood firm. After weeks of standoff and a string of promised vetoes, House Republican leaders threw in the towel Wednesday: Jan Brewer, Tea Party hero, had successfully crammed Obamacare down Arizona Republicans’ throats. “This is what we get, because we let her get away with this and we never outed her from the beginning. The chickens have come home to roost,” Frank Antenori, who battled Brewer for years when he was the Republican whip in the state Senate, told Salon. Antenori and another former state senator are now working on getting the 86,000 signatures they need to delay implementation of Obamacare and put the Medicaid expansion on the ballot for voters to decide on. When we reached Antenori yesterday, his frustration was obvious about the national perception of Brewer as some kind of conservative hero, which he blamed on Fox News, launching into a 15-minute tirade about the “so-called Republican.” “She’s a big spending, big government, tax-raising Republican. She is George Bush in a skirt. She loves to spend money,” he said. While Brewer was carefully crafting a facade as a hardcore Tea Partyer for a national audience, conservatives in Arizona say she was quietly fighting the right flank of her own party on everything from the SB-1070 immigration law to budget issues. But with Obamacare, conservatives feel especially betrayed. Conservative blogs in the state have started calling it “Obrewercare” and activists rally against the governor whenever she appears publicly. “The image of a strong, finger-waving-at-the-President leader gives way to a portrait of a puppet politician surrendering her state and turning her back on the wishes of her own people,” one popular blogger wrote. Many of the county-level Republican Parties in the state have passed resolutions opposing the governor’s move on healthcare. “She’s never been a conservative Republican,” Maricopa County Republican Party Chairman A.J. LaFaro told Salon. “We’re really disappointed here. I think she has caused irreparable harm to the Republican Party here in Arizona. There has always been a chasm in the party … but she’s made it worse.” LaFaro was in the state House chamber when Brewer announced her support for Obamacare in January and said “everyone’s jaws dropped. All the Republicans’ jaws dropped in disbelief and all of the Democrats’ jaws dropped in joy.” One of the pieces of legislation Brewer vetoed in making good on her promise to stop anything until the Legislature caved was a “religious freedom” bill favored by the Christian right in the state. “I’m an old friend, and I’ve campaigned with you, so this is not in anger, but in sorrow. I can’t believe you vetoed SB1178, which would have protected the free exercise of religion. What’s going on?” talk radio host Hugh Hewitt asked Brewer Tuesday night, exasperated. Brewer tried to explain herself, but Hewitt wasn’t having it. “I’m just shocked,” he said.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370553231361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370553372370-101</Id><Topic><Title>Top climate scientist admits that models are likely wrong and using the wrong physics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370535104524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>even in Newtonian physics there is consensus with virtually no exceptions in quantum mechanics there is consensus but with a lot of exceptions rover you don't know squat about science or economics or good manners do you</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370553372370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370553847147-102</Id><Topic><Title>so one last shot ACAD is up 12% today and over 1065% for one year al all of spartacus9991 BS is not the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370548262421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Son, quite harassing the nice people and return your mom's panties. Please get over the fact that Boeing FIRED you. We all know you are worthless. Hell, even Walamrt turned you down.</Msg><Username>dellgeorgesr</Username><Timestamp>1370553847147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370554086566-103</Id><Topic><Title>Topping?</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1370448330518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ignore.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1370554086566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370554256892-104</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party hates Jan Brewer now</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370553231361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whup--nuther RINO exposed HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370554256892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370554299020-105</Id><Title>STOP AND REMEMBER</Title><Msg>What happened on this date in 1944. And if you ever get the chance to visit northern France - take a few minutes or hours to visit U.S Soil near Ohama Beach. and consider the following speech that barely touches what happened and to whom President Reagan's Speech Omaha Beach, Normandy June 6, 1944 President Reagan addressed an audience at the United States-France Ceremony Commemorating the 40th Anniversary of the Normandy Invasion, D-Day. Mr. President, distinguished guests, we stand today at a place of battle, one that 40 years ago saw and felt the worst of war. Men bled and died here for a few feet of--or inches of sand, as bullets and shellfire cut through their ranks. About them, General Omar Bradley later said, "Every man who set foot on Omaha Beach that day was a hero." No speech can adequately portray their suffering, their sacrifice, their heroism. President Lincoln once reminded us that through their deeds, the dead of battle have spoken more eloquently for themselves than any of the living ever could. But we can only honor them by rededicating ourselves to the cause for which they gave a last full measure of devotion. Today we do rededicate ourselves to that cause. And at this place of honor, we're humbled by the realization of how much so many gave to the cause of freedom and to their fellow man. ++++</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370554299020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370555215413-106</Id><Topic><Title>STOP AND REMEMBER</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370554299020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:31:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Been there, done that more than once Don and you are exactly right. A sight to behold in ones memory! But alas, current day Dim American majority only care when their O'phones are short on minutes or their monthly G check handout is a day late! Pitiful, just pitiful state of affairs these days!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1370555215413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370555401481-107</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party hates Jan Brewer now</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370553231361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"whup--nuther RINO exposed HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR" Another pitiful Dim laughing all the way to no personal freedom!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1370555401481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370555663286-108</Id><Topic><Title>“SHE GOT IN MY FACE”</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1370467066461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Classless FLOTUS hates ordinary citizens such as this gal. Surprised Mooch Antoinette didn't bless her with "let her eat hair pie"!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1370555663286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370555728806-109</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know as little about the Patriot Act as you do about climate change. Zip. Go back to your mother's basement, please.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1370555728806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370557335748-110</Id><Title>Susan Rice 1, Rand Paul 0</Title><Msg>Susan Rice 1, Rand Paul 0 The GOP’s Benghazi scapegoat gets a promotion, and clueless Paul sacrifices his moral authority by lying about her By Joan Walsh When ABC News published doctored emails about the development of Benghazi “talking points,” and the White House countered by releasing the originals, which told a very different story, the two versions agreed on at least one fact: U.N. Ambassador Susan Rice had nothing to do with the controversial description of the Benghazi attack that she shared in her five fateful Sunday show appearances last Sept. 17. I thought at the time that Rice deserved an apology from Republicans who savaged her, once the truth about the talking points came out, but of course one never came. (Sen. Lindsey Graham countered by saying she “deserved to be subpoenaed” instead.) Now she’s gotten the next best thing: a promotion to National Security Adviser, once Tom Donilon leaves the job in July. The position needs no confirmation by the Senate, so Rice’s GOP critics have nothing to say about her new role. Well, nothing to say that makes a difference, anyway. That didn’t stop them from talking. Sen. John McCain was slightly conciliatory, tweeting that while “obviously I disagree w/ POTUS appointment of Susan Rice as Nat’l Security Adviser…I’ll make every effort to work w/ her on imp’t issues.” On the other hand, Sen. Rand Paul insisted it undermined Obama’s “moral authority…to promote basically the person who is guilty of misleading us over the Benghazi tragedy.” By lying about Rice’s role – she played no part in the behind-the-scenes controversy between the CIA and the State Department over how much and what to say about the attacks – Paul undermines his own moral authority. But lately that’s no impediment to influence within his party. (It’s possible that Paul isn’t smart enough to understand the details of what the Benghazi emails revealed, but that’s not a problem in his party either.) Coming within 24 hours of the president’s announcing that he’s nominating three people to fill three long-vacant U.S. Court of Appeals Washington D.C. Circuit seats, it’s inevitable that Rice’s promotion is being described as representing a new “in your face” approach to his opponents (in the words of James Carville on MSNBC). The timing may just be coincidence: It’s long been assumed that Rice would succeed Donilon, and the outgoing security adviser always planned to leave early in the second term. On the other hand, the fact that Obama didn’t hesitate to announce his appointment of Rice on the day after he defied Republican obstructionists with his three judicial nominees is a good sign. I’m among the observers who saw disturbing racial and gender subtexts in the right’s attacks on Rice. McCain accused her of “not being very bright,” while Lindsey Graham said Rice either “misled the country” or is “incompetent.” It’s one thing to say she did something wrong; it’s another to dismiss her as not up to her job. Even as evidence mounted that Rice had nothing to do with the development of the talking points, and the real blame ought to go to former CIA director David Petraeus, she remained the right’s target. When news of her impending appointment broke, the right-wing Townhall site sampled the old “Jeffersons” theme song for Katie Pavlich’s Rice-bashing column, “Moving on Up: Obama to Appoint Susan Rice as Top Advisor.” If you’re young to remember “The Jeffersons,” on this week that the great Jean Stapleton died, it was a spinoff from “All in the Family” featuring the Bunkers’ black neighbors, George and Louise Jefferson, leaving their working-class Queens neighborhood for the Upper East Side. Norman Lear fans of a certain age can probably still sing the theme song: “Movin’ on up, to the East Side, to a deluxe apartment in the sky …” That’s an interesting association to have when a black woman gets a promotion. Rand Paul will likely continue to run his mouth, cementing his reputation as a guy who’s clueless when it comes to the rights of African-Americans and women. Remember when he told Secretary of State Hillary Clinton that if he were president, he’d have fired her? If he were president, no one with the stature of Rice or Clinton would be found anywhere near his administration. Obama did the right thing defying the Rice-hating obstructionists to appoint it. She deserved better, and now she’s gotten it.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370557335748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370557609759-111</Id><Topic><Title>More abuse of power - Obonzo spying on all American citizens using Verizon</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370523057264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We probably don't know or will ever know what went on during the Bush administration as far as privacy goes. You have to remember that that slimy b*sta*d Cheney had his hands in a lot of things. Bush was just kind of a bystander when it came to anything criminal - that was Cheney's specialty.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1370557609759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370557995469-112</Id><Topic><Title>STOP AND REMEMBER</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370554299020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:31:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing that my post with a segment of a speech by a U.S President immediately gets two thumbs down, as does yours. Yes, I've been there, and to Dachau, to Berlin where books were burned, etc and The church in Strasbourg with a plaque described as "An interesting plaque near the front of the cathedral honors the American "officers, noncommissioned officers, and enlisted men who gave their lives for a free Alsace." The attitude today seems to be ( plagerizing a bit of Churchill ) never before have so many been complaining about the lack of free goodies provided by the few " And I've heard/ read somewhere that many students and those less than perhaps 30 years old believe that Hitler helped us win WW2 against ??? ( Russia ?? ) A FWIW- I've been to the memorial with an underground display in St Petersburg ( nee Leningrad ) and heard an interesting description of the seige when the Germans got to within about 20 miles of the city. One must see it ( underground displays ) to even start to grasp the horror and depravation involved.</Msg><Username>dwshup3</Username><Timestamp>1370557995469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:33:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370559114075-113</Id><Title>Global Warming</Title><Msg>CDC warns about heat-related deaths, blackouts, and major storms.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370559114075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559469039-114</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370559114075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the latest weather in the Kent Bath House?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370559469039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559914342-115</Id><Topic><Title>so one last shot ACAD is up 12% today and over 1065% for one year al all of spartacus9991 BS is not the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370548262421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>poor BHT missed another of my great stocks so sad and avatar name just popped up nice try spartacus99991, Now for more real news -ANGELES, June 6 (Reuters) - Technology entrepreneur Elon Musk on Thursday took to Twitter to say he had no near term plans for an initial public offering of his space transport company, Space Exploration Technologies Corp, known as SpaceX. "Only possible in very long term when Mars Colonial Transporter is flying regularly," Musk tweeted, referring to his publicly-stated desire to establish a colony on Mars. There has been speculation in the media recently that Musk might take SpaceX public. Musk, one of the founders of Paypal, also founded electric car maker Tesla Motors Inc and is the chairman of solar panel installer SolarCity Corp, both of which have logged big gains since going public</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370559914342</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559994838-116</Id><Topic><Title>which is better TSLA leeadership or Boeing leadership/</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370542267012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>latest new from a serial great leader like Steve jobs was for apple until he died, "ANGELES, June 6 (Reuters) - Technology entrepreneur Elon Musk on Thursday took to Twitter to say he had no near term plans for an initial public offering of his space transport company, Space Exploration Technologies Corp, known as SpaceX. "Only possible in very long term when Mars Colonial Transporter is flying regularly," Musk tweeted, referring to his publicly-stated desire to establish a colony on Mars. There has been speculation in the media recently that Musk might take SpaceX public. Musk, one of the founders of Paypal, also founded electric car maker Tesla Motors Inc and is the chairman of solar panel installer SolarCity Corp, both of which have logged big gains since going public</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370559994838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370560194993-117</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370559114075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the latest post from the Mickey Mouse Clubhouse?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370560194993</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:09:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370560241674-118</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 and IGZ and ACAD which is better? well IGZ is not a real stock so spartacus99991 any points?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370541043145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>121.6 should be 12.6% today gain on ACAD</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370560241674</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:10:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370561625476-119</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370559114075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370561625476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370567711879-120</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that a question on a DFC party application?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370567711879</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370567754158-121</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370567754158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370571990006-122</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370559114075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They like to fantasize about Distinguished Flying Crosses and bath houses. They probably have their very own secret password--something funny like "teabag party."</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1370571990006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 22:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370574860544-123</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>floyd, floyd, floyd. You've never been invited to a DFC party? I guess they're pretty hard to get in Flight Simulator 2004.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370574860544</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370575063998-124</Id><Title>I was telling you guys we were entering a Fscist Dictatorship 5 years ago</Title><Msg>Some of you guys are just NOW realizing this isn't a conspiracy theory</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370575063998</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370575152850-125</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a lot of differences of opinion with the administration, but I don't believe in ranting about them 24/7. and none has to do with Holder. That's a Right-Fringe Nut Job obsession.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370575152850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370575273308-126</Id><Title>Finally Brian Williams and Jon Stewart going after Obama</Title><Msg>Brian Williams Joins Jon Stewart In Going After Obama Admin For ‘Draconian’ Crackdown On Leaks by Meenal Vamburkar | 10:12 am, June 5th, 2013video» 20 comments NBC newsman Brian Williams sat down with Jon Stewart on Tuesday night when the pair discussed the controversies the Obama administration has been facing. Namely, the crackdown on leaks. Williams and Stewart agreed that the administration has been “draconian” when it wants to be — but far more lenient when the leaks are advantageous to the White House. “Do you think they’re reading your emails?” Stewart asked, referring to the Justice Department. “Because I have emailed you and said truly filthy things.” Leaks “are a big part” of our democracy, Williams contended. “Leaks are how we have learned about a lot of stories, especially in the last 10 years — this so-called war on terrorism. I think we will find our way. The attorney general is in a rough spot over this and to a lesser extent, the president.” For Republicans “who have desperately thrown their proof at the wall,” Stewart noted these scandals are “worthy of scrutiny.” It partly comes with the territory of second terms, Williams added, pointing to Bill Clinton as an example. All leaks aren’t created equal, but the DOJ “criminalizing journalism” is “enormous,” Stewart pressed. He then questioned Williams about the off-the-record meeting Attorney General Eric Holder had with journalists. “I’ll only say this,” Williams replied. “It’s been unusual to be, in a way, on both sides of the war on terrorism. I have seen the end effect of a drone. I have watched it carried out on a live television screen … It is a rare thing to witness, and that’s the other end of this.” “They leak when it’s to their advantage, and they allow that to go through,” Stewart remarked, prompting an “of course” from Williams. “But when it’s to their disadvantage, they have been very draconian.” While not using a word as strong as “draconian,” Williams agreed tha</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370575273308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370575579034-127</Id><Topic><Title>I was telling you guys we were entering a Fscist Dictatorship 5 years ago</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370575063998</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All according to the prophecies, right, Loon? Like the one where Obama would be forced from office by Sept. 1, 2012?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370575579034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370575665638-128</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370559114075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They all wish they had one, they just don't want to go to the trouble of GETTING one. Bath houses, I mean.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370575665638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370575902625-129</Id><Title>ACLU now saying Obonzo worse than Bush</Title><Msg>The ACLU has no reason to lie.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370575902625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370576052990-130</Id><Topic><Title>I was telling you guys we were entering a Fscist Dictatorship 5 years ago</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370575063998</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you haven't been keeping up with current events with the IRS</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370576052990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370576095963-131</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU now saying Obonzo worse than Bush</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370575902625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush was real bad. Obamma off the Charts</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370576095963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370576200594-132</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its called Federalism Raven. Checks and balances to keep a tyrannical Government in check</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370576200594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:36:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370576458733-133</Id><Topic><Title>ACLU now saying Obonzo worse than Bush</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370575902625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i know how much low information moore-ons/dumbos despise bushhhhhhh, but why not drop the bar lower sparty, we can go much, much, lower, worse than clinton, carter, johnson, fdr, wilson.....</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370576458733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370576671175-134</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>playing with yourself sparty, or does your jihad center have two stools in the ba board cube</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370576671175</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370576808509-135</Id><Topic><Title>I was telling you guys we were entering a Fscist Dictatorship 5 years ago</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370575063998</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're pushing for it, huh sparty, full time parasite AND community agitator</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370576808509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370576886785-136</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370559114075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty has a crush on keith olbermann</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370576886785</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:48:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370577315949-137</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whoops sorry, don't know how i replied to global hoax thread... sparty has a crush on keith olbermann how does one get fired from msdnc AND the al jazeera gore channel? he musta really rubbed the dipstiks the wrong way...i have heard he's unbearable</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370577315949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>