<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364964301615-1</Id><Topic><Title>It takes a Real Communist Type President to Sell guns to Criminals.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364950167896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You either don't know what's going on in Washington or you don't want to know what's going on in Washington. Gee, you must be a liberal.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364964301615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 00:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364984631359-2</Id><Topic><Title>Many American White Men Worship Guns Because they are criminals and they need those muthers</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364957541892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a crazy north Korean cummunist......</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1364984631359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 06:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364984687742-3</Id><Topic><Title>It takes a Real Communist Type President to Sell guns to Criminals.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364950167896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or are you a liberal #$%$?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1364984687742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 06:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364984749499-4</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats want to make it legal to mary their Sisters?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364952198802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 21:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima, a Kent bath house regular........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1364984749499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 06:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364989121967-5</Id><Topic><Title>Many American White Men Worship Guns Because they are criminals and they need those muthers</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364957541892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 22:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you must be a believer that criminals will abide by stricter gun control laws. You’re a special kind of stupid... aren’t you?</Msg><Username>kansasbadman</Username><Timestamp>1364989121967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 07:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364992485907-6</Id><Topic><Title>35 Union Democrat educators to surrender today in massive cheating conspiracy</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364938274167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 17:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That should be no problem for Obama to exercise Executive Privilege provide them the bonuses they wanted, and let them go telling the country in front of his monitor that it was racially motivated, and racial profiling. Just another case of rightwing entrapment of Blacks.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364992485907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364992686971-7</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats want to make it legal to mary their Sisters?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364952198802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 21:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has taken place many times under the BIG TENT...a goodly percentage of libtards are inbreds. Take a good look at most of them. Their eyes are too close together, and they have difficulty seeing around their nose.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364992686971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:38:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364993349507-8</Id><Title>BOEING HAD 500 ENGINEERS FIXING THE BATTERY- THEY KNOW NOTHING !!!</Title><Msg>THE FAA, which is CREDIBILITY COMPROMISED BLESSED THE "TITANIC OF THE SKY', because a lot of FAA EMPLOYEES and MANAGEMENT used to WORK FOR OR WITH BOEING AND ARE CONFLICTED, period. IF the 787 doesn't fly soon, BOEING will be a $40-$50 stock a year from now, OR MAYBE A LOT SOONER ( ????)</Msg><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364993349507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364993523670-9</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING HAD 500 ENGINEERS FIXING THE BATTERY- THEY KNOW NOTHING !!!</Title><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364993349507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you know anything about stocks, think about intrinsic value. The stock has at least $65-70 per share in value without any 787 in the picture. The 787 will come in-its a matter of when.</Msg><Username>anuandamit</Username><Timestamp>1364993523670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364993726188-10</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats want to make it legal to mary their Sisters?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364952198802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 21:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima's frequent flyer card for the Kent bath house is almost full.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364993726188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364994334934-11</Id><Title>CROOKED FAA EMPLOYEES and MANAGEMENT used to WORK FOR OR BA AND ARE CONFLICTED</Title><Msg>THE FAA is BEING INVESTIGATED !! APRIL 24th will change the destiny and future of aviation, IF THE SENATORS and REPRESENTATIVES don't just grandstand, and seriously conflict the circle jerk between Boeing and the FAA . FAA MANAGEMENT ARE SELF ENRICHING THEMSELVES BEFORE THEY WORK FOR BOEING ( as Federal government employees on the road to LUCRATIVE CONSULTING DEALS WITH BOEING) or as BOEING EMPLOYEES and MANAGERS and or OFFICERS ( on the road to government jobs fat pensions and dual retirement deals that are generally available to those who do whatever it takes to keep BOEING doing what it does best, meaning it gets whatever it wants. On the plus side BOEING is a GREAT COMPANY that the USA</Msg><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364994334934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364995223641-12</Id><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Msg>One afternoon, a 37-year-old mother of two heard a knock at the front door of her home. At first, the woman assumed the visitor was a solicitor and told her 9-year-old twins not to answer. When the knocking continued and the door bell began ringing repeatedly, the woman called her husband at work. Her husband advised her and the children to hide while he called 911. The family hid in a crawlspace in the attic. Meanwhile, the intruder had forced his way into the home using a crowbar. After rummaging through the home, the intruder worked his way to the attic where he was met with a .38-cal. revolver. The woman fired six times. The intruder was later transported to a local medical center and was expected to survive his multiple gunshot wounds. (The Atlanta Journal-Constitution, Loganville, GA, 1/5/13)</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364995247407-13</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING HAD 500 ENGINEERS FIXING THE BATTERY- THEY KNOW NOTHING !!!</Title><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364993349507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just like BA stock price went straight up when 787 got grounded. You are the one need education. Sell when there's irrational buying.....Stock Scores</Msg><Username>meinfdia</Username><Timestamp>1364995247407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364995456351-14</Id><Topic><Title>CRIMINALLY CHARGE</Title><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1364413680820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:48:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big show down coming for FAA officials &amp; Boeing CEO's . Some body face prison time</Msg><Username>meinfdia</Username><Timestamp>1364995456351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364995562625-15</Id><Title>Obama Continues to Lie and Keeps Touting Bogus Gun Control Number</Title><Msg>For months we've heard President Obama and his fellow gun control zealots using the line, "40 percent of guns are purchased without a background check." We've heard anti-gunners make this claim under oath in congressional testimony and on primetime television. The problem? The 40 percent figure is an old and bogus statistic that was debunked a long time ago. In January, the Washington Post fact checker gave Obama two pinocchios for using the figure. Rather than being 30 to 40 percent (the original estimate of the range) or “up to 40 percent” (Obama’s words), gun purchases without background checks amounted to 14 to 22 percent. And since the survey sample is so small, that means the results have a survey caveat: plus or minus six percentage points. Moreover, as we noted before, the survey was taken in late 1994, eight months after the Brady law went into effect, and the questions were asked about gun purchases in the previous two years. So some of the answers concerned gun purchases that took place in a pre-Brady environment. Despite the figure being false, Obama has been using it to push for more gun control and will likely use it again today during his trip to Colorado where he we call for federal legislation criminilizing the private transfer of firearms. During a speech last week, Obama asked, “Why wouldn’t we want to make it more difficult for a dangerous person to get his or her hand on a gun? Why wouldn’t we want to close the loophole that allows as many as 40 percent of all gun purchases to take place without a background check? Why wouldn’t we do that?” The oft-cited figure, it turns out, was pulled from a 1997 study done by the National Institute of Justice. In the study, researchers estimated about 40 percent of all firearm sales took place through people other than licensed gun dealers. The conclusion was based on data from a 1994 survey of 2,568 households. Of those, only 251 people answered the question about where they got their guns. PolitiFact tracked down the co-author of the study, Duke University professor Philip Cook, and asked him if he thought the 40 percent estimate is accurate. “The answer is I have no idea,” Cook reportedly told PolitiFact.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995562625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364995602028-16</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING HAD 500 ENGINEERS FIXING THE BATTERY- THEY KNOW NOTHING !!!</Title><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364993349507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure thing about the education which is why I like to read forums to see what people and retail investors like you and me are thinking. You and I dont havent pushed this once the 787 was grounded. If you note the timeline correctly, there was a lag after being grounded and then before the battery resolution was announced-there was a rise of the stock price into the new high. The delay and retraction at the high was and is purely due to the ETOPS which I know you know about. The stock will only rise again when extended range operations are back and deliveries resume. Buy when there's irrational selling!</Msg><Username>anuandamit</Username><Timestamp>1364995602028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364995792563-17</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bryan Lee, owner of the Almond Avenue Pharmacy, had no choice but to fire his .45-cal. pistol when a 31-year-old male entered his store firing a similar model. The gunman entered the store and immediately fired multiple rounds striking Lee’s mother, Sophie Lee, in the leg. Bryan Lee returned fire, causing the man to flee. He collapsed a block away and later died at a local hospital. Lee was unharmed and his mother was expected to make a quick recovery. Lee said, “We just did what we had to do to survive.” (The Fresno Bee, Madera, CA, 1/11/13)</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995792563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364995795540-18</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING HAD 500 ENGINEERS FIXING THE BATTERY- THEY KNOW NOTHING !!!</Title><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364993349507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 08:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Institution pump &amp; dump scheme.</Msg><Username>meinfdia</Username><Timestamp>1364995795540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364995924614-19</Id><Topic><Title>BATTERY MAKER IN TROUBLE</Title><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364434370055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:32:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FAA officials &amp; Boeing CEO's this time</Msg><Username>meinfdia</Username><Timestamp>1364995924614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364996220882-20</Id><Title>POVERTY SPIKES TO 1960S LEVEL - Thanks Obama and Democrats</Title><Msg>The more They Spend to eliminate Poverty the more Poverty Increases. - Democrats find a way to waste and screw up everything in the process everytime they get their hands on tax payers money.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364996220882</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364996609323-21</Id><Title>Intruder killed while breaking into Colorado prosecutor's home</Title><Msg>DENVER - An intruder who forced his way into the mountain home of a Colorado deputy district attorney was shot dead by either the prosecutor or her police officer husband, authorities said on Tuesday. The shooting, shortly before midnight Monday, comes two weeks after Colorado's prisons director was slain as he answered the front door to his home, and two days after the district attorney of Kaufman County in Texas was found shot to death with his wife. An assistant prosecutor in the Kaufman County district attorney's office was shot to death on January 31, and authorities have said both Texas murders and the March 19 slaying of Colorado prisons chief Tom Clements appeared to be targeted killings rather than random acts of violence. In light of the three previous cases, the Colorado Bureau of Investigation is leading the probe into the latest shooting, which occurred in Hot Sulphur Springs, about 95 miles northwest of Denver. "There are no apparent ties to recent shootings; however, investigators continue to pursue all possible leads and background information on this (dead) person," the bureau said in a written statement. Authorities did not immediately release the names of the deputy prosecutor and her husband in connection with Monday night's shooting. The deputy district attorney made a 911 emergency call and reported that a man was at her door "behaving very erratically," police said. The prosecutor then told dispatchers that the stranger forced his way into her home. An altercation ensued inside and shots were fired, leaving the unidentified man dead, police said. A spokeswoman for one of the agencies investigating the incident told Reuters that the prosecutor and her husband, himself a sheriff's deputy, both fired at the intruder, but it is too early in the probe to know who fired the fatal shot. The Colorado prosecutor and her husband both suffered minor injuries and have been placed on paid leave pending the results of the investigation.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364996609323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364996939568-22</Id><Title>Millions Face Surprise Tax Bills Under 'Obamacare'...</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — Millions of people who take advantage of government subsidies to help buy health insurance next year could get stung by surprise tax bills if they don’t accurately project their income. President Barack Obama’s new health care law will offer subsidies to help people buy private health insurance on state-based exchanges, if they don’t already get coverage through their employers. The subsidies are based on income. The lower your income, the bigger the subsidy. But the government doesn’t know how much money you’re going to make next year. And when you apply for the subsidy, this fall, it won’t even know how much you’re making this year. So, unless you tell the government otherwise, it will rely on the best information it has: your 2012 tax return, filed this spring. What happens if you or your spouse gets a raise and your family income goes up in 2014? You could end up with a bigger subsidy than you are entitled to. If that happens, the law says you have to pay back at least part of the money when you file your tax return in the spring of 2015. That could result in smaller tax refunds or surprise tax bills for millions of middle-income families. “That’s scary,” says Joan Baird of Springfield, Va. “I had no idea, and I work in health care.”</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364996939568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364997141295-23</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roger Mundell, Jr. entered his garage one morning only to be confronted by a seemingly rabid bobcat that had gained entry through an open door. The bobcat attacked Mundell, biting him in the face and clawing at his arms. Mundell was able to escape the garage and thought the bobcat was still trapped inside. Before he could warn his 15-year-old nephew, Michael, of the danger, the bobcat was spotted nearby. The cat lunged at Michael grabbing him by the arm. As Mundell tried to pull the cat off of his nephew, his wife, Cindy, then retrieved a firearm and handed it to Mundell who shot the bobcat. The family was treated for injuries and vaccinated for rabies. It was later determined that the bobcat was, in fact, rabid. (Spencer New Leader, Amherst, MA, 1/18/13)</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1364997141295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364997490762-24</Id><Topic><Title>Millions Face Surprise Tax Bills Under 'Obamacare'...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364996939568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:48:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TFB, you voted for change</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1364997490762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364997675504-25</Id><Topic><Title>Intruder killed while breaking into Colorado prosecutor's home</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364996609323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are thinking a lot of this activity is the work of a White Supremacist prison gang, although this last case has not been connected to the others yet, and could be a copycat.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1364997675504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364997682154-26</Id><Topic><Title>35 Union Democrat educators to surrender today in massive cheating conspiracy</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364938274167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 17:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check out the defendants in the Seattle School District fraud case(s).</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1364997682154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364998217868-27</Id><Title>Democrats and Other Liberals Support Lying by their Leaders</Title><Msg>Evidently Democrats are now admitting that if they told the truth no one would support their Communistic policies and programs. Therefore they reason, it's fine with them if the President and Democrat law makers lie since lying is just a means to an end. And the end is the fundamental transformation of the USA into a European socialist type country with Marxist policies. Just look at how many of their policies are built on the Marxist ideology of "from each according to his ability to each according to his needs."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1364998217868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364998515447-28</Id><Title>Is Anyone Sill in Denial about how Much Democrats Lied to Pass Obamacare?</Title><Msg>.....besides low information welfare recipients.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1364998515447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364998966692-29</Id><Topic><Title>POVERTY SPIKES TO 1960S LEVEL - Thanks Obama and Democrats</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364996220882</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:37:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same thing happened in the great depression. Although FDR's insane policies led to tremendous poverty and prolonged the depression for years, they kept voting him back into office. Proving that most poor people are poor for a reason - they keep doing the things that make and keep them poor. OTOH the rich keep getting richer because they keep doing the things that made them rich - that is, until they can afford to be liberals and buy themselves some politicians.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1364998966692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364999066864-30</Id><Title>Up in a down day!</Title><Msg>Something Leaked? Probably a 2 to 3 dollars gap up at the open tomorrow. Hope the best.</Msg><Username>keethdavid</Username><Timestamp>1364999066864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364999602046-31</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great news! ;) +</Msg><Username>brownk858</Username><Timestamp>1364999602046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364999655232-32</Id><Topic><Title>WAKE UP BIRDY</Title><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364497038406</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 14:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lazy bird don't want to fly</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364999655232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364999863094-33</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats and Other Liberals Support Lying by their Leaders</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1364998217868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, The Dems are very bad. They are at war with fundamental American values and culture. Obama complained about Americans clinging to their guns and Bibles. It's now crystal clear that he would like to take guns away from Americans, and erode any faith in the Bible. Obama needs to be opposed with each and every political move he makes, because he doesn't have our best interests at heart. That's crystal! Unfortunately the only force capable of opposing is the republican party. We'll just have to see how that works out for America. Not too well, I suspect.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1364999863094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364999972476-34</Id><Topic><Title>35 Union Democrat educators to surrender today in massive cheating conspiracy</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364938274167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 17:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The is why victims of socialized government education are low information voters that just can't figure out why socialism doesn't work. These are people who will stand knee deep in snow and tell us the global warming hoax is real because their socialized government school teachers said so.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1364999972476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:39:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365000229937-35</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Don't Mind if their Leaders Lie and Steal</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364948532219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Socialism and Communism are built on lies - Democrats know it and that should tell you why they lie so much.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365000229937</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365000389837-36</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Governed States Enjoying Huge SURPLUSES</Title><Username>white_mirah</Username><Timestamp>1364911791069</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This should be no surprise......capitalism always works better than socialism.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365000389837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365000594375-37</Id><Topic><Title>Fresh bad news for people with pre-existing conditions</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364925294340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:54:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lie after, lie after lie after lie......Democrats knew they couldn't pass Obamacare without lying.....so they shrugged their shoulders and said, "what's the problem?"</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365000594375</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365000720412-38</Id><Topic><Title>Intruder killed while breaking into Colorado prosecutor's home</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364996609323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or mexican drug gangs. They do that sort of thing in Mexico all the time, maybe they are just moving it North. You can't really trust the mainstream media, They are too involved with propaganda and disinformation to ever be very concerned with publishing the truth. Whatever works best for their agenda, that is what they call the news. So much for what "They are thinking".</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1365000720412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365004283442-39</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can see why......when you're out of amo doing nothing makes sense to a commie.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365004283442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365004519836-40</Id><Topic><Title>Up in a down day!</Title><Username>keethdavid</Username><Timestamp>1364999066864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As the stock price goes up, thumb down is ticking up in my post. I can see your desperation guys. You did not lose anything from yesterday yet. So, still have chance to cover your a...</Msg><Username>keethdavid</Username><Timestamp>1365004519836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365005563180-41</Id><Topic><Title>BA naysayers</Title><Username>anuandamit</Username><Timestamp>1364924737078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 13:45:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>23 787's are in pre-flight delivery prep. 5 787's are in pre delivery flight test but were grounded when the FAA ruled. So 28 could be delivered once they are upgraded with the battery modifications. Boeng said they would upgrade the planes already delivered first.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365005563180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365005715897-42</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>our frequent flyin lyin campaigner n chief is taking his shuck n jive road show to denver and san francisco today, still no budget and the occupiers locked the door to pesky tourists</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365005715897</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365005807560-43</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems to be a left wing pattern to attempt to escape reality. When you can't answer a question without exposing the fallacy of your left-wing dogma and ideology just retreat into hyperbole and hurl insults at the questioner.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365005807560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:16:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365006199368-44</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good work</Msg><Username>savage.richard</Username><Timestamp>1365006199368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365006753811-45</Id><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Msg>What's the difference between Kim Jong Un and Saddam Hussein?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365006845220-46</Id><Title>It's April</Title><Msg>Is Ted Nugent dead or in jail yet?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365006845220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365007166205-47</Id><Topic><Title>Intruder killed while breaking into Colorado prosecutor's home</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364996609323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, definitely white. Grand County Coroner Brenda Bock identified that dead man as Joshua Stevens, 31, of Coral, Michigan. An autopsy to determine the cause and manner of death is scheduled for Wednesday. probably a white supremacist... See, we can all speculate....</Msg><Username>bdbaca99</Username><Timestamp>1365007166205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365007205712-48</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The main difference is whether the U.S. has a cowboy president who shoots from the hip or a thoughtful and reasonable man who knows what responsibility is.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365007205712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365007551864-49</Id><Topic><Title>Up in a down day!</Title><Username>keethdavid</Username><Timestamp>1364999066864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing delivered another 747 to atlas air yesterday and another 747 for Lufthansa is being preped for delivery. A 777 is in delivery flight test today. They seem to be successful in delivering the high revenue planes to cover the 787 revenue shortfall. It may not be a coincidence that the earnngs announcement and the NTSB hearing are on the same day. Shorts are wisely starting to cover</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365007551864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365007827671-50</Id><Title>Denver Cops Criticize Obama In Advance Of Denver Speech</Title><Msg>DENVER (CBS4) – Some current and former Denver police officers have taken to Facebook to criticize President Barack Obama’s planned use of Denver police officers as a backdrop for a Wednesday speech on gun control. “This is wrong and it shouldn’t be happening,” said Mike Rossi, a retired Denver police detective who left the department in 2005. CBS4 has learned that the Denver Police Department has been asking for officers — in uniform — to volunteer to stand behind Obama as he makes his speech Wednesday at the Denver Police Academy. White House Deputy Press Secretary Josh Earnest said Obama will “continue to ask the American people to join him in calling on Congress to pass common sense measures to reduce gun violence.” Prior to the speech, the President will meet with Colorado law enforcement officials and community leaders to discuss Colorado’s newly enacted gun control measures. “Who better to stand behind you when you’re trying to ban guns than police officers. What an awesome prop,” said Rossi. He said DPD officers should not be used as a backdrop to make it appear the Denver Police Department and the City of Denver support stronger gun control measures. “It’s agenda based and they shouldn’t be there,” said Rossi. “To me if you put Denver police officers behind the President, who is pushing this agenda, then what you are telling the citizens of the city is that the Denver Police Department is for this.” DPD spokesman Sonny Jackson said the department began seeking volunteers last week who were willing to stand behind the president during his speech. Jackson said numerous officers have volunteered for the assignment.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365007827671</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365007968545-51</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Don't Mind if their Leaders Lie and Steal</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364948532219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In other news: Mark Sanford leaped another hurdle in his South Carolina political redemption tour, winning the GOP primary runoff for a U.S. House seat. His lover-turned-fiancee made a rare public appearance with him. Their affair in 2009 led many to conclude his political career was over.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365007968545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:52:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365008015964-52</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it's a president who obeys the constitution and goes to Congress to get permission to wage a war or one who is submissive to the UN and ignores the constitution.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365008015964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365008201079-53</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Don't Mind if their Leaders Lie and Steal</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364948532219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he have sex with an intern?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365008201079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:56:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365008923120-54</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After confronting a man lurking in his front yard the previous morning, Clint Lowery called police a second time when the same man tried to gain entry by forcing open the door to his home. With his 2-year-old daughter sleeping inside, Lowery did what he had to do to ensure his family’s safety. Lowery met the intruder on the front porch with a 12-ga. shotgun and held him there until police arrived. Lowry said, “I just did whatever anybody would do to protect their family.” (Peninsula Daily News, Port Angeles, WA, 1/23/13)</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365008923120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365009100014-55</Id><Title>P-8 delivery</Title><Msg>SEATTLE, April 2, 2013 -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] handed over the seventh production P-8A Poseidon to the U.S. Navy on schedule March 29, marking the first delivery from the second low-rate initial production contract awarded in November 2011. "This is our second P-8A delivery of 2013, and we'll continue to provide the Navy with new Poseidon aircraft at a rate of nearly one a month," said Rick Heerdt, Boeing vice president and P-8 program manager. "We've got a full factory of P-8As for the U.S. Navy and P-8I aircraft for India, and we're working side-by-side with both customers to introduce the aircraft's advanced capabilities into their fleets." Boeing is on contract to build and support 24 P-8A aircraft as part of three LRIP contracts awarded in 2011 and 2012. The Navy plans to purchase 117 P-8As, which are based on the Next-Generation Boeing 737-800 platform. The versatile multi-mission aircraft provides broad long-range maritime patrol capabilities -- anti-submarine warfare, anti-surface warfare, intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance -- and will replace the Navy P-3 fleet.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365009100014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365009285745-56</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Don't Mind if their Leaders Lie and Steal</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364948532219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No his family values probably kept him from doing that LMAO</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365009285745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365009950830-57</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Don't Mind if their Leaders Lie and Steal</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364948532219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no obstacle for no values dumbos, they get promoted/re-elected, huh ahkmed, i mean roksta</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365009950830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365010132019-58</Id><Title>AP Will no Longer Use the Term Illegal Alien</Title><Msg>.....now the proper term is "Undocumented Democrat."</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365010132019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365010302865-59</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Don't Mind if their Leaders Lie and Steal</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364948532219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you lost me about 2 years ago censored.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365010302865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365010458777-60</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean "obeys the Constitution" by LYING about reasons to go to war, trashing everyone who might disagree, blows the cver of CIA agents and wages a war off the books so others are stuck with his debt? That trhe kind of "obeying the Constitution" you mean?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365010458777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365011028899-61</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err spaz err fascist err bumper err shuck n jive spazzin' err permaspam machine censored brain damaged poor soul</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1365011028899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365011147488-62</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Don't Mind if their Leaders Lie and Steal</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364948532219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahkmed err roksta err bumpie-poo err dumbospaz err censored err burger barn 2nd shift assistant salad bar manager</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1365011147488</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365011259579-63</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your biggest problem is that you can only think in terms of two dimensions........you are playing checkers while the world is playing three dimensional chess........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365011259579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 13:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365012049115-64</Id><Title>ShareHolders Meeting</Title><Msg>With the annual shareholders meeting coming up the end of the month (april) Do you think anyone will get the boot? of course the major shareholders are the top people @ Boeing anyways, Wonder what changes will occur as for company directions? Any thoughts people??</Msg><Username>santac001</Username><Timestamp>1365012049115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365012652825-65</Id><Topic><Title>ShareHolders Meeting</Title><Username>santac001</Username><Timestamp>1365012049115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why would there be? Stock is up.</Msg><Username>wredde</Username><Timestamp>1365012652825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365013025348-66</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna is receptacle for left-wing propaganda. Like a cesspool, every once in a wile he get so full he oozes really foul stinky stuff.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365013025348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365013522405-67</Id><Title>Baggers Begging for Trickle Down</Title><Msg>I'm shocked, shocked the baggers on this board still gaze upward with mouths agape waiting for their masters to trickle down upon them!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1365013522405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365013528754-68</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah the whole pack has been howling louder than ever since the Novemeber elections, and now they are to the point of biting their own tails. I've heard better serenades from the neighborhood coyotes.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1365013528754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014361618-69</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Don't Mind if their Leaders Lie and Steal</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364948532219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 20:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Years from now Republicans will still be using Clinton as an answer to everything and that dog face head turned to the side look of bewilderment will be etched in stone forever.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365014361618</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014374043-70</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When two men walked into Rafael Lantigua’s store after dark with their hoods pulled tight exposing only their eyes, he grew suspicious. Understandably so as one of the men produced a gun and pointed it at him. Lantigua quickly reached for his own firearm from his waist band and pointed it in their direction. Both men jumped back in surprise before fleeing the premises. It was last reported that both men were still at large. According to police, Lantigua was unharmed and nothing was stolen from his store. (The Eagle-Tribune, Lawrence, MA, 1/14/13)</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365014374043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014406555-71</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers Begging for Trickle Down</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1365013522405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:25:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so says the nutsuker</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365014406555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365014408533-72</Id><Title>QUITE THE BEAR FLAG</Title><Msg>on the 30minute, get ready for the winning flush into close......i will cover before 4/24 below 70.</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1365014408533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014514291-73</Id><Topic><Title>remember Clinton on national news, "I did not have sex with that woman! I remember JFK showing up in Las Vegas in Air Force 1 as the media</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365013079145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:17:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kennedy got thier money running Moonshine. moonshine?? Seagrams never marketed moonshine nor did any Kennedy---so why dont you tell us why you Tbaggers have to put your big lies out all the time. If I was a liar like you I would have to take drastic action to remedy the situation - why cant you- I guess the only way you rotters can influence anybody is with your stinking lies --gregjanetom you are a liar pure and simple- put that in your nose</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365014514291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014618973-74</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I ever caught any of you jackoffs in my neighborhood with all your guns I would call the police and make a complaint- and have you arrested wor loitering at least if not stalking and threatening</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365014618973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365014679821-75</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A seven-year-old boy was killed over the weekend when a handgun his father was trying to sell accidentally discharged in the parking lot of Twig's Reloading Den, a gun store in East Lackawannock, Penn. Craig Loughrey was sitting in his booster seat in his father's truck on Saturday morning when his father's gun went off, hitting him in the chest. A few minutes earlier, he and his dad, Joseph, had been inside Twig's, unsuccessfully trying to sell a rifle and the 9mm handgun that killed Craig. Paramedics attempted to revive the seven-year-old, but were unsuccessful. Very sad news today out of Fairmont, North Carolina: Christopher Stanlane was cleaning his gun on Sunday afternoon when it accidentally fired and and a bullet struck his 10-year old son in the head. The boy, who was watching TV at the time, was pronounced dead at the scene. “Most people think that guns are what kill people, and it’s not,” said Sgt. Eric Gavaghan, a county sheriff’s official, who teaches gun safety classes. “The people and their inexperience, their lack of training, that’s what hurts other people with firearms.” No charges have been filed, while deputies are still investigating the incident.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365014679821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365015026513-76</Id><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Msg>21% Can’t Speak It Very Well - In Stockton, Calif., which has just entered into Chapter 9 bankruptcy, 41 percent of the people do not speak English at home and 21 percent cannot speak it very well, according to the U.S. Census Bureau. Data that the Census Bureau developed on what it calls the “social characteristics” of Stockton during the five-year period from 2007 to 2011, indicate that this city, located eighty miles east of San Francisco in California’s San Joaquin Valley, had a population of 289,926. Of those 289,926 people, 76,869 (or about 27 percent) were foreign born, according to the Census Bureau. Of these foreign-born, 43,084 (or about 15 percent of this city’s total population) were not U.S. citizens.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015182094-77</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michael and Amy Stephens were at home with their two young daughters when they saw deputies speeding past their home. The couple then overheard on their police scanner that there was a man in the area being sought by police. Michael grabbed a flashlight and headed outside to investigate and to make sure his family’s home was secure. As he stepped outside, he saw the 26-year-old fugitive nearby. Michael attempted to detain him while Amy dialed 911. The fugitive was able to grab Michael’s flashlight and started swinging it wildly over his head. Amy appeared with a .243 rifle and warned the man that she would shoot. Soon after, the fugitive was arrested and booked on several preliminary charges. Michael suffered a few stitches, but was otherwise unharmed. (Daily Inter Lake, Evergreen, MT, 1/5/13)</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015182094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015299454-78</Id><Topic><Title>ShareHolders Meeting</Title><Username>santac001</Username><Timestamp>1365012049115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the top Boeing people own less than 1% of the stock according to the major holders list on yahoo.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365015299454</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:54:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015415005-79</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Liberals so concerned about firearms and children?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364917160515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 11:39:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any child dying is sad but Democrats don't care about children except how they can be used to secure power.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015415005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015477902-80</Id><Topic><Title>Up in a down day!</Title><Username>keethdavid</Username><Timestamp>1364999066864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2-3 gap up? a 2-3$ s h i i i t the bed is more likely.....</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1365015477902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015740449-81</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Liberals so concerned about firearms and children?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364917160515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 11:39:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so if abortion was illegal I bet you a million dollars you would be here screaming something about give away`s and having to house , feed , educate all these poor kids.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365015740449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365015972751-82</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great responsible gun owners win! too bad there are so many guns in the hands of irresponsible people who accidentally shoot their own kids drink and go crazy and don`t secure their weapons from getting into the wrong hands. way too much of irresponsibility and something needs to change.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365015972751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365016144386-83</Id><Title>787 Flight Test Scheduled for Today</Title><Msg>This should be the battery system certification test for internal use. 12:55 departure.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365016144386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365016557720-84</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but these people only want our freebees that must explain why they all do stoop labor out in the valley all day long for sub minimum wage- they just want those freebies- language spoken at home? who in their right mind cares if they speak UTO-Aztec or Sino-Tibetan or esperanto- only the ignorant extreme right wing white supremicists or the Tbaggers and the conservatives care- aint that wunnerful</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365016557720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365016861601-85</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are Liberals so concerned about firearms and children?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364917160515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 11:39:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>same old scam about Marxism and communism when in reality the RWNJs, white supremacists and Tbaggers are all closet revolutionary communists and Marxists and its they that want something for nothing and are willing to commit any crime to have their way</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365016861601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365017066527-86</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting thing......today's illegal immigrants.....er Undocumented Democrats......come here because they can't make a decent living in Mexico because of all the political and criminal corruption. Then they want to do their best to make the USA just like Mexico. You don't see that with Asian and other immigrants but Mexicans make good useful id%ts for the Democrats (commies). Every wonder why Democrats no longer work for more Cubans to immigrate?....Gee.... it couldn't be because they don't always vote Democrat could it?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365017066527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365017563707-87</Id><Topic><Title>ShareHolders Meeting</Title><Username>santac001</Username><Timestamp>1365012049115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:00:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only reason the stock is up is because of its workforce - not because of its management.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1365017563707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365017719003-88</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a feeling if you ever saw anyone with a gun, you would squat down with your head between your legs and whimper.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365017719003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365018016097-89</Id><Topic><Title>Armed Citizen</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1364995223641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it's obvious zosima is very feminine.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1365018016097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365018229279-90</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you are playing Klondike with 51 cards.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365018229279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365018493924-91</Id><Title>787 order</Title><Msg>MADRID (Reuters) - International Airlines Group (ICAG.L)(ICAG.MC) said on Wednesday it had firmed up orders for 18 of Boeing's (BA.N) 787 Dreamliners, a show of confidence in the jet that has been grounded since January because of battery problems. The long-haul aircraft would replace some of British Airways' current fleet of Boeing 747-400s between 2017 and 2021, IAG, which owns the UK airline and Spain's flag carrier Iberia, said in a statement to the Spanish stock exchange.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365018493924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365018570634-92</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The language they speak is irrelevant compared to the taxes they pay. Not everyone in Stockton is an immigrant. Taxpayers are taxpayers regardless whether they work in the fields or in an office or a factory. There are tons of legal non citizen workers from fields to laboratories. Some of you are jealous because some of them have much higher degrees in education than you have.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365018570634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365018654636-93</Id><Topic><Title>787 Flight Test Scheduled for Today</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365016144386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look for it on flightradar24 site. Select BOE as a filter (left side of screen)</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365018654636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365019045900-94</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's so fun to see you idiots rage on with nothing.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365019045900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365019153954-95</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems like the howling got more frenzied as soon as the parolees started going door to door shooting officers of the court and of the law.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365019153954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365019337170-96</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing !</Msg><Username>bradleybrown720</Username><Timestamp>1365019337170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365019383919-97</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you? Are you broad-minded, well-informed, and intelligent? Tell us another!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365019383919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365019644910-98</Id><Topic><Title>Will Democrats Support a war with N. Korea???</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365006753811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not all the people Assad is killing in Syria are friends or allies of the US.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365019644910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365019691739-99</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. The government is bad, doncha know? So the victims, my serving the govt., ask for it. As one ofthe board's better known Aryan Brothers likes to say, "People are waking up. Take back your rights."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365019691739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365019720561-100</Id><Topic><Title>Up in a down day!</Title><Username>keethdavid</Username><Timestamp>1364999066864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 10:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you on Diaper now?</Msg><Username>keethdavid</Username><Timestamp>1365019720561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365020567768-101</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying you're playing the victim card. It's obvious you're a victim of socialized government education but what else justifies you freeloading off society?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365020567768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365021752938-102</Id><Title>A Choice Between a Lying Philanderer and a Democrat</Title><Msg>....in S. Carolina. As much as I don't want to, I guess I'll have to go with the more moral one of the two. The Democrat will just have to rely on the votes of dead people and incarcerated felons as they usually do.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365021752938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365021899100-103</Id><Title>Obama Pushes For Housing Bubble 2.0</Title><Msg>Got bad credit? Want to buy a home? You're in luck! President Obama is ramping up the country for housing bubble 2.0 as he urges banks to loan to people with poor credit so they can purchase a home. What could go wrong? Oh just about everything. And don't worry, the government is going to promise banks everything will be just fine. The Obama administration is engaged in a broad push to make more home loans available to people with weaker credit, an effort that officials say will help power the economic recovery but that skeptics say could open the door to the risky lending that caused the housing crash in the first place. President Obama’s economic advisers and outside experts say the nation’s much-celebrated housing rebound is leaving too many people behind, including young people looking to buy their first homes and individuals with credit records weakened by the recession. In response, administration officials say they are working to get banks to lend to a wider range of borrowers by taking advantage of taxpayer-backed programs — including those offered by the Federal Housing Administration — that insure home loans against default. Housing officials are urging the Justice Department to provide assurances to banks, which have become increasingly cautious, that they will not face legal or financial recriminations if they make loans to riskier borrowers who meet government standards but later default. Shorter version: President Obama's #$%$ economy has caused people's credit to decline and even though the economy isn't much better (and neither is their credit) he wants them to buy a home with money and credit they don't have. Fantastic. As a reminder, the housing market crashed after the government forced banks to lend to people who 1) shouldn't have been applying for a housing loan in the first place 2) had no way to pay a housing loan back 3) never intended to pay back the housing loan in the first place.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365021899100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365021934620-104</Id><Title>CommieCare "Navigators"</Title><Msg>from drudge link to Washington Examiner.... "Tens of thousands of health care professionals, union workers and community activists hired as "navigators" to help Americans choose Obamacare options starting Oct. 1 could earn $20 an hour or more, according to new regulations issued Wednesday. The 63-page rule covering navigators, drawn up by the Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services, also said the government will provide free translators for those not fluent in English -- no matter what their native language is. "The proposed requirements would also include that such entities and individuals provide consumers with information and assistance in the consumer's preferred language, at no cost to the consumer, which would include oral interpretation of non-English languages and the translation of written documents in non-English languages when necessary to ensure meaningful access," said the regulations...."</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365021934620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:45:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365022036923-105</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What right was he referring to Hooze?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365022036923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:47:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365022106124-106</Id><Title>fighter sale approved</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON, April 3 (Reuters) - The U.S. Defense Department said on Wednesday it has approved the sale of either the Lockheed Martin Corp F-35 stealth fighter or Boeing Co's F-15 Silent Eagle fighter to South Korea, which is expected to announce the winner of a 60-jet competition later this year. (Given the price for the F-35, Boeing should be the winner.)</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365022106124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365022539613-107</Id><Title>Don't we already have a Path to Citizenship?</Title><Msg>It's called legal immigration.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365022539613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365022821356-108</Id><Topic><Title>787 Flight Test Scheduled for Today</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365016144386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haven't seen any sign of it being in the air so far.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365022821356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365022993194-109</Id><Topic><Title>787 Flight Test Scheduled for Today</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365016144386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the news wires: For the second time this week, Boeing is putting the 787 in the air Wednesday for testing unrelated to the jet's redesigned battery. "This is a routine test flight designed to address some of the component reliability projects we have been working," Marc Birtel, a Boeing spokesman, wrote in an emailed statement. "The battery certification demonstration flight will take place in the coming days."</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365022993194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365023160343-110</Id><Topic><Title>787 Flight Test Scheduled for Today</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365016144386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess it did fly. From the newswire: "You can follow the 787's flight today on FlightAware. The 787 took off at 12:41 p.m., when local media were awaiting the grand opening of Boeing's new jet delivery center at Paine Field."</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365023160343</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365023311397-111</Id><Topic><Title>787 Flight Test Scheduled for Today</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365016144386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOE272 (787) is in the air now.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365023311397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365023366450-112</Id><Title>THAAD interceptor batteries Sent to Guam</Title><Msg>The Pentagon said it would send ground-based THAAD interceptor batteries to protect US bases on the island of Guam, complementing two Aegis anti-missile destroyers already dispatched to the region. The THAAD (Terminal High Altitude Area Defence) is a truck-mounted system that can pinpoint an enemy missile launch, track the projectile and launch an interceptor to bring it down. Guam is a US island territory 3,380 kilometres (2,100 miles) southeast of North Korea in the Pacific and is home to 6,000 American military personnel, as well as bases for submarines and strategic bombers. Representative Hank Johnson (D. GA) is alarmed that the addition weight could cause Guam to capsize. Johnson for more life preservers to be sent to Guam as a safety precaution in case such an event take should take place.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365023366450</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365024226542-113</Id><Title>NKOREA APPROVES 'MERCILESS' NUKE ATTACK ON US</Title><Msg>N. Korea approves nuclear strike on United States By Jung Ha-Won (AFP) – 38 minutes ago SEOUL — North Korea dramatically escalated its warlike rhetoric on Thursday, warning that it had authorised plans for nuclear strikes on targets in the United States. "The moment of explosion is approaching fast," the North Korean military said, warning that war could break out "today or tomorrow". Pyongyang's latest pronouncement came as Washington scrambled to reinforce its Pacific missile defences, preparing to send ground-based interceptors to Guam and dispatching two Aegis class destroyers to the region. Tension was also high on the North's heavily-fortified border with South Korea, after Kim Jong-Un's isolated regime barred South Koreans from entering a Seoul-funded joint industrial park on its side of the frontier. In a statement published by the state KCNA news agency, the Korean People's Army general staff warned Washington that US threats would be "smashed by... cutting-edge smaller, lighter and diversified nuclear strike means". "The merciless operation of our revolutionary armed forces in this regard has been finally examined and ratified," the statement said. Last month, North Korea threatened a "pre-emptive" nuclear strike against the United States, and last week its supreme army command ordered strategic rocket units to combat status. But, while Pyongyang has successfully carried out test nuclear detonations, most experts think it is not yet capable of mounting a device on a ballistic missile capable of striking US bases or territory. Mounting tension in the region could however trigger incidents on the tense and heavily-militarised border between North and South Korea. There was no immediate American reaction to the North's latest statement, but US Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel said Pyongyang represented a "real and clear danger" to the United States and to its allies South Korea and Japan. "They have nuclear capacity now, they have missile delivery c</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365024226542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365024808002-114</Id><Title>DEMOCRAT JOE KLEIN: Early Obamacare incompetence 'really bad sign'...</Title><Msg>Let me try to understand this: The key incentive for small businesses to support Obamacare was that they would be able to shop for the best deals in health care super-stores—called exchanges. The Administration has had 3 years to set up these exchanges. It has failed to do so. This is a really bad sign. There will be those who argue that it’s not the Administration’s fault. It’s the fault of the 33 states that have refused to set up their own exchanges. Nonsense. Where was the contingency planning? There certainly are models, after all—the federal government’s own health benefits plan (FEHBP) operates markets that exist in all 50 states. So does Medicare Advantage. But now, the Obama Administration has announced that it won’t have the exchanges ready in time, that small businesses will be offered one choice for the time being—for a year, at least. No doubt, small business owners will be skeptical of the Obama Administration’s belief in the efficacy of the market system to produce lower prices through competition. That was supposed to be the point of this plan. As a Democrat—as someone who believes in activist government—Obama has a vested interest in seeing that federal programs actually work efficiently. I don’t see much evidence that this is anywhere near the top of his priorities. One thing is clear: Obamacare will fail if he doesn’t start paying more attention to the details of implementation, if he doesn’t start demanding action. And, in a larger sense, the notion of activist government will be in peril—despite the demographics flowing the Democrats’ way—if institutions like the VA and Obamacare don’t deliver the goods. Sooner or later, the Republican party may come to understand that its best argument isn’t about tearing down the government we have, but making it run more efficiently. Sooner or later, the Democrats may come to understand that making it run efficiently is the prerequisite for maintaining power.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365024808002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365025383044-115</Id><Topic><Title>The Registration is going very well...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365023015184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Especially with hope4whitepeople, mir(de), gregjane, badolt, bumper, censored (same), and all others of that stripe in their best campaign mode.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1365025383044</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365025463978-116</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>key logger site. You've now been infected.</Msg><Username>basherbuste_r</Username><Timestamp>1365025463978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365025669015-117</Id><Topic><Title>787 Flight Test Scheduled for Today</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365016144386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 15:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmm, makes you wonder what else needs checking out?</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365025669015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365025845899-118</Id><Title>Hoodik and Zosima this Could be Shocking to You</Title><Msg>Indian engineers invent 'anti-rape' underwear which gives attackers electric shocks and automatically texts police for help Anti-rape underwear which delivers a 3,800 kilovolt shock to any would-be attacker has been created by a team of Indian engineering students. After disabling the assailant, the undergarment has been designed to automatically send a text message to police or family members containing the GPS location of the attempted crime. Pressure sensors on the garment, sewn in around the bust area, detect unwanted force and trigger the powerful shock. It can deliver up to 82 electric shocks, more than enough to disable any attacker. There is an anti rape device available in America. Smith and Wesson once used the slogan to advertise their .38 cal revolver¿ you cant rape a .38.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365025845899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:50:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365026110036-119</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I first saw the headline "I wouldn't do a thing" I thought Genna was going to explain why he was fired from his last job.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365026110036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365026863759-120</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers Begging for Trickle Down</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1365013522405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:25:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Recognized yourself immediately did you, fascist. Lose the fast food gig? On unemployment?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1365026863759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365027307190-121</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They hate America and will such us dry." Speaking of someone's screed about English, shouldn't you be sticking to your brand new words like "hoard" vs "horde" instead of new ones?</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1365027307190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365027790385-122</Id><Topic><Title>The Registration is going very well...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365023015184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fascist, Keep praying for the trickle to come down on you.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1365027790385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:23:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365028135094-123</Id><Title>Foxvda Ratings Down 33% in Q1 2013</Title><Msg>The highly paid propagandists of Fox/RubeRadio work hard spreading republiwhoppers amongst disaffected baggers to keep the focus away from the scams and crimes of their wealthy employers. With the ratings plunge it may be that people are wising up to the distractions and lies.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1365028135094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:28:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365028211379-124</Id><Topic><Title>The Registration is going very well...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365023015184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:03:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After all, it's not called a GOLDEN shower for nothing.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365028211379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365029598805-125</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Pushes For Housing Bubble 2.0</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365021899100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:44:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has to be aware of the last housing bubble and what caused it. This President is creepy!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1365029598805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365029678479-126</Id><Title>The NK Lunatic Declares War</Title><Msg>Unlike the I ranian crazies that pretend they are not making nuclear weapons to use against I srael and other US national interests, the NK lunatic has announced he is getting ready to use nuclear weapons against the US. He in essence has declared war against the US. He has ripped up the armistice agreement. Must the US wait for the first nuclear strike against us, with the hope that our defensive missile shield will protect us before we take any action. I hope that is not our strategy. I say the best offense is the best defense. Let's warn the NK kid by his playing with fire against the US he will go the way Saddam and Qiddafi went, one two three and mean it.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1365029678479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365031332667-127</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He'd better be well stocked with high capacity magazines.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1365031332667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365033246989-128</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, Hooz, I think that you know the answer to your own (presumed) question. The "leap" that concludes you as a traitor, for your avid liberal effervescence, is as erroneous as assuming the motives regarding questioning what Obama is doing and why he is doing it is simply because of the color of his skin. The database of any President's words and actions can be and should be compared (or judged) to standards of consistency, motive, law, and decency. The "judges" - you, Chris, Spartacus, me, this "board", Maher, Limbaugh, etc., and three hundred million other Americans - are imperfect and can only offer their opinions whose value is measued only in the aggregate.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1365033246989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365035232915-129</Id><Title>787 flight</Title><Msg>Flight landed 10 minutes ago. Flight lasted 3 hours and 28 minutes.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365035232915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365035816636-130</Id><Topic><Title>Recording Points to Race Factor in Stops by New York Police</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365032276113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:37:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anger management class.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365035816636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365035847202-131</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too freakin bad, and they all voted for the messiah, its only the beginning, you freakin #$%$</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1365035847202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365036040059-132</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I presume Jesus ate fish and lamb. Ask those eaten fish and lamb what they thought of Jesus. I believe we have a paradox here. Don't look at me, I just ask the questions! Consumption of the flesh is cruelty if you believe life is sacred.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1365036040059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365036142748-133</Id><Topic><Title>N.C. GOP Lawmakers Want to Ignore Constitution, Establish Official State Religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365027854093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now, THAT's creepy. I wonder if they'll institute burning at the stake as the punishment for being Methodist.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365036142748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365036806419-134</Id><Topic><Title>Recording Points to Race Factor in Stops by New York Police</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365032276113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:37:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brain management might also help the dolt.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1365036806419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365037333029-135</Id><Topic><Title>N.C. GOP Lawmakers Want to Ignore Constitution, Establish Official State Religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365027854093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They won't make us listen to that old 'Shakers Song', will they?</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1365037333029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365038404697-136</Id><Topic><Title>N.C. GOP Lawmakers Want to Ignore Constitution, Establish Official State Religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365027854093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seems race is a factor in many statistics disproportionate the not so great socialist dumb plantation has been a dismal failure</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365038404697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:20:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365038501059-137</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you gregjanetommax for your honest opinion of Mexicans. They don't come here to assimilate but to conquer. Why else would they not choose to speak our language? It's refreshing to hear the truth that many won't acknowledge.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1365038501059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365038801674-138</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now ask gregjanetommax why he chooses not to speak 'our' language. Then ask Native Americans if only the Mexicans enter a country to "conquer". Finally, buy a calendar and turn it to 2013.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1365038801674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365038817812-139</Id><Topic><Title>Recording Points to Race Factor in Stops by New York Police</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365032276113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:37:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh my gosh, you mean black people commit crimes? disproportionately so?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365038817812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:26:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365038997115-140</Id><Topic><Title>Recording Points to Race Factor in Stops by New York Police</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365032276113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:37:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't imagine anything could help him.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1365038997115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365039186805-141</Id><Topic><Title>Recording Points to Race Factor in Stops by New York Police</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365032276113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 19:37:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how many IDs do you need to play with yourself?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365039186805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:33:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365039510356-142</Id><Title>Does this seem familiar ??</Title><Msg>with apologies to G.O The original commandments are: Whatever goes upon two legs is an enemy. Whatever goes upon four legs, or has wings, is a friend. No animal shall wear clothes. No animal shall sleep in a bed. No animal shall drink alcohol. No animal shall kill any other animal. All animals are equal. Later, Napoleon and his pigs secretly revise some commandments to clear them of accusations of law-breaking (such as "No animal shall drink alcohol" having "to excess" appended to it and "No animal shall sleep in a bed" with "with sheets" added to it). The changed commandments are as follows, with the changes bolded: 4 No animal shall sleep in a bed with sheets. 5 No animal shall drink alcohol to excess. 6 No animal shall kill any other animal without cause. Eventually these are replaced with the maxims, "All animals are equal, but some animals are more equal than others", and "Four legs good, two legs better!" as the pigs become more human. This is an ironic twist to the original purpose of the Seven Commandments, which were supposed to keep order within Animal Farm by uniting the animals together against the humans, and prevent animals from following the humans' evil habits. Through the revision of the commandments, Orwell demonstrates how simply political dogma can be turned into malleable propaganda.[38] ++++</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1365039510356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365039532811-143</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the feds are gonna be hiring tens of thousands of officials to help people inclusive of undocumented dumbocrats "navigate" commiecare mandates...in the language of their choice, pick a language, any language, eubonics at random.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365039532811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365040051363-144</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What language do white southern rednecks speak?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1365040051363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365040715210-145</Id><Topic><Title>The NK Lunatic Declares War</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1365029678479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama cut funding for the missile shield! That no good SOB is the worst president in American history, bar none! And the Lame Stream Media and Hollywood continue to protect this SOB!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1365040715210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 21:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365041189821-146</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365035232915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 20:27:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1365041189821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 22:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365041975692-147</Id><Topic><Title>41% Undocumented Democrats in Bankrupt Stockton Don’t Speak English at Home</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365015026513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 14:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One homogeneous language is better for all of us. It makes communication between many different nationalities possible. It's the most effective means of creating efficiency within a business environment. Even the Tower of Babel was a reference to efficiency within a society. Like I like to say, "When in Rome speak as a Roman."</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1365041975692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 22:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365042896467-148</Id><Topic><Title>I wouldn't do a thing</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365004012886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a sissy?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365042896467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 22:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365044464284-149</Id><Topic><Title>The NK Lunatic Declares War</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1365029678479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phantom, I agree that we should do something that more than shuts him up. What "Un" is doing is more that "Il" (his dad) in terms of statements and actions and it is hard to justify assumptions of his being naive and "learning on the job". Too much at stake. Unlike the yahoos in the Middle East that really cannot touch us (at this time), NK is making headway towards a nuke and a delivery system. The missile shield systems are not 100% effective. As far as the delivery system is concerned, the nuke can be taken on a slow boat to Los Angeles - if the threats are real. Even setting off a nuke off-shore (12 miles) will dump radiation on Los Angeles, San Diego, San Francisco, Seattle, and create havoc. The question is: Is Obama up to the task? Another theory: It is possible that Un is doing all of this to divert our attention from Iran and move assets away from the Persian Gulf. Last year Obama tasked two of our three active aircraft carrier strike groups (out of ten possible) to monitor Iran, leaving the one remaining active AC to watch the rest of the world. If we reduce our presence nearby Iran in favor of NK, then israel may feel less secure in attacking Iran. Iran and NK are bed partners so the unusual bellicose NK behavior may simply be for the benefit of Iran.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1365044464284</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 23:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>