<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361682093532-1</Id><Title>Australia Should Go With the Super Hornet</Title><Msg>F-35 fighters are grounded once again. This time its some 51 F-35 fighters due to an engine blade crack. Australia is considering buying 24 proven reliable F/A F-18 Super Hornets within the next few weeks. Going with more Super Hornets is the wise decision. Who knows when the F-35 will be ready to run missions. After all these years its still in its testing phases.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361682093532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 00:01:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361682449950-2</Id><Title>The Dreamliner Has Larger Windows</Title><Msg>Its never too late to redesign the dreamliner as we are now witnessing. While Boeing is at it, it should should consider whether the 787 larger windows can be used as escape hatches in case of an onboard fire.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361682449950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 00:07:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361690512823-3</Id><Topic><Title>Further prood as to why tighter Gun control laws will not protect School kids</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360843620319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 07:07:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, you're so funny. And you're so... LOONY. They jus' keep comin'; but where do they come from? Or should I ask, WHO do they come from? Could God™ be playing a role in it? Regardless: keep it up, you're making my day.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1361690512823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 02:21:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361704444049-4</Id><Topic><Title>Further prood as to why tighter Gun control laws will not protect School kids</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360843620319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 07:07:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lonenut. You're as funny as your hero, Heinrich Himmler. Do you also look the same in your uniform while you goose step around your basement?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361704444049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 06:14:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361704509293-5</Id><Topic><Title>Further prood as to why tighter Gun control laws will not protect School kids</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360843620319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 07:07:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why he's a Lonenut.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361704509293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 06:15:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361704744593-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Turd Polisher Hooz Calls For Bush Impeachment</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361581074076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you crying a river?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361704744593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 06:19:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361713494026-7</Id><Title>Activists protest Terminator Machines</Title><Msg>Autonomous weapons’, which could be ready within a decade, pose grave risk to international law, claim activists A new global campaign to persuade nations to ban “killer robots” before they reach the production stage is to be launched in the UK by a group of academics, pressure groups and Nobel peace prize laureates. Robot warfare and autonomous weapons, the next step from unmanned drones, are already being worked on by scientists and will be available within the decade, said Dr Noel Sharkey, a leading robotics and artificial intelligence expert and professor at Sheffield University. He believes that development of the weapons is taking place in an effectively unregulated environment, with little attention being paid to moral implications and international law. The Stop the Killer Robots campaign will be launched in April at the House of Commons and includes many of the groups that successfully campaigned to have international action taken against cluster bombs and landmines. They hope to get a similar global treaty against autonomous weapons. “These things are not science fiction; they are well into development,” said Sharkey. “The research wing of the Pentagon in the US is working on the X47B [unmanned plane] which has supersonic twists and turns with a G-force that no human being could manage, a craft which would take autonomous armed combat anywhere in the planet. “In America they are already training more drone pilots than real aircraft pilots, looking for young men who are very good at computer games. They are looking at swarms of robots, with perhaps one person watching what they do.” Sharkey insists he is not anti-war but deeply concerned about how quickly science is moving ahead of the presumptions underlying the Geneva convention and the international laws of war. “There are a lot of people very excited about this technology, in the US, at BAE Systems, in China, Israel and Russia, very excited at what is set to become a multibillion-dollar industry. This is going to be big, big money. But actually there is no transparency, no legal process. The laws of war allow for rights of surrender, for prisoner of war rights, for a human face to take judgments on collateral damage. Humans are thinking, sentient beings. If a robot goes wrong, who is accountable? Certainly not the robot.” He disputes the justification that deploying robot soldiers would potentially save lives of real soldiers. “Autonomous robotic weapons won’t get tired, they won’t seek revenge if their colleague is killed, but neither will my washing machine. No one on your side might get killed, but what effect will you be having on the other side, not just in lives but in attitudes and anger? “The public is not being invited to have a view on the morals of all of this. We won’t hear about it until China has sold theirs to Iran. That’s why we are forming this campaign to look at a pre-emptive ban. “The idea is that it’s a machine that will find a target, decide if it is the right target and then kill it. No human involvement. Article 36 in the Geneva Convention says that any new weapon has to take into account whether it can distinguish and discriminate between combatant and civilian, but the problem here is that an autonomous robot is not a weapon until you clip on the gun.” At present, Sharkey says, there is no mechanism in a robot’s “mind” to distinguish between a child holding up a sweet and an adult pointing a gun. “We are struggling to get them to distinguish between a human being and a car. We have already seen utter incompetence in the use of drones, operators making a lot of mistakes and not being properly supervised.” Last November the international campaign group Human Rights Watch produced a 50-page report, Losing Humanity: the Case Against Killer Robots, outlining concerns about fully autonomous weapons. “Giving machines the power to decide who lives and dies on the battlefield would take technology too far,” said Steve Goose, arms division director at Human Rights Watch. “Human control of robotic warfare is essential to minimising civilian deaths and injuries.” US political activist Jody Williams, who won a Nobel peace prize for her work at the International Campaign to Ban Landmines, is expected to join Sharkey at the launch at the House of Commons. Williams said she was confident that a pre-emptive ban on autonomous weapons could be achieved in the same way as the international embargo on anti-personnel landmines. “I know we can do the same thing with killer robots. I know we can stop them before they hit the battlefield,” said Williams, who chairs the Nobel Women’s Initiative. “Killer robots loom over our future if we do not take action to ban them now,” she said. “The six Nobel peace laureates involved in the Nobel Women’s Initiative fully support the call for an international treaty to ban fully autonomous weaponised robots.”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361713494026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 08:44:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361715055315-8</Id><Title>The NWO drags over 400 US farmers to court over GM seeds</Title><Msg>Part of the agenda is to own the food supply...own the food and you own the people When will Big Ag’s corrupt reign end? J. D. Heyes Natural News Feb 24, 2013 Agri-giant Monsanto, not satisfied with being one of the world’s largest agricultural corporations, is dragging hundreds of U.S. farmers into court over alleged copyright violations for repeated usage of the company’s patented seeds. In a case that has surprised a lot of observers, the U.S. Supreme Court agreed to hear one of these complaints on Feb. 19. That case, Bowman v. Monsanto Co., was billed as a landmark battle pitting farmer Vernon Bowman against the international Ag-giant over the former’s repeated use of seeds he bought from Monsanto which the company says are only supposed to be used for one growing season. In advance of the case, The Huffington Post reported, the Center for Food Safety and the Save Our Seeds campaigning organizations released a report detailing similar cases. Price of seeds have skyrocketed According to that report titled “Seed Giants vs. U.S. Farmers,” which readers can view here, Monsanto alleges seed patent infringement in 144 lawsuits against 410 farmers and 56 small farm businesses in at least 27 states, as of January of this year. Combined, Monsanto, Syngenta and DuPont hold more than half – 53 percent – of the global commercial seed market, which the groups claim in their report has led to a massive increase in the price of seed: Between 1995 and 2011, the groups say the average cost of planting a single acre of soybeans rose a whopping 325 percent, while corn seed prices climbed a staggering259 percent. A d v e r t i s e m e n t Monsanto especially says that seed patents are a form of biological patent and that means the company’s seeds – which are genetically modified to ward off bugs and weeds, though some strains of each are becoming increasing resistant to them – are legally protected inventions or discoveries in biology, HuffPo reported. “In the case of Monsanto, that often means patents on genetically modified seeds,” said the web-based newspaper. “In recent years, these and other companies have taken farmers to court for alleged seed patent infringement – meaning they planted seeds without paying for them.” For the record, farmers have, for centuries, harvested seeds from the current years’ crop so they could plant again next year; Monsanto and the others have, in essence, made that time-tested practice illegal with a product that, according to reports, is not living up to advertised standards of resistance. That doesn’t matter to Monsanto and the other Ag-giants, but it does matter to the U.S. Supreme Court, because the issue of patent infringement becomes less clear when you consider that these farmers are growing subsequent crops with seeds they initially purchased legally – even if the ag-giants consider such subsequent planting a crime. In the case of Bowman, he allegedly replanted second-generation seeds for years, though he initially purchased them legally from a licensed Monsanto distributor. He didn’t purchase new seeds each crop year, and because of that, Monsanto says he essentially stole their product. The company has managed to win a string of victories in lower courts. The agricultural firm argues that its patents serve to protect its business interests, and that they “provide a motivation for spending millions of dollars on research and development of hardier, disease-resistant seeds that can boost food yields,” Britain’s Guardian newspaper reported. Not resistant or eco-friendly enough However, Bill Freese, one of the authors of the activist seed group report and a senior scientist at the Center for Food Safety, said in a press release that claims Monsanto’s patents are creating better crops are bogus. “Most major new crop varieties developed throughout the 20th century owe their origin to publicly funded agricultural research and breeding,” Freese wrote. He also added that the GM crops weren’t as eco-friendly as advertised. “While agrichemical corporations also claim that their patented seeds are leading to environmental improvements, the report notes that upward of 26 percent more chemicals per acre were used on GE crops than on non-GE crops, according to USDA data,” he said. Some have attributed the dramatic decline in crop diversity in recent years to the growth of a few ag-giants. In the report, the authors note that 86 percent of corn, 88 percent of cotton and 93 percent of soybeans grown in the U.S. are currently GM strains.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361715055315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 09:10:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361716190127-9</Id><Title>fear the rise of china ?, the west is in the crosshairs.</Title><Msg>we may fear the rise of china, but the bigger picture is the downfall of the west, and its double standards, both China and India see western hegemony, and thus for them to rise that has to be overturned. Europe has fallen and would never again rise, a declining population, polluted landmass, no natural resources and a rapidly declining manufacturing base, will make them he new "banana republic", the world has indeed turn. China has already created it own NATO, the shangai five, and invited India to join. after WWII, the west create institutions and then use force against the third world to join, to date no one can explain why Britain and France has to have nuclear weapons, and why the UN is not going after then, something Indian prime minister,Nehru complained bitterly about back in the 1950's. Might is right, and now the mighty is going on a downward cataclysm, in time, south africa, brazil, indonesia, India and China will be major military/economic and they will then create a new world order, hopefully for the better.</Msg><Username>manny11419</Username><Timestamp>1361716190127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 09:29:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361719280960-10</Id><Title>FAA is Giving Boeing a tough time</Title><Msg>Boeing has proposed a fix to the lithium-ion battery related problems. The FAA is not satisfied by Boeing's fix. It wants 100 % proof that the 787 is now safe.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361719280960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:21:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361720666232-11</Id><Topic><Title>FAA is Giving Boeing a tough time</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361719280960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:21:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no not 100 % per ray hood 1000 %- but in reality the proof /probability requred is more on the order of 99.99999999 percent ( maybe short a 9 or two ) safe or iow about 1 in 1 bilion hours chance of failure/fire</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361720666232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:44:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361721480496-12</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361651881753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney wouldn't have gotten away with what? Get someone to upgrade your simple thoughts. And his running mate Ryab, was right on as to what needed cut, and what needed reformed.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361721480496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:58:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361721567091-13</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361651881753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS..Romney was all about giving backn ot taking like you selfish libs, and corrupt Obama. The GOP wins when the economy grows, when new wealth is created. What a bozo you are.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361721567091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:59:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361722619260-14</Id><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Msg>Soros and his Dumb Party are No. 1 Maobowa his Puppet No. 2 but neither would be successful were it not for party of fools that confers authority/power on the enemy within credit peteetongmain... "this quote was translated into English from an article appearing in the Czech Republic as published in the Prager Zeitung of 28 April 2011. "The danger to America is not Barack Obama but a citizenry capable of entrusting an inexperienced man like him with the Presidency. It will be far easier to limit and undo the follies of an Obama presidency than to restore the necessary common sense and good judgment to a depraved electorate willing to have such a man for their president.. The problem is much deeper and far more serious than Mr. Obama, who is a mere symptom of what ails America. Blaming the prince of the fools should not blind anyone to the vast confederacy of fools that made him their prince.. The Republic can survive a Barack Obama. It is less likely to survive a multitude of Idiots such as those who made him their president.""</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1361722619260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:16:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361723920346-15</Id><Topic><Title>FAA is Giving Boeing a tough time</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361719280960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:21:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As well they should!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361723920346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:38:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361724081910-16</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Prez O can talk very well, too bad he never means anything he says.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361724081910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:41:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361724796258-17</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm for the war, I'm against it, I don't show up to vote because I have no moral values. No one should believe a word Obama says.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361724796258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:53:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361724968766-18</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But I also know that Saddam poses no imminent and direct threat to the United States, or to his neighbors...and that in concert with the international community he can be contained until, in the way of all petty dictators, he falls away into the dustbin of history." Too bad he didn't go back and re-read his own words regarding Muammar Gaddafi before he took down a nation's government and military that was contained, a ruthless dictator that was posing no threat to the United States - until after we followed "passion, not reason" and acting as "arm chair, golf weekend warriors" bringing upon ourselves the insecurity leading up to Benghazi.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1361724968766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:56:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361725194066-19</Id><Topic><Title>Activists protest Terminator Machines</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361713494026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 08:44:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems by now you would have "discovered" that the Russian meteor was an autonomous weapon of some kind, invented and deployed by the NWO, Illuminati, and the PDQXYZBFD.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1361725194066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:59:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361725256210-20</Id><Topic><Title>fear the rise of china ?, the west is in the crosshairs.</Title><Username>manny11419</Username><Timestamp>1361716190127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 09:29:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ridiculus, That's not going to happen. The self destructive liberal ideas will rapidly fade away in europe and America once the reality of the government's actions are no longer able to be ignored. Asia will always be authoritarian.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361725256210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:00:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361725825355-21</Id><Topic><Title>All Right, Guys. It's Time To Take Back The House!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361723175238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:26:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fortunately, the "electoral college" or similar method does not determine the election of anyone in the Congress, and, by 2014, the folks in Ohio and elsewhere will have rooted out voter fraud, denying the ability of some, like Democrat Melowese Richardson, who was so proud of herself for voting for Obama twice along with casting votes in the names of four others “for Mr. Obama’s right to be President of the United States". People are beginning to have "buyer's remorse".</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1361725825355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:10:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726206652-22</Id><Topic><Title>The NWO drags over 400 US farmers to court over GM seeds</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361715055315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 09:10:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rarely agree with you, but I will say that I think Monsanto is absolutely EVIL.</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1361726206652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:16:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726572907-23</Id><Topic><Title>All Right, Guys. It's Time To Take Back The House!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361723175238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:26:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only buyers remorse will be for anyone who voted for a Republican Congressman.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1361726572907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:22:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726617493-24</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are some DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361726617493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:23:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726713529-25</Id><Topic><Title>All Right, Guys. It's Time To Take Back The House!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361723175238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:26:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rule the World? Are you some sort of Neo-Nutzi or just another DFC?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361726713529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:25:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726758820-26</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361651881753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't Romney-Ryan a flavor of Kool-Aid in 2012, one that fell out of favor with the public shortly after its market launch?</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361726758820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:25:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726807596-27</Id><Topic><Title>FAA is Giving Boeing a tough time</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361719280960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:21:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you feel so confident in what Boeing says, then buy a ticket for you and your family on the first overseas 787 flight with the proposed "fix".</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1361726807596</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:26:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726872647-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Turd Polisher Hooz Calls For Bush Impeachment</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361581074076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:57:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's very upset because someone called one of his DFC aliases a DFC. Now he's crying a river.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361726872647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:27:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726917045-29</Id><Topic><Title>Further prood as to why tighter Gun control laws will not protect School kids</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360843620319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 07:07:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The operative word is lone as in singular nut.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361726917045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:28:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361726969269-30</Id><Topic><Title>All Right, Guys. It's Time To Take Back The House!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361723175238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:26:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may be right about people's attitudes, in some cases. Ms. Melowese was certain that she "did not commit voter fraud". So, as long as enough Obama voters have that mindset, one of a conscience seared with a "hot iron", collective remorse may not prevail: "whatever it takes to win".</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1361726969269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:29:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361727000218-31</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1361722619260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:16:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual, bumper-for-brains nails it. In his own inimitable way.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361727000218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:30:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361727044251-32</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361651881753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a little DFC would ask that question................</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361727044251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:30:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361727231321-33</Id><Topic><Title>All Right, Guys. It's Time To Take Back The House!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361723175238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:26:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the word of the lordly.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1361727231321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:33:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361727499740-34</Id><Topic><Title>Monoply business...</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361373555135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:19:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a few years, aapl may not in smart phone business. AAPL may be down to 200$.. But BA is the only business in town... Do you bears get that?</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361727499740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:38:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361727603784-35</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361651881753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Little floydette is apparently jealous of the DFC, or the Distinguished Flying Cross. Perhaps Floydette should buy one on eBay or something. Then he could admire it, polish it, vacuum it, etc., and make something of his worthless life.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1361727603784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 12:40:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361729771456-36</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361651881753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does DFC stand for in your world, if not for Dist. Flying Cross? I seem to have missed the crucial post that would have defined it. Thanks.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1361729771456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 13:16:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361730976077-37</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz is a corrupt person with a damaged brain Bob. You can't have a logical discussion pointing out the hypocrisy of an Obama fanatic like Hooz.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361730976077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 13:36:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361732912839-38</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1361722619260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 11:16:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maobowa err spaz err censoredMO err peteetongmain err islamospaz err censorMOspazMO</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1361732912839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:08:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361734500822-39</Id><Title>You heard it 1st hear about the 787!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Elevator shoes for all 787 managers!</Msg><Username>mike_2face</Username><Timestamp>1361734500822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:35:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361734709763-40</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner Has Larger Windows</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361682449950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 00:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you or anyone know the actual size dimensionally of the windows?</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1361734709763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:38:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361734900476-41</Id><Title>Solution to 787 problem!!</Title><Msg>Cancel the MFer!</Msg><Username>av_week_reader</Username><Timestamp>1361734900476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361735195381-42</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ali, What is interesting is that Bush supporters are willing to admit that the Iraq war was a mistake - even if it seemed rational at the time to many. Was Bush lying or simply lying to himself? The WMDs were never found. Therefore, the invasion of Iraq was without merit. We decimated Libya who was not doing anything to us - this after speeches full of "passion", not reason, in which Obama authorized without Congressional approval, to take out a sovereign government and ensure the assassination of its leader. What was the premise? That there would be a massacre in Benghazi. The only thing is: Obama was speaking about a future massacre in Benghazi. While Obamanero fiddled (or rested for his fund raiser the next day), four Americans died without any help from their government, a government more concerned about the welfare of the residents of a terrorist haven. Then, Syria is untouched by Obama’s crocodile tears of passion for suffering. Why is that? It has been suggested that the Iraqi WMDs were transferred to Syria. There certainly were rumors before we attacked Iraq that that was what was taking place. And now the fall of the Syrian government would unveil the truth. Obama had to make sure that that truth would not be revealed before the 2012 election – if ever. While he may in the end not be able to stave off the fall of the Assad regime, he certainly was able to throttle it to a slow and miserable pace full of the massacres that he so “eloquently” opined for Libya to occur after he clenched his re-election.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1361735195381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 14:46:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361736642249-43</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isnt that the same President Obama that refused to come to the aid of an Ambassador and bombed multiple sovereign countries ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361736642249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:10:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361737405027-44</Id><Topic><Title>Cynthia McKenny: "Its not that Obama is the lesser of two evils"</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361651881753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 15:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see where Obama is deploying troops into Africa...He'll be dropping loving NON RACIST bombs on Africans very shortly....Abortions among blacks at all time highs...good job ...not hypocritical at all.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361737405027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:23:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361737822529-45</Id><Title>Just in case you believed Barry Soetoro was going to bring the troops home</Title><Msg>Nato May Station up to 12,000 Troops in Post-2014 Afghanistan AFP February 22, 2013 Nato may station up to 12,000 troops in Afghanistan to train and assist Kabul’s forces after its combat mission against the Taliban ends there in 2014, US officials said Friday. US Pentagon spokesman George Little said Nato was considering deployment of between 8,000 and 12,000 troops, including any US contribution, but no final decision has yet been made. Reports of a US presence of 8,000 to 12,000 troops “are not correct,” he said. President Barack Obama “is still reviewing options and has not made a decision about the size of a possible US presence after 2014,” he said, adding that discussions will now continue with Nato allies and Afghanistan.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361737822529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:30:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361738999333-46</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz we've been though this a hundred times. We have video of every Democrat stating that they believed Saddam had or was close to having weapons of mass destruction. The Dems were lying then too because most of them agreed with General Colin Powell when he gave his assessment prior to us engaging Iraq. You are making up whacky conspiracy theories again. Once the war became an opportunity to cast Bush as evil they all lied about their prior positions on WMDs. I once posted the article where BHO was counseled by his legal team about presenting a motion for congress to officially declare war when Obama took office after Bush, in order to protect himself from the possibility that Bush had engaged in an illegal action. Obama declined and in doing so he became legally just as culpable as Bush for any illegal actions regarding Iraq and other military actions. I've never met anyone as willfully ignorant as you and or much of a fanatic as you. Your ignorance is stunning.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361738999333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:49:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361739083219-47</Id><Topic><Title>Just in case you believed Barry Soetoro was going to bring the troops home</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361737822529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:30:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry is a pyschopathic liar. Everything he says Los Vegas makes odds on what will actually take place.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361739083219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:51:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361739160805-48</Id><Title>Google Allowing Government to Read Your Emails Without Warrant or Probable Cause</Title><Msg>With 425 million Gmail subscribers, Google claims to be the largest email provider in the world. They also provide telephone service through Google Voice, document storage through Google Drive, personal blogs through Blogger and they provide You Tube services. Did you know that Google saves and archives every form of communication that used any of their services? That even includes any corporate clients. If that doesn’t make you nervous, then this will. Google reports that they had 13,753 requests from local, state and federal government agencies to access and read your communications? The request involved 31,072 users. If you’re still not too concerned, then wait, it gets better. Did you know that there is a federal law that allows government agencies, local, state and federal, to gain access to Google’s archives without a warrant or establishing probable cause? Have you ever heard of the Electronic Communications Privacy Act (ECPA) of 1986? It’s actually a combination of the Electronic Communications Privacy Act and the Stored Wire Electronic Communications Act. Passed by a Republican controlled Senate and Democratic controlled House, the Act was signed into law by Republican President Ronald Reagan. Basically, the Electronic Communications Privacy Act (ECPA) of 1986 states that all email that has been opened and stored remotely and not on the hard drive of a computer, may be accessed without warrant. Now to confuse you as to what they can and can’t get access to: “If the government wants to read the content of an email accessed through Gmail, hear a voicemail message sent over Google’s telephone service Google Voice, or read other private content, it must still obtain a search warrant under federal law.” “However, information not sent in the body of an email or recorded in a voice message can be obtained by a simple subpoena – which does not require a government agency to show probable cause. Such information includes the name of an e-mail account holder, the IP address used when signing into and out of Gmail including dates and times, and other information you gave to Google when you created Gmail or other Google account.” “Other types of information require a court order from a judge, such as the IP address of a particular email, email addresses of those you correspond with, and the web sites a person has visited.” A search warrant is required to read the content of an email stored on Google’s servers, as well access as internet search histories, YouTube videos, photos, and other documents.” Now that you are thoroughly confused as to what can be accessed by which legal means, let me share this with you: of the 13,753 requests from local, state and federal governments in 2012, Google says that most of them were granted, even though a large number did not have search warrants. Therefore, be warned that if you use any of Google’s services and you don’t want the government knowing what you are saying or doing, then find another means of communication. However, that other means is probably in the same boat Google is, so best to talk face-to-face or not all if you are concerned about anyone else knowing</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361739160805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:52:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361739237488-49</Id><Topic><Title>Just in case you believed Barry Soetoro was going to bring the troops home</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361737822529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:30:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its easy for me.. Whatever Barry Soetoro, Barrack Hussein Frank Marshall Davis Obama says....I just expect the exact OPPOSITE to take place</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361739237488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:53:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361739251708-50</Id><Topic><Title>FAA is Giving Boeing a tough time</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361719280960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:21:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will life insurance companies consider 787 pilots high risk , along with cancer, heart failure, and other high risk insurable factors?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361739251708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:54:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361739465894-51</Id><Topic><Title>Google Allowing Government to Read Your Emails Without Warrant or Probable Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361739160805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:52:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should be afraid, Spart. Be very afraid. I would have thought this was a usurpation before I started witnessing your sedition; or insanity. Face-to-face communication would cut your audience by a couple hundred, anyway. All you'd have left is BORED veterans who only wanted advice on their benefits.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1361739465894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:57:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361739680195-52</Id><Topic><Title>how many revenue passengers have not been able to fly on the 787 since the grounding ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571041385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:10:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is the difference in weight between a lithium battery and a nicad and will a nicad have enough power to work in a 787 with extensive electrical requirements? What would the time be for a re certification of a safer mature battery like a nicad over the lithium is the issue extra time required to certify the battery change or is an older style batter unable to handle the requirements, quick charge power? what is the actual reason a older proven battery is not being considered beside the idea the Boeing executives want the problem battery? Is is money , certification time, sees like if it could be done the passengers might enjoy Boeing fixing the problem with a safe battery or would the proven older batter still have the same problem is the root cause is too much charge or other electrical issues comming inot the battery?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361739680195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:01:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361739982567-53</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's right, it's hard to discuss anything with a corrupt DFC that's been brain washed.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361739982567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:06:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361739997673-54</Id><Topic><Title>Double talk by Boeing.....no temp. fix and NOT abandoning Lithium Batteries</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361563273991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is the reason a mature battery technology is not being used? How much more weight than two 70pound batteries are we talking about? Seems like one big football line man weight or a little less fuel would cancel out all that what 100 pound of extra weight? Would Boeing owe a huge amount of money to the airlines for the change from specifications? Would a heavier mature battery not work due to power requirements? Is the time to certify a mature battery longer tthan a fireproof and fire containment box? that fix says we don't know why but we know a fire is going to happen, not a very good PR for airlines of Boeing to use right?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361739997673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:06:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361740303567-55</Id><Title>why is Boeing going with a fire proof box instead of a mature battery solution?</Title><Msg>is the mature battery not powerful enough to operate the 787 electrical system? Are too many other electrical systems going to be changed for a mature battery to be installed? what is the weight difference between the fire lithium battery and the what nicad mature battery? Would Boeing have to pay back customers for changing the specification from lithium to nicad? How much time is involved in a older battery certification than a fire proof box certification? Is this a money thing over passenger safety?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361740303567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:11:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361740716309-56</Id><Topic><Title>fear the rise of china ?, the west is in the crosshairs.</Title><Username>manny11419</Username><Timestamp>1361716190127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 09:29:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wrong the NIE, compiled by all 16 u.s intelligence agencies, say in its summary of conclusion that the power is shifting from west to east and u.s decline is inevitable. read 2020 NIE.</Msg><Username>manny11419</Username><Timestamp>1361740716309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:18:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361740793307-57</Id><Topic><Title>why is Boeing going with a fire proof box instead of a mature battery solution?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361740303567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:11:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Given the 'life " span of the Boeing LI batteries and all the new special arrangements making them like NO other battery in the world it would appear that the lack of adult supervision in the corner office has reverted back to the ' gillete" razor blade business model . we give you the plane at a discount, bcut make it up in the cost of the special batteries !! YEP lose money on each plane, but make it up in volume _ SEE its right there on the power point charts</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361740793307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:19:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361740879242-58</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Stirring 2002 Speech Against the Iraq War</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361721432460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 10:57:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bob see my post further down on WMDs and Obama's legal team warning to Obama about continuing the war without a congressional vote. By continuing the war Obama became just as culpable as Bush and anyone like Hooz who doesn't understand that if they think Bush is a war criminal then Obama is also a criminal, which his legal team explained to him. It's simple. If the war was illegal then Obama continued an illegal war and is automatically a criminal too. Cornell West gets it but he has a brain whereas Hooz is an idiot and a fanatical Obama turd polisher..</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361740879242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:21:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361747961429-59</Id><Topic><Title>Google Allowing Government to Read Your Emails Without Warrant or Probable Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361739160805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:52:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Private No-Ball thinks the end of the 4th Amendment is a wonderful thing ... just like the little Communist he is renowned to be. ...and as a certified Cult member...You never hear him bad mouth the endless war NOW either do you even though American deaths in Afganistan have DOUBLED since the Kenyan became President?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361747961429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:19:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361748041910-60</Id><Topic><Title>Activists protest Terminator Machines</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361713494026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 08:44:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.....what in tarnation are you talking about ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361748041910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361748958473-61</Id><Topic><Title>Activists protest Terminator Machines</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361713494026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 08:44:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a Raven alias.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361748958473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:35:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361749067917-62</Id><Topic><Title>Google Allowing Government to Read Your Emails Without Warrant or Probable Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361739160805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:52:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Private is a DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361749067917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 18:37:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361751542130-63</Id><Topic><Title>Google Allowing Government to Read Your Emails Without Warrant or Probable Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1361739160805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 15:52:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any decent person should be afraid. Socialists/communists? It's what they do, and expect.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361751542130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:19:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361751662421-64</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing but politically motivated posts</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1361627220270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:47:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regardless of lame this message board is I'm gonna use an overused message board statement and m going to short this stok with impunity. Really since it has climbed out of the hole of the financial crisis and broke 60 in 2010 for 3 straight years it has traded between 60 and 80. For three freaking years just between 60 and 80. What would make this time any different, especially with the current headwinds. So with any POP or even right here I am shorting. I realize no one cares but I am putting it here for public record. BA is about to perform its ritual and head back down to 60. A quick launch up would be too good, looking at the chart anytime it does a quick rise it sinks just as fast. BTW I don't have a lot of money so I,m starting out with 100 shares. Around $7700 I have dry powder left for 4 tranches of 100 share on each 4-5% or so rise depending on the action. If my cash gets sucked in I will double down in one shot with 400 shares on margin. For real if it gets tht far it would put it around 90-95 a share which is impossible but ill be ready because this is the stock market and I'm well aware I could get the shaft at ay moment. In fact if this ends in a losing trade I will literally eat my hat and post it on you tube.</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1361751662421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:21:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361752885263-65</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing but politically motivated posts</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1361627220270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:47:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I shorted it Friday at 66.55. I was certain the FAA would not simply allow them to just build a modified case for batteries that could burn up or explode. The danger of shorting it is they do buy their own stock back and can skew the price anytime they choose.</Msg><Username>onedge953</Username><Timestamp>1361752885263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:41:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361753110326-66</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing but politically motivated posts</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1361627220270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:47:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typo 76.55</Msg><Username>onedge953</Username><Timestamp>1361753110326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 19:45:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361754588487-67</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing but politically motivated posts</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1361627220270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-23 08:47:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've read an informative message board concerning stocks have you? Please tell us one. Most have weirdo socialists/communists on them. Shoot your best shot.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361754588487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 20:09:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361761976915-68</Id><Topic><Title>why is Boeing going with a fire proof box instead of a mature battery solution?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361740303567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 16:11:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would think an extra 100 lbs would be about right. As far as certification is concern Cessna seemed to be able to make the switch within a month when they had a similar problem with their Li batteries and given that the 777 uses NiCad one would think that Boeing could piggy back on some of the certification used for that.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1361761976915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:12:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361763601893-69</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner Has Larger Windows</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361682449950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 00:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A more appropriate name for the Dreamliner should be the Albatross.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361763601893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 22:40:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361765420294-70</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner Has Larger Windows</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361682449950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 00:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10.7 x 18.4 inches.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1361765420294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 23:10:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361766333073-71</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner Has Larger Windows</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361682449950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 00:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the info. I don't know if I could squeeze through and opening that size or not. Probably get stuck, then what?</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1361766333073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-24 23:25:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>