<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367726855506-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Blames U.S. For Crime And Gun Violence In Mexico; No Mention Of Fast And Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367712202165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heh heh heh heh heh</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1367726855506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 00:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367731439033-2</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrr45 I will think of you when I take a trip to the can tonight</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367731439033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367731737099-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Blames U.S. For Crime And Gun Violence In Mexico; No Mention Of Fast And Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367712202165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When a Congree can legislate their own benes we all just might be doomed. Pensions &amp;healthcare and earmarks. The common manhas little. Obama has the black man thinking he is looking out for him oh sure with a 19% UE rate 49M on Food Stamps. Oh yeah Obama is looking out for blacks.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1367731737099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367732379745-4</Id><Topic><Title>A letter to George Bush and #$%$ Cheney from a Dying Veteran !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367695931405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five U.S. troops killed by IED attack in Afghanistan AFP May 4, 2013 A huge roadside bomb killed five US troops in southern Afghanistan on Saturday, officials said, in the deadliest attack on NATO-led forces this year. “Five American soldiers were killed at about noon when their armoured vehicle hit a powerful roadside mine in Maiwand district,” General Abdul Razeq, Kandahar province’s police chief, told AFP. The troops died in an improvised explosive device (IED) attack, NATO’s International Security Assistance Force confirmed in a statement without specifying the nationalities of the victims, in line with coalition policy. The attack came four days after three British soldiers were killed in a similar blast in the neighbouring province of Helmand.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367732379745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367732554308-5</Id><Title>Next time you ask yourself why the Government is stockpiling 1.6 billion rounds</Title><Msg>....remember that the Attorney General has decreed that the ICAP scandal where the worlds largest 15 banks are price fixing virtually everything and the figures are over 100 times the budget of the United States......and just remember that Holder said he would not prosecute since he is AFRAID that these 15 banks (the usual suspects) might purposely crash the economy !!! ... just in case you are wondering why the government needs to stockpile 1.6 billion rounds of hollowpoints !!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367732554308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367732887759-6</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 or mr pick a stock that is a test mule , you can try of make a fantasy trade if you want to, make a false point from a low to a high instead of using current information. I am using the default settting that is used by Yahoo finance, and I used the cnn money and their exsisting default settings.. Thi is not a scam like your attempting to do here. Itis what it is a world wide default setting and I am looking at those two accepted charts as is. spartacus99991, you asked , " Why don't I use 4 years? " Its not becausxe you have uncovered anything, the trend is the trend for short term or long term. Boeing investors have made far less than Airbus investors over time. Yes for a 3 month run on the manipulatied Boeing stock buyback to cover for the disaster of the grounded 787, to stop a run on selling Boeing stock The Chicago failure management used shareholder money to fake it and you can make money on that, well good for you but to wait for 5 years for a 20 % gain is not looking at the miss of the 184% five year gain with Airbus . I know yoru spinning but please dont be so stupid oke !, but if Boeing were good it would be up like Aribus for 5 years or 3 years and 4 years is nto the default so I do not dig for a fake term to show a point in time your are fgiring not using the figures get it well all know yoru fake game ! , I am using the default setting on yahoo finance and the cnn money does not use a 4 years trade period apparently cnn money is alos conspirinag against you too har har har get it now , nope too slooooowwww</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367732887759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367733146693-7</Id><Topic><Title>How does the conspiriscist Hillary Clinton think?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367680235156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I quoted that same article but Chris Genna claimed this very same Hoozdik article never existed..... As for Hooz...He clearly wanted to belittle anyone who questions know liars and brand them as "conspiracy theorists" as if that is a bad term...when in fact the leading crime in jurisprudence is "conspiracy"...I quoted the article and pointed out that the GOVERNMENTS verison of 9-11 ALSO was a conspiracy theory since that is EXACLTY what 19 Saudis with box cutters taking over an airplane and ramming it into buildings entails....A CONSPIRACY or I pointed out that the Warren Commissions (the Governments) entire theory rested on a MAGIC BULLET...so you see, the hypocrisy never ends. Hooz adroitly avoided this line of thought and instead started talking about Alex Jones...who made TV history by destroying Piers Morgan on TV...but Hooz wants to point out that Alex makes his OWN money....I pointed out that MSNBC gets bailout money from the Banksters...go figure</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367733146693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367736991450-8</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about your 55 low value? Both yahoo and cnn show that is not right. And I didn't use the low value to support my 150 percent figure. Bottom value would have been over a 210 percent gain. So I wasn't lying and wasn't posting "crapola". Own up and admit you made a mistake or are you above that? It's not a character flaw to admit it.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1367736991450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 02:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367741392561-9</Id><Topic><Title>How does the conspiriscist Hillary Clinton think?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367680235156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said I never saw it, Loon. That you confuse those two statements shows how you arrive at most of your conclusions.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1367741392561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 04:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367749340905-10</Id><Title>What Do Liberals And Terrorists Have In Common ?</Title><Msg>No job, and a goobermint check . There it is . . Y.T. Jumbojetski .</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1367749340905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 06:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367758102232-11</Id><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Msg>Speaking from the Milkin Institute Global Conference in Beverly Hills [on April 30], Al Gore told Bloomberg News that he helped prevent a “violent revolution” by accepting the Supreme Court’s verdict in Bush v. Gore. “I made the decision in the aftermath of the Supreme Court decision 12 or 13 years ago to respect the rule of law,” said the former vice president. “I strongly disagreed with their opinion, said so, but the rule of law is the bedrock of American democracy. There is no intermediate step between a final Supreme Court decision and a violent revolution…” ________________________________________ Who says you can't live in the past or rewrite history? Manbearpig is either demented or suffering from unreleased chakras me thinks.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367758990328-12</Id><Topic><Title>How does the conspiriscist Hillary Clinton think?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367680235156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correct..you said you never saw it at least 3 times and usd that as a pretext to "gaslight" me (google I the term)...when in fact you are the biggest gasbag on this board.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367758990328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 09:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367760028638-13</Id><Topic><Title>A letter to George Bush and #$%$ Cheney from a Dying Veteran !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367695931405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who gave him the right to speak on behalf of all soldiers killed or wounded in the war and all families who suffered? He is a disturbed person pushing his political agenda on his death bed. If he had presented this letter in a personal manner I would have found it to be acceptable but once he crossed the line and assumed he had the permission to speak for everyone, his words became empty.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367760028638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 09:20:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367760689428-14</Id><Topic><Title>A letter to George Bush and #$%$ Cheney from a Dying Veteran !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367695931405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ive found, working with a lot of injured Vets myself that he DOES speak for a lot of Veterans ... or at least a lot of Vets share his views. There is a fine line between whining and trying to effect positive change and to right egregious wrongs....I was going to ask if you think the Iraq war was worth it ? ... But the obvious question is that it was wort it to some people .....Just not most of America</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367760689428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 09:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367763058723-15</Id><Topic><Title>A letter to George Bush and #$%$ Cheney from a Dying Veteran !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367695931405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus is allied with m uslim made disasters, CAIR, etc, to find disgruntled soldiers and other critics of America's response to m uslim made disasters.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367763058723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367763313884-16</Id><Topic><Title>A letter to George Bush and #$%$ Cheney from a Dying Veteran !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367695931405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a visit from spazticus is like a visit from maobowa...demoralizing like a visit from Nidal Malik Hasan</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367763313884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367764341247-17</Id><Topic><Title>A letter to George Bush and #$%$ Cheney from a Dying Veteran !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367695931405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First I would argue that your perception of what Veterans feel about Iraq is based on your interactions with less than .05% of those who served. According to a Pew research poll only 33% of post 911 veterans feel it wasn't worth it. 67% feel it was worth it. So the person that wrote this letter certainly DOES NOT speak for all those he claims to speak for. As far as my view is concerned I am aware of my bias and I look at such things with more of a historical perspective rather than just the current war. I am bothered by the blood for oil aspect of the US involvement in the Mideast, especially today. I am upset because since 2006 we have discovered that there is more oil and gas in North America than has ever existed in the Mideast. Yet Obama inexplicably prevents exploration on government land aka "the peoples land" and is preventing/delaying America's ability to be free of foreign oil. Why are Americans not rallying to get off foreign oil ASAP now that we can? We don't need oil from the Mideast anymore and there is no reason to sacrifice our soldiers to protect corrupt oil regimes anymore. We don't send troops to protect Christians in Africa that are being exterminated by Mus lim factions so we shouldn't have troops in the Mideast either. We don't need the Arabs anymore.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367764341247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367764506884-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Blames U.S. For Crime And Gun Violence In Mexico; No Mention Of Fast And Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367712202165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about the D.H. rule?</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1367764506884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367765175744-19</Id><Title>Has Barry explained his inaccurate statements? Is he planning to?</Title><Msg>Until the press holds Barry accountable for his childish tactics born out of his being rejected on gun control, he will continue presenting his childish tactics which undermine the interests of the USA. It is clear that Barry is angry and wants to punish Americans for disagreeing with hi stance on gun control. He is an egomaniac that puts himself first and the country second. That is the real issue and the elephant in the room that no one wants to acknowledge.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367765175744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367765432198-20</Id><Topic><Title>Has Barry explained his inaccurate statements? Is he planning to?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367765175744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The good thing is more and more voters understand that Barry depends on lies to dupe them. And you are right, once the media turns on Barry, and questions his falsehoods turn out the lights.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1367765432198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367765604616-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Blames U.S. For Crime And Gun Violence In Mexico; No Mention Of Fast And Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367712202165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He blamed the USA in front of the United Nations long ago setting the stage for his gun control desire as if it were an International issue now between the USA and Mexico gaining the need for International legislation. Then Fast and Furious surfaced, and Obama had to apply Executive Privilege to protect himself.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1367765604616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367767255636-22</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More bs from waynedick..as usual! He never gives up..whats the agenda wdick?</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1367767255636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367767263122-23</Id><Topic><Title>Has Barry explained his inaccurate statements? Is he planning to?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367765175744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you may be right, our schools n media produce a never ending supply of moore-ons, and dumb crooks proved they could provide the difference in swing states with more votes than registered voters in dumb districts coming down virtually unanimous for barack (and dumb senators by default)</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367767263122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367768471255-24</Id><Title>Tensions spike after new Israeli strikes in Syria</Title><Msg>The Fateh-110, or "Conqueror" in Farsi, is a short-range ballistic missile developed by Iran and first put into service in 2002. http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/05/05/israeli-warplanes-strike-syria/2136449/</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1367768471255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:41:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367768546794-25</Id><Topic><Title>Has Barry explained his inaccurate statements? Is he planning to?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367765175744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it should have been, but without the medias help, i guess we'll have to see the occupier though another four years of destruction / looting</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367768546794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 11:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367770136792-26</Id><Title>Robert Bigelow Plans a Real Estate Empire in Space</Title><Msg>Unlike traditional spacecraft and space stations, which are restricted in size by the outer dimensions of the rockets used to deliver them into orbit, Bigelow’s vessels are inflatable. http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-05-02/robert-bigelow-plans-a-real-estate-empire-in-space</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1367770136792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367770873897-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Appoval Rating Sinks</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1367598564511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 12:29:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Landslide victories? Rewiriting history? You are deluding no one but yourself and other simple minded people which unfortunately we have far to many of. Obama received 51% and 52% of the popular vote (and that includes dead and illegal voters who voted for Obama). That means 48% and 49% of the the voters didn't want the the usurper who currently occupies the White House. Got that. Nearly half of the voters in this country didn't want Obama. Far from a landslide. And as for the electoral college, he ranks 21st and 26th place in 57 presidential elections. There was no landlslide and he has no mandate.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1367770873897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367771139627-28</Id><Topic><Title>Robert Bigelow Plans a Real Estate Empire in Space</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1367770136792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like Hooz's girlfriends.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1367771139627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367772076344-29</Id><Topic><Title>A letter to George Bush and #$%$ Cheney from a Dying Veteran !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367695931405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we don't need Arabs and we don't need Oil and we don't need the Mideast....then why are we there ? Personally I think there is a resource war going on.....Peak oil is ONLY true vis a vis the fact that America has tons of oil...just very expensive to get to and very hard to refine...we are still trying to get the last bit of Mideast oil before we break...also there is a question of the world reserve currency....Every time a Mideast country claims it no longer wants to buy and sell oil in Dollars we invade...you ever notice that ? YEAH...the Bankers rule the world</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367772076344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367772245672-30</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With those comments, there is then little to wonder how Gore would have handled the 9-11 attack. Imagine his finger on "the button".</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1367772245672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367772306327-31</Id><Topic><Title>A letter to George Bush and #$%$ Cheney from a Dying Veteran !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367695931405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As for your Poll: That is not what this site says ..and it quotes the same Pew poll...Most Vets say Iraq and Afganistan was NOT worth it http://www.cnn.com/2011/10/05/us/war-attitudes</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367772306327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367773039182-32</Id><Title>A letter from Iraq War Sodier before he was killed in IED attack</Title><Msg>2LT Mark Daily was killed in an IED attack He was named the ROTC's outstanding cadet for 2005 and also a Distinguished Military Graduate, the highest ROTC award. This was his MySpace post Sunday, October 29, 2006 WHY I JOINED Current mood: optimistic Why I Joined: This question has been asked of me so many times in so many different contexts that I thought it would be best if I wrote my reasons for joining the Army on my page for all to see. First, the more accurate question is why I volunteered to go to Iraq. After all, I joined the Army a week after we declared war on Saddam's government with the intention of going to Iraq. Now, after years of training and preparation, I am finally here. Much has changed in the last three years. The criminal Ba'ath regime has been replaced by an insurgency fueled by Iraq's neighbors who hope to partition Iraq for their own ends. This is coupled with the ever present transnational militant Islamist movement which has seized upon Iraq as the greatest way to kill Americans, along with anyone else they happen to be standing near. What was once a paralyzed state of fear is now the staging ground for one of the largest transformations of power and ideology the Middle East has experienced since the collapse of the Ottoman Empire. Thanks to Iran, Syria, and other enlightened local actors, this transformation will be plagued by interregional hatred and genocide. And I am now in the center of this...</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367773039182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367773100144-33</Id><Topic><Title>A letter from Iraq War Sodier before he was killed in IED attack</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367773039182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this why I joined? Yes. Much has been said about America's intentions in overthrowing Saddam Hussein and seeking to establish a new state based upon political representation and individual rights. Many have framed the paradigm through which they view the conflict around one-word explanations such as "oil" or "terrorism," favoring the one which best serves their political persuasion. I did the same thing, and anyone who knew me before I joined knows that I am quite aware and at times sympathetic to the arguments against the war in Iraq. If you think the only way a person could bring themselves to volunteer for this war is through sheer desperation or blind obedience then consider me the exception (though there are countless like me). I joined the fight because it occurred to me that many modern day "humanists" who claim to possess a genuine concern for human beings throughout the world are in fact quite content to allow their fellow "global citizens" to suffer under the most hideous state apparatuses and conditions. Their excuses used to be my excuses. When asked why we shouldn't confront the Ba'ath party, the Taliban or the various other tyrannies throughout this world, my answers would allude to vague notions of cultural tolerance (forcing women to wear a veil and stay indoors is such a quaint cultural tradition), the sanctity of national sovereignty (how eager we internationalists are to throw up borders to defend dictatorships!) or even a creeping suspicion of America's intentions. When all else failed, I would retreat to my fragile moral ecosystem that years of living in peace and liberty had provided me...con't</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367773100144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367773171223-34</Id><Topic><Title>A letter from Iraq War Sodier before he was killed in IED attack</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367773039182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would write off war because civilian casualties were guaranteed, or temporary alliances with illiberal forces would be made, or tank fuel was toxic for the environment. My fellow "humanists" and I would relish contently in our self righteous declaration of opposition against all military campaigns against dictatorships, congratulating one another for refusing to taint that aforementioned fragile moral ecosystem that many still cradle with all the revolutionary tenacity of the members of Rage Against the Machine and Greenday. Others would point to America's historical support of Saddam Hussein, sighting it as hypocritical that we would now vilify him as a thug and a tyrant. Upon explaining that we did so to ward off the fiercely Islamist Iran, which was correctly identified as the greater threat at the time, eyes are rolled and hypocrisy is declared. Forgetting that America sided with Stalin to defeat Hitler, who was promptly confronted once the Nazis were destroyed, America's initial engagement with Saddam and other regional actors is identified as the ultimate argument against America's moral crusade. And maybe it is. Maybe the reality of politics makes all political action inherently crude and immoral. Or maybe it is these adventures in philosophical masturbation that prevent people from ever taking any kind of effective action against men like Saddam Hussein. One thing is for certain, as disagreeable or as confusing as my decision to enter the fray may be, consider what peace vigils against genocide have accomplished lately. Consider that there are 19 year old soldiers from the Midwest who have never touched a college campus or a protest who have done more to uphold the universal legitimacy of representative government and individual rights by placing themselves between Iraqi voting lines and homicidal religious fanatics...con't So that is why I joined. In the time</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367773171223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367773303564-35</Id><Topic><Title>A letter from Iraq War Sodier before he was killed in IED attack</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367773039182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Often times it is less about how clean your actions are and more about how pure your intentions are. So that is why I joined. In the time it took for you to read this explanation, innocent people your age have suffered under the crushing misery of tyranny. Every tool of philosophical advancement and communication that we use to develop our opinions about this war are denied to countless human beings on this planet, many of whom live under the regimes that have, in my opinion, been legitimately targeted for destruction. Some have allowed their resentment of the President to stir silent applause for setbacks in Iraq. Others have ironically decried the war because it has tied up our forces and prevented them from confronting criminal regimes in Sudan, Uganda, and elsewhere. I simply decided that the time for candid discussions of the oppressed was over, and I joined. In digesting this posting, please remember that America's commitment to overthrow Saddam Hussein and his sons existed before the current administration and would exist into our future children's lives had we not acted. Please remember that the problems that plague Iraq today were set in motion centuries ago and were up until now held back by the most cruel of cages. Don't forget that human beings have a responsibility to one another and that Americans will always have a responsibility to the oppressed. Don't overlook the obvious reasons to disagree with the war but don't cheapen the moral aspects either. Assisting a formerly oppressed population in converting their torn society into a plural, democratic one is dangerous and difficult business, especially when being attacked and sabotaged from literally every direction. So if you have anything to say to me at the end of this reading, let it at least include "Good Luck" Mark Daily On his MySpace front page, he featured this quote: "Patience demolishes mountains" -Arab proverb These are the kind and caliber of men who fight for us. Twenty-three years y</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367773303564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:01:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367774000745-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Appoval Rating Sinks</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1367598564511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 12:29:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>duh corrupt apparatchiks (inclusive of our media n noncompetitive dumbocrat school system) bought it home for barack, huh #$%$</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367774000745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367774348951-37</Id><Title>BA</Title><Msg>The best aircraft company in the world. 777X is the next feather in their caps. The 777 is the best aircraft ever built. Only commercial aircraft in history that has never had a major crash. Take it to the bank. See you at 150!</Msg><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1367774348951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367774991386-38</Id><Topic><Title>How does the conspiriscist Hillary Clinton think?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367680235156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I only said it once. "Loon" doesn't really cover your case any longer.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1367774991386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367775356850-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Appoval Rating Sinks</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1367598564511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 12:29:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Along with all those illegal that hooz registered to vote and then drove them to the polls.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1367775356850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367775368458-40</Id><Topic><Title>How does the conspiriscist Hillary Clinton think?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367680235156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she thinks like barack, they were broke of the same saul alinsky, cloward-piven, SDS, black panther, weather underground, marxist mold "The Shadow Party was conceived and organized principally by George Soros, Hillary Clinton and Harold McEwan Ickes… "The Shadow Party is the real power driving the Democrat machine. It is a network of radicals dedicated to transforming our constitutional republic into a socialist hive. The leader of these radicals is ... George Soros. He has essentially privatized the Democratic Party, bringing it under his personal control. The Shadow Party is the instrument through which he exerts that control. ... It works by siphoning off hundreds of millions of dollars in campaign contributions that would have gone to the Democratic Party in normal times, and putting those contributions at the personal disposal of Mr. Soros. He then uses that money to buy influence and loyalty where he sees fit. In 2003, Soros set up a network of privately-owned groups which acts as a shadow or mirror image of the Party. It performs all the functions we would normally expect the real Democratic Party to perform, such as shaping the Party platform, fielding candidates, running campaigns, and so forth. However, it performs these functions under the private supervision of Mr. Soros and his associates. The Shadow Party derives its power from its ability to raise huge sums of money. By controlling the Democrat purse strings, the Shadow Party can make or break any Democrat candidate by deciding whether or not to fund him. During the 2004 election cycle, the Shadow Party raised more than $300 million for Democrat candidates, prompting one of its operatives, MoveOn PAC director Eli Pariser, to declare, “Now it’s our party. We bought it, we own it…”"”</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367775368458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:36:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367775373846-41</Id><Topic><Title>How does the conspiriscist Hillary Clinton think?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367680235156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know, I know, Sparty. Half your world view is based on what you learn in a big dark room watching MOVIES. (Tedll me again what lesson you learned by watching "The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King." :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1367775373846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367776789755-42</Id><Topic><Title>How does the conspiriscist Hillary Clinton think?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367680235156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err spaz err spazlamo err brain damaged err delusions of something--anything sane err Soros err spartaloon's conspiracy theory goofusbraindeluded thinking err bumper</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1367776789755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367780555170-43</Id><Topic><Title>How does the conspiriscist Hillary Clinton think?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367680235156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you copy that tripe from ?</Msg><Username>shameless_commie</Username><Timestamp>1367780555170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367780687017-44</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think of you every minute I go to the can...lol what a bs artist you are! Boeing rocks , you don't!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1367780687017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367780815841-45</Id><Topic><Title>BA</Title><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1367774348951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 13:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>could n't agree more...waynedickdick w/ his 4 ID's will downgrade your post what a joke the moron is!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1367780815841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367781047498-46</Id><Topic><Title>A letter from Iraq War Sodier before he was killed in IED attack</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367773039182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 12:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What can you say about this soldiers death knowing that the idiot Junior could have easily avoided the Iraq war eh censored-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367781047498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367781267590-47</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Infestid I know you cant remember past last week but in 2000 there were a lot of us who believed and still believe that Bush should have been elected- not appointed by a bunch of right wingt zealots polluting the US Supreme court</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367781267590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367781332573-48</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fat boy you got the worst possible handeling of 9-11 as it was</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367781332573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:15:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367781862536-49</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrr45 , what are you 3 years old , you can't come up with your own smack down, what a loser like Boeing stock har har har</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367781862536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367781916576-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Appoval Rating Sinks</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1367598564511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 12:29:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what it really included was all kinds of crookery on the part of criminal republicans to defeat him- now they weep and wail and gnash their teeth because THEIR dead and illegal voters along with their illegal voter obstruction weren't enough to stop Obama</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1367781916576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:25:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367782524822-51</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 you just copied my statement that is called Plagiarism is the "wrongful appropriation" and "purloining and publication" of another author's "language, thoughts, ideas, or expressions," and the representation of them as one's own original work.[ I also told you I used the charts as set up by Yahoo finance and cnn money you are the person making a start point and end point and I added over time Airbus is most definitely a better stock to make money on your a Boeing hack and a scam artist, a poor one at that</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367782524822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367782682278-52</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father _zosima, in the the UNITED STATES of AMERICA, we have seperation of church and state. your opinion does not count. go back to saving souls.</Msg><Username>dirtpoordog</Username><Timestamp>1367782682278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 15:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367785538982-53</Id><Title>In England, We Have The Royal Family...</Title><Msg>but Barack and Michelle Obama are even classier than the royal family. The American people are so blessed that they had the good sense to elect Mr. Obama twice.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1367785538982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367785899532-54</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh? Specifically, what statement are you referring to?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1367785899532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367785946070-55</Id><Topic><Title>In England, We Have The Royal Family...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1367785538982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING......HOPE YOU WERE JUST MAKING A FUNNY.......</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1367785946070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 16:32:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367788574482-56</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loser...? Doubled my money and more in the horizon in 3 1/2 years span...not too bad wdickdick!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1367788574482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 17:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367788949652-57</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>al gore says a lot of stuff sparty, doesn't make em true al gore is for sukers</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1367788949652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 17:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367791086701-58</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"we have seperation of church and state." Tell that to the deluded morons who would teach Creationism and "Intelligent Design" in the schools.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1367791086701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 17:58:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367791216742-59</Id><Topic><Title>Pensions and STEM</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1367716196832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 21:09:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Public pensions are funded by tax payers. Most cities and states are deeply in debt and some are even on the edge of bankruptcy. The future of public pensions is in peril. Tax payers can't and shouldn't continue to shoulder this burden.</Msg><Username>kipparoo2002</Username><Timestamp>1367791216742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367793947637-60</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush was elected despite the effort of the Floida Supreme Court to make new election laws on the spot and get AG elected. You may not agree with the results, but the USSC was correct. .</Msg><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1367793947637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367794258679-61</Id><Topic><Title>Has Barry explained his inaccurate statements? Is he planning to?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367765175744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He would win again in 2016 if he were allowed to run" "Stupid is as stupid does" continues to be favored by many - sad.</Msg><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1367794258679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367794370664-62</Id><Title>Australian order</Title><Msg>From Motely fool: The RAAF buy 12 new EA-18G Growlers to provide the electronic warfare capability it needs. The purchase price has yet been settled, but news reports say the cost could be around $1.5 billion.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1367794370664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367798998211-63</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please try to make something of your life. Join the Honey Boo Boo fan club or something. At least that would be a start for you.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1367798998211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 20:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367805456805-64</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK...TELL US WHATS YOUR AGENDA...</Title><Msg>...on knocking boeing down day after day..(w/ several id's)...were you once employed by boeing and let go? Tell us waynedddick!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1367805456805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367808045054-65</Id><Title>The Kent Raven and</Title><Msg>His aliases, are without a doubt the dumbest posters here...........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1367808045054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367808675315-66</Id><Topic><Title>Has Barry explained his inaccurate statements? Is he planning to?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367765175744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 10:46:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here we go again......Obama childish........he's a grown man that you disagree with</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367808675315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367808732787-67</Id><Topic><Title>Australian order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1367794370664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 18:52:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news</Msg><Username>brotech_az</Username><Timestamp>1367808732787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367808857839-68</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Appoval Rating Sinks</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1367598564511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 12:29:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Approval percentages rise and fall......I know one way he can raise his ratings......how about getting into another war, normally the country rallies behind a Prez when he first goes to war...........</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367808857839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367808988682-69</Id><Topic><Title>What Do Liberals And Terrorists Have In Common ?</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1367749340905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 06:22:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does a conservative and terrorist have in common......neither likes government .....have plenty of weapons.....and not much gray matter</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367808988682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809128093-70</Id><Topic><Title>Will Ron Paul or Donald Trump...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1367712973646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you really serious......you would go down the road following R Paul and Trump....... Don't tell me where you were educated ....I would start to think less of the place and maybe I don't want to do that</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367809128093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 22:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809316485-71</Id><Topic><Title>Next time you ask yourself why the Government is stockpiling 1.6 billion rounds</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367732554308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 01:42:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you know how many rounds of bullets the military has............where did YOU get the info on the govt stock piling rounds.....do you work in a ammunition factory....or are you just talking out of your hat with no factual info whatsoever.....</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367809316485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809499668-72</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrr45, you really don't know how Yahoo finance works do you , you have 6 thumbs down , nobody cares what you spew, if you had any proof that I was let go or you actually had a real name then by all means lets hear it , . I use world wide recognized stock charts and you ignore the truth and make up false stories , you smell, and like I said i will think of you tonight with I visit the can</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367809499668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:04:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809507527-73</Id><Topic><Title>Multiple Obama Birth Certificates Surface In Alabama Eligibility Case</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367466091224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 23:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please come out your underground bunker and instead of chase the tired birther issue....try to tie the Boston marathon bombing directly Obama...... you need to give the former up</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367809507527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809690270-74</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Blames U.S. For Crime And Gun Violence In Mexico; No Mention Of Fast And Furious</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1367712202165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama probably not as good House slave as Romney would have been</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367809690270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367809749655-75</Id><Title>Boeing revenues declined YOY by 24.5% so that is how I know the 24% stock price increase was stock buy back</Title><Msg>he first quarter sales were significantly down, primarily due the Dreamliner crisis. Sales dropped almost 15.3% on a QoQ basis, and fell by approximately 2.5% on a YoY basis. The Commercial Airplanes segment, within which the 787 is reported, faced a decline in revenues of around 2.3% on a YoY basis, and a staggering 24.5% on a QoQ basis. As per my estimates, the effect of the 787 battery crisis on the Commercial Airplanes segment's revenues was from $3 to $4 billion.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367809749655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367809869135-76</Id><Topic><Title>Another 747 BellyFlops on Afghani Runaway</Title><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1367535576926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 18:59:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yee Haaw..............??? You like to see planes with people in them crash??? What comes around goes around........</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367809869135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367810038432-77</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing revenues declined YOY by 24.5% so that is how I know the 24% stock price increase was stock buy back</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367809749655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOY decline of 24.5%??? Total company??? Read the article closely and quit hollering the sky is falling</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1367810038432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367810106577-78</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then moron...tell us your agenda...be a man! Were u let go? U did work in one of their planes u claimed once..didnt you? sorry #$%$ loser you are..visit teh can and enjoy yourself!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1367810106577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367810194397-79</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK...TELL US WHATS YOUR AGENDA...</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1367805456805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 21:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BE A MAN...TELL US YOUR AGENDA WAYNEDDDDICK!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1367810194397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367811007417-80</Id><Title>domerrrrr45 read my user comments on mismangeent the dual role of CEO and BOD chairman</Title><Msg>then you would know what i think is wrong with Boeing. That was posted here this week! Domerrrr45, are you so lazy and childish you can not take the time to read my user comments . As I told you I will think of you when I go to the can tonight ! you need to learn how to trade stocks and get off being a boor domerrrrr45 a BOOR-A person with rude, clumsy manners and little refinement</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367811007417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811075637-81</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore claims that he averted a civil war in 2000</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1367758102232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 08:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, Zosi, ignoring the juvenile taunt, do you judge by results or do you judge by political persuasion? Under Bush, zero undetected terrorist attacks in seven years in the United States, post-911; under Obama, three undetected terrorist in the United States, post election doomsday.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1367811075637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811125880-82</Id><Topic><Title>domerrrrr45 read my user comments on mismangeent the dual role of CEO and BOD chairman</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367811007417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:30:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Domerrr45 be a man, not a boor and read my comments for a change, stop the insanity of being a fool</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367811125880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811324816-83</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing revenues declined YOY by 24.5% so that is how I know the 24% stock price increase was stock buy back</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367809749655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read the whole article and torgeted the important information try learning how to trade stocks and stop being a boeing hack for 15 years i recomended apple and was right and i have called more than one stock here and been right only to have yahoo;s like you try some type of false and misleading conclusions docfunknstein you need to understand how a quarterly report is made and what is imporatant and what is not that is the truth not your sky is falling meaning nothing comment lie and make it up or know what your talking about ok then</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367811324816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367811508225-84</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing the week in review up</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367631974141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 21:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So 28 thumbs up for wayne and 27 thumbs down for the boeing hacks then</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1367811508225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-05 23:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>