<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361426775403-1</Id><Title>TSA Manhandles Disabled Three-Year-Old in Wheelchair, Offers No Explanation</Title><Msg>The Transportation Security Administration is apparently not content with fondling America’s private parts or administering airport prostate exams. They have now uncovered a more nefarious kind of terror threat – three-year-old girls confined to wheelchairs. Nathan Forck and his wife Annie, along with their three children were heading to Disney World for a family vacation. Lucy, their three-year-old, has Spina bifida and is confined to a wheelchair. The family managed to make it through the TSA checkpoint at Lambert-St. Louis International Airport without any problems. But as they prepared to walk to their gate, a TSA agent pulled aside Lucy for additional screening measures. “They specifically told me that they were singling her out for this special treatment because she’s in a wheelchair,” he told me. “They are specifically singling out disabled people for this special scrutiny. It’s rather offensive to me as a father of a disabled child." The agent said they needed to pat down Lucy and swab her wheelchair – even though both had already gone through the checkpoint. “They treated her like a criminal,” said Forck. “And by extension they were treating us as criminals.” Additional security personnel were summoned after the Forck’s refused to stop filming the incident. “You can’t do touch my daughter unless I record it,” Mrs. Forck told the agent. The agent replied by telling the parents “It is illegal to do that.” “The problem is, I don’t allow anyone to touch my little daughter,” Mrs. Forck said. Agents also confiscated Lucy’s stuffed animal, “Lamby,” – as the child wept uncontrollably. “I don’t want to go to Disney World,” she pleaded with her parents. For 30 gut-wrenching minutes, government agents detained and harassed this American family before finally sending them on their way with nary a hint of an explanation. OBVIOUSLY A TERROIST - SEND IN THE DRONES !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361426775403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:06:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361427796326-2</Id><Title>BA hires 2000 people here in Portland,,</Title><Msg>get ready for big productions... This is what really going on...</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361427796326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:23:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361427929600-3</Id><Title>Estimates have been raised...</Title><Msg>kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361427929600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:25:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361428120940-4</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One ironic bit of trivia is that on October 13, 1955, the day when Pan Am ordered the first commercial passenger jets (other than the earlier Comets) they ordered 25 DC-8s and 20 707s. This even though the 707 had been flying for over a year and the DC-8 was still almost 3 years from first flight. So, temporarily, Douglas had the most orders over Boeing and even by first flight in May 1958 was only trailing by 133 to Boeing's 150. Things slowly started going downhill from there and eventually led to the 1967 buyout by McDonnell and then Boeing in 1997.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1361428120940</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:28:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361436144597-5</Id><Topic><Title>BA hires 2000 people here in Portland,,</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361427796326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:23:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK,what is your source and how many of that 2000 will be for production or engineers/techs ?</Msg><Username>loftndude2000</Username><Timestamp>1361436144597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 03:42:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361436712522-6</Id><Topic><Title>BAD day at Auburn for Boeing</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361329228663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 22:00:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what about the lower Duwahmish river where Plant 2 use to be? That was there for over 70 years</Msg><Username>loftndude2000</Username><Timestamp>1361436712522</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 03:51:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361443414828-7</Id><Title>Boeing using very talented IAM and SPEEA workers, excuse me while I gloat, no sabotage</Title><Msg>Boeing on Wednesday instructed a small team of top IAM machinists( not cheap outsourced workers ) at its Auburn parts plant to begin building new, high-strength containment boxes for the lithium-ion batteries on its 787s as part of a redesign intended to get the planes flying again as soon as April. Three crews of six (IAM) volunteers — all “very talented (IAM) mechanics” —(not Chicago style cheap outsourced workers ) will work in three daily shifts. The parts needed have not yet come in, and design changes are expected as the work proceeds, the employee said. A congressional aide said Boeing representatives in one such meeting “were adamant that it will be a permanent fix, and rejected reports that mentioned a temporary fix.” Remember if it flies in the Boeing board room, it does not mean it will fly in the real world. Boeing also cited the April target date, the aide said This is once more a clear demonstration that the fix is much harder than the problem, Chicago outsourced the work to cheap inexperienced companies and now Boeing IAM and SPEEA workers must attempt to fix the CEO failure to use the Boeing Company workers who would have designed the 787 for 5 billion and made the plane on time and on budget , like they have done for the 777 Attention Boeing . CEO you give yourself a 34 % pay raise and have a 22 million dollar Boeing pension( not a 401k) while you take away from the workers who could have built the 787 right the first time. Excuse me while I gloat. James McNerney, a Boeing CEO failure especially for the Boeing shareholders . The stock sucks for price gain. But wait CEO of Boeing James McNerney, you have one supporter a guy who goes by the user name of jjovaz, this user hates workers, especially any American worker who is in a union. ” JJOVAS has named both SPEEA and IAM as guilty of sabotage, without any convictions and in spite of the Boeing company standing behind their workers . Here is JJOVAZ statement concerning the 787 problems jjovaz has named virtually all Boeing workers except the Boeing CEO and Boeing supervisors of sabotage“ Aircraft could have been tampered with by the union rank and file , IAM has done this in the past while negotiating a new contract.....its possible there are rouge SPEEA members that caused the problems so FAA has to tread lightly here before they destroy the one of the biggest exporters in the country for the actions of a few.” In fact there were no arrest, or any evidence that showed it was any Boeing employee and many cheap outsource workers have access to Boeing planes in the factory as well as Boeing Supervisors , customers and many other visitors , which jjovaz apparently excluded in his witch hunt . JJOVAZ why is Boeing trusting highly skilled IAM workers and SPEEA now to engineer and fabricate yet another fix ?BTW this is a Boeing management mandated fix that the workers do not support, and yet , as loyal workers the IA mans SPEEA workers will do the best they can to make a fix of the cheap outsourced Chicago style battery and power delivery problem. Once more this fire problem resulted from the cheap out sourced parts. and engineering ., JJOVAZ the 787 plane is 4 years late and 33 billion over budget , due to the Boeing management failure business plan of out sourcing which caused the delay. If the 787 was miss wired that does not mean sabotage or lazy union worker. Jjovaz, first find out if the cheap engineering drawings are wrong, then find out if the assembly was done by cheap outsourcing workers , most of the plane is built in modules and it is a plug in at the sections , that does not mean sabotage. Jjovaz you are an ignorant union basher . .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361443414828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 05:43:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361447168838-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik must be terrified of losing his welfare</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361324773132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:46:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmmm.....the Raven and BrokeDik....always seem to show up to compliement each other...hmmmm...I wonder ?</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361447168838</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:46:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361447451384-9</Id><Title>WACO = Chris Dorner</Title><Msg>Just like they purposly burned Koresh and innoncet women and children at WACO...looks like they did it again with Chris Dorner 1:00 “we’re going to go forward with the plan with the burn” 1:14 “like we talked about” 1:27: “burners deployed, we have a fire” “copy 7, burners deployed, we have a fire” RPG round? 2:27 “Guys be ready on the #4 side, we have a fire out front, might come out the back” Eliminating any possible chance for further publicity and exposure, the “burn” most likely destroyed Dorner and other additional evidence he might have had. We’ll have to wait and see if this will be “spun” by the media into being “necessary” and “essential for safety” or “accidental” or whatever. Clearly it was intentional. There are already many Americans who think this was necessary. They’re willing to trash the rights of anyone who has become targetted or deemed “guilty” without a trial. This is a very bad sign for America, because it means that we not only have no rule of law, but that the People do not want the rule of law either. For the record, this is the same tactic used on Osama Bin Laden, the alleged “mastermind” of 9/11. He was “convicted” without trial. No evidence of his guilt or crime has ever been shown. He was not even on the FBI most wanted list (ever). It was the same tactic used on David Koresh and 73 others. Koresh could have easily been arrested on his weekly trips into town, but the tactics chosen were to assault the compound where many other innocent people lived, including dozens of children. All died. While we are all rightly concerned about NDAA and the so-called “authority” to assassinate Americans taken by the President, the practice of assassinating Americans has already been well underway for many years. It is always claimed as “justified”. All they’re doing now is trying to legitimize it and implant this practice into the minds of Americans as being “ok”. Millions of Americans ARE ok with this. It’s one of the reason I’ve stopped writing. America is being overtaken by people who are dangerously deluded, abandoning all notions of law, restrictions, common sense and the need to adhere to our Constitutional rights. They’d rather just let the government and it’s agents handle all of that. Whatever they say, goes. And if it means assassinating trouble-makers, so be it. I’m making no apologies for Dorner. I’m pointing out that murder is murder, and even murderers are supposed to get their day in court. Law enforcement does not have the right to commit murder, period. There is no discussion about this. For all of you that think this is “ok”, God help you. One day it will be your turn as you stare down the barrel of your judge, jury and executioner who has taken it upon his or herself to arbitrarily decide if you should live or die. That is EXACTLY what is at the heart of these crimes. Abdicating the rule of law, the requirement of evidence and the day in court is a terrifying precedent, already long established. The NDAA is just icing on the cake.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361447451384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:50:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361447762212-10</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik must be terrified of losing his welfare</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361324773132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:46:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holy bat turd, there are no coincidences anymore. Yes, of course they are the same sick and twisted poster.</Msg><Username>justshutupnfish</Username><Timestamp>1361447762212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:56:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361447927607-11</Id><Title>Subject</Title><Msg>Gun Control Advocates Think The Second Amendment Is Up For Debate – IT's NOT !!!!!!!!!!!!! “Never trust a government that doesn’t trust its own citizens with guns.” – Benjamin Franklin After the president, with help from his fraternizers in the deceptive state-run media, somehow won his re-election campaign, I thought it was important to note the first thing Obama and his administration did was turn its attention to the United Nations gun treaty talks. Hmm, I wonder … If he really had the support of the American people, why is he so busy trying to disarm those who supposedly love him so much? And all the while Obama and his administration are busy trying to disarm the American people by conjuring up criminals guilty of some sort of gun crimes as an excuse for new gun legislation. Well, then, let me help: This administration need not look any further than within its own ranks. And this, friends, is the very reason we are an armed people. Fast and Furious As you know, Attorney General Eric Holder is guilty of putting thousands of assault rifles (AK-47s) into the hands of Mexican drug lords in an attempt to blame the American people for the crimes administration officials are guilty of contriving and committing. As a result, Border Patrol Agent Brian Terry was killed, along with hundreds of Mexican civilians, including teens at a birthday party and a Mexican beauty queen. The state-run media conveniently pulled a media blackout on Fast and Furious, and some Americans gave them a pass and have “forgotten” the atrocities committed upon them by their own government, therefore strengthening tyranny so it might assault the people again on a later date. Benghazi The “later date” occurred in Benghazi, when Ambassador Chris Stevens, two Navy SEALs and another U.S. citizen were killed on Sept. 11, 2012. The Blaze reported: “The details of the September 11 attack that killed four Americans at the U.S. consulate in Benghazi are still murky, and there is certainly more to be known. Former CIA officer Clare Lopez argues that the key issue is the relationship of the U.S. government, Ambassador Christopher Stevens and the U.S. diplomatic mission in Libya with al-Qaida. ‘That relationship, Lopez argues, could be connected to the rise of Islamic brigades in Syria, who recently created a ‘Front to Liberate Syria’ to wage jihad against the Syrian regime and turn the country into an Islamic state.’” The Business Insider stated: “In 2011 the U.S. sold $33.4 billion worth of weapons to Saudi Arabia and $1.7 billion to Qatar as sales tripled to a record high and accounted for nearly 78 percent of all global arms sales. ‘The opposition groups that are receiving most of the lethal aid are exactly the ones we don’t want to have it,’ one American official familiar with the situation told the New York Times.” So, America, was Ambassador Stevens gun running to extreme jihadists? Was Eric Holder responsible for putting guns into the hands of Mexican drug cartels? You decide. Long-time gun grab attempt Holder has been contriving a gun grab for years. For those who didn’t know, it recently came to light that Holder encouraged the media to “brainwash” the youth about how bad guns are when he was a part of Clinton’s anti-gun administration. What is interesting here is that the young, through Hollywood and video games, are conveniently taught a “thug” mentality and how to commit crimes. In the meantime, corrupt politicians await to trample the Constitution and legislate new policies to disarm the American population, leaving them defenseless when the crimes are committed. Just look at Sandy Hook, Aurora, Columbine, etc. Thomas Jefferson stated that the whole purpose of government is to “ensure your rights,” not to take them away. What this administration is attempting to do is exactly what Hitler, Stalin, Mao, or any other dictator has done. They blame the weapon rather than the person committing the crimes and all the while subtly encourage criminal activity. Friends, this is not about guns; it is about control. And this issue is not to be overlooked, because gun rights stand between a free country and an enslaved, possibly an exterminated, people. The Second Amendment: “A well regulated Militia, being necessary to the security of a FREE State, the Right of the people to keep and bear Arms, shall not be infringed (violated).” (emphasis added) According to Federal Statute Title 10, Chapter 13, Section 311 (a), all males between the ages of 17 and 45 who are either citizens of the United States or have declared their intent to become citizens are members of the “unorganized” or reserve militia. It is time for America to get out of the debate because there is no debate. We have rights given unto us by our Creator. Period. President George Washington, when arming the people of the United States of America, said: “A free people ought not only to be armed, but disciplined; to which end a uniform and well-digested plan is requisite; and their safety and interest require that they should promote such manufactories as tend to render them independent of others for essential, particularly military, supplies.” We would do well to heed President Washington’s warning, since over 56 million people in the 20th century were exterminated by their own governments under the guise of gun control.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361447927607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:58:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361448191916-12</Id><Topic><Title>Any Truth to the Rumor Hozdik and his Blow Up Doll have Broken Up?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361388486245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:28:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They had a fight over a Twinkie.................and the welfare check.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361448191916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:03:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361448341130-13</Id><Topic><Title>Subject</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361447927607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:58:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All Communists love gun bans.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361448341130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:05:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361450201325-14</Id><Title>A 787 will be at the bottom of hte Pacific within months of being back in the air.</Title><Msg>Anyone who gets on one is going to get a real thrill.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361450201325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:36:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361450226872-15</Id><Topic><Title>Subject</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361447927607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 06:58:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you DO realise America is in huge trouble don't you</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361450226872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:37:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361450315589-16</Id><Topic><Title>Any Truth to the Rumor Hozdik and his Blow Up Doll have Broken Up?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361388486245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:28:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The man is a De-generette cult member</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361450315589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 07:38:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361452622044-17</Id><Title>Gun Control is about Racism</Title><Msg>Google it</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361452622044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:17:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361453923595-18</Id><Title>Gartman getting out of stocks!</Title><Msg>Market Music Stopping, I'm Getting Out: Gartman By Holly Ellyatt | CNBC – 2 hours 20 minutes ago The U.S. Federal Reserve's signal that it may not continue its bond buying program is a game changer for global equity markets, Dennis Gartman, editor of "The Gartman Letter" told CNBC on Thursday. "I was very bullish on stocks, until yesterday," Gartman told CNBC Europe's "Squawk Box." "Suddenly the game has changed. ... We're in for a leg lower, and this is from someone who was publicly very bullish on stocks because of the monetary authorities."</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361453923595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:38:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361454291609-19</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing's really sucking up to the Obama Administration</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361453917825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:38:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any company that gets special regulation attention from the feds, and stockholders see a secure investment because of the special preference is going down because there is no longer any security that will be seen as coming from the feds. Obama has the feds deep in debt, and anything coming out of his mouth is just wasted verbage. It is austerity time not Obama spending time.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361454291609</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 08:44:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361455544743-20</Id><Title>Jobless claims rise more than expected</Title><Msg>Oh Really? What did you expect when Obama and the Democrats are on a vendetta to destroy the mediocre class? "WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits rose more than expected last week, but still remained at levels consistent with a steady improvement in labor market conditions. Initial claims for state unemployment benefits increased 20,000 to a seasonally adjusted 362,000, the Labor Department said on Thursday. The prior week's claims figure was revised to show 1,000 more applications received than previously reported." Well ain't that just hunky dory. This administration hasn't kept up with population growth much less acutual having any real growth in job. E</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361455544743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:05:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361455682522-21</Id><Title>Jobless claims rise more than expected</Title><Msg>Who didn't expect them to rise that much? lol! A liberal maybe? It had to be folks that are incapable of being informed. There is no way this economy isn't going to tank further than it has given federal policy that won't allow the private sector to grow. Another headdline: Stocks worried about what the feds are saying. BS Corporate America knows where we are headed. The only reason stocks have gone up is investors know of the inflation we are having, and stock prices have reflected the aniticipated inflation.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361455682522</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:08:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361456150387-22</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless claims rise more than expected</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361455544743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:05:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ave. Joe and the poor are being hit in the cruelest of ways. Their paychecks shrinking while inflation is on the rise. ObamaCare costs are just kicking in, and that will force consumer costs to rise. Now the feds are forced to cutback on spending, and that will hurt the poor the most. Five years now of complete mismanagement of the economy is costing the country bigtime. And Obama is trying to blame it on the GOP for forcing the feds to cutback on their wasteful spending.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361456150387</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:15:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361458224731-23</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless claims rise more than expected</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361455544743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:05:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's true Joe, but hey, it's so cool the way the way Obama tells us he's all for saving the mediocre class and going to make the "wealthiest among us" pay for all his socialist policies. Never mind that it's the wealthiest among us that he keep shoveling the money to while he screws the mediocre class.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361458224731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:50:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361459184465-24</Id><Topic><Title>BA hires 2000 people here in Portland,,</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361427796326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:23:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here in Greshman, Oregon... Non union workers..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361459184465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:06:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361459254286-25</Id><Title>Global Warming Snow stuns golfers in AZ...</Title><Msg>"A rare snowfall sweeping the southeastern corner of Arizona blanketed the saguaro cactus-studded high desert with several inches of white stuff, leading the Professional Golfers' Association to cancel play at a tournament near Tucson. "I don't think I have (ever seen anything like this), to be honest," competitor Ian Poulter said of the first-round interruption of the World Golf Championships-Accenture Match Play tournament. "It's absolutely remarkable to think one minute we're playing golf, albeit it's a little cool, and then within a space of 25 minutes, it turns from playable to cold drizzle to sleet and to snow. And within an hour and a half of all that starting, you've got 2 inches of snow plus on the ground. It's just bizarre." I lived in the Phoenix area for 18 years and never once saw it snow there. This global warming thing is turning into one of the cruelest and costliest hoaxes ever perpetrated on mankind. It's worse than the Global Cooling, the Population Bomb, the Ozone depletion, the DDT, Cranberry scare , the Nuclear Winter, the Acid Rain, the Spotted Owl, the Alar, the Radon and the Y2K scams all put together.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361459254286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:07:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361460112098-26</Id><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Msg>There’s at least two points worth re-emphasizing: (1) The budget process commonly known as “sequestration” originated in the corridors of the White House, and was signed into law by President Obama himself. Hence, the president’s insistence that Republicans are somehow solely responsible if the negotiations fail -- and the cuts kick in -- is erroneous. (2) The negative consequences of sequestration -- discussed endlessly by this president and his lieutenants -- are exaggerated to a mystifying degree. Yuval Levin blew the lid off Team Obama’s opportunism and endless fear-mongering yesterday in a piece at National Review Online: Let’s get a grip. In its first year, fiscal year 2013, which ends September 30, the sequester would involve a total of $85 billion in spending cuts. That’s a reduction of 3% from what federal spending otherwise would have been this year.But even that significantly overstates the effects the sequester would actually have this year. The federal government is so lumbering and huge that it can’t even reduce its own spending that quickly. That’s why “first year” cuts are always so difficult in even the most fiscally conservative budget proposals. The Congressional Budget Office (on page 11 of its latest budget outlook, published earlier this month) estimates that while FY 2013 spending will ultimately be reduced by $85 billion, “discretionary outlays will drop by $35 billion and mandatory spending will be reduced by $9 billion this year as a direct result of those procedures; additional reductions in outlays attributable to the cuts in 2013 funding will occur in later years.” So in this fiscal year, we would actually be looking at a $44 billion spending cut, or less than a 1.5% reduction from what federal spending otherwise would have been. It would mean that federal spending in 2013 will be about $3.553 trillion. In 2012, federal spending was $3.538 trillion. Yes, that means that even with the sequester we will be spending slightly more in 2013 than we did in 2012. In fact, we will be spending more than we did in any year in American history except for 2011 (when we spent $3.598 trillion). Here’s a quick sense of what we’re looking at (the historical figures are from this CBO spreadsheet and the 2013 ones are from this one, both are updated as of earlier this month): In other words, the sun will still rise on March 1, 2013 if the “sequestration” cuts go into effect. Murderous criminals will not go free and millions of Americans won’t die of food poising. Put simply, these cuts are anything but “draconian”</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361460130493-27</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming Snow stuns golfers in AZ...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361459254286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:07:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? The PGA organizers scheduled the tourney at that time knowing it snows at that time of year often? Leftwinggunowners never shoot straight me thinks.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361460130493</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:22:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361460286543-28</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>indeed!!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1361460286543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:24:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361460338607-29</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Fix Weight Impact</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361391993895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:26:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will reconfigure the cells so they will not antagonize each other. Li ion has much more capability as far as recharging, and much more energy for their size. Many other types of batteries are rechargeable, including your car battery, but they take much longer and never have the amount of energy that can be achieved with Li ion batteries. As cars advance and go for ever higher fuel efficiency, they will most likely start using at least some Li ion batteries to provide much of the electrical energy consumed by passengers and auto functions, such as brakes, onboard computers and air conditioning.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1361460338607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:25:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361460369340-30</Id><Topic><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But now our leaderless Pres says it was all a joke his sequestration signing. It wasn't intended to go into effect. And it did originate in the White House. BO was sure the GOP would go along with tax hikes to pay for his socialist policies. Fact is they won't, and shouldn't. Look what tax hikes are doing to the economy right now.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361460369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:26:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361460403386-31</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming Snow stuns golfers in AZ...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361459254286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:07:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does snow occasionally near Tucson but mainly in the higher elevation of the surrounding mountains. It almost never snows in Phoenix or Yuma. I've seen pictures of snow in Phoenix but it's an extremely rare event.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460403386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:26:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361461056139-32</Id><Title>Hmmmmm Now Liberals Seem to Want to Tackle the Issue of a Minimum Wage</Title><Msg>For Two days I asked Libs to explain why, if a $9 an hour minimum wage would help lift people out of poverty they would not be in favor of raising the minimum wage to $50 an hour?.....or at least equal to the highest paid union wage? their response....Nothing but crickets and an occasional insult for putting them on the spot with such a exposing question.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361461056139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:37:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361461601827-33</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming Snow stuns golfers in AZ...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361459254286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:07:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could you explain to us what the weather in Tuscon yesterday has to do with global warming?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1361461601827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:46:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361462164088-34</Id><Title>Why Liberals Hate the New Simpson-Bowles Deficit Reduction Plan</Title><Msg>The short and obvious explanation is that the revamped proposal emphasizes spending reductions, which is a blow to Democrats' false mantra du jour; namely, that the country doesn't have a spending problem. The Atlantic's Derek Thompson gripes that the new bipartisan framework, advanced by the former co-chairmen of President Obama's fiscal commission earlier this week, emits a distinct whiff of Republicanism. The MSNBC crew is predictably unimpressed, as are lefty bloggers like Matt Yglesias. Conservative economist Kevin Hassett (who goes out of his way to describe his own misgivings over Simpson-Bowles 2.0) explains why the president's ideological kin probably regret his decision to assemble the commission in the first place. Pretending to care about deficits, then utterly ignoring the advice of the council you charged with fashioning a workable way forward, has its consequences -- as does basic budgetary math, it turns out: This new plan calls for about $1 trillion more in total spending cuts than was previously sought by the two gentlemen; in addition, the tax revenue they seek is about half of what was contained in their original plan. It seems that Simpson and Bowles have moved in the Republicans’ direction big time. Their plan emphasizes the pressing need to contain the debt and makes it clear that spending cuts are necessary to do so, something Democrats have seemed to be woefully ignoring in recent months. This shift in position clearly suggests that they were strong armed by the president the first time around, and forced to push a plan that they viewed was harmful for the economy. Despite making concessions towards higher taxes, they were double crossed by Obama, who dropped their plan the minute it was delivered. Overall it seems like this exposes a big gap between Simpson and Bowles and the president. President Obama has pretended to be an advocate of their position, but never been serious about doing anything. This is payback time, and Simpson and Bowles have not made any friends in the White House today. At the other end of the spectrum, the Heritage Foundation has also come out against the new plan, arguing that it relies too heavily on increased tax revenues and does not include necessary structural reforms to entitlement programs. These are definitely valid concerns, but I think they miss the forest for the trees. Simpson-Bowles 2.0 has zero chance of becoming policy reality, chiefly because Democrats would never allow it to see the light of day. Still, it offers several relevant openings for conservatives: (1) It again highlights the serious and systemic crisis of long-term government debt. (2) It correctly identifies overspending as the prime culprit and driver of this problem, powerfully refuting the denialists. (3) It tilts the solution towards spending reductions and de-emphasizes the revenue component, perhaps because the president just enacted a $600 billion tax increase. (4) It does all of these things through a pristine prism of bipartisanship, as established by the president himself. Alan Simpson and Erskine Bowles cannot be dismissed as right-wing cranks or knee-jerk partisans. Their reputational heft and credibility can therefore be leveraged by conservatives to demonstrate that their policy solutions are based on fiscal realities that undergird the bipartisan consensus -- which Democrats have taken to flatly denying. In short, Simpson-Bowles 2.0's underlying assumptions and broad remedies can be wielded as an effective cudgel against the denialists' obfuscations and fantasies -- even if conservatives have substantive quibbles over some of its elements. On a related note, Carol has noted the continuation of Howard Dean's fascinating truth-telling campaign, wherein he's been candidly admitting something that his fellow Democrats can't bring themselves to publicly articulate: “[S]omebody has to tell the middle class that either your taxes are going to go up or your programs are going to get cut or else we're going to go into financial oblivion, and nobody really wants to tell them that.”</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361462164088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:56:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361462469804-35</Id><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Msg>love it</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361462469804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:01:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361463381515-36</Id><Topic><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361462469804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:01:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it his murder of women and children in drone strikes that excites you, or his claim of the right to assassinate American citizens? If these powers excite you now, wait 'til you see what President Rubio's going to do with them!</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1361463381515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:16:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361463453298-37</Id><Title>Boom: "The Obama Sequester"</Title><Msg>The Republican National Committee has President Obama dead to rights on his breathtaking hypocrisy and demagoguery regarding the impending automatic "sequestration" cuts that he's now trying to attribute to the GOP. This video doesn't break any new ground on substance, but its stark juxtaposition of Obama's 2011 veto threat and this week's attempt at blame shift is absolutely damning: "In 2011, President Obama proposed the devastating sequestration cuts and stood by them. Now the Democrats continue saying Washington doesn’t have a spending problem, showing just how out of touch the Democrats are with the American people. House Republicans have passed two bills that provide common-sense solutions that would reduce spending and preserve and strengthen our safety net for future generations. Instead of admitting we have a problem, Obama and the Democrats would rather find more tax increases. Our nation’s problem is spending and it’s time the president realizes that." The bills to which Priebus refers are two pieces of legislation passed by the Republican House of Representatives that would have cleaned up the president's sequester cuts to make them less reckless. Both were dead on arrival in Harry Reid's Senate, thanks to Obama's veto vow (see above). Obama's performance earlier this week was just another class warfare-laden stump speech for more tax hikes from a president addicted to bullying through sensationalism and vilification. Republicans were forced into a corner during fiscal cliff negotiations at the end of 2012, but they have the inertia and law on their side in this skirmish. Another tax increase is off the table. House Speaker John Boehner made this crystal clear in a Wall Street Journal op/ed published yesterday, which also took the president to task for his pitiful leadership: Having first proposed and demanded the sequester, it would make sense that the president lead the effort to replace it. Unfortunately, he has put forth no detailed plan that can pass Congress, and the Senate—controlled by his Democratic allies—hasn't even voted on a solution, let alone passed one. By contrast, House Republicans have twice passed plans to replace the sequester with common-sense cuts and reforms that protect national security. The president has repeatedly called for even more tax revenue, but the American people don't support trading spending cuts for higher taxes. They understand that the tax debate is now closed. The president got his higher taxes—$600 billion from higher earners, with no spending cuts—at the end of 2012. He also got higher taxes via ObamaCare. The sequester is the law of the land; demanded by the White House, passed by both houses of Congress, and signed by the president. Republicans have twice proposed specific plans to restructure its cuts, both of which were swatted aside by Democrats. These same impudent Democrats -- you know, the ones who came up with the sequester and voted for it -- are now suddenly frantic to offset the cuts, yet they haven't voted on any mechanism to do so. For his part, the president doesn't even have a plan on paper to do so. He's too busy pounding the table about Republicans, surrounded by human props. Who can be bothered with governing when one has opponents to demonize?</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361463453298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:17:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361463648699-38</Id><Topic><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361462469804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:01:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it's the way he is destroying the mediocre class while s.c.r.e.w. ing them and their children.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361463648699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:20:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361463747895-39</Id><Topic><Title>Boom: "The Obama Sequester"</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361463453298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" but the American people don't support trading spending cuts for higher taxes"= complete nonsense Obama won the election pretty much on this issue and the people want more revenue from the higher income folks.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1361463747895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:22:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361464447169-40</Id><Topic><Title>Boom: "The Obama Sequester"</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361463453298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course rockstar is completely ignorant and wrong about “Obama won the election pretty much on this issue.” From Real Clear Politics: About three-quarters of voters like President Obama personally, but a small majority don't like his policies, according to a Quinnipiac University poll conducted Feb. 21-28. The numbers break down like this: -- Forty-one percent of those surveyed like Obama and his policies. That includes about three-quarters of Democrats, a little over a third of independents and 7 percent of Republicans.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361464447169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:34:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361464588889-41</Id><Topic><Title>Hmmmmm Now Liberals Seem to Want to Tackle the Issue of a Minimum Wage</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361461056139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:37:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will never answer your question because it exposes their illogical denial of logic.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361464588889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:36:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361464710575-42</Id><Title>Boeing just needs to prove the 787 can crash land in the ocean.</Title><Msg>If the fire gets out of the new vented box and the plane can crash into the Pacific I say we load her up with Mon, Dan , Brother, Sister and our childern. Let them prove the 787 does not fly.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361464710575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:38:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361465362058-43</Id><Topic><Title>Hmmmmm Now Liberals Seem to Want to Tackle the Issue of a Minimum Wage</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361461056139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:37:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey cricket tell us how great things were for the American worker before unions and minimum wage laws and you have you answer.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1361465362058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:49:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361465419943-44</Id><Topic><Title>What's that Sound?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361402111366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:15:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent post Mir! There have been many economic studies of the great depression and most objective economist agree that FDR's policies caused the depression to last several years longer than necessary. The comparison of FDR's devastating policies and those of Obama's is history repeating its self. What's even more amazing is that in spite of the economic devastation to the poor an middle class the propaganda fed to these illinformed and low information voters kept them voting for their own economic ruin. Interesting how history keeps repeating its self.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361465419943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:50:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361465901063-45</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing just needs to prove the 787 can crash land in the ocean.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361464710575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well they do need to put that 787 in a test flight, blow the battery up and set it on fire. All to determine if the temporary fix will hold. Keep it in the air several hours after the blow up and fire. Have some execs sitting directly above the battery. Their family's aboard also.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1361465901063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:58:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361465945756-46</Id><Topic><Title>Hmmmmm Now Liberals Seem to Want to Tackle the Issue of a Minimum Wage</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361461056139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:37:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rockstar wants to turn back the clock over 100 yrs. as his answer. Again our rock is just about as dense. There are more than enough employee protection laws on the books. The question is what does raising the minimum wage do for those needing a job? What does it do to price inflation? What does it do to those on a fixed income? All the results are negative which connects the dots to other liberal policy, and what are the "unintended consequences" of those policies?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361465945756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:59:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361466011457-47</Id><Topic><Title>BA hires 2000 people here in Portland,,</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361427796326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:23:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Type message</Msg><Username>gnufool</Username><Timestamp>1361466011457</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361466022696-48</Id><Topic><Title>BA hires 2000 people here in Portland,,</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361427796326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:23:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are they going to make batteries there?</Msg><Username>gnufool</Username><Timestamp>1361466022696</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:00:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361466251925-49</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing just needs to prove the 787 can crash land in the ocean.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361464710575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>think of all the toxic gases &amp; fumes if that plane was to catch fire. It's mostly all composite material</Msg><Username>gnufool</Username><Timestamp>1361466251925</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:04:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361466467800-50</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes I agree.</Msg><Username>gnufool</Username><Timestamp>1361466467800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:07:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361466491073-51</Id><Topic><Title>Boom: "The Obama Sequester"</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361463453298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lmao pulling the old revisionist history trick and some stupid poll from somebody selling commercial time don`t mean a thing. Romeny and the Republican agenda lost and will continue to loose in the future.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1361466491073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:08:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361466649741-52</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing just needs to prove the 787 can crash land in the ocean.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361464710575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is really frightening.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361466649741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:10:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361468164059-53</Id><Topic><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361462469804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:01:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468164059</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:36:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361468324847-54</Id><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Msg>You probably know me as the writer of such songs as "Penny Lane", "Jet", "My Love", and "Let It Be". But today, I'm here to tell you how blessed you are to have a president and first lady like Barack and Michelle Obama. So ignore the haters and take a moment to be grateful that they represent you on the world stage. God bless you.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361468781553-55</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing just needs to prove the 787 can crash land in the ocean.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361464710575</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:38:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's OK. Your pillow turns into a gas mask, and your blanket turns into a parachute!</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1361468781553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:46:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361468902125-56</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"King Kong was pretty too." Pretty to whom?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1361468902125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:48:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361469803874-57</Id><Topic><Title>Why Liberals Hate the New Simpson-Bowles Deficit Reduction Plan</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361462164088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>¿qué usted hará sobre los pobrecitos?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361469803874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:03:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361470031668-58</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sir Paul Please keep up the good work. Always good to be reminded of beauty, especially in the face of such dreary, dull, drab, ditzy, dumb Republican hate on this board.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1361470031668</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:07:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361470469560-59</Id><Topic><Title>Why Liberals Hate the New Simpson-Bowles Deficit Reduction Plan</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361462164088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Takes some large cajone's to convince the folks the govt doesn't have a spending problem, GIVEN....Obama expanded the size of big bloated govt by 25% on just his first two years. GIVEN..Obama admits that $800,000,000,000 of tax payer money was virtually wasted in the stimulus. Infrastructure wasn't built as he said it would be spent on in large part....said "our shovels weren't ready." 98,000 new pages of business regulation was written under Obama, and layers upon layers on more bureaucrats were added to administrer the regulaions.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361470469560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:14:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361470668403-60</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a beast !!!</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1361470668403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:17:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361470711292-61</Id><Topic><Title>BA hires 2000 people here in Portland,,</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361427796326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:23:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would just about double personnel there. If this is not just a malicious rumor, dome up with more conclusive information.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1361470711292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:18:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361470973811-62</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why does she straighten her har with chemicals ?</Msg><Username>king_kwanza</Username><Timestamp>1361470973811</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:22:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361471220929-63</Id><Title>Stop the Fire from Spreadig is the Fix!?!?</Title><Msg>The FAA proposal appears to be the use of ceramic to stop any fire from cascading to other cells within the battery. I am perplexed! Why is the stock heading higher? It is crazy. This is not a solution but one simple stop-gap measure to hopefully stop a fire from spreading. How about a REAL solution that saves real lives!? If the FAA and others approve this band-aid, then we will know what is happening behind the scenes! Let's be clear - the role of government is to protect real people and real lives! It is NOT to promote private business. enterprise at all cost!</Msg><Username>beingtheonenow</Username><Timestamp>1361471220929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:27:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361471294043-64</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you know she does?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1361471294043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:28:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361471514110-65</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No you're not! Paul McCartney died years ago when he joined the Green Movement!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361471514110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:31:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361471698896-66</Id><Title>the 787 problem can be traced to former Boeing Management, the fail of the Sonic Cruiser , then the 787</Title><Msg>Boeing's ongoing problems with the batteries in its Dreamliner passenger jet can be traced back to Alan Mullaly, who used to run Boeing Commercial Airplanes and is now the CEO of Ford, an executive at rival Airbus says. Mulally was at Boeing for the launch of the Dreamliner, but left in 2006 for Ford, while the jet was being developed, according to Flightglobal. In an interview with Airline Business, Airbus chief salesman John Leahy said that Mulally was so concerned with producing a "game-changing" product, he pushed Boeing into creating a plane that would be costly to develop and difficult to make safe: I think Alan Mulally wanted to be gamechanging. So 'job one', as he would say at Ford, was 'everything on this airplane is going to be game-changing'... We don't think having an airplane flying at 41,000ft, in minus 60 degree outside temperature, should be heated electronically. We've got sources of power called the engines that aren't using all their power, and you can use some of that to pressurize and heat the cabin, to deice the airplane. To deliver improved fuel economy, a key upside of the 787, Boeing uses a powerful lithium ion battery and five times more electricity and electrical systems than other jets. Battery malfunctions caused two fires onboard Dreamliners in January, and the planes have been grounded for more than a month. Airbus was planning to use a lithium ion battery in the A350 XWB, its Dreamliner competitor, but without using the all-electric architecture that's in the 787. Last week, it announced it would use more proven nickel cadmium batteries instead. This is the problem with boeign Executives, they are so insulated from the real world Mulally spent years attempting to sell the sonic cruiser , no customer wanted a plane marginally faster with a huge extra cost in fuel , so the company under Mulally kept wasting shareholder money attempting to be first to make a game changer. history tells us that is foolish look at the comet, that allowed Boeing to jump on the failure and become number one, now a very weak Airbus is doing the same thing to Boeing. Let Boeing make the mistakes , bleed them then take over with improvements , the ego and incompetence of Boeign Executives is destroying Boeing from within.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361471698896</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:34:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361471889522-67</Id><Topic><Title>Why Liberals Hate the New Simpson-Bowles Deficit Reduction Plan</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361462164088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:56:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaeces what you know about economics I can put in my eye do yourself a favor and keep your mouth shut unless you know what you are talking about- and if you do I guess you wont be posting anymore</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361471889522</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:38:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361472765567-68</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait... what?</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361472765567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361472810873-69</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you kindly, sir. You bet I will.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361472810873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:53:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361473600440-70</Id><Topic><Title>Stop the Fire from Spreadig is the Fix!?!?</Title><Username>beingtheonenow</Username><Timestamp>1361471220929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The largest business and contributor to GDP in any nation, is the aircraft industry. The USA can't survive without it. You are correct is assuming a bacck door fix with the government. I'll never the Dreamliner. Only Airbus.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361473600440</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:06:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361474564388-71</Id><Title>Just Out Dreamliners out until JUNE 1!!!!!</Title><Msg>Stock will tank any second</Msg><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361474564388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:22:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361475030135-72</Id><Title>Boeing has succeeded in driving a wedge in SPEEA</Title><Msg>my dear SPEEA - you guys had Goliath by the short hairs but then let him Go.... so welcome now to the age where your union influence will matter Little... if at all !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361475030135</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:30:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361475156606-73</Id><Topic><Title>Just Out Dreamliners out until JUNE 1!!!!!</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361474564388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:22:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jun 1 2014 if your are lucky !</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361475156606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:32:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361475374305-74</Id><Topic><Title>Dems love gimmick like Grow the Deficit</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1361474083140</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:14:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of lunatics, something must be wrong with gregjanecheckn. Even more today than yesterday, that is. No accusations of the President being gay.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1361475374305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:36:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361475576870-75</Id><Topic><Title>Just Out Dreamliners out until JUNE 1!!!!!</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361474564388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:22:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you under shorts just get soiled and you are that desperate? LMAO</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1361475576870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:39:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477040728-76</Id><Topic><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361462469804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:01:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I loveit too. And hey, it's not too early to start working on that third term., heh heh.. :)</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1361477040728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:04:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477116282-77</Id><Topic><Title>Just Out Dreamliners out until JUNE 1!!!!!</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361474564388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:22:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats just EWE nited</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361477116282</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:05:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477200558-78</Id><Topic><Title>Boom: "The Obama Sequester"</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361463453298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yada yada, yack yack. Your mother needs to let you out a bit more, it seems.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1361477200558</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:06:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477200599-79</Id><Topic><Title>Stop the Fire from Spreadig is the Fix!?!?</Title><Username>beingtheonenow</Username><Timestamp>1361471220929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its not an FAA proposal - it is Mother Boeing If you cant fix it - FOG it</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361477200599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:06:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477504095-80</Id><Topic><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get the sense that this President is always preforming. This guy is still in campaign mode. Barack's a GREAT PREFORMER but a LOUSY PRESIDENT!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361477504095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:11:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477523327-81</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she's the vacation lady. 4 plus million here, 2 million there. What can she do besides spend taxpayer money like crazy, with no remorse??</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1361477523327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:12:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361477634990-82</Id><Topic><Title>What's that Sound?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361402111366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:15:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Opinions are like a.s.s.h.0.l.e.s: everybody's got one.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1361477634990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:13:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361477665963-83</Id><Title>second airline company not going with 787 for now, United the launch customer for the 777 says nope to outsourcing</Title><Msg>Feb 21 (Reuters) - United Continental Holdings said on Thursday it was taking Boeing Co's grounded 787 Dreamliner out of its flying plans through June 5, except for the Denver to Tokyo Narita route now scheduled for a tentative launch on May 12. United spokeswoman Christen David said in a statement the Denver to Tokyo Narita route, originally set to start March 31, had been postponed. The route launch would depend on a successful resolution of 787 battery failures that have grounded the plane fleet for five weeks.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361477665963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:14:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361477677745-84</Id><Title>obama &amp; the left think they can SPEND THEIR WAY OUT OF A SINKHOLE!!</Title><Msg>they're nuts! Cut the left arm off to save the Body....</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1361477677745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:14:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361478303628-85</Id><Title>Realistic Timeline for FAA Approval</Title><Msg>Why would the FAA rush to approve a new battery for Boeing. They are going to have to run alot of test flights to show how the battery will function is real life. Safety is not a haphazard approach where boeing says we fixed the battery and gets a rubber stamp; it is truly atrocious for a company like BA to first deny any issues with the battery and then to redesign the battery??? HELLO</Msg><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361478303628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:25:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361478652920-86</Id><Title>787 survivers</Title><Msg>787 passengers should recieve some kind of recognition for surviving flights. mayb a pin or something like that.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1361478652920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:30:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361479418356-87</Id><Topic><Title>obama &amp; the left think they can SPEND THEIR WAY OUT OF A SINKHOLE!!</Title><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1361477677745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:14:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They, the left, like to avoid the term "spending". There new propoganda is to say we are "investing" in America. Of course their own CBO (congressional budget office) has reported it would be easy to lop off over a trillion dollars in wasted spending, duplications, etc. yet BO says it would be a disaster to make the mandatory $22 Billion dollars this year in cuts. Now we still will spend an increase, a spending budget of $ 3.5 trillion dollars this year. Can a math deficit lib tell us what percentage cutting $ 22 Billion dollars from a $ 3.5 trillion dollar budget would be? Give us the percentage in cuts Obama says we can't make.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361479418356</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:43:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361479621887-88</Id><Title>BA may break 80$</Title><Msg>first time since little ice age..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361479621887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:47:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361479728648-89</Id><Topic><Title>787 survivers</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1361478652920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:30:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nah a free pack of marshmallows and roasting sticks</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1361479728648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:48:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361479800354-90</Id><Topic><Title>obama &amp; the left think they can SPEND THEIR WAY OUT OF A SINKHOLE!!</Title><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1361477677745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:14:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The left arm is full of GANGRENE and left unchecked, it will spread to the rest of the Body and kill it....</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1361479800354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:50:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361480243364-91</Id><Topic><Title>Boom: "The Obama Sequester"</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361463453298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Obama won the election because the alternative was Romney. So Obama was the lesser of two evils. That's not saying much. I don't think you leftys will be bragging much in 2 years after the midterm elections.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361480243364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:57:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361480434289-92</Id><Title>Issa Investigating: IRS Funneled Nearly $500M in Contracts to One IT Firm in 2012</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — The House Oversight Committee is investigating whether a personal relationship between an Internal Revenue Service employee and the owner of a computer company produced a series of government contracts worth about $500 million. In a letter obtained by The Associated Press from the committee's chairman, Rep. Darrell Issa, R-Calif., to acting Treasury Secretary Neal S. Wolin, Issa writes that he recently has learned about a personal relationship between an IRS employee and Braulio Castillo, the owner of Signet Computers Inc. Signet Computers' website lists company addresses in Virginia and Washington, D.C. The name of the IRS employee, who works in the agency's procurement department, is blacked out in the letter obtained by the AP. The IRS operates within the Treasury Department. Issa writes that prior to 2012, Signet Computers, which advertises itself as specializing in information technology issues, "does not appear to have received any federal contracts." Since then, he writes, Signet has been awarded approximately $500 million worth of federal contracts, all but $180,835 of them from the IRS. "The fact that Signet Computers was able to secure federal contracts worth a half-billion dollars in a matter of months, despite having no track record of past performance, raises many questions," Issa writes. A spokeswoman for the IRS declined comment. Phone and email messages to Signet Computers were not immediately returned Wednesday. Witnesses have told investigators with the Oversight Committee that the unidentified IRS staffer told several people that if they wanted their companies to receive contracts from the IRS they needed to speak with Castillo, Issa writes. "At best, this is a conflict of interest that runs afoul of ... Federal Acquisition Regulation," Issa writes. "At worst, the IRS may have a situation in which a contracting official is awarding sole source contracts based on false justifications, or receiving kickbacks in exchange for government contracts." Issa's letter also lays out other allegations against Signet Computers, including that it may have misled the Small Business Administration in order to obtain designations from the agency that made it more likely to obtain federal contracts. The company also changed its name several times in 2012, possibly to avoid scrutiny from the SBA, Issa writes. The IRS' contracts with Signet Computers also may have been tailored so that Signet was the only company that could win them in open bidding, Issa writes. According to the letter, a whistle-blower contacted the Office of the Treasury Inspector General for Tax Administration in August 2012 with evidence that the unidentified IRS staffer directed contracts to Castillo and Signet Computers. In January, according to the letter, a separate whistle-blower wrote to the Small Business Administration with similar concerns. Issa asks for a series of documents related to Castillo and Signet from the IRS to be delivered to the committee by March 6 so it can continue its investigation.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361480434289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:00:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361480540197-93</Id><Topic><Title>Just Out Dreamliners out until JUNE 1!!!!!</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361474564388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:22:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Denver/tokyo 787 flights are still scheduled.for May 12.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1361480540197</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:02:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361480587511-94</Id><Topic><Title>What's that Sound?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361402111366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:15:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps but not everyone's is resting on facts.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361480587511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:03:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361480590144-95</Id><Title>He Brayed He Got 98% 0f what He Wanted</Title><Msg>Mr Boehner, a sharpie negotiator, brayed about how he got 98% of what the repubs wanted. Mr Boehner and the repubs own 98% of the SEQUESTER, especially 98% of the defense cuts.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1361480590144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:03:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361480612454-96</Id><Topic><Title>BA hires 2000 people here in Portland,,</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361427796326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:23:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They only employ 2000 people in the whole plant, probably less than that.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361480612454</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:03:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361480757497-97</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does Moochie take vacations sepaerate from the eternal campaigner in chief ??/ Why does obumbles hang with a porn star fornicator who was married with children, not to mention the other women involved. ? Doesn't that send the wrong message to his young daughters? Strange relationship. Bet her hair smells like a wet dog ...</Msg><Username>affirmative_action_obama</Username><Timestamp>1361480757497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:05:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361480870067-98</Id><Topic><Title>Boom: "The Obama Sequester"</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361463453298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>first off Obama sure doesn't want the sequester to take effect because it would demonstrate how he has been lying about all the damage that would be done by the cuts. His own CBO has reported we could easily lop off over 1 trillion in cuts by just eliminating duplications, and obvious waste. This year's mandatory cuts would amount to around 22 B. Given we will spend an increase of $ 3.5 Trillion this year I wonder if a math deficit lib like cliberg could give us what percentage cut of the budget that would be? Don't hold your breath getting that answer. all he can do is say yada, yack.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361480870067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:07:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361481214619-99</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expensive too............</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1361481214619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:13:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361481396190-100</Id><Topic><Title>Realistic Timeline for FAA Approval</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361478303628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:25:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who says the FAA is in a rush? Any solution (temporary or permenent) will be fully evaluated. Based on all the reports available, the problem surfaced on two batteries, The replacement of other batteries is reported to be due to power draining activity such as leavnig the gas cap ajar. Once the power level in the battery drops to a specific low point, the automatic triggers built into the battery prevent a recharge and the battery had to be replaced.. We have not seen the actual interim modifications Boeing is proposing to get the planes back in the air. Until then, everything is speculation. So those who who babble on negatively about the problem are either inane or very, very short.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1361481396190</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:16:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361481612307-101</Id><Topic><Title>Any Truth to the Rumor Hozdik and his Blow Up Doll have Broken Up?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361388486245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:28:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is his blow-up love doll really named "Sir Paul."</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361481612307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:20:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361482855644-102</Id><Topic><Title>Any Truth to the Rumor Hozdik and his Blow Up Doll have Broken Up?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361388486245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:28:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Otto Pilot.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1361482855644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:40:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361483015984-103</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361483015984</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:43:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361483274201-104</Id><Topic><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361462469804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:01:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one DFC.....and an anti-American POS.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361483274201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:47:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361483365693-105</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven, You are the Fool On The Hill.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361483365693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:49:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361483478833-106</Id><Topic><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much of Obama's past voting record he doesn't want made known. That is why he avoided voting on measures much of the time...a no show. He didn't want to get pigeon holed as to his views. He wants to be the Black Knight that comes riding in, and works on the countries problems. Truth is, he is the problem.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361483478833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:51:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361483832700-107</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And who are you?</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361483832700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:57:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361484897312-108</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am the walrus.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361484897312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:14:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361485217465-109</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect you are the elephant.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361485217465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:20:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361485843519-110</Id><Title>Low information Voters</Title><Msg>This is a great gig, if you can get it. You conceive of a bad idea, demand that it be given the force of law, sign it into existence, and adamantly oppose efforts to alter or undo it -- then when it no longer serves your fleeting political purposes, you drop the whole thing in the lap of your adversaries, and most people buy it. Let's face it: Average people don't know what sequestration is, what it would do, or why it even exists. If they were briefed on the very basics, these numbers would probably shift a bit, but most Americans have no appetite for following Washington's endless political brinksmanship. So what do they do when a pollster calls to ask about the latest impending crisis? They use shortcuts. Although he's not especially popular, the president is viewed much more favorably than Republicans in Congress these days. Between this reality and the supine posture of his battered-spouse media supporters, Obama occupies the public opinion high ground in most of these battles, even before he begins his tendentious bullying. On broad and intuitive issues like guns and Obamacare, his powers of persuasion are limited. But on easily-demagogueable budget minutiae with baffling names like "sequestration," a lot of people don't quite understand what's going, nor do they really want to know. So they pick the guy they like better. And if they're choosing between a recently re-elected president who smiles and jokes on that show they like, and faceless Republicans who always seem to be the bad guys in these standoffs, the choice is pretty easy. Until Republicans aggressively and effectively engage in the messaging battle, their approval ratings will remain in the gutter. And as long as their brand is in the gutter, Obama will benefit by default. On the bright side, Jim Geraghty notes that the president's support is a mile wide and an inch deep: With Obama at a 51 percent job approval but in the low to mid-40s in his handling on most issues, discussion of the president should note that a certain segment of the population likes him, personally, a lot more than his policies. Chalk it up to his appearances in non-political programming like The View, The Tonight Show, and ESPN, or chalk it up to the happy images of him spending time with Michelle and his daughters. Obama is a lot more effective at getting people to like him than persuading them. Pew's data bears this out, as does Gallup's recent issue-by-issue survey. Even on the larger question of deficit reduction (on which Obama gets especially poor marks) public opinion should be relatively hospitable to the GOP position. Pew is touting their finding that a large majority shares the president's "balanced approach" rhetoric; largely ignored is the 73 percent of of the public who say deficits should be curtailed using only or mostly spending cuts. Just 19 percent of Americans share Democrats' obsession with the revenue side of the ledger:</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361485843519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:30:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361486161008-111</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You certainly sound as wacked out and dingy as Paul McCartney.....how long you been on drugs?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361486161008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:36:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361486341479-112</Id><Topic><Title>What's that Sound?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361402111366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:15:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That sound is the chatter liberals make as they stick their fingers in their ear so they won't hear the sound and can stay in denial.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361486341479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:39:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361486545719-113</Id><Topic><Title>Issa Investigating: IRS Funneled Nearly $500M in Contracts to One IT Firm in 2012</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361480434289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 16:00:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just more standard activity by the Democrat Party of Corruption.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361486545719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:42:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361486911917-114</Id><Topic><Title>Realistic Timeline for FAA Approval</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361478303628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:25:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>However we are not dealing with an airframe problem or an engine problem....we are dealing with a battery problem.... much simpler in my opinion...</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1361486911917</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:48:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361487656598-115</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You certainly sound as wacked out and dingy as Paul McCartney" I AM Paul McCartney. You have to be intelligent to understand a genius like myself. Obviously you are a simpleton.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361487656598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:00:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361488396810-116</Id><Topic><Title>Low information Voters</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361485843519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All this alarm about the Sequestration proves one thing, how dependent our economy now is on the federal government. Thats why the republicans have to stay quiet on this one. They can't cry cuts when something like this could cause a major blow to the economy. We all really have to take a good look at what the heck has gone on for the past thirty years and how we all got into this mess in the first place. Personally, I think every republican in the house and senate should be voted out. They created a fraud of an economy, destroyed our manufacturing base, made us dependent on blood sucking financials, cut tax rates but kept increasing government spending without any additions to revenues, and brought back the loopholes that got the tax rates decreased in the eighties. Everything has been on the sneek and maybe that is why hannity and lambaugh gets paid so much. Seriously, why would you pay someone $20 million dollars a year just to talk. That talk has to be worth a lot.</Msg><Username>flyininmytaxi</Username><Timestamp>1361488396810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:13:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361489461738-117</Id><Topic><Title>Low information Voters</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1361485843519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:30:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Initial action on sequestration first came from President Obama. Republicans agreed to the suggestion but were later stunned by the Senate Democrats and the President for their unwillingness to address out of control spending and dramatic increases in debt while Obama has been president. All of Obama's previous Budget Proposals called for trillions in new spending. Not one democrat in Washington chose to vote FOR Obama's Budget Proposals.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361489461738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:31:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361489571111-118</Id><Title>Since BA is based in Chicago, home city for Obamma, I expect a quick solution to the problem.</Title><Msg>All hands on deck, this 787 puppy will be flying before you know it.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1361489571111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:32:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361490138209-119</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1361468324847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:38:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're not fooling anybody. Paul is dead. The walrus was Paul! I am the eggman. Koo koo koo choob!</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1361490138209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:42:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361492013682-120</Id><Topic><Title>Japanese discover new problems in 787</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361488204664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:10:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shouldn't build such a complicated airplane. No need for so much luxuries. and so on ..................</Msg><Username>oroplata68</Username><Timestamp>1361492013682</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 19:13:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361492080052-121</Id><Topic><Title>Japanese discover new problems in 787</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361488204664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:10:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All airplanes should be simple &amp; safe. Period.</Msg><Username>oroplata68</Username><Timestamp>1361492080052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 19:14:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361492715769-122</Id><Topic><Title>Since BA is based in Chicago, home city for Obamma, I expect a quick solution to the problem.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1361489571111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:32:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the news: "The battery fixes that Boeing is expected to propose to the FAA on Friday — and the idea of proposing a fix before the problem is fully understood — both seem reasonable to a few leading technology experts we were able to contact. Lithium-ion battery expert Jim Manning and aviation technology expert Hans Weber both think that there’s a way forward to get the 787s aloft again. The National Transportation Safety Board has said that at least one Dreamliner battery suffered an internal short circuit, but the root cause of the short isn't known. Yet Boeing is widely expected to propose some fixes, including a battery-containment box, to get the plane flying relatively soon. “To me, it looks like the most reasonable approach,” said Weber, president of San Diego-based Tecop International Inc. “I expect it will be quite a while before the may find a root cause,” Weber said, adding that keeping the entire 787 fleet grounded until that cause it found, “will be a very serious economic impact on Boeing, and on all of its customers who have a 787 in their fleets.”</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1361492715769</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 19:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361494070822-123</Id><Topic><Title>What's that Sound?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361402111366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:15:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of denial, I TIVO'd several election day programs and just watched one again. Somehow I missed the Romney acceptance speech. Would you like to re-phrase your statement of dubious merit?</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1361494070822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 19:47:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361494159590-124</Id><Topic><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take it easy on those dang 2-syllable words you don't really know and you may cut down on the public humiliation. By the way, how's that ESL class going?</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1361494159590</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 19:49:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361494928288-125</Id><Topic><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's not bonifide if he's for it before he's against it. The world is a stage and Barack is the complete actor on that stage. If Barack told me he had a mother, I'd have to think twice before I agreed with him.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361494928288</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 20:02:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361496334360-126</Id><Topic><Title>Japanese discover new problems in 787</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361488204664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:10:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That should be an quick easy fix, unlike the battery. From the sounds of things it should be an easly fixed quality control issue, that might be resolved by a simple switch in venders</Msg><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1361496334360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 20:25:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361497094018-127</Id><Title>Thank you Professional Bargaining Unit</Title><Msg>I thank members of the Professional Bargaining Unit for not listening the riff raff here that wanted you to go out and strike. Thats why you are called Professional because you recognize that Boeing offered you a good deal and you took it. For that I think Boeing should reward you by giving you plenty of work on the 737MAX for years to come.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361497094018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 20:38:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361497863427-128</Id><Topic><Title>Japanese discover new problems in 787</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361488204664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:10:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever since we stopped using horse and buggy there has been problems.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361497863427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 20:51:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361498249533-129</Id><Title>BA sould be 40$</Title><Msg>BP is getting slammed for an oil spill while BA is selling a jet that can kill people, and the US gov is backing them up and upholding this stock price, imagine if it was a jet made by any other company(airbus)</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1361498249533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 20:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361502213436-130</Id><Topic><Title>Monoply business...</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361373555135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:19:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with hundreds of billions of back log... This should be at 100$ now..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361502213436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 22:03:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361502962673-131</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Automaton's get Zilch, Bupkus, Nada - Fools</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361500327521</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 21:32:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awwww, no strike followed by social unrest followed by chaos from which the Marxist revolution can rise . Keep your hammer dull, and your cycle sharp lefty, there'll be another day . . . . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1361502962673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 22:16:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361503295882-132</Id><Topic><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BO is a Liberal dim bulb on a 24/7 smear campaign . He doesn't give a rats rear end about responsibility . . . . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1361503295882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 22:21:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361504158991-133</Id><Topic><Title>BA sould be 40$</Title><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1361498249533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 20:57:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dont know about gov suport or 40 but I dont see why this things near a 52 week high it going to cost some real money before its all over.</Msg><Username>averyed510</Username><Timestamp>1361504158991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 22:35:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361508100433-134</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ are finally getting tired of Obama gas............</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1361504904383</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 22:48:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to say one thing about gregjanetommax. He firmly believes on Wednesday whatever happened on Monday. Regardless of what happened Tuesday. The he takes apparently great joy in posting roughly 500 times until it goes through what must be a very thick skull that his simplistic post is #@(%"&amp;2.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1361508100433</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 23:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361508310267-135</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was a rumor recently that Republicans were going to allow "science" back into their world. A huge event if true.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1361508310267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 23:45:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361508419627-136</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Automaton's get Zilch, Bupkus, Nada - Fools</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361500327521</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 21:32:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy there, djUmbO. No need to try to use the big words again. You'll feel better in the morning.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1361508419627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 23:46:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>