<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376885541094-1</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't even be sure hooz is hooz, Spart. He might be me, right? Loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376885541094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 00:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376886343603-2</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News Again Proves It's... Well, Crazy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376859742808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 17:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His bread is buttered on both sides and most of us R wingers don't care about that either, except it is just one more lie of many he is telling the country. The middle east is burning and hates us more than ever, a big part of this country is on handouts and our leaderless leader is out playing golf.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1376886343603</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 00:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376886945510-3</Id><Topic><Title>Hannity Defends Racist Rodeo Clown at MO State Fair</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376490215074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-14 10:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was not a free speech issue, Don. It was a case of classlessness and crudity. Free speech was never in question. It was a matter of subjecting people to a political philosophy they did not care for, and they complained. They were members of the public and it was publicly funded. In other words, some customers were not satisfied. There were kids present. Breast feeding could be seen as free expression, too, Don, but some Chick fil-A's (sp?) don't allow THAT either. The guys -- the PA commentator more than the clown -- deserved to be chastised for inappropriate material They should be made to sit a few out and think about it, just as professional sports players sometimes have to do. Did you come to see the bull riding of to smell the bull ----?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376886945510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 00:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376887065705-4</Id><Topic><Title>Hannity Defends Racist Rodeo Clown at MO State Fair</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376490215074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-14 10:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please, Loon. Don't take me on a Magical Mystery Tour of the warps and roadblocks in your brain.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376887065705</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 00:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376889135174-5</Id><Topic><Title>Hannity Defends Racist Rodeo Clown at MO State Fair</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376490215074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-14 10:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AFIK it was indirectly public funded. Halloweeen masks of all presidents have been around for multi decades No such national press #$%$ were made about ragging on other presidents as I recall everything nowdays is or must be PC or the race baiters like sharpton and jesse and . . . make it an issue. Now they want the non partisan Justice department and FBI to get in volved Currently our advantage on this issue is that in other countries - dissing the glorious leader brings on sever punishment- with such minor issues as beheading or similar. And to quote Hillary- so what difference does it make ? or perhaps this is **really ** a phony scandal . . just the same as the IRS, Benghazi, Obama care, NSA, except for the body count ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1376889135174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 01:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376890271341-6</Id><Topic><Title>Hannity Defends Racist Rodeo Clown at MO State Fair</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376490215074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-14 10:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever gets you through the night, Don. I saw rodeo turned to political -- and Obama-hating -- theater. I saw kids being taught disrespect for the presidency of the United States.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376890271341</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 01:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376904239722-7</Id><Title>What is up with the low delivery rates and all the Q.C. problems--make people resonsible!!</Title><Msg>Things mush change. Things are getting near the embarrasement level. Increase Q.C. checks after full inspecition control documents and start new Tiger teams to address these and the low delivery improvement problem. Need a little image repair now</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376904239722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 05:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376907881990-8</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh ...lets see here...Orly Taitz might even be you...or Nowarrantneeded, or General Melee or...well, you get the idea. At this point of the conversation I will direct you to Bulky Bob's comments at the top of the thread.....far more relevant to the original post.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376907881990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 06:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376908268548-9</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bulky....Let me tell you something....I used to not be a religious guy but the older I get the more I see the absolute wisdom of the Bible and the immutable truths it holds ...truths that affected men of old. As Ecclesiastes said..."there is nothing new under the sun". There were petty greedy and vain men in the time of King Soloman and there are greedy corrupt and petty men now.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376908268548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 06:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376908812454-10</Id><Title>Glenn Greenwald's Partner Detained At UK Airport Under Terrorism Act</Title><Msg>Remember when Obonzo addressed Ohio State graduates and told then they could implicitly trust Big Brother Government? Here is Glen Greenwald's response to UK and USA intimidation and harassment. "This is obviously a rather profound escalation of their attacks on the news-gathering process and journalism. It's bad enough to prosecute and imprison sources. It's worse still to imprison journalists who report the truth. But to start detaining the family members and loved ones of journalists is simply despotic. Even the Mafia had ethical rules against targeting the family members of people they feel threatened by. But the UK puppets and their owners in the US national security state obviously are unconstrained by even those minimal scruples. If the UK and US governments believe that tactics like this are going to deter or intimidate us in any way from continuing to report aggressively on what these documents reveal, they are beyond deluded. If anything, it will have only the opposite effect: to embolden us even further. Beyond that, every time the US and UK governments show their true character to the world - when they prevent the Bolivian President's plane from flying safely home, when they threaten journalists with prosecution, when they engage in behavior like what they did today - all they do is helpfully underscore why it's so dangerous to allow them to exercise vast, unchecked spying power in the dark."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376908812454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 06:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376911039758-11</Id><Topic><Title>Well, The Asteriod Missed by 17,000 Some Miles</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360983644903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 22:00:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>airy Weed and Chrissy now playing back seat Philadelphia lawer . Hilarious .</Msg><Username>drinkbleach99</Username><Timestamp>1376911039758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 07:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376912311817-12</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparticus now showing his true colors by defending the Taliban and Al Qaeda by railing against Obama's drones. That really takes the cake-- sparticus time was when we executed people for treason - doesn't it bother you?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376912311817</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 07:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376914456569-13</Id><Topic><Title>Hannity Defends Racist Rodeo Clown at MO State Fair</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376490215074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-14 10:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...is he racist because the mask was brown or cause the mask was in the likeness of the real clown?" He shoots, he scores!</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376914456569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 08:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376919899823-14</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz is attempting to get the Number # 1 libtard hack of the year award, and liar of the year naturally goes along with it. So far zosima is a distant second, but he always was a late bloomer, a kind description for one who is mentally challenged.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376919899823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 09:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376919919571-15</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus, Solomon wrote Ecclesiastes after a long and rich life, full of wealth, wisdom, wine, and women. In Ecclesiastes 12:13,14, he wrote, "Now all has been heard; here is the conclusion of the matter: Fear God and keep his commandments, for this is the duty of all mankind. For God will bring every deed into judgment, including every hidden thing, whether it is good or evil." One of the Proverbs points out what determines or distinguishes wisdom: "The fear of the LORD is the beginning of wisdom, and knowledge of the Holy One is understanding." (Proverbs 9:10) And who is the "Holy One"? It is Jesus. Even the demons know who Jesus is: "What do you want with us, Jesus of Nazareth? Have you come to destroy us? I know who you are--the Holy One of God!" (Mark 1:24) Reading and understanding God's Word is the right thing to do; knowing Jesus as your Savior is what this life is all about (John 14:6).</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376919919571</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 09:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376920442411-16</Id><Topic><Title>Part of the problem no accountability in shop or out of shop but Boeing Blames the other guy always</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376850738740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 14:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good morning Boeing employees I see 4 of you people read my post</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376920442411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 09:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376920514782-17</Id><Topic><Title>Could it be the result of the McDonnell/Douglas influence within what was once a great company Boeing?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376849750178</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 14:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well 4 Boeing employee's or one retired MD hater read my post</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376920514782</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 09:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376920552446-18</Id><Topic><Title>Fire suppression problems on the 787 Firebird? Hmmnnn....how's that outsourcing working out...</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376850131184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 14:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so three Boeing employee's read my post</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376920552446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 09:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376920709388-19</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with the low delivery rates and all the Q.C. problems--make people resonsible!!</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376904239722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 05:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>finally rs2ms2ts2ks272 your thinking of what needs to be done to fix Boeing, instead of posting hand clap dreamer crapola about Boeing . No company gest well ignoring that the kings cloths are off</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376920709388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 09:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376920727901-20</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More mentally challenging statements form da father. One can be against terrorism, such as against Obama's friends, the Muslim Brotherhood who are radical Islamists, and be against the use of drones. I am not although I would be against Obama from doing much of anything, but some are.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376920727901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 09:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376921142004-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why are 787 problems newsworthy , because BOEING ALWAYS SAYS “Blame them.”</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376827824650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 08:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well at least the usual crapola from the Boeing employees is not besmirching the post, good job guys, post your own crapola if you want brag up Boeing all you want, ie airplane deliveries, talk about how the contractor admitted it made the part wrong, but please add that Boeing is responsible for delivery of a working, correctly functioning airplane, the supplier is not ultimately responsible, their contract can be cancelled at any time for non performance of failure to supply the part right, by the company that is responsible for a type certificate approved plane not a flawed out of compliance airplane, the 787 is a Boeing product</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376921142004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376922938774-22</Id><Title>Who wants to fly on the 787? The general public is worried</Title><Msg>Fires and the FAA grounding the fleet, more fires of planes parked at the gate, now fire extinguisher problems. This doesn't really resonate well with the flying public. People are scared to fly as is and panic at little turbulence, now put in their mind a plane which appears plagued by problems. Sure it might save on fuel, but if more problems develop and it's likely with so many cheap suppliers all building parts with no quality control the general flying public isn't going to want to fly on these.</Msg><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1376922938774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376923035875-23</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Outsources 787 Maintenance to Zimbabwe Poison Dart &amp; Plane Fixer Uppers, Inc.</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1376677833945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing loves outsourcing</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1376923035875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376924151214-24</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh I`m sure they will be bashing Obama for the next 50 yrs everytime they need to point a finger at somebody.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376924151214</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376924278720-25</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another one of the anything but Obama racists puts in his two cents. He bashes the use of drones even tho they are one of the most effective weapons the USA has against the Taliban and Al Qaeda. That is virtually the same thing as treason</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376924278720</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376924421428-26</Id><Title>when will the next A300/A330/A340 auger in waynedickensen?</Title><Msg>concerned flyers want to know</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376924421428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376924492027-27</Id><Topic><Title>Fire suppression problems on the 787 Firebird? Hmmnnn....how's that outsourcing working out...</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376850131184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 14:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kiddie makes the fire suppression system for Boeing. Kiddie is a subsidiary of United Technologies. United Technologies was created as a spin-off from Boeing because of government intrusion/anti-trust intervention. Maybe your outsourcing beef should be directed at the government. Further, kiddie is an American corporation.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376924492027</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376924549497-28</Id><Title>Boeing outsourcing maintenance?- Airbus says why do maintenance</Title><Msg>jist letem fall out of the sky</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376924549497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376924889734-29</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoodz, is right about winning being all that matters. Hitler was winner too and beyond question or criticism.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376924889734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376925120963-30</Id><Topic><Title>Fire suppression problems on the 787 Firebird? Hmmnnn....how's that outsourcing working out...</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376850131184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 14:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""United Technologies was created as a spin-off from Boeing because of government intrusion/anti-trust intervention."" pure stinking BS------- UTC was formed from Sikorski, Pratt and Whitney, Schweizer, In 2005 UTC acquired Rocketdyne a moribund and minuscule Boeing entity</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376925120963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376925534818-31</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will make the right-wing wacko's head explode when Hilliary succeeds him - LOL.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1376925534818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:18:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376925778684-32</Id><Title>Boeing Space and Defense Sector</Title><Msg>This was the gravy train of government contracts. Now it looks like NASA is quickly being replaced by private industry, and the military pull out of Iraq and Afghanistan. Followed by Sequestration cuts, this really impacts this as evidenced by the decline in revenue in this sector the last quarter and Boeing's announcement they are cutting 30% of the managers to pre-2010 levels. This division has major problems going forward as the country is broke and can no longer afford to chunk money on space programs when basic necessities such as infrastructure investments are lagging.</Msg><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1376925778684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376926116545-33</Id><Topic><Title>Who wants to fly on the 787? The general public is worried</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1376922938774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The similar issues plagued the 747. If you're shorting this you will be in trouble.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1376926116545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376926305584-34</Id><Topic><Title>Who wants to fly on the 787? The general public is worried</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1376922938774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>virtually every airplane flying went thru the same phase- some even had fatal crashes like the A320, A300, A330 and all these airplanes went into service anyway</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376926305584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376926420635-35</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"we are all moving toward the same goal. evolving our spirituality" This is not politically correct as you are offending atheists as well as emerging artificial intelligence.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376926420635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376926671189-36</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys are still bashing Reagan and he is dead so what makes you believe that criticism of Obonzo will end with his 2nd term? lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376926671189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376926824490-37</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Oliver Stone a low IQ RWNJ? He called Obonzo a snake which is the symbol of the devil.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376926824490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376927068797-38</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Space and Defense Sector</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1376925778684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, that's OK. How about cooking up big F-16 contracts with Egypt, Venezuela, Cuba, North Korea, Somalia, and Yemen?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376927068797</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:44:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376927723541-39</Id><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Msg>Why is it so easy for one guy from Harvard to find and release such a document while another guy from Harvard can't? lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376928099543-40</Id><Title>Profiteering by Keeping Americans Terrified</Title><Msg>Michael Hayden, the former director of the National Security Agency, has invaded America’s television sets in recent weeks to warn about Edward Snowden’s leaks and the continuing terrorist threat to America. But what often goes unmentioned, as the Guardian’s Glenn Greenwald pointed out, is that Hayden has a financial stake in keeping Americans scared and on a permanent war footing against Islamist militants. And the private firm he works for, called the Chertoff Group, is not the only one making money by scaring Americans. Post-9/11 America has witnessed a boom in private firms dedicated to the hyped-up threat of terrorism. The drive to privatize America's national security apparatus accelerated in the aftermath of the terrorist attacks, and it’s gotten to the point where 70 percent of the national intelligence budget is now spent on private contractors, as author Tim Shorrock reported. The private intelligence contractors have profited to the tune of at least $6 billion a year. In 2010, the Washington Post revealed that there are 1,931 private firms across the country dedicated to fighting terrorism. What it all adds up to is a massive industry profiting off government-induced fear of terrorism, even though Americans are more likely to be killed by a car crash or their own furniture than a terror attack.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376928099543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376928950492-41</Id><Title>Stupid Things Republicans Say And Do</Title><Msg>Larry Klayman: America 'Has Been Hijacked by Islam and Our President Is the leader of this Muslim Revolution' Conservatives are predictably freaking out that a tiny fringe group closely linked to the 9/11 Truthers is organizing a “Million Muslim March” in Washington D.C. on September 11. In a WorldNetDaily column, Larry Klayman suggests that President Obama is behind the march—the name of which has since been changed to the “Million American March Against Fear”—and believes he might even speak at the rally: “They have been given a virtual green light to do so by the mullah in chief. And, even if he does not show his devilish face at this highly provocative demonstration of the growing Islamic influence in the United States and abroad, Obama will be there with his fellow Muslims in spirit.” Klayman, who links to another WND article that wonders if Obama is the Antichrist, goes on to accuse Obama of supporting the Muslim Brotherhood and charging that the President fears the US military “may one day rise up and oust him and his comrades,” calling on readers to pray for a coup so that “we the People will soon be liberated from this modern-day pharaoh.” Finally, there is good news in the Middle East. The Egyptian military, having removed the Muslim Brotherhood President Mohamed Morsi after he and his terrorist group hijacked the democratic process, is now in the act of systematically destroying this Islamic cancer on the Arab state’s secular body politic. But the good news for Egypt and by extension Israel, its Jewish neighbor, is bad news for Barack Hussein Obama, our so-called “Muslim president.”</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376928950492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376929389123-42</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet I can bash America's illegal immigrant president 1230 consecutive days in a row if this web-site sticks around that long!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376929389123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376929719902-43</Id><Topic><Title>Stupid Things Republicans Say And Do</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376928950492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If WND says it, then it is probably totally false and nuts. This one takes the cake.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1376929719902</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376929721230-44</Id><Title>zosima</Title><Msg>United Aircraft and Transport Corporation the forrunner to United Technologies was formed in 1929 by the merger of Boeing and Pratt and Whitney. Sikorsky wasn't added until later along with United Airlines. The government then forced United Aircraft to split into three entities Boeing, United Tech and United Airlines.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376929721230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376929736820-45</Id><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Msg>love it !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376929856171-46</Id><Title>F-15 silent eagle</Title><Msg>By Joyce Lee SEOUL Aug 19 (Reuters) - Boeing's bid in the 8.3 trillion won ($7.4 billion) tender to supply South Korea with 60 fighter aircraft was the only one below the price ceiling set by the country's arms procurement agency, sources close to the process said on Monday. A final decision was not expected until mid-September, the sources said, but the price submitted by the U.S. company appears to be a significant step toward winning the contract. Boeing is pitching the latest variant of its F-15 fighter, dubbed the F-15 Silent Eagle, against the Eurofighter consortium's Typhoon and Lockheed Martin's F-35 stealth jet.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376929856171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376930945532-47</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a reason for that.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1376930945532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376931197656-48</Id><Topic><Title>zosima</Title><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376929721230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These entities being the original entities that made up United Aircraft and Transport and little of Boeings organization if any was leached into these separate organizations during the grand conglomerate. However today since 2006 the Rocketdyne organization which was originally part of North American Aircraft and then Rockwell and then Boeing became part of UTC Pratt and Whitney thru acquisition and this is about the only real Boeing that has survived in UTC- and even Rocketdyne was never functionally part of Boeing-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376931197656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376931311140-49</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmmmmmm I saw a copy of Obamas BC on TV along time ago- so whats your problem infested?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376931311140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376931573266-50</Id><Topic><Title>F-15 silent eagle</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376929856171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:30:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are in on this contract what with a large number of F-15K aircraft already in service with the ROK airforce, an enormous price on an F-35 which hasn't been tested in service virtually rules it out and the Eurofighter being another largely unknown entity not having commonality with the K's which would not offer any war fighting advantage over the F-15</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376931573266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376932646838-51</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In your dreams of greatness. In reality, they'll see your face in a painting of Don Quixote and the windmill.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376932646838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 13:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376932786792-52</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why was the space for "Father" left blank?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376932786792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 13:19:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376932932811-53</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I say, Spart, you make it too easy. Nutball.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376932932811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 13:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376933460949-54</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well her and Romeny have something in common than lmao</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376933460949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 13:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376935108694-55</Id><Topic><Title>Profiteering by Keeping Americans Terrified</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376928099543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:01:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So no need to safeguard against terrorists because a 911 or a Boston bombing every now again is acceptable because we're more likely to die from an car crash?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376935108694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 13:58:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376935147512-56</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what do you like best? Torture? His gutless failure to prosecute Bush? Keeping Guantanamo open? Drone strikes on women and children? Interfering with the Spanish Court when they wanted to prosecute US torturers? Sops to the 1%? Assault on the Occupiers? Illegal wars? Trying (and failing) to keep the Iraq war going after the Bush-set withdrawal date? Goldman Sachs in the administration? Illegal wiretapping? What do you like best of Obama's achievements?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376935147512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 13:59:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376935293542-57</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course he will. That's because the Republicans want it that way. How can he take the blame for everything if he's not there to blame?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376935293542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:01:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376935397018-58</Id><Topic><Title>Only 1230 days of Obama bashing remain</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1376836146708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 10:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama winning IS the Republican strategy. How can you be so dense?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376935397018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376935610512-59</Id><Topic><Title>zosima</Title><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376929721230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So getting back to the original thread, what was wayneker's point in disparaging Boeing for outsourcing the fire suppression system? Does he want Boeing to make every nut and bolt and piece of cloth used on their airplanes. Regardless, Boeing was prevented from making the fire suppression system because the government wouldn't allow United Aircraft and Transportion Corporation (Boeing and Pratt and Whitney and Sikorsky and United Airlines and Stearman, Chance Vought, etc, from operating under one roof.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376935610512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376935974354-60</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with the low delivery rates and all the Q.C. problems--make people resonsible!!</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376904239722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 05:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually they are on track to deliver well over 50 planes this month. With half the month over, they have delivered 28 planes and have a high number of first flights completed. As for Q.A issues, having quality checks by QA does more damage than good. Workers can simply say to themselves "I dont need to check my work because Q/A will find any problems." Putting the ownership of the work quality on the workers themselves rather than on Q/A inspectors has improved quality accross the manufacturing industry. Those companies which stick to the old Q/A model continue to suffer (just ask Kiddie).</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376935974354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:12:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376936091858-61</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was it on "History's Mystery" or "Believe it or Not".</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376936091858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376936169904-62</Id><Title>is every aspect of Obamacare now being delayed to its failure....even Ben Carson told Obama at the National Prayer Breakfast</Title><Msg>its was a very poor legislation. Who in the world making $10.50 an hr going to afford this Obama care? Soon every small business employer is going to cut every employee's hr back to avoid it. All you have to do it read to be able to understand its junk. Romney had it right do the same as the Congress healthcare, get the insurance companies to compete, but no the poor wanted something for FREE. Hope these people got a brain to figure this out for themselves.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376936169904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376936259177-63</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it was another immaculate conception?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376936259177</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376936696035-64</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only in America the nationality of a presidential candidate be squashed and then hidden behind executive order after he is elected. Obviously this guy is a liar, never before in our nations history.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376936696035</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376936962791-65</Id><Topic><Title>Glenn Greenwald's Partner Detained At UK Airport Under Terrorism Act</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376908812454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 06:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Power corrupts.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376936962791</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376937781409-66</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what do birthers become when they reach adulthood?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376937781409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376939437266-67</Id><Topic><Title>is every aspect of Obamacare now being delayed to its failure....even Ben Carson told Obama at the National Prayer Breakfast</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376936169904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 14:16:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It might have been better legislation if the Republicans had participated in writing and passing it. It would certainly have been better if Obama hadn't bent over backwards trying to give the crybabies what they wanted, only to have them slap his face on the final vote. You get what you pay for, and you get what you goons wished for. The American people STILL re-elected him, and most Americans love its provisions. So let me buy you a beer to cry into while lamenting your complete lack of willingness to try to serve the people.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376939437266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 15:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376941776719-68</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gnomes like Ron Paul.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376941776719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 15:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376941925569-69</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Passed Health Care Reform, Passed the Stimulus, Recovered US Recession Improved America’s Image Abroad, Reversed Bush Torture Policies, Ended the War in Iraq, Eliminated Osama bin laden Repealed “Don’t Ask, Don’t Tell, Protected Two Liberal Seats on the U.S. Supreme Court, Avoided Scandals (or lack thereof) Turned Around U.S. Auto Industry, Killed the F-22, Signed Lilly Ledbetter Fair Pay Act, but most of all - threatens the functionality of Republicans</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376941925569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 15:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376943466126-70</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Knowing Obonzo, he ran out of rolling papers and in desperation rolled his BC and smoked it at one of choom gang get togethers.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376943466126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 16:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376944021221-71</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody believe you wake up before 3 in the afternoon.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376944021221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 16:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376945172897-72</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody believes you wake up until the moon is full.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376945172897</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 16:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376946827928-73</Id><Topic><Title>Who wants to fly on the 787? The general public is worried</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1376922938774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father_zosima • or as he used to be called whstleffanms is taking up space here, he is a Boeing lover end of story. anything he posts is to try to convince you Boeing is good, end of story . Boeing was up today forget the fact that TSLA was up more , or that Airbus over time beats Boeing for the year to date and for 5 years for stock price gain, if you listen to this guy your not making as much money as you can over time . his opinion is not credible he has only one opinion he is in love with Boeing no matter what , he said "</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376946827928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376946911694-74</Id><Topic><Title>Who wants to fly on the 787? The general public is worried</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1376922938774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 10:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing has only 1.3% shorts and those people are hedging their longs it is a stay out stock not a short what are you binder Jim a shill for Boeing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376946911694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376947155243-75</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>once in a full moon - that's when ali comes out to receive his welfare check !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376947155243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376947455999-76</Id><Topic><Title>Why are 787 problems newsworthy , because BOEING ALWAYS SAYS “Blame them.”</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376827824650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 08:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeveritas and zoshima father aka wstleffanms are talking among them self's , if one talks , he is crazy, if two of them talk it is a conspiracy, so here they are pretending that since Bill Boeing had his company broke up by the government way past when any of us were alive , somehow that means I want Boeing to build all parts , nope I want Boeing to assure that any parts made are per plan, specification and blueprints nothing more or less. "Boeing can pick any way they want to build an airplane as long as the type certificate is 100% followed and at 100% not with fire in the battery, fine in the rear section, fire suppression going to the wrong engine , oil leaking, false signal in the flight deck and on and on you boys are really not with it are you freeveritas and zoshim are in a conspiracy ,"So getting back to the original thread, what was wayneker's point in disparaging Boeing for outsourcing the fire suppression system? Does he want Boeing to make every nut and bolt and piece of cloth used on their airplanes. Regardless, Boeing was prevented from making the fire suppression system because the government wouldn't allow United Aircraft and Transportion Corporation (Boeing and Pratt and Whitney and Sikorsky and United Airlines and Stearman, Chance Vought, etc, from operating under one roof. " har har har Less . .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376947455999</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376947652751-77</Id><Topic><Title>777x fuselage may not be built it Everett?</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1376856584339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 16:09:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good article when the wing line went automated Boeing was able to move over 500 people off that job company wide, if I am guessing about right and as long as the one man operating the gem core does not fall asleep like he did once and the machine destroyed one wing it was a good labor saving device, I am for good workers doing a good job not cheap outsourced work being fouled up like now with the 787 and the 747</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376947652751</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376947762831-78</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is 100% at fault on the utx fire suppression system fail , Boeing should have caught the problem per flight cert.</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376826882603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 07:54:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jjovas even you fellow unconditional Boeing lover boys don't like your union bashing posts</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376947762831</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376947890032-79</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9 Boeing lovers do not like reading the truth , Boeing is responsible for their contractors work being per plan Boeing lover boys</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376947890032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376948484321-80</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, Well, of course, it is opinion based upon the reality of my personal experience, but stating it as fact as a generality is also not inaccurate. I know that you like to often quote what Jesus has said - I presume for the authority of His knowledge and the fact of His being the Son of God. And, I offer this as well: Jesus answered, "It is written: 'Man shall not live on bread alone, but on every word that comes from the mouth of God.' " (Matthew 4:4). If it is indeed a fact that man shall live by every word that comes out of the mouth of God, then my statement, while it is certainly my opinion, Jesus has thus said in Matthew 4:4 that it is also a fact. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376948484321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376948659676-81</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I am a Dem welfare cheat #$%$. You got me. LMAO</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376948659676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376948880638-82</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the stimulus and the recovery are so great, how come he gets only 35% approval on the economy? His economic policies have benefited the 1%. He reversed the torture policies in name only. He left so many loopholes his "reversal" is meaningless--it only fools fools like you. According to the ACLU he has created a "New Normal" that not only continued the worst of the Bush-era policies but even accelerated them. Bush never claimed the right to assassinate American citizens. You guys are so infatuated you can't see what he is.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376948880638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376949169210-83</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots he scores!!!</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376949169210</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376949245917-84</Id><Topic><Title>Profiteering by Keeping Americans Terrified</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376928099543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:01:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you ever read "Red Harvest" by Dashiell Hammett. It's about what happens when you hire thugs for security and then they take over the place. You can't have freedom AND foolproof protection from every nut with a pressure-cooker bomb. We used to be the Land of the Free and the Home of the Brave. Cowards like you want us to be the Land of the Surveilled and the Home of the Cowards.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376949245917</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376949325888-85</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick#$%$ is a fascists pretending to be a Liberal.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376949325888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376949568889-86</Id><Topic><Title>Well, The Asteriod Missed by 17,000 Some Miles</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360983644903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 22:00:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard something on the news about Hostess threatenning to close their doors for good if the resident labor union goes on strike . The end of an era .</Msg><Username>cluck_head_00</Username><Timestamp>1376949568889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 17:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376950801025-87</Id><Topic><Title>Glenn Greenwald's Partner Detained At UK Airport Under Terrorism Act</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376908812454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 06:40:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greenwald is #$%$ now and states, ""I will be far more aggressive in my reporting from now on. I am going to publish many more documents. I am going to publish things on England too. I have many documents on England's spy system. I think they will be sorry for what they did". It looks like at least one reporter is going to expose Obonzo's lies and corruption. The best thing is that Greenwald was once a favorite of hoodz_wiener and hoodz_wiener posted lots of his articles when he aimed his pen at Bush. I doubt that hoodz_wiener will post Greenwald's work now that Greenwald's pen is aimed at Obonzo and in a strange twist of fate and the circle of life will find me posting Greenwald's work instead of hoodz_wiener. Irony doesn't get any sweeter than this. ROTFLMAO.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376950801025</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376951654175-88</Id><Topic><Title>Why The Right Is A Collective Cesspool</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_33</Username><Timestamp>1252775511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2009-09-12 13:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This a priceless post by Hoodz_wiener from 2009. Glenn Greenwald will now be questioning the legitamacy of the Obonzo regime much more than the far right. I love where he mentions the "the crazed conspiracy-mongers" as Greenwald is now the one reporting on Obonzo regime conspiracies. ROTFLMAO</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376951654175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376952236746-89</Id><Topic><Title>Why The Right Is A Collective Cesspool</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_33</Username><Timestamp>1252775511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2009-09-12 13:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>El_fiesto is the man that inspired me to choose ali_infesto. Unlike Glenn Greeenwald contard is now only one of the few disillusioned fools who still believe in Obonzo dogma and though he has switched IDs he is still barking dogma fed to him by the Obonzo regime. Irony is so sweet. LMAO</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376952236746</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376953153013-90</Id><Title>A Song My Best Friend Wrote For His Conservative Friends</Title><Msg>Inside" Ringtone to your Cell Crippled Inside Ringtone "Crippled Inside" you can shine you're shoes and wear a suit you can comb your hair and look quite cute you can hide your face behind a smile one thing you can't hide is when you're crippled inside you wear a mask and paint your face you can call yourself the human race you can wear a collar and a tie but the one thing you can't hide is when you're crippled inside well now you know that your cat has nine lives babe nine loves to itself but you only got one and a dog life ain't no fun mamma take a look outside. you can go to church and sing a hymn judge me by the color of my skin you can live a lie until you die one thing you can't hide is when you're crippled inside.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376953153013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376953307736-91</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is 100% at fault on the utx fire suppression system fail , Boeing should have caught the problem per flight cert.</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376826882603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 07:54:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waynedickenson961, you are the one in most of your posts (as in this one) accusing the union of not discovering the fault during the functional tests. I just happen to agree, you just wont admit that SPEEA does the sign off.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1376953307736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376953614858-92</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks fake to me.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1376953614858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376953963500-93</Id><Topic><Title>A Song My Best Friend Wrote For His Conservative Friends</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376953153013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sure this isn't about Obonzo being molested as a child? lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376953963500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376954116538-94</Id><Topic><Title>What is up with the low delivery rates and all the Q.C. problems--make people resonsible!!</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376904239722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 05:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Self checking sounds good in theory doesn't work as well in practice. I would not allow it in my organization unless I knew the fabricator and even then I would do spot checks occasionally. And I would NEVER allow outside contractors to do self checks. Was asked to consult on a quality issue for another group. What we found was that self checking worked well at first but gradually the quality would slip, particularly if there was schedule pressure. One of my peers received a batch of assemblies from Charleston for testing. Quality was so bad he sent them back. He wanted to send a QC inspector on site but Charleston would not allow them in because they were IAM!</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1376954116538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376954269670-95</Id><Topic><Title>A Song My Best Friend Wrote For His Conservative Friends</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376953153013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's on the Imagine album. Pure genius. Your observations are not.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376954269670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376954684443-96</Id><Topic><Title>A Song My Best Friend Wrote For His Conservative Friends</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376953153013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judging by the lyrics I'm guessing that your friend wrote this when she was still in grade school.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376954684443</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376955208306-97</Id><Title>Question of the Ages for Waynedickenson961.......</Title><Msg>So every time Boeing sells off a dollar or so you say.......Miss managment by McDonald Douglas hired managers, out sourcing problems, Mcnerney incompetence, blah blah blah...etc. So what is it when Boeing gains a dollar? could it be 787 back on track, management functioning, outsourcing cancelled, 787's flying without a fire.....well what is it? board wants to know....OK well maybe a few......Ok maybe just me. (The board thinks you're a fraud) You may want to bounce your answer off Burt Ruttan first!</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1376955208306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376955895920-98</Id><Topic><Title>A Song My Best Friend Wrote For His Conservative Friends</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376953153013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, of course. Uh, John's "Imagine" album was received quite well by the critics.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376955895920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376956006775-99</Id><Topic><Title>A Song My Best Friend Wrote For His Conservative Friends</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376953153013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could see where 10 year olds and brain dead pop rock groupies would think this is the work of a genius. I'm sure you thought the Archies were geniuses too. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376956006775</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376957670885-100</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cruz can do it but not our Illegal immigrant President. I'm of the notion that Barack Obama has something to hide. Maybe he has a lot of things to hide! With a 100% certainty, can you tell me that Barack Obama was born in America?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376957670885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376958349187-101</Id><Topic><Title>A Song My Best Friend Wrote For His Conservative Friends</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1376953153013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 18:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yoko Ono wrote these Lyrics. You thinking that Yoko Ono is a genius should be used in a PSA warning of how drug use can cause brain damage. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376958349187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376958580366-102</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even hoozdik isn't 100% certain that Barry Soetoro was born in America! What you didn't say is every bit as important as what you did say!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376958580366</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:29:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376958986428-103</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when I Wake Up in the Morning and Barack Obama is President</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376929736820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you say you love it when you wake up in the morning with a pair of Obama's shorts around your neck?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376958986428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376960010270-104</Id><Title>ObamaCare "Navigators no background checks or finger printing. Americans wide open to identity thieft</Title><Msg>a criminal to help me navigate into Obama care. Repeal It Now Not Ready for Prime Time: Thirteen state Attorneys General have written to Kathleen Sebelius at HHS to warn her and ask for more attention and more time for security and privacy. In the headlong rush to launch the flawed program, ObamaCare "Navigators" are being hired without criminal background checks. They and their helpers will have tax and social security information that are the keys to identity theft. Even fingerprinting has been skipped. Add to this the absence of security in the ObamaCare data hub that the former Social Security Commissioner warned was wide open to identity theft. As usual, government itself is the problem. As usual, we pay the price</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960010270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376960279700-105</Id><Title>Larry Sinclair won the sutie Obama verses Larry Sinclair....Obama is in fact a closet Homosexual</Title><Msg>the first polygrapher indicted for lying then Sinclair passed two polygraphs and was able to publish his book. Obama is a non reciprocating oral sex #$%$...seeks old men to suck. The media just walks away. I say be proud and come out of the closet #$%$ Obama.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960279700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376960722297-106</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Party Cheers As Congressman Tells Eleven-Year-Old Her Father Is Going To Be Deported</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376959687640</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:48:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>liberals think laws are passed to be broken and not to be enforced. Unless it fits their specific fancy. Democraps voted for the law along with GOP. There a immigrant who came here legally, do we send one of those home and reward an illegal entry into this country. Libs destroy this country, no respect for laws.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960722297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 21:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376960820717-107</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>has any president in this nations history hid behind as many executive orders as Obama. NO!</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960820717</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 21:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376961689588-108</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair won the sutie Obama verses Larry Sinclair....Obama is in fact a closet Homosexual</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960279700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:57:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hooz, like Obama walk away from truth, they like to make up truth and laws on their own. Truth means nothing to these people. Findings of a court of law means nothing to these people. Obama and hooz are cowards.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376961689588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 21:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376962319044-109</Id><Title>Obama vows spying over haul. So is Snowden a hero or a criminal?</Title><Msg>WSJ says Snowden would win in court. I think I am beginning to like Putin over Obama, a lot of people are. The media won't cover it but the Russians do not hold kindly to the #$%$sexual president. Larry Sinclair won in the courts to publish his book. Obama verses Sinclair...you can find it on Amazon. Obama is a non reciprocating oral sex #$%$. and is a card carrying member of two #$%$ bath houses in Chicago. The historians are going to have a hay day with this Less</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376962319044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 21:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376962529820-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obama vows spying over haul. So is Snowden a hero or a criminal?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376962319044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 21:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. It is "best seller" #107,241 per Amazon's site. I wonder what is 107,240, or 107,242?</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1376962529820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 21:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376963995952-111</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. has a $7.25 minimum wage. Australia’s is $16.88</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376956243078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, There may be different results that you might find on this subject, but the Aussies have a graduated minimum wage based upon age: Age/ Aus$ US$</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376963995952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 21:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376964122991-112</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The President ranks about 20th in the issuance of executive orders. Therefore, this subject joins the other 100% of issues on which you have no clue. Here are a few modern Presidents with their executive orders: Theodore Roosevelt 1,081 William Howard Taft 724 Woodrow Wilson 1,803 Warren G. Harding 522 Calvin Coolidge 1,203 Herbert Hoover 968 Franklin D. Roosevelt 3,522 Harry S. Truman 907 Dwight D. Eisenhower 484 John F. Kennedy 214 Lyndon B. Johnson 325 Richard Nixon 346 Gerald R. Ford 169 Jimmy Carter 320 Ronald Reagan 381 George Bush 166 William J. Clinton 364 George W. Bush 291 Barack Obama 157</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1376964122991</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 22:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376964756339-113</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. has a $7.25 minimum wage. Australia’s is $16.88</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376956243078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will try this again: The exchange rate makes some difference, but Australia has a graduated rate based upon age and being on an apprentice program: Age 16: Aus ($6.03); US ($5.49); 17 years: $9.46/$8.61; 18 years: $11.18/$10.17; 19 years: $13.51/$12.29; 20 years: $16.00 /$14.56 Apprentice program: $9.46 to $16.00 (US, $8.61 to $14.56) The US minimum wage in 1970 was $1.70. In today's dollars, that would be $10.23 (on-line inflation calculator) Here is what the Bible has to say (don't skip this): "Now to the one who works, his wages are not counted as a gift but as his due." (Romans 4:4) "You shall not oppress your neighbor or rob him. The wages of a hired servant shall not remain with you all night until the morning." (Leviticus 19:13) “Woe to him who builds his house by unrighteousness, and his upper rooms by injustice, who makes his neighbor serve him for nothing and does not give him his wages." (Jeremiah 22:13) Some might rationalize that a low/oppressive minimum wage is being lawful, but they will have a hard time explaining that to Jesus - assuming that they care.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376964756339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 22:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376964844851-114</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair won the sutie Obama verses Larry Sinclair....Obama is in fact a closet Homosexual</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960279700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:57:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to get your brain out of your pants. Leave the other stuff IN your pants.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376964844851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 22:14:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376964895795-115</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. has a $7.25 minimum wage. Australia’s is $16.88</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376956243078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My, my, my, the "thumbs down" clickers are simply chopming at the bit.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376964895795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 22:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376965071859-116</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. has a $7.25 minimum wage. Australia’s is $16.88</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376956243078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe this is their "hissing adder" mode.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1376965071859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 22:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376965210282-117</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair won the sutie Obama verses Larry Sinclair....Obama is in fact a closet Homosexual</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960279700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:57:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how many closet #$%$'s on this board? all cowards</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376965210282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 22:20:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376965282717-118</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair won the sutie Obama verses Larry Sinclair....Obama is in fact a closet Homosexual</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960279700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:57:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop re-re-re-re-re-re-re-re-re-re-re-re-re-reading your precious Larry Sinclair book. You'll go blind.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1376965282717</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 22:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376965421154-119</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. has a $7.25 minimum wage. Australia’s is $16.88</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376956243078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said it.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376965421154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 22:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376968325777-120</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. has a $7.25 minimum wage. Australia’s is $16.88</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376956243078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad you can't immigrate to Australia. You have to prove that you will be self sustaining and can contribute to society.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376968325777</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 23:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376969444397-121</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair won the sutie Obama verses Larry Sinclair....Obama is in fact a closet Homosexual</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376960279700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 20:57:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376969444397</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 23:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376969502403-122</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. has a $7.25 minimum wage. Australia’s is $16.88</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376956243078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're hot tonight, true. That one's going to leave a mark!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376969502403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 23:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376969560714-123</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a shame they're going to forget all about your facts once they sit down at the bar.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376969560714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 23:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376971049061-124</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz has made his birth certificate public</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376927723541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 11:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you don't understand English.....hid means hide behind a rock. This Obama hides behind several rocks. a hider. stupid</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376971049061</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-19 23:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>