<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377750496816-1</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries still increasing</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377633107373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 15:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is where Boeing stores its backup supply of wing nuts !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377750496816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 00:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377756877391-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cant do your thinking for you Raven.....Its part of the Maturation process and growing up to be a man. Indeed it is part of a long period of self reflection in which you shake off the acquired opinions of CNN and MSNBC and feel a faint glimmer of the simple recognition that your Lord and Savior may be a Major War criminal and may have lied to you all along...and that ole Sparty can be viewed as a Mentor as I guide you through a voyage of self discovery. This journey will not be an easy one. You've been a Parrot your whole life. Your first step in recovery is to admit you have a problem.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377756877391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 02:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377773497501-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post!</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1377773497501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 06:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377775316593-4</Id><Title>50 Years Later – West Defiles Martin Luther King’s Memory</Title><Msg>Tony Cartalucci August 29, 2013 The differences between Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. and current US President Barack Obama could not be greater. In fact, the only thing they have in common is that they are both black. Yet somehow, Western media outlets have managed to draw parallels between these diametrically opposed figures – presumably because they are indeed both black. AP recently published an article titled, “Obama Embodies King’s Dream and His Struggle,” stated: “The scheduled appearance later Wednesday of Obama, the first African-American president, was certain to embody the fulfilled dreams of hundreds of thousands who rallied there in 1963…” Why? Merely because President Obama is black? Or because President Obama embodies any of the ideals of justice, equality, and peace that Martin Luther King Jr. championed for during life, and ultimately died for? There is no greater way to defile the memory of Martin Luther King Jr. than to compare him with US President Barack Obama – a servant of an engine for the greatest disparity, inequality, and injustice on Earth – driven by the very corporate-financier interests King stood up against, was opposed by throughout his entire life, and most likely was killed by.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377775316593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:21:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377775363603-5</Id><Topic><Title>50 Years Later – West Defiles Martin Luther King’s Memory</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377775316593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indeed, despite the left-leaning facade President Obama displays publicly, his entire cabinet, past and present, is a collection of corporate-financier special interests, warmongers, criminals, and elitists who merely couch a corporate-fascist, self-serving agenda behind well-meaning liberal-esque causes. A look at these characters more closely reveals just this: - Timothy Geithner (Secretary of the Treasury): Group of 30, Council on Foreign Relations, private Federal Reserve - Eric Holder (Attorney General): Covington &amp; Burling lobbying for Merck and representing Chiquita International Brands in lawsuits brought by relatives of people killed by Colombian terrorists. - Eric Shinseki (Secretary of Veteran Affairs): US Army, Council on Foreign Relations, Honeywelldirector (military contractor), Ducommun director (military contractor). - Rahm Emanuel (former Chief of Staff): Freddie Mac - William Daley (former Chief of Staff): JP Morgan executive committee member - Jacob “Jack” Lew (Chief of Staff) Council on Foreign Relations, Brookings Institution (Hamilton Project) - Susan Rice (UN Ambassador): McKinsey and Company, Brookings Institution, Council on Foreign Relations - Peter Orszag, (former Budget Director): Citi Group, Council on Foreign Relations - Paul Volcker: Council on Foreign Relations, private Federal Reserve, Group of 30 - Ronald Kirk (US Trade Representative): lobbyist, part of Goldman Sachs, Kohlberg, Kravis, Roberts, and Texas Pacific Group partnership to buyout Energy Future Holdings. - Lawrence Summers (National Economic Council Director): World Bank, Council on Foreign Relations, Brookings Institution (Hamilton Project)</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377775363603</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377775389661-6</Id><Topic><Title>50 Years Later – West Defiles Martin Luther King’s Memory</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377775316593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:21:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, representation of the Council on Foreign Relations and the Brookings Institution (page 19, .pdf)should give any genuine left-leaning liberal pause for thought. These are think-tanks created by and for big business. The Brookings Institution in particular is home of the very architects of “George Bush’s” myriad of wars – as well as the wars now being waged under Obama. In reality, Obama’s policy is driven by not only the exact same corporate-financier interests that drove Bush’s, but in fact, many of the exact same individuals are writing the policy versus nations like Libya, Syria, and Irantoday who were behind “Bush’s” Iraq and Afghanistan wars – the consequences of which still are reverberating. This is what is called, “continuity of agenda,” with the feigned political proclivities of both Bush and Obama being nothing more than carefully orchestrated theater to divide and distract the public as a singular agenda transcends presidencies and perceived political lines. King was also an Adamant Anti-War Activist On the 50th anniversary of Martin Luther King Jr.’s famous “I have a dream” speech, should he still walk this world today, would undoubtedly be taking the podium and speaking out against the latest war the US and its collaborators are gearing up for against Syria. He would undoubtedly have condemned the global war Obama has waged from Mali to Libya, from Syria to Afghanistan and the borders of Pakistan, from Yemen to Somalia, to Uganda and beyond. In a speech given on April 4, 1967 in New York City titled, “Beyond Vietnam – A Time to Break Silence,” King gives what is perhaps the widest encapsulation of his philosophy and worldview, one that would undoubtedly criticize and clash with the disingenuous US presidents of today, during their hollow celebrations of King’s iconic speech. We should carefully reread King’s enlightening speech criticizing the Vietnam War which in part states [emphasis added]: A true revolution of values will lay hand on the world order and say of war, “This way of settling differences is not just.” This business of burning human beings with napalm, of filling our nation’s homes with orphans and widows, of injecting poisonous drugs of hate into the veins of peoples normally humane, of sending men home from dark and bloody battlefields physically handicapped and psychologically deranged, cannot be reconciled with wisdom, justice, and love. A nation that continues year after year to spend more money on military defense than on programs of social uplift is approaching spiritual death. America, the richest and most powerful nation in the world, can well lead the way in this revolution of values. There is nothing except a tragic death wish to prevent us from reordering our priorities so that the pursuit of peace will take precedence over the pursuit of war. There is nothing to keep us from molding a recalcitrant status quo with bruised hands until we have fashioned it into a brotherhood.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377775389661</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377777534265-7</Id><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Msg>Obama: "The President does not have power under the Constitution to unilaterally authorize a military attack in a situation that does not involve stopping an actual or imminent threat to the nation." - Interview with Charlie Savage, December 20, 2007 (full text here) Ok, so Obama lied again…what’s new. Well what’s new is that launching missiles into Syria right now could lead to a much wider global conflagration, i.e. World War III. I don’t think anybody wants that. Or do they?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377777624498-8</Id><Topic><Title>Kucinich: USA Will Become 'al-Qaeda's air force'...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377652608490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777624498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 08:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377778638074-9</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you ever going to man up and apologize to me for saying Obama backs AlQaeda ? ...which of course is now apparent to everyone ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377778638074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 08:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377782813485-10</Id><Title>westjet</Title><Msg>NEW YORK (AP) -- Canadian airline WestJet plans to buy 65 of the new fuel-efficient 737 Max aircraft from Boeing as it looks to modernize its fleet. Boeing said Thursday that the pending order is valued at $6.3 billion at current list prices. The deal includes 40 737 Max 8 planes and 25 737 Max 7 aircraft. Deliveries are expected to start in September 2017. The 737 Max will have CFM International LEAP-1B engines, and is expected to reduce fuel burn and CO2 emissions by 13 percent as compared with the most fuel-efficient single-aisle aircraft currently available.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377782813485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 09:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377784802875-11</Id><Title>Marching on Syria !</Title><Msg>neocons have a dream - that one day on the red hills of Damascus - that all Syrians will join with the Arab league and Kneel to the $$$....</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377784802875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377784976574-12</Id><Title>Republicans Absent from March on Washington</Title><Msg>Not a single Republican elected official stood on the steps of the Lincoln Memorial on Wednesday with activists, actors, lawmakers and former presidents invited to mark the 50th anniversary of the March on Washington — a notable absence for a party seeking to attract the support of minority voters.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377784976574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377785813686-13</Id><Title>Airbus has great friendships with people throughout the Mobile community, thanks for hiring USA workers Airbus</Title><Msg>Airbus Americas Chairman Allen McArtor praised last month the relationships the company has made with state and local officials. Construction continues on the $600 million aircraft assembly plant at Brookley Aeroplex. The Mobile City Council, partnered with the Mobile County Commission and the state, is also moving forward on contracts to improve roads and drainage systems in the areas near Brookley. The U.S. assembly plant for Airbus' A320 line of commercial planes is slated to come online in 2015, with the first shipment of parts expected sometime next year.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377785813686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377787051779-14</Id><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Msg>A Harvard Study titled "Would Banning Firearms Reduce Murder and Suicide?" looks at figures for "intentional deaths" throughout continental Europe and juxtaposes them with the U.S. to show that more gun control does not necessarily lead to lower death rates or violent crime. Because the findings so clearly demonstrate that more gun laws may in fact increase death rates, the study says that "the mantra that more guns mean more deaths and that fewer guns, therefore, mean fewer deaths" is wrong. For example, when the study shows numbers for Eastern European gun ownership and corresponding murder rates, it is readily apparent that less guns to do not mean less death. In Russia, where the rate of gun ownership is 4,000 per 100,000 inhabitants, the murder rate was 20.52 per 100,000 in 2002. That same year in Finland, where the rater of gun ownership is exceedingly higher--39,000 per 100,000--the murder rate was almost nill, at 1.98 per 100,000. Looking at Western Europe, the study shows that Norway "has far and away Western Europe's highest household gun ownership rate (32%), but also its lowest murder rate." And when the study focuses on intentional deaths by looking at the U.S. vs Continental Europe, the findings are no less revealing. The U.S., which is so often labeled as the most violent nation in the world by gun control proponents, comes in 7th--behind Russia, Estonia, Lativa, Lithuania, Belarus, and the Ukraine--in murders. America also only ranks 22nd in suicides. The murder rate in Russia, where handguns are banned, is 30.6; the rate in the U.S. is 7.8.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377787065686-15</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The authors of the study conclude that the burden of proof rests on those who claim more guns equal more death and violent crime; such proponents should "at the very least [be able] to show a large number of nations with more guns have more death and that nations that impose stringent gun controls have achieved substantial reductions in criminal violence (or suicide)." But after intense study the authors conclude "those correlations are not observed when a large number of nations are compared around the world." In fact, the numbers presented in the Harvard study support the contention that among the nations studied, those with more gun control tend toward higher death rates.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787065686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377787069126-16</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps if you tell me what reply I could make that will NOT bring on another insane fit of rage a pique. Oh. Who says he back Al Qaeda? How is it apparent? Who is everyone?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377787069126</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377787430979-17</Id><Title>Boeing Cargo-Jet Sales at Low on Global Slump</Title><Msg>Boeing is the world’s largest maker of air freighters, is headed toward its fewest cargo-jet orders since the 2009 recession as demand wanes for the overnight shipments that once drove purchases. With 13 sales through July, Boeing’s tally was just one-fifth the total of six years earlier. Airbus SAS, which didn’t begin shipping freighters until 2010, has no orders this year, and the market for secondhand passenger aircraft being converted to fly cargo has dried up. the trend continues Airbus stock is up over one hundred and sixty percent over three years for Airbus and less than half that for bowing only sixty one percent . Only the retirees who hope their pensions will not go to the pension guarantee fund and lower returns post here for bowing as jh-s said the best way to get to md is to outsource . and thanks to AB for employing American workers in Alabama</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377787430979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377787540364-18</Id><Title>AP News reports that Obonzo's certainty on Assad use of chemical weapons is misguided</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) -- The intelligence linking Syrian President Bashar Assad or his inner circle to an alleged chemical weapons attack that killed at least 100 people is no "slam dunk," with questions remaining about who actually controls some of Syria's chemical weapons stores and doubts about whether Assad himself ordered the strike, U.S. intelligence officials say. President Barack Obama declared unequivocally Wednesday that the Syrian government was responsible, while laying the groundwork for an expected U.S. military strike. "We have concluded that the Syrian government in fact carried these out," Obama said in an interview with "NewsHour" on PBS. "And if that's so, then there need to be international consequences." However, multiple U.S. officials used the phrase "not a slam dunk" to describe the intelligence picture - a reference to then-CIA Director George Tenet's insistence in 2002 that U.S. intelligence showing Iraq had weapons of mass destruction was a "slam dunk" - intelligence that turned out to be wrong. A report by the Office of the Director for National Intelligence outlining that evidence against Syria is thick with caveats. It builds a case that Assad's forces are most likely responsible while outlining gaps in the U.S. intelligence picture. Relevant congressional committees were to be briefed on that evidence by teleconference call on Thursday, U.S. officials and congressional aides said. The complicated intelligence picture raises questions about the White House's full-steam-ahead approach to the Aug. 21 attack on a rebel-held Damascus suburb, with worries that the attack could be tied to al-Qaida-backed rebels later. Administration officials said Wednesday that neither the U.N. Security Council, which is deciding whether to weigh in, or allies' concerns would affect their plans.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787540364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377787617303-19</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Cargo-Jet Sales at Low on Global Slump</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377787430979</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>har har har the guy thumbs everything I post no comment just a em bashier without any bla bla bla to go with it</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377787617303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:46:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377787676189-20</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus has great friendships with people throughout the Mobile community, thanks for hiring USA workers Airbus</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377785813686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:16:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for all the ba posters don't you want jobs for Americans har har har</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377787676189</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:47:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377787837617-21</Id><Topic><Title>I Have a Dream</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377777060776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:51:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take your meds, please. You are even goofier than usual this a.m.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1377787837617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377788339710-22</Id><Topic><Title>AP News reports that Obonzo's certainty on Assad use of chemical weapons is misguided</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787540364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since "sparty" now occupies a special place in the deluded mind of censored aka fascist aka bumper, perhaps a new LIST post is appropriate. LIST LIST LIST LIST please.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1377788339710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377788432542-23</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377787913220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been wondering if that isn't what's going on ... ;-D</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377788432542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377788707328-24</Id><Topic><Title>AP News reports that Obonzo's certainty on Assad use of chemical weapons is misguided</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787540364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Isrealis have told us they know that the Syrian government used gas, and we know the Isrealis would never misinform anyone. LMAO</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377788707328</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377788721472-25</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377787913220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine the terror in fascist's** mind--the prospect of another "President Clinton." ** plus Chemical_Ali_Infested, Hope4K lan membership, et al.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1377788721472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377788882593-26</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, that sucks!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377788882593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377789384754-27</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The devil inspired this bloodshed, and I know he is a democrat.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377789384754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377789595735-28</Id><Topic><Title>I Have a Dream</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377777060776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:51:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some humor from an Illinois Pol I have a dream that all black parents will have the right to choose where their kids attend school. I have a dream that all black boys and girls will grow up with a father. I have a dream that young black men will stop shooting other young black men. I have a dream that all young black men will say "no" to gangs and to drugs. I have a dream that all black young people will graduate from high school. I have a dream that young black men won't become fathers until after they're married and they have a job. I have a dream that young unmarried black women will say "no" to young black men who want to have sex. I have a dream that today's black leadership will quit blaming racism and "the system" for what ails black America. I have a dream that black America will take responsibility for improving their own lives. I have a dream that one day black America will cease their dependency on the government plantation, which has enslaved them to lives of poverty, and instead depend on themselves, their families, their churches, and their communities.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377789595735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377790214479-29</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377790214479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377790331090-30</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm here to help...you have a tormented soul reaching out ...taking those first few tentative steps toward independent thought</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377790331090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377790388243-31</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this isnt about your petty existence fatso - try fracking, xlkeystone, koch bros, walmart, looting pensions, enslaving the poor, gutting the middle class, msm... and best of all - corporate owned "elected" officials</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377790388243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377790444774-32</Id><Title>N korea plays hardball with dissidents or family black sheep</Title><Msg>North Korea's Communist dictator reportedly purged his own step-mother, Kim Ok, from her post as a senior official in the Workers' Party Finance and Accounting Department as he sought to tighten his grip on power within the country. She was luckier than Kim Chol, vice minister of the army, who was executed with a mortar round in October 2012. Kim Chol was reportedly executed for drinking and carousing during the official mourning period after Kim Jong-il's death. On the explicit orders of Kim Jong-un to leave "no trace of him behind, down to his hair," according to South Korean media, Kim Chol was forced to stand on a spot that had been zeroed in for a mortar round and "obliterated."</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377790444774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377791182985-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Independence is one thing, spart. Thought is quite another. Hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377791182985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377791481972-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sure it wouldn't be "out of character" for me?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377791481972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377791816735-35</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, where have you been lately? 50 million people are now getting free food, free phone(s), free bus rides to polling stations to include lunch voucher and carton of cigs, free healthcare provided by tax base, assistance with rent / utilities payment, and about $1100 per kid out of wedlock.......You may want to take advantage of your day off today (fast food strike) and head on down to your state gov offices and claim what is yours....just refer them to the Obama campaign promises.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377791816735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377791837760-36</Id><Title>delivery update</Title><Msg>Now 50 planes for August. L/N 73 787 for HAinan delivered yesterday. 36 737's 1 747 2 777's 11 787's</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377791837760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377791938013-37</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like you and the hooz don't cling to the Tryvon issue like stink on ship.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377791938013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377792519185-38</Id><Topic><Title>Zacks rating on boeing up earnings per share 30% current year , airbus up 83.9 earnings per share</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377792250447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:04:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>should be fourtyfour percent for ab to that lower for ba airplane orders mean nothing when both companies are about equal it is the earnings per share that make ab much better than bowieng fmh is getting all those thumbs down because investors know better During the first half of the year, Boeing delivered 306 jetliners, . On the other hand, Airbus delivered 295 commercial planes so far this year at a much better earnings per share fmh needs to get another job</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377792519185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377792660056-39</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The two of you must be very close.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1377792660056</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377793471760-40</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said! American capitalism enriches the wealthy at the expense of the shrinking middle class and impoverished. Awake citizens, our democracy has degenerated into a blood sucking plutocracy. It's that simple! Druid</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1377793471760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377793504545-41</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When was the last time I posted about Trayvon? Just another case of the right fringe imagining I posted something they don't like?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377793504545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377793533408-42</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obonzo pushing again for gun control that studies show is useless. Obonzo must be reading far left propaganda rather than peer reviewed studies by Harvard experts. 'Obama Offers New Executive Actions On Gun Control ' The National Rifle Association dismissed the administration's moves as misdirected, arguing that background checks for corporations and a ban on reimporting outdated guns wouldn't keep criminals from getting weapons. "The Obama administration has once again completely missed the mark when it comes to stopping violent crime," said NRA spokesman Andrew Arulanandam. "This administration should get serious about prosecuting violent criminals who misuse guns and stop focusing its efforts on law-abiding gun owners."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377793533408</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377793916562-43</Id><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Msg>here is another worthless statistic, Europe's Airbus notched up approximately $70 billion in sales at the Paris show with respect to deals for 466 planes. Boeing was not too far behind with agreements inked for 442 planes worth $66 billion." , it would appear Airbus is better, well no, Boeing and Airbus are about equal! airplane orders is a statistic that on its own is of no value, it is the EARNINGS PER SHARE that make airbus a much better stock holder investment better management = better EPS both Airbus and Boeing have about the same number of plane orders and deliveries over time, but airbus has a almost 300% better earnings per share 84% rounded up to 30% for Bowing , that equals Airbus has better management if you want to find the reason or make up an excuse, the bottom line between the duopoly as the press calls them, airbus this year and for three years is still twice plus the money in your shareholder back pocket if you own airbus and not bowing and it increases for five years if you own airbus over time</Msg><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377793963300-44</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simply not being Christian is not enough to qualify as being Atheist. As mentioned by Zosima, most of the people mentioned above had some form of religion or another. And what was your original point, that charitable work arises from the guilt of something? Were you implying that atheists should build more hospitals and libraries to compensate for the deaths they have caused, leading us to believe that that is why those institutions exist now, only because Christians are trying to atone for their sins? Libraries?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377793963300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377794420089-45</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the President can not do is declare war. Even Roosevelt beseeched Congress to declare war after Pearl Harbor was attacked. But aside from declaring war, there are a lot of things the President and Military can do, and many interpretations of situations that will qualify them to do it.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377794420089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377794892437-46</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Communism, maybe. But muslim made disasters don't begin to account for the amount of carnage that has taken place on this planet. They don't even compare to the carnage imposed on humanity by the Catholic Church during mideval times. And that is far outdone by the Khans. Then in modern times, most of the casualties in most of the wars claimed some form of religion or other. Atheism means not religious.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377794892437</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377795331365-47</Id><Topic><Title>I Have a Dream</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377777060776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:51:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377795331365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377795476236-48</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush's overt contempt for the Constitution created the environment of disrespect that Obama is continuing.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377795476236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:57:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377795503733-49</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Damn, 7 o clock in the morning and Bumper's already drunk.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377795503733</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377795581461-50</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, thanks.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377795581461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377796031887-51</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing EPS (TTM) = $5.47 Airbus EPS (TTM) = E1.73= $2.30</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377796031887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377796333864-52</Id><Title>New training center</Title><Msg>MIAMI, Aug. 29, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] today marked the launch of 787 customer training in Miami, site of the company's largest commercial aviation training campus. Aeromexico and LAN Airlines are the first two customers to train on the 787 suites at the Boeing Flight Services Miami campus. At an event attended by Florida Governor Rick Scott as well as a number of other federal, state and local officials, community leaders and airline customers, Boeing also established Miami as its pro forma flight training campus for the Americas -- the location where airline crews will receive the initial training provided to Boeing customers for new model airplane introductions.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377796333864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377796627245-53</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe bumper should try to get in on the $765M NFL players' concussion settlement. He would qualify under the severely brain damaged part. OR maybe they'll just feel so sorry for him that they'll include his brain in the research department.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1377796627245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377796924108-54</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"but airbus has a almost 300% better earnings per share 84% rounded up to 30% for Bowing" Another poster with bad math skills (even if you believe his EPS numbers). 84% compared to 30% is about 180% BETTER, not 300% Better (60% would be 100% better, etc). LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377796924108</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377797127879-55</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earnings per share is relatively meaningless without knowing the share price. P/E is a better comparison, and both companies are roughly equivalent there.</Msg><Username>dkmax</Username><Timestamp>1377797127879</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377798245595-56</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I imagine nothing. Excluding this thread I have made 3 posts regarding Shorty over 10 days. That is hardly wallowing in it. On the other hand you have made posts regarding Trayvon a 5 month period starting on 2/27 and continuing until 7/25. I quit counting how many post you made regarding Trayvon after 70 and that was in just a three week period. I also feel confident that your and hooz's persecution of an innocent man (Zimmerman or "zipperman" as you like to call) him) and promotion of racial turmoil will continue.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377798245595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377798580070-57</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Absent from March on Washington</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377784976574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:02:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you were a big MLK supporter back in the day, eh Bumpy? BTW I'm not Sparty. He showed up on this board years after I started mocking you. Do you remember The_Ministry_of_Truth? That was me. And it's STILL painfully true that whether angels are corporeal or non-corporeal, an infinite number can dance on top your head.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1377798580070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377798711329-58</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If DDT hadn't been bannned, it would be killing or deforming us directly by now instead of just moving up the food chain.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377798711329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377798741744-59</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I can say is: Does a n a l -retentive have a hyphen? Your research disregards a couple of salient points: A) The Travon case went on over a period of months, from shooting through shenanigans to trial and verdict, when I laid it to rest. Whereas the Shorty case SO FAR has gone on about three days. B) YOU continued flinging Shorty a the board (like feces) after most people, including myself, had expressed our dismay at the one-off senseless crime. C) You "wallowed" in Shorty's case by calling the assailants Obama's "sons," something no one but you suggested -- a typical case of accusing others of saying or thinking what they did NOT say or think. Now stop wallowing and move on.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377798741744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377798848647-60</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, if you think I made 70 posts about Trayvon, you must be counting all the posters you THINK are me! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377798848647</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377798875161-61</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That new moniker will not serve you well, either. Ignore.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377798875161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 13:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377799681148-62</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another new member to this board. This one was fired from Boeing for inappropriate activities there condit242 1 post | Last Activity: 1 hour 33 minutes ago Member since: Aug 29, 2013</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377799681148</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 14:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377800144260-63</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope. All the post regarding Trayvon were in you name and I'm sure an official count would have you well over 200. And for the record look up a post/title by team_hozomeen dated 8/23/13 when it comes to dispel your "something no one but you suggested" comment. That was before I "suggested" it.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377800144260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 14:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377801285204-64</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Iran is less worried about USA power much more so since Obama took over. Syria's Assad supports Iran's take over of the Middle East. That is a big concern regarding our national security. Watch what Obama supports. An easy quick strike would takeout Assad's airforce, and render his air strips useless. That would greatly support the moderates fighting to over-throw Assad. Obama, however, will support the Iranians, and make, more than likely, nothing more than a token, symbolic strike. Russia, and the Iranians, will be very happy with Obama.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377801285204</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 14:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377801645656-65</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Absent from March on Washington</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377784976574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:02:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The celebration was nothing more than a radical liberal, dem convention....sad day for civil rights. King would have been shocked. Dr. King was very vocal about the Black Race's role in gaining civil rights. Laws suppressing Black's have been eliminated. Laws are no longer the problem. It is the social problems that liberals have brought on Blacks, and liberal legislator's that will not address these social problems that are destroying Blacks in this country. Liberals have too big of financial stake in seeing Blacks remain oppressed.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377801645656</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 14:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377801740198-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He can't stop trying to turn #%&amp;@ into shinola.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1377801740198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 14:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377801880078-67</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>true....not just continuing but ..if it is possible totally disregarding</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377801880078</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 14:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377803149751-68</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Absent from March on Washington</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377784976574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:02:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What office are you running for?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377803149751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 15:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377803240560-69</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under the charter of the UN, to which the USA is signatory, he can only wage war if there is a military threat to the USA or if the UN authorizes it. Article VI of the Constitution provides that treaties entered into are the supreme law of the land.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377803240560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 15:07:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377804550372-70</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The administration could try to keep guns away from people with mental illness.. Just a thought since mental illness goes along with mass shootings, but why use common sense in the debate on guns.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1377804550372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 15:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377804839303-71</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it will help you move on, I agree. You are 100 percent correct; the count may be more like 2,000. Now, back to Shorty...</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377804839303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 15:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377805964093-72</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx, he might be AKA waynedickless.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377805964093</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 15:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377806073161-73</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No pro-American should give Obama any respect given the socialist/progressive agenda Obama is on. And the pool hall gang needs to get informed if they want their pool hall to remain open.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377806073161</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 15:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377806510192-74</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Wayne. Got another alias I see ... That's nice. I understand if you collect 12 or more Yahoo! awards you with a nice set of steak knives. It has been almost two weeks and I've still heard nothing whatsoever from Ethics. Told ya so ... That's game, set and match. Have a nice day!</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1377806510192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 16:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377807556672-75</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It says that in existing federal gun laws. (You know; like how the NRA says, "Let's enforce the laws we have on the books.") The problem is, without background checks and with the loophole for gun swap meets. no one has to ask or answer "have you ever been adjudicated mentally incompetent?" (Or something like that. I just renewed my CWP yesterday, but I can't remember the exact wordin of the questions I swore a "NO" to.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377807556672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 16:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377809927114-76</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VN said ... I understand if you collect 12 or more Yahoo! awards you with a nice set of steak knives... I thought it was a free colonoscopy- but for Wayne they haven't yet determined which orifice to use as they both have identical outputs. At 15 awards - they provide free KY . ..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377809927114</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 16:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377810009555-77</Id><Title>Rand Paul Warns Obama Against Starting “Major War” With Russia</Title><Msg>Senator says rebels more likely to be behind chemical weapons attack Paul Joseph Watson August 29, 2013 Kentucky Senator Rand Paul says it’s more likely the Syrian rebels were behind last week’s chemical weapons attack, warning President Obama that military escalation risked provoking a major war with Russia in the longer term. “There are some questions, it sounds more and more like chemical weapons were used but there are some questions and it should be investigated who used them,” said Paul during a radio interview, adding, “Pat Buchanan had an article the other day and he asked the Latin phrase cui bono – to whose benefit is this?….This is to the benefit of the rebels because now it’s bringing other people in on their side, so there’s a great incentive for this to have actually been launched by rebels not the Syrian Army.” Despite the Obama administration initially claiming it was “undeniable” that Bashar Al-Assad’s forces were behind last week’s attack, US officials admitted to the New York Times that there is no “smoking gun” that directly links President Assad to the attack.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377810009555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377810161428-78</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Decade !</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377777534265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 07:58:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earlier Pennetta and Obama said they don't take orders from Congress to go to war only the UN...impeachable treason of course...but it gets better...now that two of the major players on the UN security counsel (Russia and China) have vetoed a Syrian attack , NOW Kohn Kerry says they take orders from NATO...which of course is run and made up by the Bilderberg group...so basically we NOW take our orders from Bilderberg</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377810161428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377810239620-79</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most people make a conscious effort to hold on to their sanity. Some people consciously let their sanity slide in stressful situations. Some people's sanity slides away to the point of not getting it back. Point being, a person could be perfectly sane at the time of applying for a gun permit, but allow that sanity to slide away temporarily or permanently at a later date. On the other hand, certain types of background checks could thin out those who are already known to have difficulty maintaining their sanity. When asked what would have prevented him from shooting Reagan, Hinckley said, "If it had been at all difficult to get a gun, I probably wouldn't have done it." Back then, there were way less guns in private possession than there are now. Regardless of law, anyone with a few dollars can have a gun. I think the Harvard study is accurate.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377810239620</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377810471186-80</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Kent Raven alias congratulating the Kent Raven............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1377810471186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377811299511-81</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There most definitely IS a correlation between guns and violence...the more guns to protect law abiding citizens the less aggressive the criminal...a well armed population is a POLITE population</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377811299511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377813769051-82</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Easier To Buy An Assault Weapon Than To Vote, In One Graphic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377812742208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was that a stupid Slick Willy statement, or what? Only a lib democrat could make such a stupid statement. Harvard just came out with a study report that gun control does not reduce murders committed with a gun.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377813769051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377813926335-83</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with most of what you said, such as "anyone with a few dollars can have a gun" and "certain types of background checks could thin out those who are already known to have difficulty maintaining their sanity." As for the Harvard study, it may be being misrepresented by those who posted it to support a political point, but if it's about banning handguns as the original topic line suggests, I find that odd -- since no one in the United States with any authority is talking about BANNING anything except a few types; all SERIOUS proposals include reasonable regulation of the right to keep and bear arms, just as there are reasonable regulations on the right of free speech, the right to freedom of religion, the right to habeus corpus, and every other right guaranteed to individuals under the Constitution.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377813926335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377814063148-84</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Everyone being armed has not made YOU any more polite.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377814063148</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377814200859-85</Id><Topic><Title>Assad Must Be Punished</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377811437968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:23:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no hope to it. The facts speak for themselves. Assad supports Iran's desire to take over the Middle East. Iran needs Assad to remain in power, and he will given he has air superiority. It would be easy, and there is a plan to wipe out his planes, and his air fields rendering them useless. Easy to do with missiles, and no need to enter Syrian air space. That would allow the moderates to over throw Assad. But will Obama do that, or just symbolic strikes justifying his loud mouth on chemical weapon use, and save face? I know what I am betting non.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377814200859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377814380016-86</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Easier To Buy An Assault Weapon Than To Vote, In One Graphic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377812742208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah yes; but to remain on the point, doublewide, he said it was easier to get an assault weapon than vote. I don't believe he mentioned per capita murder. Nor did hooz.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377814380016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377815333690-87</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Easier To Buy An Assault Weapon Than To Vote, In One Graphic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377812742208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm calling you on the Harvard report- I think there is no such report and that you just your same old lying self--you made up another one of your lies--try telling the truth once maybe you don't have to spend eternity in the hottest circle of hell after all</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377815333690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377815454084-88</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Warns Obama Against Starting “Major War” With Russia</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377810009555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:00:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rand Paul doesn't have a clue about Russian Intentions in the Middle Ease- in fact he is extraordinarily stooopid about foreign affairs</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377815454084</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377815574131-89</Id><Topic><Title>delivery update</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377791837760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now at 52 planes. 2 more 777's delivered.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377815574131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377815878201-90</Id><Topic><Title>Assad Must Be Punished</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377811437968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:23:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doublefault is under the hilarious hallucination that there are "moderates" to over throw (sic) Assad.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1377815878201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377816248192-91</Id><Topic><Title>Assad Must Be Punished</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377811437968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:23:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, Robinson should sign up immediately to participate in the fight - a fight that has nothing to do with protecting the United States. What we know is that chemical weapons were used - with claims of it being done by both sides. Not sure we can believe Obama when he says that it was Assad that did it. Consider what he said about the IRS. And Benghazi. And the NSA spying on Americans. The question is whether the United States is responsible to police the world. CNN made an astute point the other day by asking why 100K deaths were not a "red line" not to cross, but chemical weapons which killed about 1% of the deaths to date is. Setting that to the side, this "thin line" that Robinson things that Obama can walk - by lobbing bombs all over Syria, destroying or severely disabling the military and the government - assumes that only a minor amount of chaos will ensue. Say we create the chaos and the Syrian people go at it big time with the military now thinking that they have nothing to lose by further and greater use of the chemical weapons - and 100K will seem like a small number of deaths. Then, Obama, having realized that he has embroiled us in another factional war, will be compelled to put "boots on the ground". Who will he blame for the daily American deaths of the American troops that tried to restore order but were hunted and killed by all sides?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1377816248192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377816389065-92</Id><Title>Numerous studies find that strict gun control reduces gun deaths accidental and criminal by huge factors in many cases.</Title><Msg>Do Gun Bans Work? Posted: 01/08/2013 5:23 pm The Definition of 'What Works' 'What works' is defined as a statistically significant reduction in the occurrence the crime. Statistically significant means that the intervention or program is responsible for the reduction in the occurrence, and the reduction is not due to chance or part of a trend. For example, there have been studies on getting guns out of the hands of criminals. The Kansas City Gun Experiment is one such excellent example. Firearm offenses were reduced by nearly 50 percent. This was a very effective way to decrease gun crimes without displacement. This is an empirical approach to finding out what works. Success reduces the prevalence of the violence but any reasonable person knows we are unlikely to ever eliminate crime. Defining What isn't Evidence (and Why?) There is a lot of junk science out there. The three most commonly used means of so-called evidence that I consider junk science include: •Anecdote •Correlation •Pre-test / Post-test Here is why I consider these junk science. Anecdote is not evidence. It is a story. It may or may not be true. Even if it were true, it may not be representative; any changes may be caused by third variables; and any changes may only be temporary. For example, claiming that crime decreased because Virginia passed a concealed weapons law is not evidence. The decrease in crime could have been</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816389065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377816515382-93</Id><Topic><Title>Numerous studies find that strict gun control reduces gun deaths accidental and criminal by huge factors in many cases.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816389065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:46:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anecdote is not evidence. It is a story. It may or may not be true. Even if it were true, it may not be representative; any changes may be caused by third variables; and any changes may only be temporary. For example, claiming that crime decreased because Virginia passed a concealed weapons law is not evidence. The decrease in crime could have been caused by some other variable; it could have been part of a trend; it could have been part of other less salient crime prevention efforts. It could be anything. This isn't evidence. Correlation is not causation. Correlation is not evidence. My age correlates with the population growth in America. Does the number of my days on the Earth have anything to do with population rates? Clearly not. We can correlate an unlimited number of variables that have nothing to do with each other. Correlation is not causation. People who suggest causality with correlation are not using evidence. For example, the states with the strictest gun laws are among the states that have the lowest gun violence. Also, states with higher gun ownership and weak gun laws lead nation in gun deaths. These are true findings, but these do not prove gun bans work. It could be than laws or it could be the culture in those states; it could be police funding; it could be an excellent mental health or an excellent school system. It could be any number of third variables. Pre-test / post-test isn't evidence. It doesn't account for third variables; it doesn't account for trends; and it doesn't always have to have a logical relationship. This so-called evidence is most frequently used in the gun ban debate. This is not evidence. It is junk science. For example, pro-gun advocate and economist John Lott often points out that countries that started a gun ban saw an increase in gun crimes after the ban. A line on a graph is not evidence. The examples he provides are not evidence. It could be part of a trend; it could be due to some third variable; it could be d</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816515382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377816652688-94</Id><Topic><Title>Numerous studies find that strict gun control reduces gun deaths accidental and criminal by huge factors in many cases.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816389065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:46:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is Evidence (and Why?) For something to be considered 'evidence' we need rigorous scientific evaluation. This is more than a line on a graph. It is more than a single state or a single country's experience, or even the collection of a group of states or countries. Evidence is something that shows causality. It rules out trends, it rules out third variables, and it rules out bias. Evidence is very hard to come by. 'Little evidence' doesn't mean something does or doesn't work; it means we need more research to make a conclusion. The best form of an experiment is a randomized-controlled trial (RTC); an experiment. These are very hard to come by but this is the highest level of evidence. We could also have a matched pair comparison of two groups that are essentially identical except that one group gets an intervention, such as a gun ban, and the other group does not. This is not as rigorous as a RTC, but it is far better than pre-test / post-test, correlation, and isolated examples. Evidence must make use of a comparable group that did not get the intervention; without a comparison group, we really can't get an effect size to determine the effect of the intervention. Pre-test / post-test, correlation, and isolated examples don't show effect sizes. Researchers often used various types of regression analyses to do research. Regression has its limitations; it should not be used to claim a causal relationship unless all potential third variables are ruled out, which is extremely difficult. This is why good researchers don't claim 'cause' with regression and why the experimental design is the preferred research method. The Evidence There have not been, to my knowledge, any experimental empirical studies (using the definition of evidence above) on the effectiveness of gun bans. For various reasons, we don't have very good evidence (read: experimental or quasi-experimental studies) on gun bans' effect on gun crimes. The 1994 assault weapons ban has yielded "mixed</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816652688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377816814567-95</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Warns Obama Against Starting “Major War” With Russia</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377810009555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:00:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul is an isolationist like American unions are. A very dangerous position to take. Assad gave the orders to use chemical weapons. Once Iran takes over the Middle East we are going to regret that day realizing we could have stopped them with a very doable knockout of Assad's air planes ,and air fields. Given that the moderates could easily oust Assad from power. Russia, and Iran are betting Obama will not do what needs to be done.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377816814567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377816906812-96</Id><Topic><Title>Numerous studies find that strict gun control reduces gun deaths accidental and criminal by huge factors in many cases.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816389065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:46:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 1994 assault weapons ban has yielded "mixed" results. One reason is that the law sought to reduce the prevalence of assault weapons that were not being used in gun crimes. When we don't target the type of crime we are interested in decreasing and we focus on high profile items that are very emotional and fear inducing, we are going to miss what we really need to be addressing. There are also studies on the availability of guns, which shows that with increased access, increased caliber and increased round capacity, so too do we see an increase in homicides. It would stand to reason that if we can decrease access, caliber, and round capacity that we would decrease gun violence. But we need to have good evidence to make this claim. In addition to this, we have a phenomena known as the 'etiology-maintenance-treatment confound', which means that which caused a problem isn't necessarily that which maintains the problem, and the solution to the problem may be unrelated to the cause or the maintenance of the problem. In other words, the cause of crimes with guns (whatever that may be) may or may not be related to the solution. In short, maybe gun bans reduce gun violence, maybe they don't. We really don't yet know. What Should We Do? Any good law will seek to identify the type of gun violence we are trying to reduce. Non-specific laws will produce non-specific results. Specific laws will produce specific results. If we are trying to reduce homicides in an inner city neighborhood, our law should be very different than if we are trying to reduce mass shootings. One could argue that if we just ban the guns then we won't have the gun crimes. Well, as noted above, we don't have good evidence for that -- maybe we would, maybe we wouldn't. If a state legislature or the federal government is going to pass a law that is intended to restrict some aspect of guns in one form or another, it would behoove citizens to have performance measures (experimental or quasi-experimenta</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816906812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377816941348-97</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Warns Obama Against Starting “Major War” With Russia</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377810009555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:00:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps the largest dump load of doublehaul doofusery today. Considering the doublehaul level of goonese and doofusness, a bad condition.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1377816941348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377816973063-98</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Easier To Buy An Assault Weapon Than To Vote, In One Graphic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377812742208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How hard is it for you to see what is going on in Chicago with the toughest gun laws in the nation? You need to drive through the inner city tonite around midnite, and see how it is working.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377816973063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377817345081-99</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VN jealous then ?</Msg><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377817345081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377817395896-100</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Republican Party Survive the Monster They Helped Create?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377817011381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:56:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The enemy is self evident. Ask a Black how their race is doing under Obama. Check out BO's foreign policy, and see how many wars are going on, and how Al Queda has done since he became President. Check out the economic GDP numbers since BO became Pres. Check out the run-a-way debt he has created. Check out the disaster ObamaCare has become. Check out the corruption, and scandals Obama is involved in. You'd have to be a leftist lib to not get it....uups, I think I get your problem.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377817395896</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377817419633-101</Id><Title>British Parliment votes against bombing Syria - Obonzo has zero international support</Title><Msg>Obonzo gave his "I have a drone" speech but no one is interested in supporting him. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377817419633</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377817423328-102</Id><Topic><Title>interesting argument Airbus is only 180% better not 300% , than Boeing sparti step back, your view is too close</Title><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377816915338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:55:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lies, damn lies, and statistics. I never agreed that the 84% was correct. Just pointing out that some on this board (quite a few lately) don't know how to do simple math. Maybe Gonzaga doesn't teach that anymore. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377817423328</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377817461607-103</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Republican Party Survive the Monster They Helped Create?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377817011381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:56:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The country needs two sane parties, and at this moment we have only the Democrats. Let's hope sanity ensues.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1377817461607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377817728522-104</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>747 by whatever name , you rude slam does not change the EPS number. it is still EPs topic and Airbus has a EPS of above 80% and Boeing has 30% checked it out with Zacks the original message is correct anthing else is minutia or ooutright charactere assanation and avoidance of the fact that Airbus shareholders make more on thier stock investment than Boeing shareholders</Msg><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377817728522</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377817954888-105</Id><Topic><Title>interesting argument Airbus is only 180% better not 300% , than Boeing sparti step back, your view is too close</Title><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377816915338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:55:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA EP S = $5.47 eadsy EPS = $2.24 Want to talk EPS? LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377817954888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377818307327-106</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fred, james, Dell whatever albucucu,, no matter what you say the Airbus stock has done much better for Airbus shareholders than boeing spin it any way you want your only fooling yourself</Msg><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377818307327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377818367946-107</Id><Title>"New" posters lately?</Title><Msg>Anyone able to keep track of all the "new" posters on the board lately? elonmusk909 randywright133 condit242 gsylvia16 ? others</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377818367946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377818512059-108</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"so while mostof us just give you thumbs down" Who are the "us"? LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377818512059</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377818906176-109</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>twoweeks VN , and you VN, stopped posting for a week on fear , how do you know Wayne"s not building the case first, Wayne , can now go to ethics and suggest he warned you ! Wayne watched to see if you stop with the policy statement in your hands You did stop for a week so you know your personal activities on a Boeing public forum is subject to Company scrutiny like going to the Seattle times without authorization, VN, yes some former boeing employee's were terminated for that too. . I noticed how you cowarded for a week in seclusion VN and you should be disciplined if you do work for Boeing you are a poster child for what is wrong with their help at Boeing , you are a bad guy for Boeing public relations to have here on the Boeing message Board</Msg><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377818906176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377819011281-110</Id><Topic><Title>Numerous studies find that strict gun control reduces gun deaths accidental and criminal by huge factors in many cases.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816389065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:46:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Law.Harvard.edu WOULD BANNING FIREARMS REDUCE MURDER AND SUICIDE? A REVIEW OF INTERNATIONAL AND SOME DOMESTIC EVIDENCE DON B. KATES* AND GARY MAUSER**</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377819011281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377819070208-111</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>donshuper50 , I sure hope this is not the real boeing engineer , if so , you have come a long way down Don. What are you doing messing around with the likes of this group of trolls !</Msg><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377819070208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:31:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377819493482-112</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well you are the group of pensioners you understand that then thats all you need to know still in agreement with your 180% better for Airbus BTW your argument style is worthless, your losing to make a nitpicking point it is reallly 180% better for Airbus not 300% better for Airbus what are you thinking or are you thinking that is at least one of us questions, me LOL grow up sparti</Msg><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377819493482</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377819596871-113</Id><Topic><Title>Numerous studies find that strict gun control reduces gun deaths accidental and criminal by huge factors in many cases.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816389065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:46:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem is you strict progressive/socialist power control freaks on everything under the sun becomes a huge infringement of citizens freedoms, and an expensive bureaucratic tax payer expense that just ends up rewarding leftist bureaucrats. I'd say your day in the sun is about to take a huge hit at the polls.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377819596871</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377819781887-114</Id><Topic><Title>Numerous studies find that strict gun control reduces gun deaths accidental and criminal by huge factors in many cases.</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377816389065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:46:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Father's socialism seeks equality in restraint, and servitude, and the father pursues that fact to the max.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377819781887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377819887347-115</Id><Title>Boeing pensioners talking about how great Boeing is without any comparison to airbus just political spam</Title><Msg>great EPS and share price and the probems with freighters and the problems with the 787 will not go away because you attack Fred,Wayne,Dell, or complain that Tom O'Brien called it right Boeing for several months now has not been able to break out above 110 and hold you don't like being told tesla has done better well get over it. If you ignored Wayne-Fred-Dell he would probably go away he is feeding on your replys how dumb are you retirement Boeing message baord users</Msg><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377819887347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377820151363-116</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't refrain from occasionally posting or "coward" out of fear. I have this thing which occupies a lot of my time, but is quite enjoyable. It's called a life. You ought to think about getting one Wayne. ROFL!!!</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1377820151363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377820167563-117</Id><Topic><Title>Our advantage at the Lincoln Memorial</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377818550287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:22:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sir Pecker Demwit: They were, well, Democrats -- and I don't just mean those who celebrate democracy. Still haven't quite recognized this USofA was founded as a republic huh? Only need to grant a few million illegals to get to the 51% needed for you Dem dream "democracry" right?</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1377820167563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377820516317-118</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Easier To Buy An Assault Weapon Than To Vote, In One Graphic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377812742208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sir Pecker: A great democracy does not make it harder to vote than to buy an assault weapon... Republic, fool...republic!!! Get it through your thick skull Pecker!...Republic!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1377820516317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:55:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377821299587-119</Id><Topic><Title>interesting argument Airbus is only 180% better not 300% , than Boeing sparti step back, your view is too close</Title><Username>randywright133</Username><Timestamp>1377816915338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 18:55:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Randy, elon, wayne, sylvia, anyone? No reply to the facts about EPS. Typical.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377821299587</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 20:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377821685651-120</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Easier To Buy An Assault Weapon Than To Vote, In One Graphic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377812742208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democratic Republic. In some instances we elect people to represent our interest, and in other instances we vote our own wishes directly.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377821685651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 20:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377821852555-121</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Easier To Buy An Assault Weapon Than To Vote, In One Graphic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377812742208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FatherZ, in this case he is correct. Google it. WOULD BANNING FIREARMS REDUCE MURDER AND SUICIDE? A REVIEW OF INTERNATIONAL AND SOME DOMESTIC EVIDENCE DON B. KATES* AND GARY MAUSER**</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377821852555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 20:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377823393371-122</Id><Topic><Title>delivery update</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377791837760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wondering why you got 5 thumbs down for that statement, as if it were an opinion.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377823393371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 20:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377824413285-123</Id><Title>Comedy hour on the world stage ! and the clown is Obama.</Title><Msg>Britain and Jordan tell Obama......NO! English Parliament says Obama "owns" his threat of crossing "red" line and that England will not support military action just so Obama can save face. Lessons allies have learned here, Liberals/Dems talk war and have a very difficult time completing the initial mission due to fighting a politically correct war and threatening combat troops of war crimes for kicking in doors instead of knocking weeks after voting to send them into harms way. Looks like the U.S. is becoming the laughing stock of the world stage.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377824413285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:00:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377825017256-124</Id><Topic><Title>"New" posters lately?</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377818367946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:19:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's bad enough with spartaloon #1 through spartakookfreakloon #999999999999999999.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1377825017256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377825653635-125</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth About Voter Fraud</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377820086031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:48:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>649 million votes 47,000 UFO sightings 441 Americans killed by lightning 13 credible cases of in-person voter impersonation and about 3 remaining sane Republicans.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1377825653635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377826081710-126</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep It is I .. been here since 1997 off and on. as have a few others One needs a bit of humour in life. Spare time I take a few whacks ( shareholder proposals to boeig, and a few whacks at good ole SPEEA, now run by a card carrying marxist for an exec director and a president who was over the bend a decade ago..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377826081710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377826578248-127</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings per share, compared to airplane orders, and stock price</Title><Username>condit242</Username><Timestamp>1377793916562</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 12:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH BTW randy - what number of alias is that for w #$%$ head ? As to BA watching this board for employee trolls - they ususally dont bother- As long as it is NOT on company time or company computers - they could care less And yes, many many moons ago, I had a chat at a shreholders meeting with a BA exec who did from time to time check this board out of curiosity- but by 2002-3 it became so overloaded with trolls like you he gave it up. And even then He knew me since I posted using my name- got quite a chuckle. When I posted that little bit re my conversation, several BS artists like you jumpedd up and down and said I had dummied the whole thing up- using the execs name. He then AGAIN posted under his name as he had a few times before ( nobody believed it was him ) and verified my comments. So when is mcnearney or corporate HR going to support your claims by posting here ?</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377826578248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377826670096-128</Id><Topic><Title>Comedy hour on the world stage ! and the clown is Obama.</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377824413285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:00:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys are really pieces of ... work. First you don't want Obama to do anything about Syria, Then you call him a weenie when there are positive (for non-intervention) developments. So what do you REALLY want? No blacks in the White House?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377826670096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377827242043-129</Id><Topic><Title>Harvard Study: No Correlation Between Gun Control and Less Violent Crime</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377787051779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL hooz. My point was "Who defines polite? The guy who is quicker on the draw? Anything any of us say at any time could insult someone and having an armed society can't make society more polite, only less numerous. As Johnny Cash once sang, "Don't take your guns to town, son. leave your guns at home..."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377827242043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377827298188-130</Id><Topic><Title>Comedy hour on the world stage ! and the clown is Obama.</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377824413285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:00:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would settle for someone competent and more experience than community advisor- who understood the constiutution and read something other than ,Sol Alinsky and used bill ayers as a mentor. And who could make a decision on his own without Mother Val Jerret ( SP) Could care less what color.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377827298188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377828083603-131</Id><Topic><Title>Comedy hour on the world stage ! and the clown is Obama.</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377824413285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 21:00:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And they have collectively clicked their heels together 3 times and said "Saddam really did have WMDs" even though it has been proven that he did NOT and the W administration KNEW this before invading anyway. So the previous war cowboys think they have credibility this time.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1377828083603</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 22:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377830352691-132</Id><Topic><Title>"New" posters lately?</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377818367946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 19:19:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne doesn't need to talk to himself all day anymore with all his new followers</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377830352691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-29 22:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>