<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378268707829-1</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wail me a river, you sanctimonious loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378268707829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 00:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378268974713-2</Id><Topic><Title>Flash Flood Warning for 20 million residents</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1378260710886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm ever see that big empty trench about the size of a 4 lane freeway that runs from pasedena ( arroyo seco ) thru LA dosn to long beach ? 99.9 % of the time there may be about 8 inches of water in the center v section. Then even with no rain locally- It becomes full, fuller, and sometimes floods rosemead thru downey to long beach surrounding area. welcome to the LA river from the west and arroyo seco from the east side of town.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1378268974713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 00:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378269000616-3</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh Boy. The old "you must be genna too" ploy...</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378269000616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 00:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378287710306-4</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you answer the question?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378287710306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 05:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378287754086-5</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The board is waiting for your answer............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378287754086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 05:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378287809294-6</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you support AQ?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378287809294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 05:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378291428718-7</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hoozdik_hertz_the_turd : "I have their collective analysis. It's used as toilet paper" That would by definition include all your analysis</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378291428718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 06:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378291670792-8</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hippo-Crissy: "Wail me a River" Spartacus: "Build a Bridge and get over it"</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378291670792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 06:47:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378292775423-9</Id><Topic><Title>Putin is beotch slapping Obonzo who has become an international embarrassment</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377965175115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-31 12:06:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"She won't do anything to hurt the interests of the 1%" HoozdikcanIlick thinks he is on the winning team....as if he is in the "one percent" of the folks receiving the Largesse of the looting of the Obama administration and the Wall Street Interests he represents ......in the end he'll lose as badly as everyone else. In the meantime...lying and spending countless hours proving to everyone how "unracist" he is is very "trendy and hip"</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378292775423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378294831089-10</Id><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Msg>The Anti American Authoritarian Obama worshippers will not like this ,,,, Emphasizing that the Constitution mandates that the legislature has the final decision on war, Paul stated, “I am proud of the President for coming to Congress but….he has to say he will adhere to our verdict, he can’t come to us in theater and say you guys get to vote but it may not count if I don’t like your vote – he can’t do that.” Responding to claims by John McCain and John Boehner that a vote against military intervention in Syria would undermine the credibility of the United States and the office of President, Paul asserted, “I take my responsibility very seriously and I’m not too concerned about the President’s public relations – I am concerned though about young men and young women who serve in our military and I vote as if it’s my son or your son going to war.” “I can’t send them to war to fight for stalemate, I can’t send them to war with no clear military objective, and I can’t send anybody to war when our goal is not victory. Our goal is stalemate, they’ve already said they don’t even want to topple Assad, they just want a negotiated settlement after they blast him with a few bombs – I can’t see anyone’s son or daughter fighting for that,” added Paul.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378301835372-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's America: Income Inequality Grows -- and Prosperity Declines</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378299067861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 08:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only an ignorant liberal tail wagger would believe that successful people will do what Obama promises the poor, and the middle class...turn over their income, and greatly divide up their wealth among the masses. The only income that gets distributed is among Obama'a wealthy contributors. Conservative ideology is the only way to increase wealth among the masses....grow the economy, job creation, and provide the revenue for those in need, and get the crony, socialist capitalists off the back of the masses.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378301835372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 09:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378302690550-12</Id><Topic><Title>Current Democrats Have Harmed the Mediocre Class Tremendously</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378298676593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 08:44:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And I see the dear price workers pay everyday. I didn't leave my garbage out to get picked up on Labor Day only to find out from the workers that it is no longer a holiday for them. And they had to give up other holidays. I find out that teachers with years of teaching are being let go for lower paying first year teachers, and bigger classes with less planning time. Retail sales people that have a hard time making it anyway that had a full time job now have a part time job. Obama has crushed our standard of living in but a few short years......and it will get worse.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378302690550</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 09:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378302946124-13</Id><Topic><Title>Current Democrats Have Harmed the Mediocre Class Tremendously</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378298676593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 08:44:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't make any difference if there were more wealthy people. They aren't going to risk their wealth turning it over to Obama, and his cronies. They rathole their money, invest it out of the country, relocate their businesses, cutback, layoff workers, etc., etc. The economy shrinks, tax money shrinks, and the poor, and the middle class pay a big price.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378302946124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 09:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378302980268-14</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a joke- the pipsqueak from Tennessee who thinks he has the world of righteousness behind him trys to berate President Obama who is 10 times the man and politician Rand Paul is and then--------Kerry proceded to clean Rands clock by showing Rand how little Rand knew about the situation</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378302980268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 09:56:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378303248482-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does Obama Always Want to Help #$%$ but Not Christians</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378300159624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 09:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does somebody care if Obama goes to church or not? Soros?????? a minor player compared to Charley Koch (30 billion) David Koch (30 billion) Bill Gates (60 billion) Warren Buffit (45 billion) Larry Ellison 35 billion etc etc your choice of Poor old George Soros against these wannabe oligarchs who have 5-10 times as much money each as does Soros-- just proves how GD dumb you really are doubledipsh.t</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378303248482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 10:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378303649008-16</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does Obama Always Want to Help #$%$ but Not Christians</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378300159624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 09:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosima.....are you an atheist Marxist or a believer Marxist?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378303649008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 10:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378304799266-17</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is all about Obama attempting to blame the GOP for supporting the atrocities taking place in Syria....now wanting to get congressional approval. Now he can wait for weeks to get approval, when initially he was pushed past his red line? He makes the case he doesn't need approval, and that innocent children are getting chemically WMD'd? He could care less about Syrians. It is all about himself, and blaming the GOP period..</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378304799266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 10:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378307904047-18</Id><Title>Chicago Tribune Blasts Obamacare</Title><Msg>A withering editorial from President Obama's hometown paper -- which, incidentally, endorsed him in both 2008 and 2012: As of Sunday, there's one month to go before the grand opening of the Obamacare online health insurance exchanges. Americans will be required to buy insurance or pay a penalty as of Jan. 1. What will insurance cost in Illinois? What companies will offer coverage? With what benefits That's part of the Obamacare guessing game here. If you live in Utah, Ohio, Indiana or a dozen other states, you've seen your proposed rates. But if you're in Illinois, you're clueless. State officials still haven't released proposed rates....Illinois officials have submitted proposed insurance plans and rates to the federal government but won't tell the public what they are. Illinois folks say they are waiting on federal officials for final approval, but the feds keep pushing back the deadlines. This didn't get much attention last week, but Reuters reported that the feds have slipped in another delay on finalizing agreements with insurers about the plans that will be sold through the exchanges. Those approvals won't come until mid-September. So we have to keep guessing. Federal officials didn't explain the latest delay. But such deadline busters aren't a surprise. The feds have already missed more than half the deadlines in the rollout to Obamacare...Oh, and by the way, federal officials dumped another 300 pages of Obamacare rules on states and insurers just last week. No wonder some major insurers don't want to touch the exchanges with a ten-foot pole. The standards keep shifting, elements of the law are unilaterally delayed without warning, and pages of new regulations pile higher and higher by the day. The Tribune editors upbraid Illinois' unresponsive and non-transparent state government for spending big bucks to sell a product that remains a confounding mystery to most consumers: With a month to go, Illinois is scrambling to ready its online marketplace. The state is hiring 800 temporary workers to help people navigate the confusing maze of Obamacare coverage options and subsidies through still-to-be-tested, likely-to-be-glitchy computer systems. What could go wrong? Ahem. More than 4 in 10 Americans still don't have a clue that Obamacare is coming and that coverage is mandatory, according to a Kaiser Family Foundation poll released in August. Illinois is gearing up to launch a massive marketing and information campaign to explain Obamacare, to be orchestrated through a $35 million contract with FleishmanHillard. The company has a huge job to do. Our suggestion is simple: If you want to persuade people to buy something, tell them how much it will cost and what they will get. In Illinois, that's still anyone's guess.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378307904047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 11:18:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378308678726-19</Id><Title>Delta airbus order</Title><Msg>5.6B$, expects most to be built in Alabama.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1378308678726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 11:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378310419842-20</Id><Topic><Title>Chicago Tribune Blasts Obamacare</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378307904047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 11:18:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any respectable, group, or people that evaluate liberal policy at the bottom line, where the rubber meets the road, will always evaluate liberal policy to be a total failure. You can not provide taxpayer funds to rich bureaucrats, and have them then pass down the money that is left to other layers of rich bureaucrats, and have much money left for those the money was falsely intended to go to. Liberalism is a scam, and it depends on ignorant uninformed people in order for it to be accepted.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378310419842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378310914706-21</Id><Title>As The President Goes, So Goes The Nation</Title><Msg>Aren't you guys sick of King Obama yet? Everything from meddling in Syrian affairs, giving free stuff to buy votes, Obamacare nobody wants, degrading success, vacations every other week, more rounds of golf than any other president and this kind of a make it up as you go along approach.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378310914706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378311094926-22</Id><Topic><Title>"First of all, I didn't set a red line"</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378310707855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:05:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Dumbocrats", quite clever.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378311094926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378311599782-23</Id><Title>Their Must Be More Communists Here</Title><Msg>Every post that has any reference to Obama gets more thumbs down. Even though the posts are all correct.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378311599782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:19:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378311678326-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does Obama Always Want to Help #$%$ but Not Christians</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378300159624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 09:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a M U S L I M.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378311678326</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378312774711-25</Id><Topic><Title>"First of all, I didn't set a red line"</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378310707855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:05:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Picture: Two dozen zealous Marxists and loyal Obama supporters in the crises management office sitting around thumping their heads and one of them yells out, "I got it, I got." "We'll have Obama tell them he didn't set the red line."</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378312774711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378312848145-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does Obama Always Want to Help #$%$ but Not Christians</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378300159624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 09:09:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No billionaire George is NO minor player. He is rich enough he came close to toppling England's total economy by shorting their currency in time of economic peril. The guy is a slimy socialist that wants to change the face of America by crippling USA economy, and has placed his worthless puppet, BO as his stooge to do so. Soros is the one world govt instigator that can only get what he wants if world economies are in peril. Sure has Europe where he wants Europe, and BO has created the European model of failure.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378312848145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378312974672-27</Id><Title>Team Obonzo says we must help the terrorists</Title><Msg>Al-Qaeda linked terrorists in Syria have beheaded all 24 Syrian passengers traveling from Tartus to Ras al-Ain in northeast of Syria, among them a mother and a 40-days old infant. Gunmen from the terrorist Islamic State of Iraq and Levant stopped the bus on the road in Talkalakh and killed everyone before setting the bus on fire. According to media reports, the attack was carried out because the passengers who were from three different villages in Ras al-Ain, supported anti-terrorist Kurdish groups which were formed recently to defend Kurdish population against anti-Syria terrorists. Bodies of a mother and her 40-days infant were also seen among the dead, which were recognized by their relatives. Syrian Kurdish leader Saleh Muslim warned on Friday that the Kurd minority is facing an ethnic cleansing by al-Qaeda terrorists. While there is no end in sight to the bloody foreign-fueled conflict in Syria, another front has been formed between the Kurdish militia and extremist militants in Northern Syria. Al-Qaeda-affiliated terrorist groups operating in the country, including the al-Nusra Front, are trying to capture Kurdish territories and make them part of a state they want to create in the region. Following deadly attacks on Kurdish regions in recent months, groups of Kurdish militia were formed to protect their people. Anti-Syria armed groups continue to target civilians amid US threats against Syrian army and government which have made militants find it easier to widen their attacks. Following worldwide criticism, US President Barack Obama delayed an imminent military strike against Syria on August 31, sending the matter to the Congress to get more support. - Alalam News _______________________________ Funny how we aren't getting this information from US news agencies. I guess it conlflicts with the Obonzo Ministry of Truth who says we have to help the terrorists for the good of Syria and the world.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378312974672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378313449668-28</Id><Title>How Many Countries Dose Obama have in His Coalition of the Willing?</Title><Msg>France, maybe sort of, possibly, might could.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378313449668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378313649928-29</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next you're gonna say kerry actually has proof (that people actually believe) that Assad used chemical weapons....Get it straight...Obama is arming AlQaeda ... not maybe...its acknowledged..and 80 percent of our troops do NOT want to fight for AlQaeda....These people are beheading Christian Priests and outraging Nuns.......</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378313649928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378313768817-30</Id><Topic><Title>How Many Countries Dose Obama have in His Coalition of the Willing?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378313449668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will the coalition be wearing al-Qaeda lapel pins during on camera interviews?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378313768817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378314380142-31</Id><Title>Why did Obama Want to Lead from Behind in Libya and now in Front in Syria</Title><Msg>This box-o-rox of a president is consistently inconsistent.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378314380142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378314456130-32</Id><Title>Good News</Title><Msg>There appears to be a glimmer of hope for a more peaceful resolution to the situation in Syria. Russia, or Putin rather, has signaled that there may be room for discussion, and that he would be willing to consider proof, which I think we have a convincing measure of, before having the US take action.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378314456130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378315201692-33</Id><Topic><Title>"First of all, I didn't set a red line"</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378310707855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:05:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful idiots err spaz err censored err fascist err bumper err bumperspaz</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1378315201692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378315565477-34</Id><Topic><Title>From the Fever Swamps: Obama Planned the Syrian Gas Attacks</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378314404051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartaloon should be all over this one. He has an inside track to nearly all known conspiracies. Mostly inside his cranium, but still "inside."</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1378315565477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378315609494-35</Id><Title>Sold @ 106.84</Title><Msg>It's been a great run but the stock (and market) are showing signs of wear. Volume not there and tech indicators are diverging. I'll let the pumpers take the risk from here on, wish them well.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1378315609494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378316002867-36</Id><Topic><Title>From the Fever Swamps: Obama Planned the Syrian Gas Attacks</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378314404051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More than likely the falsehoods are coming from the incompetent Obama Administration. Their leaks are profuse. They attempt to cover up their ineptitude with one falsehood leak after another. World govts are now dismissing what Obama puts out through his leaky sources.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378316002867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378316067903-37</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jesus. You sound like William Randolph Hearst tryinfg to start the U.S. war with Spain. You sound Hysterical. And you don't have a shred of truth. You've repeated your lies so often, YOU are starting to believe them. But no one sane is. For God's sake get help.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378316067903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378316088748-38</Id><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Msg>......do any of you useful idiots (Democrats) know?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378316088748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378316377426-39</Id><Topic><Title>"First of all, I didn't set a red line"</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378310707855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 12:05:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pathetic how incompetent Obama is. Major leftist supporters of Obama were panicked at the ineptitude of Obama, and had no idea how he could avoid terrible results as a result of his Syrian debacle.....then they come up with the "let's try to blame the GOP if we can." Democrats up for re-election, and election in 2014 have to see our incompetent President as a time bomb.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378316377426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378316420154-40</Id><Title>John Kerry: I actually was Against Attacking Syria before I was for it.</Title><Msg>,,,,,but then I was against American military personnel before I was for them."</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378316420154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378316534807-41</Id><Topic><Title>From the Fever Swamps: Obama Planned the Syrian Gas Attacks</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378314404051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoodz_weiner_da_turd puts on his al-Qaeda lapel pin and goes to work for the Obonzo Ministry Of Truth Squad. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378316534807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378316543149-42</Id><Title>767</Title><Msg>Today Fedex took delivery of the first of 50 767 cargo jets it has on order.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1378316543149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378317017411-43</Id><Topic><Title>From the Fever Swamps: Obama Planned the Syrian Gas Attacks</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378314404051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz#$%$_the_turd: 'Syrian opposition actually carried out the attack, hoping that Bashar al-Assad would get blamed and President Obama would retaliate with a huge bombing campaign" ... ummmm...Exactly...so whats your point ? Everyones talking about it...The military is saying they dont want to fight for alQaeda and the Rebels are even bragging they did it on YouTube......So I say again...Whats your point ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378317017411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378317141060-44</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans should get out of the way of Obamacare</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378256220290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stopping Obonzocare is one of the few things that has brought Repubs and Dems together in a bipartisan effort. Nobody wants it and public support has fallen to a paltry 36%.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378317141060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378317475249-45</Id><Title>RON PAUL: "I SMELL IRAQ ALL OVER AGAIN"</Title><Msg>WOLF BLITZER, CNN: Congressman Paul, first to you. You are totally -- correct me if I'm wrong -- totally opposed to any U.S. military force in Syria right now despite all of that evidence that the Syrian regime used chemical weapons against its own people, is that right? RON PAUL: Yes, but I don't accept your statement because I think that a lot of people question some of that evidence. But I don't -- that is beside the point because of the policy that I advocate is a noninterventionist foreign policy. I don't believe it's in our interest. I don't believe it's our national (INAUDIBLE) best interest to be involved. I don't think it's legal under national law or international law. I think just killing more people because he has killed some people, if that is the case, doesn't make a whole lot of sense. So a noninterventionist doesn't pretend that they are all wise, that they can go into a country that has been in civil war, where there's several different factions fighting and killing each other. There's Christians getting killed by rebels and the Assad regime being blamed for doing this and that. I don't believe it's capable, morally, nor are we able to go in and say, we know who the good guys are. We know there's three different groups on the rebels, but we know that we won't give any help to the al Qaeda, we just have to punish Assad. It's a civil war and there's no way you're going to figure it out. I smell Iraq all over again. I remember the assurances that were given us 10 years ago and members of Congress believed that. But let me tell you, the situation is a lot different. The American people are on my side on this issue today and there's a lot more people in Congress now who are saying, it makes no sense. And just listen to the military commanders. They said, you know, we don't even have the money for this.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378317475249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378317571781-46</Id><Topic><Title>From the Fever Swamps: Obama Planned the Syrian Gas Attacks</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378314404051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You saying RUSH is lying ? So you back AlQaeda ? Why do you support terrorists ? Why do you hate Freedom ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378317571781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378317679049-47</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378316088748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still can't answer, eh?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378317679049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378317892200-48</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry: I actually was Against Attacking Syria before I was for it.</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378316420154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:40:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kerry was always the little rich boy who always got handed to him what other boys had to earn.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378317892200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378317922291-49</Id><Topic><Title>From the Fever Swamps: Obama Planned the Syrian Gas Attacks</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378314404051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's funny coming from the guy who admitted to me that you never write your own thoughts in a post because your not smart enough.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378317922291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378318075573-50</Id><Topic><Title>From the Fever Swamps: Obama Planned the Syrian Gas Attacks</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378314404051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You never answered my question. Do you support Obonzo and want to attack Syria?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378318075573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:07:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378318244298-51</Id><Title>Incompetent President, Incompetent Sec. of State, Incompetent Sec. of Defense</Title><Msg>.......what could go wrong? Heck, let's hurry up and go to war.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378318244298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378318723229-52</Id><Title>Censored is Hooz#$%$</Title><Msg>Censored always gets upset when I challenge Hoodz#$%$ and he sides with Hooodz#$%$ in passive aggressive fashion. Hoodz created censored and portrays him as a paranoid loon of the right. Censored always responds in a fashion that reinforces the paranoid loon characterization.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378318723229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378319042932-53</Id><Topic><Title>From the Fever Swamps: Obama Planned the Syrian Gas Attacks</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378314404051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love doing that to you because it reminds me of all the grammar/punctuation police who I constantly outthink. I always preferred ee cummings you moron. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378319042932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378319733940-54</Id><Title>Outhouse Labeled 'Obama's Presidential Library'</Title><Msg>TUCUMCARI, N.M. - Most Presidential libraries are constructed after the President completes his term. However, according to KOAT-ABC, a New Mexico man has determined the location for President Obama's library and has marked it with a sign that is sparking controversy in one small town. The sign rests on top of an outhouse. It reads: Obama's Presidential Library. Some in town view the sign as bad taste while others are supportive. One man told a local reporter that folks are treating it as a tourist destination and that it is frequently photographed. The man responsible for the sign would not reveal his name nor would he give any information as to his motivation but did say the following: "It's like watching TV. If you don't like what the hell you're watching, turn the channel. I'm not even certain he even deserves that level of respect, but that's my opinion." He added "...and fortunately, that's one thing they haven't taken away from us ... is our right to our opinion,"</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378319733940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378320312009-55</Id><Topic><Title>A Truly Great Phony</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378319394883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you can forgive Bush for his many references to 'nucular' material and constantly threatening us with mushroom clouds, I can forgive Obama for his faux pas. I've noticed that he isn't a very easy to listen to speaker, not as bad as Condoleeza Rice, but still halting and grasping. But he's doing the job.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378320312009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378320754834-56</Id><Title>Obama Admin says yes and no when asked about regime change - it's like Obonzo answering "present" for his entire career</Title><Msg>Last week Jay Carney said, “The options that we are considering are not about regime change,” Carney told reporters at his daily briefing. ”That is not what we are contemplating here.” We get a different story from John (Let's help al-Qaeda) Kerry today: Secretary of State John Kerry said at Wednesday’s hearing that Arab counties have offered to pay for the entirety of unseating President Bashar al-Assad if the United States took the lead militarily. “With respect to Arab counties offering to bear costs and to assess, the answer is profoundly yes,” Kerry said. “They have. That offer is on the table.”</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378320754834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378320884161-57</Id><Topic><Title>Outhouse Labeled 'Obama's Presidential Library'</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378319733940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This man is obviously perpetuating a fraud. Everyone knows the site of the real Obama Presidential Library well be built in Mumbassa Kenya ...He already has a statue erected on the spot of the Nativity ...</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378320884161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:54:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378322013959-58</Id><Title>test</Title><Msg>testing</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1378322013959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378322280085-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Admin says yes and no when asked about regime change - it's like Obonzo answering "present" for his entire career</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378320754834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:52:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obonzo Ministry Of Truthiness never seems to get their story right, but I'm a racist for pointing it out.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378322280085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:18:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378322717864-60</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus acute psychosis is treatable but first you have to have your psychiatrist commit you to an insane asylum considering the severity of your illness</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378322717864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378322955132-61</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction the first line SB what a joke- the pipsqueak from Kentucky who thinks he has the world of righteousness behind him trys to berate President Obama who is 10 times the man and politician Rand Paul is and then-----Kerry proceded to clean Rands clock by showing Rand how little Rand knew about the situation.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378322955132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378323022863-62</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bapsychodept I made the correction to my earlier post - be sure to read it again --it will do you good--</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378323022863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378323118060-63</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth ? You wouldnt know what truth was if it bit you in the Alpha Sierra Sierra ..... US troops in droves are going to Twitter and You tube saying they don't want to fight for AlQaeda .... Why are you siding with known Muslim terrorists ? why do you hate freedom ? Why are you backing Unprovoked Illegal Wars against a Sovereign country ? Why are you an Anti American #$%$ bag ? ...</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378323118060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378324579589-64</Id><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Msg>Wow.......Google "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)" Pictures are worth a Thousand Words !!!!! The quote below sums up the feelings of the web page administrator "These pictures have been making the rounds on Facebook the last couple days showing American serviceman and I presume woman holding up placards telling their displeasure at the war hype against Assad. For protection they hide their faces, smart move. These serviceman have morals and know that they would be fighting on the wrong side. Obama is wrong, going through with an attack would be almost treasonous. How do you drum up support to fight with al-qaeda in Syria while working others into a killing frenzy to kill those same terrorists. Its a first in American military history as far as I can tell." -Mort</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378325376908-65</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A fringe website, photos that may or may not be active duty military who may or may not have the correct info -- and who aren't going to be asked to fight in Syria in any case ... I gotta hand it to you, Spart, that is Lunar PROOF</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378325376908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 16:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378325720965-66</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it when you talk phonetics, Sparty, You sound like Maverick or Iceman. And who do you always say is clinging to past glories? Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378325720965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 16:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378327730455-67</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're full of Bravo Sierra !!!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378327730455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 16:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378327922553-68</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually Military Officers BY NAME are coming forward talking openly about the insanity of attacking Syria...they have wargamed this and they know this could spin out of control into World War III....WORD IS TOO that General Dempsey told Obama to back off for exactly this reason...saying "If you attack Syria you will get in deep and if you do not have Congressional Approval you are screwed" ...which is EXACTLY what Obama is doing...but he is determined. like a maniac to attack Syria .... As for Evidence about who started this mess According to Reuters, the UN has had evidence that Syrian rebels have been using sarin gas against Assad forces since May... U.N. human rights investigators have gathered testimony from casualties of Syria's civil war and medical staff indicating that rebel forces have used the nerve agent sarin, one of the lead investigators said on Sunday. And as I discussed the other day, Syrian rebels have admitted to an Associated Press reporter that they were the ones that used sarin gas during the incident that the Obama administration is so concerned about. The chemical weapons were supplied to the rebels by Saudi Arabia, but the Obama administration will never, ever admit this. If the U.S. called the Saudis out on this, it would potentially endanger the status of the petrodollar. Instead, the U.S. government is going to end up doing exactly what the Saudis want, which is to attack Syria.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378327922553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 16:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378328013210-69</Id><Title>Oh Goodie - The Kent Raven has Fined his Shift at Burger King</Title><Msg>I hope he doesn't forget to tell the welfare office.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378328013210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 16:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378328073663-70</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like all conflicts that the US is or will be involved in, the question should be, " are you willing to send your own son or daughter there to possibly be injured or killed or to Kill"? There are No easy attacks anymore,IMO, because technologically advanced weapons and defenses are deployed in most of these countries. Stand off attacks seem to always hurt the wrong people / targets. I at least hope that serious evaluation of drone and satalite data provides good tactical targets if we decide on a punitive attack with some allies... Just the hype of a punitive attack will stress the Syrian military and detract from their effectiveness and possibly provide for rebel successes. Shelling a populated suburb like in Damascus cruelly injures and kills many more civilians than the few possible 'rebel fighters' and comparing it to chemical attacks is the same as if one is injured by a aimed round or stray round. It sucks for the one hit. Why doesn't the US fight in Africa or Burma or India/Pakistan etc? Answer is 'we cant settle all world conflicts, bush Jr proved that sadly and his tactics has proved this and our Military limits to the world. Now we lack credibillity and our Military is assumed to have a much lesser footprint and effectiveness. As my brother says ' just let them kill each other off for awhile', sad but true. As LBJ correctly said, " its time for * sons to fight instead of expecting US sons to do that for them"...JMHFO...</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1378328073663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 16:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378328377820-71</Id><Title>How Did Obama's War Mongering in Libya Turn Out?</Title><Msg>Special report: We all thought Libya had moved on – it has, but into lawlessness and ruin A little under two years ago, Philip Hammond, the Defence Secretary, urged British businessmen to begin “packing their suitcases” and to fly to Libya to share in the reconstruction of the country and exploit an anticipated boom in natural resources. Yet now Libya has almost entirely stopped producing oil as the government loses control of much of the country to militia fighters. Mutinying security men have taken over oil ports on the Mediterranean and are seeking to sell crude oil on the black market. Ali Zeidan, Libya’s Prime Minister, has threatened to “bomb from the air and the sea” any oil tanker trying to pick up the illicit oil from the oil terminal guards, who are mostly former rebels who overthrew Muammar Gaddafi and have been on strike over low pay and alleged government corruption since July. As world attention focused on the coup in Egypt and the poison gas attack in Syria over the past two months, Libya has plunged unnoticed into its worst political and economic crisis since the defeat of Gaddafi two years ago. Government authority is disintegrating in all parts of the country putting in doubt claims by American, British and French politicians that Nato’s military action in Libya in 2011 was an outstanding example of a successful foreign military intervention which should be repeated in Syria. In an escalating crisis little regarded hitherto outside the oil markets, output of Libya’s prized high-quality crude oil has plunged from 1.4 million barrels a day earlier this year to just 160,000 barrels a day now. Despite threats to use military force to retake the oil ports, the government in Tripoli has been unable to move effectively against striking guards and mutinous military units that are linked to secessionist forces in the east of the country. Libyans are increasingly at the mercy of militias which act outside the law. Popular protests against militiamen have been met with gunfire; 31 demonstrators were shot dead and many others wounded as they protested outside the barracks of “the Libyan Shield Brigade” in the eastern capital Benghazi in June</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378328377820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 16:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378328526301-72</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a whiskey delta charlie hotel and a bravo hotel sierra all rolled up into one delta foxtrot charlie..............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378328526301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378328559874-73</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul Demands Obama Adhere to Congress on Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378294831089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 07:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has he explained why he supports AQ yet?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378328559874</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378328606118-74</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's obvious our military is on to Obama's game. Obama declared there would be no boots on the ground in Lybia and that statement became another one of Obama's lies. Kerry and Obama only want to reduce the noise coming forward over his many other scandals. lIKE RULES FOR RADICALS AUTHOR SAUL ALINSKY IS TELLING OBAMA AND KERRY, CREATE A DIVERSION TO COVER FOR YOUR SCANDALS. America has a treacherous lying president!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1378328606118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378329584266-75</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All that is going on now is a product of terrible Obama foreign policy over the last few years. The guy is clueless. Now he is saying his red line statement wasn't his to make, the world created it. Always looking to blame others for his failures.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378329584266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:19:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378329832457-76</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Administration has gone to a Messianic level of Hubris and arrogance. Some armchair generals think we can just lob a few missles into Syria to "Punish Assad" and then pride is salvaged and we can go home...WRONG......even ASSUMING Assad gassed his own people (he did not) and even ASSUMING the US is the policeman of the World (it is bankrupting us and a whole generation is being affected) .this could REALLY spin out of control...and Obama is no JFK during Cuban Missle Crises ...</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378329832457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378330508627-77</Id><Title>Why do Democrats hate Christians?</Title><Msg>.....are they all Jihadists?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378330508627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378330730749-78</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well at least all the looney tunes sites spread around the world are using the same mantra- IF the photos really were military- they can be traced via facebook to point of origin- and while experressing your opinion as a civilian not in uniform is OK- doing it in uniform could be hazardous to your career- and refusing to follow a lawful order may get more than a wist slap. IMO- those photos are basically made by some wing nuts who MAY be in the military - which has a few wingnuts just like this board.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1378330730749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378331392186-79</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378330831061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:40:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are you quoting?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378331392186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378335133981-80</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps he is sympathetic to their cause?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378335133981</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378335377555-81</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My answer to Kerry is that US bombing will have zero effect on Assad's future actions at best. At worst our bombs will end up killing innocent civilians and Assad will leverage that into a huge anti US campaign that Russian and many others will jump on and Assad will say the US has no coalition and is acting as a rogue bully. Also if the US is not willing to put boots on the ground in Syria Assad will capitalize by painting the US as cowards thus propping up Assad. Kerry was made to look totally incompetent by Chris Wallace last Sunday. We will pay a huge price for Obonzo to try to reclaim his manhood but I doubt it will work and more likely it will backfire.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378335377555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378336058812-82</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here's Your #$%$ Moment of the Day!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378335892188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:04:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obonzo employs tactics that are very similar to Hitler as I explained yesterday, when all my troubles seemed so far away.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378336058812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378336293650-83</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats hate Christians?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378330508627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 17:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrat are angry elitists who think they are smarter than God and they are the ones who should be giving instructions and rules to live by, not God.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1378336293650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378336490214-84</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378316088748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have never been able to answer that question ......that's why they ignore it and pretend it shouldn't be addressed,</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1378336490214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378338061675-85</Id><Title>Congressman: "Syria authorization will Fail"</Title><Msg>Arizona congressman Matt Salmon’s constituents have called his office 500 times about Syria, he tells National Review Online in an interview, but only two callers have expressed support for intervening there. “This is not hyperbole!” he says emphatically. And Salmon himself is firmly against authorizing a strike. “I don’t see any national-security imperative for our country at all. Both sides in this equation are bad actors.” He also notes that Obama has been unable to form an international coalition and hasn’t laid out an overall objective for a missile strike. “Other than saving face for the president, I don’t understand what we would be doing,” he says.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378338061675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378338086466-86</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BRAVO SIERRA !!!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378338086466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378338381485-87</Id><Title>A-10 wing contract</Title><Msg>ST. LOUIS, Sept. 4, 2013 – Boeing [NYSE: BA] will continue improving U.S. Air Force A-10 Thunderbolt II mission readiness, and decreasing maintenance costs, through a follow-on order for 56 replacement wings for that aircraft. Boeing is on contract to build up to 242 wings, including these, at its plant in Macon, Ga. Refitting the fleet with new wings will improve the mission availability of A-10s by an estimated 4 percent and will help save the Air Force an estimated $1.3 billion in maintenance costs during the next 30 years. This latest order is valued at $212 million. Including this agreement, the Air Force has ordered 173 wings. The efforts of Boeing, its suppliers, and the Air Force will allow the A-10 fleet to operate into 2035.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1378338381485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378338519966-88</Id><Title>tanker design</Title><Msg>Boeing on track to deliver 18 combat-ready tankers by 2017 MUKILTEO, Wash., Sept. 4, 2013 -- The U.S. Air Force and Boeing [NYSE: BA] have validated the final design elements of the KC-46A Tanker and concluded that the proposed design embodies and can meet Air Force requirements, clearing the way for production and testing of the next-generation aerial refueling tanker.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1378338519966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378338575583-89</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Common sense, Don. I'm slack-jawed ! :-D</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378338575583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 19:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378339929457-90</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you know the people calling in are military? And how do you imagine they feel about the oaths they took, oathkeeper?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378339929457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 20:12:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378340708844-91</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The depth of your ignorance and just being consistently WRONG are breathtaking ...the Military members calling in talk PREDOMINATLY about the oath they took and how the Oath is TO the Constitution and NOT to a President or another person.....and that the oath is to defend the Republic against all enemies foreign AND domestic....get your facts straight Raven</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378340708844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 20:25:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378341654350-92</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A paid shill could not have done any more to advance Sec. Kerry's case than what Sen. Rand Paul did today. Even Mitt Romney in that position would have demonstrated some awareness of the facts and issues. Senator Rand Paul is totally clueless!</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1378341654350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 20:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378341972362-93</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ketchup John, a street bum until he married into wealth couldn't expose anyone as a fraud any more so than he has been. He's spewing Obama's bad strategy of bombing who? He doesn't even know who WMD'd who. Who is horseface supporting?...the Al Queda rebels, or Assad?</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378341972362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 20:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378341992792-94</Id><Topic><Title>His own reality: Ted Cruz earns 3 'Pinocchios' in ObamaCare tv ad</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378335066473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why am I not surprised that a Republican Senator would falsely claim support from another Senator who strenuously opposes his position. Sen. Cruz deserves all the Pinocchios that Politico awarded his false and fraudulent commercial.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1378341992792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 20:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378342195959-95</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forget Rand Paul it is leaderless Obama who is not selling the attack to the American people. He has no principles. He's already passing the buck to everyone , but himself, and acts like he's not 100% behind the need to attack...called a spineless socialist.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378342195959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 20:49:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378343038944-96</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John Kerry exposes John Kerry as a fraud, just do a search on all past comments and comentary about going to war or starting hostilities with other countries. Every one of those liberals backing an attack on Syria would not even consider it if Romney or a replublican was President. Thats a fact! Great watching the Nobel Peace Prize winner getting beat up by the European press.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1378343038944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 21:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378344507074-97</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's hippo chrissy kent raven style.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378344507074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 21:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378344586495-98</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does the raven support AQ?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378344586495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 21:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378344619640-99</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378316088748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because he ran out of closet commies and marxists ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1378344619640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 21:30:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378344957709-100</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378316088748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a damn good question that democrats are ashamed to have to answer!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1378344957709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 21:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378345179688-101</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378316088748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If freedom in America is lost to Socialism, you have my permission to blame all the Obama voters AND Hoozdik!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1378345179688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 21:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378345424158-102</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why he's the ideal repugnantcon to run for president! The teabaggers will vote for him in droves and he'll get 30% of the total U.S. vote.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378345424158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 21:43:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378347349494-103</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual, doubledump is campaigning for the D folks again, and doing a fine job. Please keep up the good work, and maybe you should supplement this with a few picket signs. Hillary is guaranteed to win with such "opposition" campaigning from the weird opposition.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1378347349494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 22:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378347812523-104</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good to see the war hero John Kerry talk about how someone other than US troops kill civilians. Don't ever recall him doing that.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1378347812523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 22:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378348242580-105</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry Exposes Rand Paul as a Fraud While Obliterating Him During Syria Hearing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378333938849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 18:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"My answer to Kerry ...." And like 100% of your previous flaccid, worthless "answers," your attempt this time is once again in goonese.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1378348242580</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 22:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378348992760-106</Id><Topic><Title>A Truly Great Phony</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378319394883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 14:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And all the R speakers suddenly have amnesia about the greatest foreign policy blunder in the history of the USA--the Iraq war--dreamed up and carried out by the Bush Crime Family.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1378348992760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 22:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378349696446-107</Id><Title>Obonzo killing Christians</Title><Msg>'Al-Qaida-linked Syria rebels hit Christian village' BEIRUT (AP) — Al-Qaida-linked rebels launched an assault Wednesday on a regime-held Christian village in the densely populated west of Syria and new clashes erupted near the capital, Damascus — part of a brutal battle of attrition each side believes it can win despite more than two years of deadlock. As the world focused on possible U.S. military action against Syria, rebels commandeered a mountaintop hotel in the village of Maaloula and shelled the community below, said a nun, speaking by phone from a convent in the village. She spoke on condition of anonymity for fear of reprisals.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378349696446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 22:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378350063776-108</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Red Line Calculus</Title><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1378349036806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 22:43:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Team bozomeen is blissfully and enthusiastically unaware that something like 188 countries set the red line.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1378350063776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 23:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378350102763-109</Id><Title>al-Qaeda should send Obonzo some human liver to eat</Title><Msg>al-Qaeda leaders being supported by Team Obonzo are cutting open the people they kill and eating their body parts. I'm so proud of Obonzo.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378350102763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 23:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378351064306-110</Id><Topic><Title>Google: "American Military Refusing To Fight For Al-Qaeda In Syria (Pictures)"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378324579589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartaloon calling somebody else wrong . . . another classic. The "Prophesies of Spartaloon" come to mind, specifically Obama would leave office last August.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1378351064306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-04 23:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>