<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360733726064-1</Id><Topic><Title>Post of the Day</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360620626852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:10:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rino republicans?????? you screwball baggers are so full of sh.t I can smell you across the internet</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360733726064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 00:35:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360733887712-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Hit Another Home Run</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360706873242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are a liar</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360733887712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 00:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360737318086-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Hit Another Home Run</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360706873242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Searched the transcript of Obama's speech tonight. Had no desire to watch it. The following words turned up zero results: "ambassador", "Stevens", "Benghazi", "embassy", "lessons learned", and "truth". I guess four dead Americans on his watch, and ostensibly his fault, are not what matters, but Obama insists that "there is much progress to report". Who really believes that?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1360737318086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 01:35:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360740412177-4</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Asks: Should Dorner Be Killed With a Drone Strike?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360670659030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:04:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great idea! According to various liberal estimates, it costs about $1 million to bring a death row inmate to the "death table". Way not "cost effective", goes the anti-death penalty logic. An Obama "judge and executioner" death drone would save money. No trial, no jail time, no death cocktail. No sensational and inconvenient "stories" to distract from the more important Obama Love Festival editorials presented during the 6 PM nightly news. One hundred and seventy-eight child collateral drone deaths and counting, per HuffPo.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1360740412177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 02:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360742293976-5</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, in a way your still right, someone just pointed out a older plane had to shut down 3 of the 4 engines, I looked it up. Nope,a businessman who was on a tight business schdule to meet with the CEO of Boeing about the cheap lithium batteries, started to complain that the flight was late to the destination by an hour due to 3 engines shut down and was complaining that he needed to advise the BA CEO that if they had used the same lithium battery company that the F35 uses then the 787 would probably be flying right now. Then he grabbed a flight employee and complained saying I suppose now the pilot will feather the 4th engi ne and we will be up here all day long. And that employee of Boeing will no doubt, be blamed for the cheap outsourcing battery company that the CEO went with instead of the other French Company that the American taxpayer spent billions of tax payer dollars to get a better lithium batter. PS tha tbatter does not catch fire , it just does not like cold weather so far</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360742293976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 02:58:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360742588703-6</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360597143838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was not checking up on you, just pointing out the failure rate for fire or smoke is the major deal the battery charging problem is most likely a symptom of the route cause. The billions spent on the JSF uses another battery maker and it is lithium seems not to catch fire only does not like to work in cold weather for start up. If the Chicago bean counters were not foucused on cost, but safety of flight, they might have spent a few million more on a provven battery supplier they are both French companies .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360742588703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 03:03:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360758984991-7</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Asks: Should Dorner Be Killed With a Drone Strike?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360670659030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:04:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Bob...they beat us to it. LAPD ordered a WACO style execution yesterday. CNN (CIA) ordered the cameras turned off and cut the live feed...then LAPD was heard to say over the radios "let burn this motherf______"....</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360758984991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360759091588-8</Id><Title>Will Obama take over the Internet via Executive Order this week ?</Title><Msg>Will Obama Take Control of the Internet This Week? Too many Americans waking up and getting the truth ...interferes with the New World Order agenda...somthing has to be done about this. Joe Wolverton, II, J.D. New American Feb 13, 2013 As early as Wednesday, President Obama could issue an executive order granting the federal government expansive and unprecedented power over one of the few remaining outposts of uncensored information — the Internet. Various news agencies are reporting that a cybersecurity executive order has been drafted and will be issued by the president this week. A story on NextWeb indicates that the president will address the issue (and announce the executive order) in Tuesday’s State of the Union address. Bloomberg adds credibility to the speculation, quoting “two former White House officials briefed on the administration’s plans” who corroborate the Wednesday release date for the executive order. The Wall Street Journal reports that unnamed White House officials disclosed that the order will indeed be issued Wednesday and that it “would create a federal-government led group to work with the private sector to create and implement voluntary standards for companies running critical infrastructure. It would also take additional measures to improve information sharing and bolster cybersecurity through current regulatory authorities.” Voluntary is a word — like so many others — that doesn’t have the same meaning in Washington, D.C., as it does in the rest of the country. Given the the federal government’s penchant for vague language, however, it is likely that despite the denial of compulsory cooperation with the government there will be a loophole just large enough to force through a requirement of corporate cooperation with the intelligence agencies of the Obama administration. According to information obtained by The New American, the executive order will resemble in almost every detail a cybersecurity bill that will be introduced to Congress on Wednesday. A d v e r t i s e m e n t That bill, as reported by the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), will empower the “National Security Agency (NSA) and the military to collect your private internet records.” All in the name of national security, of course. The measure that will be offered in the House of Representatives on Wednesday will be nothing less than a resurrection of the Cyber Intelligence Sharing and Protection Act (CISPA), that was passed by the House in April of last year. According to The Hill, House Intelligence Committee Chairman Mike Rogers (R-Mich.) and ranking member Representative Dutch Ruppersberger (D-Md.) will re-introduce an unamended CISPA this week during a speech at the Center for Strategic and International Studies in Washington, D.C. That bill, H.R. 3523, established an exemption to all privacy laws allowing companies to transmit private user/subscriber information with other companies and with the government for the purpose of protecting cybersecurity. In exchange for their compliance with the “voluntary” delivery of users’ private data to the NSA and Department of Homeland Security (DHS), the federal government will shield participating companies for any liability stemming from challenges to the government’s use of the electronic communication of its customers. The AP reported last October that “selected employees at critical infrastructure companies would receive security clearances allowing them to receive the information.” CISPA is yet another example of the cooperation between industry and government that threatens to squeeze the life out of the Constitution and place every actual and virtual activity of every American under the constant surveillance of government. There is a curb on that power, however. CISPA mandates that the government may use the information it obtains only for “lawful purposes,” defined in the bill as preventing anything that could potentially threaten the nation’s national or Internet security. There is no time limit on this power and the only oversight will be an annual audit by the inspector general of the federal intelligence community. Despite these extraordinary and chilling abridgments of the Fourth Amendment, there is broad bipartisan support for CISPA, despite its unpopularity outside the Beltway. As The New American reported after the House passage last year, “Passage in the House was assured with more than 70 percent of those supported by the Tea Party voting for it.” When the measure moved to the Senate it was voted down and President Obama threatened to veto it. That could be, of course, because the White House preferred to set the boundaries of the authority to monitor the traffic on the Internet. President Obama has consistently added one document after another to his bulging dossier of dictatorship. As early as last fall, President Obama began work on the fiat that will, according to a draft of the executive order obtained by the Associated Press, order “U.S. spy agencies to share the latest intelligence about cyberthreats with companies operating electric grids, water plants, railroads and other vital industries to help protect them from electronic attacks.” For some time, government officials have insisted that Iran is planning a cyberattack on the electronic communications infrastructure of the United States. The AP reports that Defense Secretary Leon Panetta said that the U.S. armed forces are “ready to retaliate” should Iran — or any other country — attempt an attack on U.S. cybersecurity. Those reports as well as recent allegations of Chinese cyberattacks against the New York Times, the Wall Street Journal, and theWashington Post, and attacks by Anonymous on the Federal Reserve’s cyberstructure have given the president the threats of a “cyber 9/11” that he needs to justify his issuing of an edict with all the unconstitutional assaults on civil liberty of a “cyber Patriot Act.” President Obama’s administration has been prepping members of Congress for some time on their irrelevance in the upcoming electronic information monitoring scheme. In a hearing held last September before the Senate Committee on Homeland Security and Governmental Affairs, Department of Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano testified that assuming control of the nation’s Internet infrastructure is a DHS responsibility. “DHS is the Federal government’s lead agency for securing civilian government computer systems and works with our industry and Federal, state, local, tribal, and territorial government partners to secure critical infrastructure and information systems,” she informed senators. Napolitano’s report on the role of DHS squares with the information revealed in the seven-page version of the executive order obtained last year by the AP. According to the report of their findings: The draft order would put the Department of Homeland Security in charge of organizing an information-sharing network that rapidly distributes sanitized summaries of top-secret intelligence reports about known cyberthreats that identify a specific target. With these warnings, known as tear lines, the owners and operators of essential U.S. businesses would be better able to block potential attackers from gaining access to their computer systems. The president’s de facto re-routing of all Internet traffic through federal intelligence officers deputizes more than just DHS as cybertraffic cops. The AP reports that “the Pentagon, the National Security Agency (NSA), the director of national intelligence, and the Justice Department” will all cooperate in the surveillance — again, the same agencies whose powers were either created or expanded in the Patriot Act. Despite the anticipated similarities between CISPA, the Patriot Act, and President Obama’s forthcoming cybersecurity executive order, there is one very significant difference. Legislation can be repealed. Constituents can unite and threaten the reelection hopes of lawmakers who vote for such a bill. An executive order, on the other hand, is unassailable, and the president — particularly one in his final term — is beyond accountability for the edicts he hands down and for the irreparable harm they might do to civil liberties and to the Constitution that protects them.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360759091588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:38:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360759433539-9</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you suggsting that Barrack Hussein Obama really ISN'T funding and arming AlQaeda in Libya and Syria..ok..you wont here it on CIA run CNN...but ALL OVER THE INTERNET FROM HUNDREDS OF SOURCES ? are they all lying...here is yet ANOTHER source just came out yesterday...I just have to keep beating you up with the truth..ad hominems are not required. Hypocrisy: US Arms Al Qaeda in Syria, Mass-Slaughters Civilians in Afghanistan AFP has reported that a recent NATO airstrike in Afghanistan has killed over 10 civilians in an all-too-familiar headline glossed over by the Western media in an exercise of both depravity and hypocrisy. RT’s article, “NATO airstrike kills 10 Afghan civilians, mostly women and children – officials,” notes in particular that up to 11,864 civilians were killed in Afghanistan between 2007 and 2011, and that civilian deaths before 2007 were not even tracked by the UN. Such facts reveal alarming hypocrisy as the UN keeps almost daily, inflated tallies of civilian deaths elsewhere, in particular, in nations like Libya and Syria where Western interests have been heavily involved in regime change and in dire need of manipulating public perception worldwide. The United Nations had in fact pieced together a dubious report crafted from “witness accounts” compiled not in Syria, or even beyond its borders in a refugee camp, but instead, in Geneva by “witnesses” supplied by the so-called Syrian “opposition.” Image: Just some of the corporate members of the US-Qatar Business Council, whose president just so happens to sit on the same board of directors of the Middle East Policy Center as Karen AbuZayd, co-author of one of many conveniently timed UN Human Rights Council reports on Syria. …. Worse yet, that UN report was co-authored by Karen Koning AbuZayd, a director of the US Washington-based corporate think-tank, Middle East Policy Council. Its board of directors includes Exxon men, CIA agents, representatives of the Saudi Binladin Group (Osama Bin Laden’s family business), former ambassadors to Kuwait, Oman, and Qatar, US military and government representatives, and even the president of the US-Qatar Business Council, which includes amongst its membership, Al Jazeera, Chevron, Exxon, munitions manufacturer Raytheon (who supplied the opening salvos during NATO’s operations against Libya), and Boeing. In other words, the very underwriters of the armed militancy that is consuming Syria are sitting along side the head of the UN commission producing reports portraying the Syrian government as guilty of “war crimes and crimes against humanity. The hypocrisy does not end there. The pretense the US and NATO have used for over a decade to occupy, subjugate and slaughter the people of Afghanistan – in a conflict increasingly creeping over both Afghanistan’s borders with Pakistan and Iran – is supposedly to fight “terrorism.” Western interests have been allowed to fight this “war on terrorism” with impunity, and even without UN monitoring for years, while Syria was immediately condemned for fighting against Al Qaeda terrorists overtly flooding into their nation with NATO assistance. Indeed, as NATO claims to fight terrorism in Afghanistan, it has already handed over the North African nation of Libya to Al Qaeda terrorists, specifically the the US State Department, United Nations, and the UK Home Office (page 5, .pdf)-listed terrorist organization, the Libyan Islamic Fighting Group (LIFG). The US in particular oversaw the rise of the Al Qaeda terror-emirate Benghazi, even having a US ambassador slain there by the very terrorists it had armed, funded, trained, provided air support for, and thrust into power. These same terrorists have been documented extensively as spearheading the invasion of northern Syria via NATO-member Turkey, with NATO cash and weapons in cooperation with Saudi Arabia and Qatar. The glaring hypocrisy of so-called “international law” and “international institutions” is on full display. Nations like Russia, China, Iran, India, Pakistan, Indonesia, Brazil, and many others should give serious thought to peeling away from the United Nations, the compromised International Criminal Court, and other corrupt, Western-serving institutions that will, and in many cases already are, being turned against them, their interests, and national sovereignty.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360759433539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:43:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360759972971-10</Id><Title>WHILE YOU WERE SLEEPING</Title><Msg>THEY CAME AND TOOK IT ALL AWAY While you were sleeping They came and took it all away The lanes and the meadows The places where you used to play It was an inside job By the well-connected Your little protest Summarily rejected It was an inside job Like it always is Chalk it up to business as usual While we are dreaming This little island disappears While you are looking the other way They'll take your right to own your own ideas And it's an inside job Favors collected Your trusted servants Have left you unprotected It was an inside job Like it always is Just chalk it up To business as usual You think that you're so smart But you don't have a f____ing clue What those men up in the towers Are doing to me and you And they'll keep doin' it and doin' it And doin' it and doin' it And doin' it and doin' it And doin' it and doin' it Until we all wake up Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up I know what I've done wrong I am acquainted with the night I know how hard it is To always walk out in the light And it's an inside job To learn about forgiving It's an inside job To hang on to the joy of living They know the road by which you came They know your mother's maiden name And what you had for breakfast And what you've hidden in the mattress Insect politics Indifferent universe Bang your head against the wall But apathy is worse It's an inside job It's an inside job It's an inside job Yeh, yeah It's an inside job It's an inside job It's an inside job It's an inside job It's an inside job It's an inside job DON HENLEY</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360759972971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:52:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360760712087-11</Id><Title>Progress report up date on 787 progress post !</Title><Msg>Please correct me if I am wrong but BA has made zero progress in a month. This plane has other issues like dumping 15 gallons of gas on the runway. If there is an Ace in the back pocket let me know.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360760712087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360760745104-12</Id><Topic><Title>BULLISH</Title><Username>nanceedacosta1367</Username><Timestamp>1323310999000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-12-07 21:23:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined too.</Msg><Username>edwardantony835</Username><Timestamp>1360760745104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:05:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360763867473-13</Id><Title>Dorner dead</Title><Msg>Nobody was going to get the million $$ revard for Dorner's capture, and prosecution. Not a cop killer. You, or me quite likely, but a cop killer comes back in a bag. And Dorner knew that. Great sign made in Weat Virginia for those entering the state...WECLOME TO WEST VIRGINIA. Bullet points...our citizens are armed. Bullet point..If you kill one of us, we will kill you. Bullet point. We have no jails, and we have 519 cemetaries. Have a good stay.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360763867473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:57:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360764512052-14</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Striking seeing Drymouth Marco's non-responsive lying speech follow the President's methodical outline of his program, his policies, and what he will passionately pursue by appealing to the people. Everything Drymouth Marco said sounded like the rehashed, warmed over repub primary debate talking points of 2012 ... backward thinking, backward looking, and frankly dumb. When will the repubs and their virulent bagger followers get that future American voters are about to leave them in the dust if they persist in living in some fantasy past?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360764512052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:08:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360765795740-15</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio Has Learned Nothing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360765033609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:17:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now the commie attacks start coming from the left. Want to know who the commies are threatened by?....easy, follow who they attack. Rubio is a huge threat because of his silver tongue, willingness to go on the attack exposing libtards, and has a proven, hardworking successful background. And it doesn't hurt that he is a minority.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360765795740</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:29:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360767037555-16</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio Has Learned Nothing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360765033609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:17:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And it doesn't hurt that he is a minority." In his case, it won't help either.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1360767037555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:50:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360767311090-17</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Quite the grand slam." You're right; terrific speech.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1360767311090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 09:55:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360767802163-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Bombs - Marco Rubio Hits Grand Slam</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360763573321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:52:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Evenly divided focus groups preferred Rubio's message over Obama.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360767802163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:03:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360767908853-19</Id><Topic><Title>WHILE YOU WERE SLEEPING</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360759972971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:52:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember when you ran away and I got on my knees and begged you not to leave because I'd go berserk?? Well... You left me anyhow and then the days got worse and worse and now you see I've gone completely out of my mind.. And.. They're coming to take me away, ha-haaa!! They're coming to take me away, ho-ho, hee-hee, ha-haaa To the funny farm. Where life is beautiful all the time and I'll be happy to see those nice young men in their clean white coats and they're coming to take me away, ha-haaa!!!!! You thought it was a joke and so you laughed, you laughed when I had said that loosing you would make me flip my lid.. RIGHT??? I know you laughed, I heard you laugh, you laughed you laughed and laughed and then you left, but now you know I'm utterly mad... And.. They're coming to take me away, ha-haaa, They're coming to take me away, ho-ho, hee-hee, ha-haaa. To the happy home. With trees and flowers and chirping birds and basket weavers who sit and smile and twiddle their thumbs and toes and they're coming to take me away, ha-haaa!!! I cooked your food, I cleaned your house, and this is how you pay me back for all my kind unselfish loving deeds.. Huh?? Well you just wait, they'll find you yet and when they do they'll put you in the ASPCA, you mangy mutt!!! And... They're coming to take me away, ha-haaa. They're coming to take me away, ho-ho, hee-hee, ha-haaa. To the funny farm, where life is beautiful all the time and I'll be happy to see those nice young men in their clean white coats and they're coming to take me away, ha-haaa!!! To the happy home, with trees and flowers and chirping birds and basket weavers who sit and smile and twiddle their thumbs and toes and they're coming to take me away, ha-haa!!! To the funny farm, where life is beautiful all the time... (fade out) Hey, buddy! Yes officer.. You a head? No, but I'm catching up, ha ha ha.... original recording by Napoleon XIV</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360767908853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:05:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360767928643-20</Id><Title>UN regulators looking to ban airplane battery transportation</Title><Msg>A U.N. agency that sets global aviation safety standards is moving to prevent aircraft batteries like the one that caught fire on a Boeing 787 last month from being shipped as cargo on passenger planes, people familiar with the effort said. Over the past few days, the members of the International Civil Aviation Organization's dangerous goods committee have proposed revoking an exemption that permitted lithium ion aircraft batteries as heavy as 77 pounds to be shipped on passenger planes, the sources told The Associated Press. All other lithium ion battery shipments on passenger planes are limited to 11 pounds or less because of the batteries' susceptibility to short-circuit and ignite. The head of the agency's air navigation commission has signed off on the proposal, the sources said. Late Monday, agency officials were trying to reach the agency's council president, who was traveling, for his signature, which they hoped to secure Tuesday. As soon as the council president signs off on the change, it will be posted online and become effective immediately, those familiar with the situation said. They requested anonymity because they weren't authorized to speak publicly. The agency's standards aren't binding, but are widely followed by countries around the world. The exemption for aircraft batteries, which was sought by the airline industry, has been in effect for less than two months. Airlines wanted to be able to ship replacement batteries quickly to planes whose batteries were depleted or had failed rather than wait for a cargo plane. The Federal Aviation Administration and aviation authorities in other countries grounded the 787 fleet more than three weeks ago after a battery caught fire in a plane parked in Boston and another 787 with a smoking battery made an emergency landing in Japan. The 787, dubbed the Dreamliner by Boeing, is the first airliner to make extensive use of lithium ion batteries, which are lighter weight, charge faster and contain more energy than conventional batteries similar in size. The 787 has two lithium ion batteries weighing 63 pounds each. The same day as the Boston fire, the Transportation Department published new regulations adopting the U.N. exemption to allow lithium ion aircraft battery shipments greater than 11 pounds on passenger planes.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360767928643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:05:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768027383-21</Id><Topic><Title>.Batteries for 787 Can’t Be Shipped on Passenger Planes</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360715915490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:38:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your right</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360768027383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:07:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768147216-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Bombs - Marco Rubio Hits Grand Slam</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360763573321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:52:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rubio should be ashamed of himself. He knows its not a level playing field he is on. He kicks Obama's #$%$ because he has the facts vs. Obama's socilaist lies. Rubio should be made to tie one hand, and half his brain behind his back to even things up.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360768147216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:09:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768272767-23</Id><Topic><Title>So is BA losing 100 million a day, 200 million a day or $300 million</Title><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360625390901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:29:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA has to break below 75.32 and hold below for at least two weeks for much to happen on the down side . boeing is a dead cat bouce stock no long no short a nothing stock too much cap to do much</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360768272767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:11:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768377433-24</Id><Topic><Title>Progress report up date on 787 progress post !</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360760712087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:05:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still nothing. I wlll be back to report on "nothing" by COB.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360768377433</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:12:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360768601157-25</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360597143838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as you know the UN is making an effort to ban the use of aircraft to move replacement batteries and that will make it difficult to use the lithium battery in any airplane, maybe kill the battery in a moe that takes out the investigation and makes the battery a non issue. That will take the 787 a long time to plan, design and get an approval as well as change the customer cost of flight, heavy means more cost to operate the 787</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360768601157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:16:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360769102871-26</Id><Topic><Title>How many lies will Obama tell tonight?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717362518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:02:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>had to adjust for the Uhhhhhhhhhs and biden jumping up and down</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360769102871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:25:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360769406387-27</Id><Topic><Title>We go ex dividend tomorrow...not much selling today !</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360676534433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You were on the right track. $ 481/2 cents. The dividend is payable March 8, 2013, to shareholders of record as of Feb. 15, 2013. I had not read the company announcement.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360769406387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360769688717-28</Id><Title>Boeing and Pension myths</Title><Msg>.from the annual report Boeing claims poor poor poor - hose the employees ( SPEEA and IAM )- they already hosed the rest ..At December 31, 2012 and 2011, our pension plans were $19.7 billion and $16.6 billion underfunded as measured under GAAP. ****On an ERISA basis our plans are more than 100% funded at December 31, 2012 with minimal required contributions in 2013. *****We expect to make discretionary contributions to our plans of approximately $1.5 billion in 2013. We may be required to make higher contributions to our pension plans in future years... ++ Under ERISA accounting there are some interesting goodies and baddies 1) maximum surplus ( over 100 percent ) is about 120 to 150 percent- after which NO tax deductions allowed 2) ERISA counted surplus - ON PAPER - can be directly transferred into OPERATING EARNINGS - BUT no real $$ are involved 3) Smoothing of ERISA minimums and maximums over bucu years is allowed to avoid direct relationship to market issues So why would BA - with 100 percent ERISA funding want to make discretionary deposits ?? Answer- read above about SURPLUS- its like a tax free piggy bank- allowing tax free money to go into earnings ! Increased earnings make for Bone-yous to top executives. So when the going gets tough - the execs get more !! For other info and the annual report search on pensions BA terminated NS&amp;S (space) pensions and gained a mere 30 plus million.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360769688717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:34:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360769846737-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Bombs - Marco Rubio Hits Grand Slam</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360763573321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:52:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Rubio is going to save the republican party? NOT!! The guy can't even give a speech. The poor republicans. They better find someone to lead them who's not an idiot. Seems simple enough but I bet they can't do it.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360769846737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:37:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360770484503-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Bombs - Marco Rubio Hits Grand Slam</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360763573321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:52:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Pope resigned for the good of the Church....San Fran Nan and Prince Harry should do the same!</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1360770484503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:48:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360771035544-31</Id><Title>Medal of Honor winner turns down invite to State of the Union</Title><Msg>A man who understands the meaning of Honor Medal of Honor winner turns down invite to State of the Union By Emily Goodin - 02/12/13 12:52 PM ET Former Army staff sergeant Clint Romesha, who was awarded the Medal of Honor at the White House on Monday, has declined the first lady's invitation to sit in her box on Tuesday night during the State of the Union address.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360771035544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:57:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360771168638-32</Id><Topic><Title>WHILE YOU WERE SLEEPING</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360759972971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:52:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cointelpro</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360771168638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:59:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360771254509-33</Id><Title>Even Democrats like Marco Rubio Better</Title><Msg>.....who could blame them?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360771254509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:00:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360771633298-34</Id><Title>FACT CHECK: Obama's State of the Union Whoppers</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — President Barack Obama did some cherry-picking Tuesday night in defense of his record on jobs and laid out a conditional path to citizenship for illegal immigrants that may be less onerous than he made it sound. A look at some of the claims in his State of the Union speech, a glance at the Republican counterargument and how they fit with the facts: OBAMA: "After years of grueling recession, our businesses have created over 6 million new jobs." THE FACTS: That's in the ballpark, as far as it goes. But Obama starts his count not when he took office, but from the point in his first term when job losses were the highest. In doing so, he ignores the 5 million or so jobs that were lost on his watch, up to that point. Private sector jobs have grown by 6.1 million since February 2010. But since he became president, the gain is a more modest 1.9 million. And when losses in public sector employment are added to the mix, his overall jobs record is a gain of 1.2 million. ___ OBAMA: "We have doubled the distance our cars will go on a gallon of gas." THE FACTS: Not so fast. That's expected to happen in 12 more years. Under a deal the Obama administration reached with automakers in 2011, vehicles will have a corporate average fuel economy of 54.5 miles per gallon by 2025, twice the 27 miles per gallon, on average, that cars and trucks get today. Automobile manufacturers won't start making changes to achieve the new fuel economy standards until model year 2017. Not all cars will double their gas mileage, since the standard is based on an average of a manufacturers' fleet. ___ OBAMA: "Already the Affordable Care Act is helping to reduce the growth of health care costs." THE FACTS: The jury is still out on whether Obama's health care overhaul will reduce the growth of health care costs. It's true that cost increases have eased, but many experts say that's due to the sluggish economy, not to the health care law, whose main provisions are not yet fully in effect. ___ OBAMA: "Real reform means establishing a responsible pathway to earned citizenship — a path that includes passing a background check, paying taxes and a meaningful penalty, learning English and going to the back of the line behind the folks trying to come here legally." THE FACTS: The seemingly stern admonition that illegal immigrants must go to the back of the line, often heard from the president, doesn't appear to have much practical effect except in the most obvious sense. Everyone who joins a line, whether for a movie, a coffee or citizenship, starts at the back of that particular line. It's not clear he is saying anything more than that illegal immigrants won't get to cut in line for citizenship once they've obtained provisional legal status. Like those living abroad who have applied to come to the U.S. legally, illegal immigrants who qualify for Obama's proposed path to citizenship will surely face long waits to be processed. But during that time, they are already in the U.S. and will get to stay, work and travel in the country under their new status as provisional immigrants, while those outside the U.S. simply have to wait. Sending illegal immigrants to the "back of the line" is something of a distinction without a difference for some legal immigrants who dutifully followed all the rules before coming to the United States. For instance, some legal immigrants who are in the U.S. on an employer-sponsored visa can't easily change jobs, or in some cases take a promotion, without jeopardizing their place in line to get a green card. In other cases, would-be legal immigrants in other countries wait for years to be able to settle in the U.S. Obama is using "back of the line" somewhat figuratively, because there are multiple lines depending on the applicant's relationship with family already in the U.S. or with an employer. Generally, a foreign-born spouse of a U.S. citizen or someone with needed skills and a job offer will be accepted more quickly than many others. But even as a figurative point, his assertion may cloak the fact that people who came to the U.S. illegally and win provisional status have the great advantage over applicants abroad of already being where they all want to go. ___ OBAMA: "Study after study shows that the sooner a child begins learning, the better he or she does down the road. ... And for poor kids who need help the most, this lack of access to preschool education can shadow them for the rest of their lives. ... Every dollar we invest in high-quality early education can save more than $7 later on — by boosting graduation rates, reducing teen pregnancy, even reducing violent crime." THE FACTS: Dozens of studies have shown Head Start graduates are more likely to complete high school than their at-risk peers who don't participate in the program. But a study last year by the Department of Health and Human Services that found big vocabulary and social development gains for at-risk students in pre-kindergarten programs also found those effects largely faded by the time pupils reached third grade. The report didn't explain why the kids saw a drop-off in performance or predict how they would fare as they aged. ___ OBAMA: "I urge this Congress to pursue a bipartisan, market-based solution to climate change, like the one John McCain and Joe Lieberman worked on together a few years ago. But if Congress won't act soon to protect future generations, I will. I will direct my Cabinet to come up with executive actions we can take, now and in the future, to reduce pollution, prepare our communities for the consequences of climate change and speed the transition to more sustainable sources of energy." THE FACTS: Obama failed to get a global warming bill through Congress when both Houses were controlled by Democrats in 2010. With Republicans in control of the House, the chances of a bill to limit the gases blamed for global warming and to create a market for businesses to trade pollution credits are close to zero. The Obama administration has already acted to control greenhouse gases through existing law. It has boosted fuel-efficiency standards and proposed rules to control heat-trapping emissions from new power plants. And while there are still other ways to address climate change without Congress, it's questionable regulation alone can achieve the reductions needed to start curbing global warming. ___ FLORIDA SEN. MARCO RUBIO, in the Republican response: "The real cause of our debt is that our government has been spending $1 trillion more than it takes in every year. That's why we need a balanced-budget amendment." THE FACTS: That statement may reflect the math behind recent debt, but it doesn't get directly to the cause — the worst recession since the Depression and its aftereffects. The deficit is not only caused by spending, but by reduced tax revenues. And during the recession, revenues from both individual and corporate taxes fell markedly. The steep increases in debt and the measures that should be taken to ease the burden are central to the debate in Washington. But there is no serious move afoot to amend the Constitution to prohibit deficit spending. The ability to take on debt has been used by governments worldwide and through U.S. history to shelter people from the ravages of a down economy, wage war and achieve many other ends. An effort to amend the Constitution for any purpose faces daunting odds; this would be no exception. Most state constitutions demand a balanced budget, but states lack some big obligations of the federal government, including national defense. And Washington's ability to go deeper into debt provides states with at least a minimal safety net in times of high unemployment. ___ Associated Press writers Tom Raum, Dina Cappiello, Andrew Taylor, Christopher S. Rugaber, Ricardo Alonso-Zaldivar, Alicia A. Caldwell and Philip Elliott contributed to this report.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360771633298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:07:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360771767321-35</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obama Promise more welfare, unemployment, food stamps and disability checks....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717509170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:05:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, he will. That's the base of his political power. As long as those checks keep going out the Dems can win elections. They aren't going to let go of that.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360771767321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360771848287-36</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Hate America so Much?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360704612729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we never see another header that starts with the word why it will be too soon.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360771848287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:10:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360772328065-37</Id><Title>Dr. Ben Carson: "You've got to realize that you're the president of everybody."</Title><Msg>Obama needs to realize he's the president of all Americans, lower class, middle class and upper class and work for the betterment of all people. He needs to quit pitting one class against another.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360772328065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:18:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360772438509-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Hate America so Much?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360704612729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you believe in Science? Evolution? Global Warming? Guns really do kill people? Woman's right to choose? Equal pay? Carried is earned income? there were no WMD in Iraq? I can go on and on!!! Republican party is indeed the party of STUPID as Gov. Bobby Jindal said!!</Msg><Username>fountain123_45</Username><Timestamp>1360772438509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360772956527-39</Id><Title>Obama's Minimum Wage Folly Shows His Ignorance of Basic Economics</Title><Msg>If Obama really believes raising the minimum wage really helps poor people, why is he such a cheap bast*rd? How can a family of four live on $9 an hour? Why not raise it to $50 an hour or make it mandatory to be exactly the same as the highest paid union wage? Why not tell Hatti and Somalia they can solve their poverty problem by simply raising the minimum wage? Waiting for liberal name calling to substitute for an inability to answer these questions.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360772956527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:29:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360773161341-40</Id><Topic><Title>Comment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360772584735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's Keith Olbermann?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360773161341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:32:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360773484696-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Minimum Wage Folly Shows His Ignorance of Basic Economics</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360772956527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:29:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another example of how destructive, and ignorant liberals are. Entre' level jobs are improtant for many folks entering the work force in the way of training, and teaching responsibility. Many a successful person can point to a entre level job as what propelled them up the pay scale ladder. Having big govt mandate minimum wage rather than economic forces, supply/demand dictate minimum wage creates more unemployment, creates inflation, as then everyone elses wages have to move up to compensate, Products reflect the added cost, and they go up. Minimum wage hurts poor people that need a job. Just another example of the unintended consequences of liberalism.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360773484696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:38:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360773888846-42</Id><Title>737 order</Title><Msg>REYKJAVIK, Iceland, Feb. 13, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] and Icelandair announced a firm order today for 16 737 MAX airplanes, valued at more than $1.6 billion at list prices. The order, originally announced as a commitment for 12 airplanes in December 2012, has been increased to 16 airplanes and includes 737 MAX 8s and 9s, as well as purchase rights for eight additional 737 MAXs. Today's announcement brings the total number of 737 MAXs ordered to date to 1,180.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360773888846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360773991955-43</Id><Topic><Title>Comment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360772584735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was this another bathtub tantrum for Olberwomann?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360773991955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:46:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360774333157-44</Id><Title>787 problems</Title><Msg>Could it be that the us government thinks that if boeing is outsourcing there airplane out of the country,well let the outsourcees solve the problems ?</Msg><Username>wharestheprofit</Username><Timestamp>1360774333157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:52:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360774486501-45</Id><Title>Obama: 57 Vacation Days Since Vowing He 'Will Not Rest .....</Title><Msg>....Until Anyone' Can Find A GOOD Job.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360774486501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:54:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360774822962-46</Id><Title>Sen. Coburn: Sequestration will happen</Title><Msg>And this is from a top ranking Republican. If you think BA stock drops when 787 announcement hits that the plane could be grounded for month, you ain't seen nothing compared to what happens to BA stock if sequestration kicks in. We're talking major blood bath for BA longs. The government may have averted sequestration in December, but it won’t avoid it for long, according to Sen. Tom Coburn, R-Okla. “We’re gonna have a sequestration. we’re gonna have some pain because the politicians on the Hill aren’t going to make cogent, smart decisions about alternatives to this until they start feeling some pain,” Coburn said on Wednesday’s Morning Joe.</Msg><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1360774822962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:00:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360774882982-47</Id><Topic><Title>Medal of Honor winner turns down invite to State of the Union</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360771035544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360774882982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:01:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360775001294-48</Id><Topic><Title>Medal of Honor winner turns down invite to State of the Union</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360771035544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So they got Cook (The Apple CEO) as a quick back up? So that's why Apple stock was tanking yesterday?</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1360775001294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:03:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360775235207-49</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Coburn: Sequestration will happen</Title><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1360774822962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heading into month two regarding BA major Dreamliner problems and the silence coming from Senior Management is stifling. Airbus must be licking their chops thinking of the major delays the 787 is going to have and financial setbacks with huge delayed shipment penalty fees, cost overruns, pushed back 787 delivery dates and potential lawsuits for hiding faulty battery related data from FAA. Where there is smoke there is fire and right now BA is one big dark smoke cloud.</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1360775235207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:07:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360775871396-50</Id><Title>ULA 2nd launch atlas V</Title><Msg>The United Launch Alliance, a joint venture between Boeing (NYSE: BA ) and Lockheed Martin (NYSE: LMT ) , announced in a press statement Monday that it successfully launched an Atlas V rocket carrying a NASA Landsat Data Continuity Mission (LDCM) load. The Monday launch marked the second Atlas V rocket launch in just 12 days and the second this year. The ULA has another scheduled Atlas V launch coming up next month, when one of its rockets is scheduled to take off March 19 from Cape Canaveral with a missile-warning satellite payload from the U.S. Air Force.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360775871396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:17:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360775923289-51</Id><Title>Is there a timely solution to battery problem?</Title><Msg>I have serious doubts as to whether there is a timely solution for Boeing to their battery problem. Batteries are dangerous as we all have probably experienced personally (acid leaking in flashlight batteries and elsewhere, my apple laptop lithium battery almost exploding - it expanded by a good 3/8 to 1/2 inches while in the laptop one day). And of course the airlines' recent experience with the 787 batteries. 1. How does one know whether a battery has dendrites forming inside that could short circuit the battery? How does one inspect for this without ripping the battery apart and destroying it? 2. Dendrites can form at ANY time, or maybe they even may form all the time - except that they do not always grow enough to cause a short circuit. If that is the case, how can one have a fail safe lithium battery on a plane? Sure, you could design a system to electrically isolate a short-circuited battery, but who wants ANY such battery on a plane. There is no way that the FAA will let Boeing put batteries on a plane that have the potential to catch fire, even if they can be isolated. What then if the isolation system fails. Or what if the battery fails massively and catches fire in an instant even though the isolation system took the battery off the power grid. If dendrites form all the time in a battery, one is asking for serious serious trouble. That means any and every battery could go haywire at any time. Some could just heat up a bit. Some could simply explode. 3. It takes a long time for dendrites to form in the battery. So, if that is the case, how do your "test" a battery. If it takes a battery months or years to develop the problem, for how many months and years do you have to look at at reasonable sample of batteries to figure out the exact problem and solution. And every time you look inside the battery, you destroy it making it useless for further ongoing observation and testing. You would probably have to test a huge number of batteries, maybe more than one thousand. And they would all have to be testing in active flights! How is that going to happen? 4. Even if a reasonable solution for battery isolation or change were found, it is going to have to be tested to an enormous level of detail. This probably means tons of test flights - and I do not mean 50 to 100. 5. Maybe Boeing has to use a different non-lithium battery or redesign the whole electrical plant on the plane. That will take a huge amount of time and also new testing. Given the situation, any new testing will be lengthy and rigorous - which means extensive delays in the 787 delivery schedule, delivery penalties, cancelled orders, etc. I just do not see any good way out of this for Boeing. I bet my bottom dollar that Boeing , in addition to doing current investigative work, has engineers dusting off either prior battery/electrical plant designs or are working on completely new system - in case a full redesign is required.</Msg><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1360775923289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:18:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360776311656-52</Id><Topic><Title>Is there a timely solution to battery problem?</Title><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1360775923289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:18:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't you think by now BA would announce "a walk through plan" to correct this very serious electrical/battery problem. Its as if BA management is no closer to a solution today, then they were four weeks ago. The longer things go with silence from BA senior officials the more likely the 787 will be grounded for most of 2013.</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1360776311656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:25:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360776512972-53</Id><Topic><Title>Is there a timely solution to battery problem?</Title><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1360775923289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:18:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A buying opportunity awaits.</Msg><Username>okatiejack</Username><Timestamp>1360776512972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:28:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360776622974-54</Id><Topic><Title>Is there a timely solution to battery problem?</Title><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1360775923289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:18:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dendritres my balls! What planet are you from?</Msg><Username>stokby</Username><Timestamp>1360776622974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:30:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360776677092-55</Id><Topic><Title>Is there a timely solution to battery problem?</Title><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1360775923289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:18:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea - for "SHORTS" or maybe folks that want to go long Airbus.</Msg><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1360776677092</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:31:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360776785841-56</Id><Title>I and R folks rated Obama a minus 100% for climate remarks on Bing Pulse</Title><Msg>D folks, except for green socialists, weren't all that impressed either. It must be because everyone remembers that when Obama had total Dem control of congress, he wasn't interested in climate. He might have mention climate a couple of times on his weekly radio address over four years but it was clearly not a priority for him even though NASA scientist James Hansen warned him that if he didn't do something in his first term it would be too late. Tomorrow the socialist greens in the Dem Party along with socialist Bernie Sanders will introduce a carbon tax. The phony outrage and theatrics by green socialists should be hilarious entertainment to watch on C Span.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360776785841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:33:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360776815589-57</Id><Topic><Title>Dorner dead</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360763867473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 08:57:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reward for Dorner is $1.2 million. It was contributed by about 6 different groups, each of which had somewhat different rules for payout. Seems like none of the rules were contingent upon being captured alive. Officials were sorting out the rules even before contact was called in by the cleaning lady near Big Bear.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360776815589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:33:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360776906596-58</Id><Title>How Many Years Late Will the 737 Max Be</Title><Msg>After the 787 fiasco and the 747-8 fumble#$%$, what do you think the odds are Boeing will screw up the new 737 ???? I give it 50 / 50 chance...especially if McNinney is still mismanaging this abortion.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1360776906596</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:35:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360777116270-59</Id><Topic><Title>Medal of Honor winner turns down invite to State of the Union</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360771035544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would have sat with her. I would love to ask her how she likes being Barry's "First Beard". lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360777116270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:38:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360778963556-60</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obama take over the Internet via Executive Order this week ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360759091588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:38:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you cut-and-pasted that article, you forgot to edit out "A d v e r t i s e m e n t" in the middle.</Msg><Username>dkmax</Username><Timestamp>1360778963556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:09:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360779275060-61</Id><Title>Side-By-Side Comparison of How Obama, Rubio, &amp; Paul View the State of the Union</Title><Msg>The Economy: Obama: [W]e gather here knowing that there are millions of Americans whose hard work and dedication have not yet been rewarded. Our economy is adding jobs – but too many people still can’t find full-time employment. Corporate profits have rocketed to all-time highs – but for more than a decade, wages and incomes have barely budged. Most Americans — Democrats, Republicans, and Independents — understand that we can’t just cut our way to prosperity. They know that broad-based economic growth requires a balanced approach to deficit reduction, with spending cuts and revenue, and with everybody doing their fair share. Rubio: Unfortunately, our economy actually shrank during the last three months of 2012. But if we can get the economy to grow at just 4 percent a year, it would create millions of middle class jobs. And it could reduce our deficits by almost $4 trillion dollars over the next decade. Tax increases can’t do this. Raising taxes won’t create private sector jobs. And there’s no realistic tax increase that could lower our deficits by almost $4 trillion. That’s why I hope the President will abandon his obsession with raising taxes and instead work with us to achieve real growth in our economy. Paul: Under the Obama economy, 12 million people are out of work. During the President’s first term 800,000 construction workers lost their jobs and another 800,000 simply gave up on looking for work. [...] Under President Obama, the ranks of America’s poor swelled to almost 1 in 6 people last year, reaching a new high as long-term unemployment left millions of Americans struggling and out of work. [...] With my five-year budget, millions of jobs would be created by cutting the corporate income tax in half, by creating a flat personal income tax of 17%, and by cutting the regulations that are strangling American businesses. National Debt: Obama: Obama: [T]he time has come to pass comprehensive immigration reform. […] Real reform means establishing a responsible pathway to earned citizenship – a path that includes passing a background check, paying taxes and a meaningful penalty, learning English, and going to the back of the line behind the folks trying to come here legally. And real reform means fixing the legal immigration system to cut waiting periods, reduce bureaucracy, and attract the highly-skilled entrepreneurs and engineers that will help create jobs and grow our economy. Rubio: We can also help our economy grow if we have a legal immigration system that allows us to attract and assimilate the world’s best and brightest. We need a responsible, permanent solution to the problem of those who are here illegally. But first, we must follow through on the broken promises of the past to secure our borders and enforce our laws. Paul: We are the party that embraces hard work and ingenuity, therefore we must be the party that embraces the immigrant who wants to come to America for a better future. We must be the party who sees immigrants as assets, not liabilities. We must be the party that says, “If you want to work, if you want to become an American, we welcome you.” [T]he biggest driver of our long-term debt is the rising cost of health care for an aging population. And those of us who care deeply about programs like Medicare must embrace the need for modest reforms – otherwise, our retirement programs will crowd out the investments we need for our children, and jeopardize the promise of a secure retirement for future generations. Rubio: The real cause of our debt is that our government has been spending 1 trillion dollars more than it takes in every year. That’s why we need a balanced budget amendment. The biggest obstacles to balancing the budget are programs where spending is already locked in. One of these programs, Medicare, is especially important to me. It provided my father the care he needed to battle cancer and ultimately die with dignity. And it pays for the care my mother receives now. I would never support any changes to Medicare that would hurt seniors like my mother. But anyone who is in favor of leaving Medicare exactly the way it is right now, is in favor of bankrupting it. Paul: Over the past four years [President Obama] has added over $6 trillion in new debt and may well do the same in a second term. What solutions does he offer? He takes entitlement reform off the table and seeks to squeeze more money out of the private sector. [...] This massive expansion of the debt destroys savings and steals the value of your wages. Big government makes it more expensive to put food on the table. Big government is not your friend. The President offers you free stuff but his policies keep you poor. [...] Both parties have been guilty of spending too much, of protecting their sacred cows, of backroom deals in which everyone up here wins, but every taxpayer loses. It is time for a new bipartisan consensus. It is time Democrats admit that not every dollar spent on domestic programs is sacred. And it is time Republicans realize that military spending is not immune to waste and fraud. Where would we cut spending; well, we could start with ending all foreign aid to countries that are burning our flag and chanting death to America. Immigration:</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1360779275060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:14:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360779705294-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Hate America so Much?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360704612729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Small minded Liberals down understand the economics of goods and services in small business and how it can reflect on a profit oriented business. They believe that since you're a business owner you must be filthy rich and can afford to pay medical insurance and high wages to an uneducated working force who flip burgers. They do not grasp the concept of overhead and how that effects ones profit margins. The ability to make a profit is the main reason of establishing a business.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360779705294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:21:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360780375022-63</Id><Title>Moody's: Prolonged 787 Review Is Credit Negative for Boeing</Title><Msg>The longer the plane is grounded, the greater the risk of the company's 2013 cash flow meaningfully declining," Moody's said in a report issued Monday. "Boeing is unable to collect what amounts to several hundred million dollars of cash remittances from its airline customers every month that it cannot deliver planes." Additionally, Boeing spends an estimated $750 million to $1 billion a month to produce five 787s a month that are not being delivered, the rating agency said.</Msg><Username>try2try</Username><Timestamp>1360780375022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:32:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360780537083-64</Id><Topic><Title>It Doesn't Matter - We Still Love Obama</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360694796598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:46:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes we now know from leaked memos that Obama is the most abusive president in history with respect to privacy rights and human rights but we love him more than ever.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360780537083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:35:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360781230963-65</Id><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Msg>Employer wants to hire someone for $6 an hour. A guy without a job agrees to work for $6 an hour. Now these are obviously two stupid people. Anyone should be able to see the Employer would be better off not hiring anyone at all if $6 an hour is all the can pay and the employee would be better off with no job at all than to get paid a measly $6 an hour. Both people would be making very bad choices. That's why we need president Obama to make their choices for them. Most of us democrats realize we're too stupid to make their own choices but those arrogant Republicans and Independents still think they're smart enough to make their own choices. What fools.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360781336695-66</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us about how well the middle class was doing before minimum wages ,Unions and workers rights?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360781336695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:48:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360781365296-67</Id><Topic><Title>Comment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360772584735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The lies, shallowness, policy, blaming of others, sophistry, and his fear" This is clearly contents taken from Olberwomanns resume summarizing his work at MSNBC and Current TV. Olberwomann has to be livid knowing that he got hosed by Al Gore who then made millions selling Current TV to anti-American Arab oil interests.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360781365296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:49:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360781627688-68</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point rock star. It seems no matter what the economy is like the middle class is always stuck between the lower and upper class.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781627688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:53:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360782195835-69</Id><Topic><Title>Comment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360772584735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you call them anti-American?</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1360782195835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:03:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360782252300-70</Id><Title>Why hasn't FAA come out &amp; said 787 shut down for long haul?</Title><Msg>Who is running this show The FAA, Boeing, Big Brother, The White House, etc.? Boeing problems are no longer day to day. They are month to month and could go well into 2013. So shouldn't the FAA which has the responsibility for protecting the flying public just come out and say the 787 Dreamliner will be grounded for an extended period of time (3 to 6 months) so Boeing and Federal Investigators can properly check all safety issues with the 787. Why all the "hush - hush" from the FAA when they are a public agency that is supposed to share all relevant flight data on an new airplane that some say needs a major over haul.</Msg><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360782252300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:04:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360782682935-71</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unions are not and never have destroyed state economies politicians do that . Blaming the unions is just a excuse for politicians to keep doing more of the same.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360782682935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:11:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360782795392-72</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obamna play the race card tonight?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360716294521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:44:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you feel the need to bring race up everyday? your like the best player in the game from my observations.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360782795392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:13:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360783149360-73</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obamna play the race card tonight?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360716294521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:44:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why do you feel the need to bring race up everyday?" Because he can't stand an African-American being the president and commander-in-chief.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1360783149360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:19:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360783287135-74</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point rock star.....unions forcing employers to pay higher than market wages have never hurt anyone except those willing to work for market wages and those people who lose their jobs because the employers they work for can't afford to pay higher than market wages. People are simply not smart enough to make their own choices. That's why we need elitist politicians and union bosses to tell us what to do.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360783287135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:21:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360783364798-75</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't FAA come out &amp; said 787 shut down for long haul?</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360782252300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:04:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FAA and Boeing are probably investigating why the problem showed up on two recently delivered aircraft with very low hours while other aircraft have been flying for many months with no apperant battery thermal run away issues. Aircraft could have been tampered with by the union rank and file , IAM has done this in the past while negotiating a new contract.....its possible there are rouge SPEEA members that caused the problems so FAA has to tread lightly here before they destroy the one of the biggest exporters in the country for the actions of a few.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1360783364798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:22:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360783556034-76</Id><Title>Illegal Immigrant: Don't Call Me "Illegal"</Title><Msg>Jose Antonio Vargas, an illegal immigrant and former reporter, scolded a congressional panel on Wednesday, saying that he should not be called illegal, and saying it is an insult to his family who brought him here. “When you inaccurately call me illegal, you not only dehumanize me, you’re offending them,” he said. “No human being is illegal.” Mr. Vargas testified to the Senate Judiciary Committee alongside Chris Crane — a U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement agent and president of the ICE agents’ union — who is unable to arrest him under the administration’s new non-deportation policies. Mr. Vargas, who “came out” as an illegal immigrant several years ago, delivered an emotional plea for the country to legalize him.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360783556034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:25:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360783613933-77</Id><Topic><Title>Illegal Immigrant: Don't Call Me "Illegal"</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360783556034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:25:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slow news day?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1360783613933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:26:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360783670749-78</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and your excuse for not being smart enough?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360783670749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:27:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360784549914-79</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't FAA come out &amp; said 787 shut down for long haul?</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360782252300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:04:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Making comment saying IAM tampered with planes can land you in jail. Suggeting SPEEA possibly caused the problems could land you in court, then the outcome would decide your fate.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360784549914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:42:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360784707947-80</Id><Topic><Title>Comment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360772584735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 11:23:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It isn't just me. CNN reported that a document found in bin Laden’s compound after his death referred to a meeting with the Al-Jazeera bureau chief in Pakistan. It was reported that 9/11 mastermind Khalid Sheikh Mohammed was protected by the government of Qatar and also that they fund the terrorist group Hamas. That is enough for me is it enough for you?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360784707947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:45:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360785400836-81</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't FAA come out &amp; said 787 shut down for long haul?</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360782252300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:04:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are there other entities with motives to sabotage the 787 batteries?? It might be profitable for ANA or JAL to get some kind of huge penalty from Boeing for faulty products delivered How about it anybody</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360785400836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:56:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360785946008-82</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obama promise to Cut Spending.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717643850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:07:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Republicans cry forever about spending until they regain power and continue with increased spending as they have done in the past?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360785946008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:05:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360786012950-83</Id><Topic><Title>Has any one noticed......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717859251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:10:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Martin was shot by an American dummy</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360786012950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:06:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360786525704-84</Id><Topic><Title>Has any one noticed......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717859251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:10:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cop killer is being supprted by the left as a victimized dude by his cop agency buddies who were racist, and who intentionally burned him to death. Typical liberal lies, but something that comes out of Socialist Central Headquarters, and the Hoozes jump all over it in support. Trevon Martin was portrayed as a kind, innocent kid when he really was a thug kicked out of school numerous times for smokin dope, and other crimes. Martin was the community helper/good guy they portrayed as the evil guy looking to kill a Black kid. The Mexican(name?) was followed by Martin, and attacked, and had all the legal right to shoot Martin. And he will get off when everything cools down, and all forget about the case.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360786525704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:15:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360786765359-85</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't FAA come out &amp; said 787 shut down for long haul?</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360782252300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:04:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FAA would look pretty foolish if they said the plane will be shut down for 6 months, and then a solution is found in 6 days. It is not their responsibility to behave that way.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360786765359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:19:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360787067480-86</Id><Topic><Title>Has any one noticed......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717859251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:10:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like the report describing how a white couple was beaten savagely by a group of between 30 and 100 black youths in Norfolk VA last year. Their was a great example why automatic weapons are needed and why seven bullets isn't enough. It was covered like it never even happened.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360787067480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:24:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360787648930-87</Id><Title>You Should Have Shut Up When Obama Wouldn't Wear The US Flag Pin</Title><Msg>and put his hands on his man candy during the National Anthem. Don't you regret it now? ;-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360787648930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:34:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360789822934-88</Id><Topic><Title>Stadium sized ASTEROID to SLAM Earth on Friday!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360788489665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:48:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this part of Obama's plan to cool the Earth because a meteor impact would certainly do the trick. Are you sure about China? Have you accounted for the gravitation forces of Chris Christie? I say it hits New Jersey right in the labonza.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360789822934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:10:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360790493211-89</Id><Title>how long can BA stall the coming train wreck?</Title><Msg>another day - another week? How long can Boeing stall the FAA, Media, general public, investors that the 787 has extremely serious flying problems that will take a very long time to address and repair?</Msg><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360790493211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:21:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360790627654-90</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Politicians bought and paid for by unions. The corruption of unions and politicians is a mutually beneficial arrangement. In Illinois the state pension fund is short $80 billion and we have crooks running the unions and state legislature.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360790627654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360791272151-91</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The point is if the unions were not around a majority of people in this county would be pretty much slaves living in poverty working 12 hours a day for pennies and the rich would be even richer taking even more advantage of people, and the biggest contributor to politicians is not unions it`s corporations. you can re write history and facts all you want but you will continue to be losers. Americans no longer fall for the Republicans baloney. Keep you head buried in the dirt if it makes you feel good I`m sure typing away your fantasy on message boards all day is good therapy for you I find it quite comical myself.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360791272151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:34:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360792927692-92</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't FAA come out &amp; said 787 shut down for long haul?</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360782252300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:04:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow jjovaz, you manage to accuse 2 different unions of sabotage - so let me be blunt, you're nothing but an anti-union POS.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1360792927692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:02:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360793974996-93</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obama promise to Cut Spending.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717643850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:07:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Obama has severly cut my spending. Almost 100 percent. Because I cant even buy 20 percent of the Hamburger with my money. He is going to cut all your spending as well because in the end your money cannot buy the weight of toilet paper. So maybe it might be wise to accumulate toilet paper and exchange it for dollars. Does anybody think of a toilet paper exchange/Futures in Wall street.</Msg><Username>cmps309</Username><Timestamp>1360793974996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:19:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360794668283-94</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obama promise to Cut Spending.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717643850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:07:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're making about as much sense as Nugent. In which country did you learn English?</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1360794668283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:31:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360794794551-95</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. YOU and your greedy ilk are living proof that unions must become stronger.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1360794794551</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:33:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360795065279-96</Id><Title>Obama Served up More Kool Aid for The Mediocre Class to Gulp Down</Title><Msg>promises promises .......all kinds of people will be lifted to a high level of mediocrity. If they ever escape mediocre incomes......punishment awaits and they will be forced to pay their fair share and a couple of taker's shares to boot. You shouldn't think for yourselves.....after all that's why you need and depend on elitist politicians. Mediocre people will always out number high achievers so why shouldn't you keep voting for people who will protect the middle class and make sure you never escape it. We will spend and borrow our way to prosperity on the backs of our children and those yet unborn......assuming we don't kill them before they're born. Greece ain't got noth'n on us.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360795065279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:37:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360795808460-97</Id><Title>When Did It Become a Great Honor to be In the Mediocre Class?</Title><Msg>When Politicians realized why people were in the mediocre class.....their reasoning and ambition were also mediocre. Easily manipulated with thinking rationally easily replaced with envy and jealousy. Tell them the mediocre class is sacred and never, never let then think it's something they should escape and not be satisfied with or a pathway to high achievement.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360795808460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:50:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360795931952-98</Id><Topic><Title>how long can BA stall the coming train wreck?</Title><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360790493211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:21:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A long time. Much longer than you think!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360795931952</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:52:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360796386786-99</Id><Title>"FAIR SHARE" and "Middle Class"</Title><Msg>These are two term you will always hear Obama and his minions use over and over again. Never define the terms.....just use them to stir up hatred and resentment of the non-thinkers against the minority numbers of those who refuse to let others think for them.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360796386786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:59:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360796672007-100</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Coburn: Sequestration will happen</Title><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1360774822962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Where there is smoke there is fire and right now BA is one big dark smoke cloud." Smoke clouds aren't good. That's what started this mess.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360796672007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:04:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360796724772-101</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very useful report, thanks</Msg><Username>seanperkins879</Username><Timestamp>1360796724772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:05:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360796888830-102</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360796888830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:08:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360797003009-103</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ted Nugent defecates all over himself every time he opens his mouth. Of course, that's also the only time he can see daylight.</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1360797003009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360797568110-104</Id><Title>FAIR PRICE</Title><Msg>The classic definition of a "fair price" is whatever buyer and seller agree it is and the exchange leaves both parties being more pleased than if the exchange had never happened. Intervention that distorts or alters the "FAIR PRICE" will reduce the number of exchanges buyers and sellers will voluntarily participate in. That's why price controls produce shortages of whatever it is they're controlling the price of. And that's why a minimum wage always produces higher unemployment of low skilled and entry level workers and WHY IT'S DUMBEST MOST ECONOMIC ILLOGICAL AND HARMFUL POLICY implemented.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360797568110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:19:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360798373624-105</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ted Nugent is a great Patrtiot.....our troops love him......a lot more than their Commander in Chief. That goes for veterans too.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360798373624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:32:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360798538292-106</Id><Topic><Title>Illegal Immigrant: Don't Call Me "Illegal"</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360783556034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:25:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Illegal Immigrant SOB! America is the only stupid nation in the world that actually allows illegal immigrants to stay. You elect me president and that will change! My first appointee will be Sheriff Arpaio to Secretary of Homeland Security!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360798538292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:35:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360798779336-107</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't FAA come out &amp; said 787 shut down for long haul?</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360782252300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 14:04:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How soon we forget! I remember not too long ago when IAM rank and file members cut wiring harnesses on 737's awaiting delivery in Renton during contract negotiations and it made national news! also, a couple of homes were burnt down in the Enumclaw area by an IAM member because another Ba employee crossed the picket line. Bring the law suit on!! I will bury you with the FACTs.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1360798779336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:39:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360799010262-108</Id><Title>Ted Nugent There For The Troops</Title><Msg>It's easy to demonize people who are voluntarily do good things when you never do them yourselves like hoozdik and Chrissy the Kent Raven. USA Patriotism! proudly recognizes . . . patriot Ted Nugent for his ongoing support of our troops through his performances and other charitable patriotic efforts. With over 30 million albums sold, Ted Nugent has not only earned his status as an American music icon . . . he has used it to bring smiles, enjoyment, and a helping hand to our valiant, proud troops in performance tours in association with the USO and other organizations. Ted Nugent and his wife, Shemane, also founded the Freedom's Angels Foundation to support our brave troops. In Ted's own words... "As the Nugent family spent more time with US hero soldiers who have sacrificed so much, yet remained in need of special attention and specialized medical and rehabilitation equipment, we were compelled to show our appreciation and gather support for these great warriors for freedom . . . The Freedom's Angels charity was formed to bring relief, joy and a heartfelt salute to those most deserving." Here are just a few things Ted Nugent has done for the troops... Donated in excess of 2,000 tickets and backstage passes to the military, 2005-2006. Performed for 55,000 Marines, Sailors and their families at Camp Pendleton's Rockin' the Corps on April 1, 2005, along with fellow musicians Destiny’s Child, Godsmack, Kiss, and more. The Performance was also shown as a Big Screen Concert Event in 74 Markets Nationwide. In 2004, participated in a USO Tour of the Persian Gulf with Toby Keith, and toured with Keith in The Big Throwdown Tour, 2005. Ted's humanitarian and patriotic efforts has earned him numerous commendations from state police, sheriff departments, FBI and police agencies nationwide . . . and he has been lauded for his Ted Nugent Kamp for Kids, his work as a national spokesman for D.A.R.E, and for his work with the U.S. Military. Ted Nugent is also an avid supporter of the USO and encourages other stars to do the same. In Ted's own words again... "It’s surprising how little you hear about the USO back in the States . . . especially, when you consider that it’s such an awesome, compassionate, generous and positive force . . . What Bob Hope did during World War II, and the Korean War, and Vietnam, and what Robin Williams and Kid Rock and Toby Keith are doing . . . I’m moved to be a part of that."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360799010262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360799967541-109</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man, Mr. Fugelsang hit the nail on the head, didn't he?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1360799967541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:59:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360800655741-110</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ted Nugent supports the troops, however, little Chrissy spends all his time supporting his aliases.........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1360800655741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:10:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360800761963-111</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Especially when he dumped in his pants on purpose to dodge serving.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1360800761963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:12:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360800974705-112</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Ted Nugent was simply boycotting the toilet paper industry?</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1360800974705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:16:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360800982998-113</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This IS bizarre. You have all those Dems at the SOTU like Obama who never served, along with all those Dem draft dodgers who started the progressive movement after turning their brains to #$%$ getting stoned during their youth as well as Dem Bob Menendez who is being investigated by the FBI for pedophilia, and it seems impossible that Ted Nugent isn't a Dem. As this article points out Nugent seems to possess all the qualities needed to be an ideal Dem. So why isn't he a Dem? I checked to see if maybe he started out as a Dem like me and had a revelation but I couldn't find anything in his youth that would indicate that he was a Dem. Then I came across this passage: Nugent: Democratic Party Is A "Modern-Day Slave Master" To "Poor, Unemployed," And Republicans "Want To Liberate Them." In a June 18 Washington Times column, Ted Nugent suggested that the Democratic Party is the "modern-day slave master" to low-income Americans, writing that Democrats "convinc[e] them that evil, greedy Republicans are the reason they are poor, unemployed and underemployed" and that "many are obviously too clueless to see which political party is their modern-day slave master and which one wants to liberate them." That's where the problem is it seems. Nugent like Abe Lincoln can't condone the slave master/ slave arrangement between Dems and poor blacks that Dems have embraced for hundreds of years and continue to enjoy today.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360800982998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:16:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360801136933-114</Id><Topic><Title>"FAIR SHARE" and "Middle Class"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360796386786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:59:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of not thinking, isn't it about time for the vapid Mir(de) to conduct his weekly lecture on public education and conversion of F to C?</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1360801136933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:18:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360801145063-115</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent There For The Troops</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360799010262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:43:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the Hoozes demonize Ted Nugent, and champion Dorner for killing cops. It is all about focusing on how disgusting the Hoozes are.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360801145063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:19:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360801149300-116</Id><Topic><Title>It Doesn't Matter - We Still Love Obama</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360694796598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:46:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>excellent observations all of you. Very ascerbic &amp; true. Now we need to see this all in other publications GO!!</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1360801149300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:19:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360801512463-117</Id><Topic><Title>When Did It Become a Great Honor to be In the Mediocre Class?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360795808460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:50:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dems always were uncaring of logic or ethics or words. Lombardi said " winning is everything" . This word works &amp; will punish the GOP in the process. The big thing is to hurt the GOP; remember what Obama said " Talk is nothing...its all politics "</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1360801512463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:25:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360801639570-118</Id><Topic><Title>"FAIR SHARE" and "Middle Class"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360796386786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:59:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Straight from the Alinski book. I got one &amp; you can read it to tell what Obama will do next. BYW it dedicated to the "devil" What does that tell you????</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1360801639570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:27:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360802021501-119</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We already know Ted runs away from anything that can fight back." Line of the year!</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1360802021501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:33:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360802802647-120</Id><Title>BA says let battiers melt and catch on fire</Title><Msg>We don't care and "Hey it might take six months to figure out the problems". Instead lets just encase the piece of junk in a fire proof box. If Passenger don't smell burning batteries and see or smell smoke, we can get the FAA to approve and fly these lemons into the sunset. Its the BA way - cover your tracks, lie and play the FAA as dummies. (read on) lithium-ion batteries in a sturdy container to keep heat, flames and toxic chemicals from escaping if the power packs overheat. This is BA answer to major 787 electrical problems. HA</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1360802802647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:46:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360802957002-121</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he's just running away from slave master Dem Progs that want to control every aspect of his life.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360802957002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:49:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360803323564-122</Id><Topic><Title>Stadium sized ASTEROID to SLAM Earth on Friday!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360788489665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:48:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check your tin foil hat - be sure to wear it friday - the bozon rays will protect you !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360803323564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:55:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360803628893-123</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see the R folks like Mir are busily campaigning already, using their most valuable secret weapons such as Ted "Brown Pants" Nugent and their other trump cards. Keep it up, please.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1360803628893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:00:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360804022161-124</Id><Topic><Title>BA says let battiers melt and catch on fire</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1360802802647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:46:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the FAA allows the Dreamliner to fly with fire proof battery boxes, then pigs will fly next week and Republicans and Democrats will cross marry. Can't believe BA posted some idiot theory that they can prevent airplane fires by encasing smoldering batteries in fire proof tin boxes. This is the 787 DreamLiner Captain speaking. "We now have four lithium batteries burning in flight but don't worry. Even though we are over the Atlantic Ocean and a thousand miles from any landing area, our four degraded batteries that have turned into soup are protected by special boxes that don't melt and don't smell. Please sit back and enjoy the rest of the flight as the crew starts to turn off all unnecessary power like emergency exits signs and fasten your seat belt signs".</Msg><Username>marketcrashsoon</Username><Timestamp>1360804022161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:07:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360804169463-125</Id><Topic><Title>how long can BA stall the coming train wreck?</Title><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360790493211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 16:21:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Boeing said it would spend between $1.5 billion and $2 billion in 2013 on share repurchases. The purchases were authorized in 2007 as part of a $7 billion buy-back plan that was halted in 2009 with $3.6 billion remaining." At today's close that would be over 26.7 million shares. This was announced on Dec 17th, so who knows how much they've used so far. Oh, good timing too.</Msg><Username>try2try</Username><Timestamp>1360804169463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:09:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360804203198-126</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do they really make him #$%# his pants?</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1360804203198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360804226375-127</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is more about who the hoozes are than the Nugents. They attack success, and folks that give directly to those in need wanting them to get the benefits, and not the big liberal govt cronies getting the benefits, and power....the Hoozes, that attack Nugent, and champion Dorner. Nice guys those Hoozes.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360804226375</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:10:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360804349113-128</Id><Topic><Title>Stadium sized ASTEROID to SLAM Earth on Friday!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360788489665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 15:48:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The commies will say the attack was directed by the USA, and Spart, along with the libdems will say it was planned long ago by GW Bush.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360804349113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:12:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360804494894-129</Id><Title>Hooz and the Kent Rave Repeat Urban Legends</Title><Msg>The Raven was outed for knowing repeating false statement attributed to George Bush now they are repeating unverifiable information about Ted Nugent. Now they have joined together in the liberal's favorite tactic of demonizing people that don't happen to share their far left-wing radical Marxist ideology.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360804494894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:14:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360804897399-130</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oily_Taint - It's clear you prefer "Brown Shirt" Obama the self appointed emperor and slave master over "Brown Pants" Nugent. Good for you.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360804897399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:21:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360804911523-131</Id><Topic><Title>"FAIR SHARE" and "Middle Class"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360796386786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:59:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's 26 degrees C here in St. George........that would be 79 F. Too bad you can't enjoy it Bawawawahahahahaha.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360804911523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:21:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360805167037-132</Id><Topic><Title>Hooz and the Kent Rave Repeat Urban Legends</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360804494894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:14:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You probably think Sir Paul has a yellow submarine too.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360805167037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:26:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360806654231-133</Id><Topic><Title>Hooz and the Kent Rave Repeat Urban Legends</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360804494894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:14:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would this board be without the comical right-fringe hatefest that the stuffed shirt mir champions? I give you lots of credit, bloviator, for making this board a read I look forward to each day. I always sing you a couple of hims when I read your nonsense. The U.S. Constitution -- it's not just something the right wipes with anymore. Har har har har har</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360806654231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:50:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360806758983-134</Id><Title>Batteries are US</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON—The Obama administration's electric car efforts took another hit on Wednesday after a federal inspection found a South Korean advanced battery maker never scaled up U.S. production despite receiving $142 million in federal grants. A Holland, Mich., factory owned by LG Chem Ltd., 051910.SE +0.50% part of LG Corp., 003550.SE 0.00% was half-funded by a government grant and estimated to add some 440 jobs building battery cells for General Motors Co.'s GM +0.42% Chevrolet Volt and other vehicles. When demand for the plant's batteries didn't meet expectations, the company filled orders with cells made at a factory in South Korea, leaving the Michigan plant largely idle, according to the report by the Department of Energy's Inspector General, Gregory Friedman. LG Chem said in a statement that production delays at the Michigan facility were "market-driven," adding that it is "developing specific plans for the start of production." The company said it regretted that it applied for reimbursement for "employment costs that were not allowed" under its U.S. grant. The inspector general said that to avoid layoffs at the factory LG Chem paid idle workers $1.6 million in the third quarter of last year, about half of which was covered by its U.S. grant, even though there was nothing for them to do. The workers played board games, watched movies, and volunteered at local animal shelters during regular work hours, Mr. Friedman said. LG Chem has since paid back the government's share of those charges. "Until the shift in production takes place or some alternative use for the plant is developed, U.S. taxpayers will receive little direct benefit from a plant for which they provided up to half of the funding," Mr. Friedman said in his report. In 2010, Mr. Obama attended the plant's groundbreaking and said such grants would "unleash private sector growth" and called the factory "a symbol of where America is going." The facility today has about 150 workers, some of whom are hourly employees and are furloughed one week a month.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360806758983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:52:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360806965413-135</Id><Topic><Title>Conventional Wisdom</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1360801572119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 19:26:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for posting. That says it all. I didn't sir mir in there, but then that's just an alias anyway. Maybe he's Mr. Wells or Mr. Fargo.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360806965413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 20:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360807568243-136</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent There For The Troops</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360799010262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:43:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm still waiting for Nugent to be what he said he'll be after April 16, 2013, if Obama is re-elected. Maybe it will be for illegally killing that bear in Alaska’s Tongass National Forest last year. WHAT A SPORTSMAN!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360807568243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:06:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360807606430-137</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent There For The Troops</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360799010262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:43:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He supports the troops; but in the 1960s, he refused to become one.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360807606430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:06:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360807687989-138</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent There For The Troops</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360799010262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:43:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A man who supports the troops but not his country and who violates its hunting regulations for money is no patriot.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360807687989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:08:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360807983484-139</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent There For The Troops</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360799010262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:43:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"violates its hunting regulations for money is no patriot." Chrissie, you wouldn't be lying again would you? or Maybe you're just like Obama and don't believe in due process.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1360807983484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:13:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360808072979-140</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent There For The Troops</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360799010262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:43:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems to be a pattern with them.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1360808072979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:14:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360808091281-141</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent There For The Troops</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360799010262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 18:43:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, Chris Genna.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1360808091281</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:14:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360808339286-142</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1360808339286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 21:18:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360811573139-143</Id><Topic><Title>Has any one noticed......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717859251</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:10:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point and lets not forget the white cop who obama said acted stupidly and didn't obama mouth off about the white lacrosse team who was falsely accused of raping the black stripper. Funny how when a lib media loving brother goes on a shooting spree with an AR, obama gets lockjaw.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1360811573139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:12:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360812061437-144</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and Panetta BOTH request the TROOPS disarm before they give a canned speech/photo-op in front of them....NEVER ...EVER listen to Barry Soetoros words....WATCH HIS ACTIONS ....PS ... Ted Nugent is a great Patriot...Muhamid Ali refused to goto Nam too...he KNEW we didnt have any quarrel with no Cong....just like some of you racists think we have a quarrel with the Muslims.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360812061437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:21:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360812133341-145</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obama take over the Internet via Executive Order this week ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360759091588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 07:38:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thx for the heads up</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360812133341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:22:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360812247428-146</Id><Topic><Title>Medal of Honor winner turns down invite to State of the Union</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360771035544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cook CEO ..is not as good a photo op to parade around tho</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360812247428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:24:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360812482809-147</Id><Title>F-35 and Li batteries</Title><Msg>Cant make this up !! ....."We are monitoring our full battery system on a daily basis as we flight test. We have continual data updates, and we've had no indication that we are connected to the same issues that grounded the 787," Rein said. The F-35's battery system has run into a different problem on the ground, with some airplanes failing to start during cold temperatures under 10 degrees Celsius, DellaVedova said. He cited "minor irregularities" that had been traced back to a software issue in the jet's battery charger control unit, and a fix was in the works for new jets in production and would be retrofitted on earlier jets. The problem, he said, was not related to the batteries themselves. +++ 10 degree C = 50 degree F And thats Cold ??? A multi billion $$$ plane that wont start in seattle other than may june july and aug ? Works in sandiego and southern texas - but not in colorado ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360812482809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:28:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360812715162-148</Id><Topic><Title>Is there a timely solution to battery problem?</Title><Username>thedeathrace</Username><Timestamp>1360775923289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 12:18:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WELL yours may be the size of dendrites - but they wouldnt short out anything !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360812715162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:31:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360812866262-149</Id><Topic><Title>Medal of Honor winner turns down invite to State of the Union</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360771035544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 10:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the men, and women in uniform overwhelmingly vote against their leaderless Commander.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360812866262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:34:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360813229631-150</Id><Topic><Title>Two Stupid People - Why we need Obama to make Choices for them.</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360781230963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 13:47:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to be exceptionally stupid to not know that "a lot" is 2 words. Dumb #$%$.</Msg><Username>jimbucks</Username><Timestamp>1360813229631</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:40:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360815460280-151</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The speech was almost preempted by news coverage of trapping Dorner. Was it in Dorner's manifesto or while he was still an active cop that he said we really need to get a handle on too many guns in the wrong hands.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360815460280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 23:17:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360817290185-152</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Nugent: SOTU or #$%$?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360794092858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 17:21:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nugent? Didn't you meen Pooptriot?</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1360817290185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 23:48:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360817729842-153</Id><Topic><Title>Cyber Polluters Talking Heads</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1360812906454</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 22:35:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This group is precisely why Rove is forming his new PAC. They are trying to cut down on the TRULY insane Republican candidates who have zero chance of actually winning. Teabaggers are irate, because they are Rove's target.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1360817729842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-13 23:55:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>