<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369542597272-1</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the department chiefs say not to do something but the underlings do it any way. Now why would that happen? Obama verbally lets Americans know he does not like Conservitives, he does not like the Supreme Court he does not like Congress. Some to unmine them happens then he says I dd not do that. Liberals want to belive this liar, but truth will be heard and read once this guy is not hiding behind Executive Orders. The historians will step in and record it</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369542597272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369543646313-2</Id><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Msg>the scndals are overwhelming, deaths, debt, breaking the Constitution and the Bill of Rights. Then he claimes a" I was sleeping" The guy is a Facist thug. Funny numbers across American Unemployment Falling while Welfare is Surging 49M and counting. 30% surge for those living under the Poverty Line. His own Party won't vote for his jobs Bill. One loser, once he is gone the Freedom of Information Act historians will be able to identify what he is hiding. This guy is worse the Clinton, worse the Carter.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369543874126-3</Id><Topic><Title>EPA Accused Of Bias Against Conservative Groups; Fuels IG Probe - Cavuto -</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369455214531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why is gas $4 and surging even higher, when supply would drive it lower? No mensa on this board, just followers.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543874126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369544414006-4</Id><Topic><Title>Deliveries as of week 3 May,</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369509804103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad your posts only give deliverys of commercial planes---nothing from the defense/space and security divisions. Would show more of Boeings power and diversity. Lot of F-18, Chinook, etc etc and defense and satellite and other work not mentioned. You must love the commerical aircraft, which is good. I have tried but am hacked and many of my posts are deleted within seconds and there are no violations of the rules. So, someone out there help for more visability of Boeings awards and deliveries.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369544414006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 01:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369546805989-5</Id><Title>Yesterday Boeing launched an advanced military communications satellite--2nd ULA in nine days</Title><Msg>This is the fifth advanced comm satellite of a planned 10 system total. To be used by US and its allies. Can be used by drones in addition to advanced comm features. I like that this is the 2nd lauch in 9 days of the Boeing/Lockheed United Launch Alliance.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369546805989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 01:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369547686702-6</Id><Title>Royal International Airshow take place in July----should be great for Boeing</Title><Msg>Largest military airshow in world. 70 country's attending. Go F-18(in attack and Growler), go Chinook, maybe one combined order to get another good C-17 run. Too many products to mention here. Shows are good for business</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369547686702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 01:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369563401802-7</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sir Paul, you are an old washed up no-talent limey who needs to fix your own country first. You might start with finding ways to stop Mus lim terrorists from slaughtering people in the streets. It's odd that you feel that Obonzo's record of lying to dumb people to trick them into supporting him is a great thing and worth your adoration. He is the most arrogant pompous puffed up empty suit in history but you are an idiot musician living in a world of phonies in the entertainment business, so Obonzo is right up your alley. Please convince him to move to your country as he is dividing and destroying the US.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369563401802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 06:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369569258446-8</Id><Title>gregjanetommax is a felon</Title><Msg>He is a foul hatefilled racist who regulary slanders and commits criminal libel against our black president</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369569258446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 07:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369569728828-9</Id><Title>BA Next stop- 150/shr put that in your nose WayneDickensen</Title><Msg>Har har har har har har har har har har har har har har</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369569728828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 08:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>23</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369573292696-10</Id><Title>Fighting Radical Muslim Preachers</Title><Msg>It took the violent and brutal murder of a British soldier in the heart of England for the Brits to begin to call for action to fight radical Muslim preachers. President Obama wants to step down the war on terrorism to pre-9/11 days. On the contrary when it comes to combatting domestic terrorism America like Britian should step up the war against terrorism. Law enforcement should crack down firmly on those who preach radical I slam, whether from a Mosque, a university or the internet. Free speech has its limits. A call to violence against American civilians is a crime.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369573292696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369573515696-11</Id><Topic><Title>Happy long weekend... Happy BA 100$</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1369426629808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:17:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 dislikes over the success of BA. Must be a lot shorts that got scorched.</Msg><Username>juanruiz1330</Username><Timestamp>1369573515696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369573795818-12</Id><Topic><Title>Fighting Radical Muslim Preachers</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369573292696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That has been going on for a long, long time, and our BO protects them, would never ever criticize them. But a Catholic preachers stance on abortion, BO jumps all over them to the point they feel it necessary to sue the Feds.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369573795818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369577812764-13</Id><Topic><Title>Fighting Radical Muslim Preachers</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369573292696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are posters on this board who have been radicalized. How can I tell. Anyone that gives me a thumbs down on my above post has been radicalized.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369577812764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 10:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369581575195-14</Id><Title>TO THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Msg>Thank YOU for your service.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369581575195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369582011691-15</Id><Title>America is blessed to have Barack Obama as its president</Title><Msg>I've dined with heads of state, the Royal Family, Kings...and the Guinness World Records described me as the "most successful composer and recording artist of all time", with 60 gold discs and sales of over 100 million albums and 100 million singles, and that ore than 2,200 artists have covered my song "Yesterday", more than any other song in history. I've written, or co-written 32 songs that have reached number one on the Billboard Hot 100. In 2010, Mexican promoters for the show Bruce Moran at Live Nation and Memo Parra at OCESA commented: "Paul McCartney has made history once again! His upcoming Mexico City show is the fastest sellout in the history of the venue, Foro Sol. Everyone at Live Nation and OCESA are thrilled and honored that Sir Paul has agreed to return to Mexico, and the public has responded to the news in just an overwhelming fashion. Only the thrill of seeing Sir Paul McCartney live at Foro Sol will top the excitement in Mexico today!" And I'm currently touring yet again. So I'm as relevant today as I was in 1964. You can believe me when I tell you that America is blessed to have Barack Obama as its president.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369582011691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369582085370-16</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>List your accomplishments, ali_infesto. Oh, and I hadn't heard the term "limey" since 1953. Grow up.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369582085370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369582507676-17</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's always come out, but a winner only in the mind's eye of a pinko. Decent folks can't wait for him to be impeached.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369582507676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369582575656-18</Id><Topic><Title>Deliveries as of week 3 May,</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369509804103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rs2, I have had the same problem with defense deliveries and posts that never show up. Any post that is already on a newswire is almost immediately blocked. If it is not on the newswire, it does get posted. It is also an issue of what time you post.Posts in the late afternoon/evening get squashed where posts in the early morning seem to be accepted.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369582575656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369582709114-19</Id><Topic><Title>Deliveries as of week 3 May,</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369509804103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have not seen any planes parked in the desert. Can you be more specific?</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369582709114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369583155334-20</Id><Topic><Title>Fighting Radical Muslim Preachers</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369573292696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phantom, The misnomer about "radicalization" of some Muslims is that the violence they perform is proscribed and demanded by the Koran. In other words, the so-called “radicals” are actually being "faithful" to their scriptures. Thus, anyone who does not impose violence and/or death to Christians and Jews (non-believers in Islam) is not being faithful. People wonder how a young person can be “radicalized” in Islam; well, it is because he or she actually reads what the Koran has to say and seeks to implement its teachings. Some will suggest that the Bible is also violent and indeed there are passages that speak of death and destruction. The difference is this: "open-ended violence performed at the personal level” (Koran) vs. "God dictated judgments" against specific groups in historical, non-repeating context (Bible). While some might dismiss this difference, it is significant and key. When Jesus came along, He revoked the death and destruction judgment (for sin) to "love your neighbor as yourselves", "pray for them that despitefully use you", and "turn the other cheek". The Koran comes along 600 years after Jesus' crucifixion and a person might be, but should not be, very confused trying to correlate what the Old Testament is saying (specific national judgment for sin in specific historical context during a dispensation of law), the New Testament is saying (Jesus universal message of salvation and love in a dispensation of grace), and then the words and instructions of the Koran (open-ended violence at the personal level). The Koran has nothing to do with God but everything to do with Satan. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1369583155334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369584064323-21</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Islam condemns the killing or even the persecution of people merely because they embrace a different religion. The Quran mandates absolute freedom of religion in society. It does not allow Muslims to fight except in self-defence and to enforce peace. It does not allow restrictions on those who disagree on religions matters. It urges the Muslims to treat such people kindly and equitably. (Quran 2256) “There shall be no compulsion in religion….” (Quran 60 8) “God does not enjoin you from befriending those who do not evict you from your homes. You may befriend them and be equitable towards them. God loves the equitable.” (Quran 861) “If they resort to peace, so shall you and put your trust in God. He is the Hearer, the Omniscient.” (Quran 490) “… Therefore, if they leave you alone, refrain from fighting you and offer you peace, then God gives you no excuse to fight them.” Regrettably, many terrorist groups have used the name of Islam to promote their cause. This gave many non-Muslims an opportunity to label the Muslims as terrorists deliberately ignoring the fact that there are many terrorists who happen to be non-Muslims. This does not make these laws evil but rather brings to light the evil nature of the criminals.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584064323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369584393905-22</Id><Topic><Title>BA Next stop- 150/shr put that in your nose WayneDickensen</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369569728828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 08:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you agree that Boeing is going to 150. Boeing is about to do a slam dunk on AirBus. This 100+ year old company is firing on all cylinders. You do know what the sound of an engine running on all cylinders sounds like, don't you. Smooth baby smooth!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1369584393905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369586748049-23</Id><Title>Waynedick</Title><Msg>What you don't know is that Boeing already has a permanent fix for the Lithium ion battery problem. Elon Musk of Tesla talked to Boeing engineers and told them that they needed to redesign their batteries using smaller cells. Tesla had the same problem as Boeing when they designed their batteries for their cars!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1369586748049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369586802727-24</Id><Topic><Title>BA Next stop- 150/shr put that in your nose WayneDickensen</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369569728828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 08:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>defense_junky or father-z or whistle your the same person , glad your still crazy after all these years ha ha ha after 11 years of leading Boeing and taking market share away from Boeing Airbus is about to beat the 787 with their new more practical jet har har har and Boeing stock price gain over 5 years proves it to Boeing. Attention the 3 stooges and they are the same person father,whistle and junkie get it right Boeing stock price for 5 years is up 22% and Airbus stock value is up 132% so to the 3 stooges all the same person father, whistle and junkie, as Boeing stock price is about to go three digits that is less than 1 % gain from 99.70 fools, I am giving you my single digit finger salute on memorial day, your number one in my book! I dont care what Dell says about you. a fool can post here too or make that three names all owned by one fool can talk all day long about how boeing is a gainer and yet is behind Airbus in stock price 132% gain to 22% gain over 5 years fools read my hand gesture and then look at the stock gains</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369586802727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369587427790-25</Id><Title>defense -junkie Elon Must of Tesla ? wow that is my stock read my user recommendation May 3 buy Tesla up 90%</Title><Msg>defense_junky • 1 minute 5 seconds ago Flag said, "Waynedick What you don't know is that Boeing already has a permanent fix for the Lithium ion battery problem. Elon Musk of Tesla talked to Boeing engineers and told them that they needed to redesign their batteries using smaller cells. Tesla had the same problem as Boeing when they designed their batteries" Defense-junkie, or stupid person , On May 3, (you really need to start reading my user comments ) I pointed out that tesla has lithium batteries in their cars and that stock was the one to own , like me, I have owned it for a long time . . So what part of stupid are you now demonstrating. I know a lot more about tesla and Elon than you seem to know. For example my stock TSLA is up 400% in 3 years and your stock Boeing is up 22% in 5 years. I alos know that Jim went to Elon ans asked his advice on how to fix the battery. Now defense junkie that should tell you which stock to own adn it is not boeing duh !!!!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369587427790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369587949217-26</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Terrorism is an act of violence committed by people belonging to all religions.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369587949217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369588394829-27</Id><Topic><Title>defense -junkie Elon Must of Tesla ? wow that is my stock read my user recommendation May 3 buy Tesla up 90%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369587427790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:57:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>defense junkie, here is my user comment and I have made many recommendations on TSLA not Boeing defense-junkie, are you learning yet? here is my May 3 user comment"waynedickenson961 • May 3, 2013 9:46 PM Flag • • Boeing the week in review Boeing stock price up under 1% for the week ! , Airbus stock price increased 2.8% , tesla which uses lithium batteries and has beat Boeing all the way for the past several years huge, and I own TSLA and am making a fortune on it, is up 6.7% again as usual this seek, but par for the coarse, the Boeing hacks instead of a real stock price gain continue with a lot of gibberish and no substance Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369588394829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369588411447-28</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Terrorists who happened to be non-Muslims raised their religious beliefs to claim legitimacy for the violence and terrorism that they commit on thousands of men, women, and children in attempts to achieve special interests – political, social or religious. Those who do not comprehend Islam and those who have an interest in distorting the truth about Islam have been trying to make terrorism synonymous to Islam.A mistaken notion has been common in the western media.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369588411447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369589044193-29</Id><Topic><Title>defense -junkie Elon Must of Tesla ? wow that is my stock read my user recommendation May 3 buy Tesla up 90%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369587427790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:57:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>defense junkie you can not say fool about your self any better than your comment that Jim Went to tesla to fix the lithium batteries , what you just said was you should be in TSLA stock not Boeing stock. Finally the Boeing batteries are not fixed as they have a fire box on them . that means Boeing "sometimes does not know what they do not know" and expect more fires . the box and the lithium battery are heavier than a safe nicad battery! DJ, how stupid is that fix? a dangerous experimental battery on a plane that can not pull over to the side of the road or a testla car with a lithium battery? defense junkie you are so stupid fisker also had and still has battery problems and is fighting bankruptcy right now they use lithium batteries too stupid ! the technology is not ready for a lithium battery in a airplane! Boeing engineers , told Cessna to get rid of their lithium batteries and they did! Cessna by number of planes produced makes more airplanes than any other airplane maker once more defense junkie you a very stupid person DJ are you ar have you ever worked for Boeing or worked the aerospace industry like me? nope, DJ, your a fool talking about something of which you know nothing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369589044193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369589562642-30</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, You missed including the conclusion of the article that you copied and posted from a Pakistani news company: "Islam stands for peace, harmony and understanding. It does not preach hatred or condones acts of violence. Unfortunately the message of Islam has been distorted by the enemies of Islam." And, yet, other than a sparse number of writers like this author, Dr. Saeed, the vast majority of Muslims speak no words against the violence as it is likely well to provide them the proxy for what the Koran teaches. If one does not speak out against and resist an evil, one must be in agreement. So, despite Dr. Saeed's protestation and incomplete picture of Islam, and unless she is saying that the enemies of Islam are within the Islamic community (very doubtful), she is really imposing the guilt to the victims of Islamic violence, the so-called "enemies of Islam" - in other words, those that speak the truth.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1369589562642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369590340446-31</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some accurate thoughts on religion. Christianity made this country, the USA, the greatest country in the world. Christianity was the foundation of our constitution, and our motivation to be great. Liberals that attack Christianity because it doesn't conform well to their valueless religion of Liberalism are as dangerous as Al Queda to our health and welfare.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369590340446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369590485479-32</Id><Title>Listen #$%$!</Title><Msg>I think you should look at your options when you invest in stocks. The perfect storm is brewing for Boeing. There are only two companies in the world that build world class aircraft that can fly anywhere in the world. We all now who they are. Boeing is about to kick a little butt here. Take it to the bank!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1369590485479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369590842778-33</Id><Title>Yeah right!</Title><Msg>I need to apply for Section 8 housing so I don't have to pay rent. What a wonderful life.</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1369590842778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 13:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369592115667-34</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joe, seemed to me the writer was simply saying that there are good folks in every religion who will do positive things, and a few who will do destructive/cruel things. Seems only logical to me.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369592115667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 14:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369592256272-35</Id><Title>The best religion in the world</Title><Msg>Believe in yourself!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1369592256272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 14:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369593267585-36</Id><Topic><Title>BA Next stop- 150/shr put that in your nose WayneDickensen</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369569728828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 08:02:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you don't know is that Boeing is going where no aircraft company has in a long time. The 787 has been a pain in the #$%$. But when the sun rises in the East and sets in the West, Boeing is going to put a serious dent in the AirBus Armor. Boeing is the best aircraft company in the world, bar none!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1369593267585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 14:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369594461037-37</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course you dont mention 8 of the years were under Bush...or did you bother to read the arti le at all</Msg><Username>penmouse68</Username><Timestamp>1369594461037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 14:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369596591739-38</Id><Topic><Title>TO THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369581575195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP IT UP !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369596591739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 15:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369596642087-39</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you need to get an education. Subprime Lending Legislation was Clinton's Bush tried to stop it but a couple more liberals like Brarnwy Frank and Marilyn Waters only laughed. Odd how #$%$ blame the financial crisis on Bush, who had nothing to do with it.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369596642087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 15:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369596812620-40</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, "seemed to me the writer was simply saying that there are good folks in every religion who will do positive things, and a few who will do destructive/cruel things" Well, of course, by definition, that is correct. As long as there are humans ... But the author is delusional if she things that whatever evil seems to plague Islam is somehow found in equal measure, if measureable at all, with all other beliefs on the planet. There is simply no basis for such a presumption. In fact, I would venture to say that no other religion on the planet enjoys, like Islam, the evil fervor of mass killing and blowing up property while invoking the name of its deity. Ergo, everyone knows what “Allah Akbar” means – and know it not for the reason that Dr. Saeed may have learned in her mosque. Because it was heard on doomed Egypt Flight 990, on the flights into the Pentagon and Twin Towers, by Nidal Hassan, and most recently by the Jihad Hacker in London the other day. Name one recent terrorist incident in the name of Shiva or Buddha. And certainly, no one invokes the name of Jesus or Jehovah while they are butchering and maiming. No, Islam owns this and owns it almost exclusively. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1369596812620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 15:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369596944394-41</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think even Bernanke was shocked when Obama won the election, who said in late November Obama's policies do not support a recovery. Jobs! Now we have an 8% payroll tax, of course a jobs killer. Looks good on the books for right now. The gov. funny numbers of a falling Unemployment Rate while Welfare and Poverty is surging. i talk to guys at the Worksource in Washinton State, every time they go into the place they learn thier accouts have been deleted, but nobody has the answer Why.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369596944394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 15:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369598894934-42</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has been so consistently counter productive that the notion this Regime', and his liberals in congress consider their failures as an accomplishment, and did it intentionally. The more folks on the dole, the more votes the left can count on as long as you can blame someone else for the failures.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369598894934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 16:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369600790490-43</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when 13 #$%$ respond to my messages negatively I count that as a huge success. A total denial of the printed facts. As the facts transpired in Greece, liberal liberals and more liberals promissing what could not be maintained, now Greeks who believed the liberals are faced with deminished benefits, all gone never to return.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369600790490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 16:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369602984112-44</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Islame is the religion of "pieces" as #$%$ like to blow people to bits.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369602984112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369603019556-45</Id><Title>NO MONEY</Title><Msg>NO MONEY to replace old bridges and dams. NO MONEY to fight al qaeda and spin off terriorists NO MONEY to combat the growing Chinese threat NO MONEY to improve primary education NO MONEY to make good on disabled veterans affairs NO MONEY from taxes to address any of the above issues But $Billions upon $Billions to give to the leader of the Pashtun pediphiles And $Billions upon $Billions more to give to the leader that kicked the US out of Iraq with no oil contracts</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369603019556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369603190505-46</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sir Paul, you can pucker up with your royal lips and kiss my peasant #$%$.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369603190505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369603558881-47</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I designed and brought a product market that reduced the spread of HIV and much more. I am currently involved in a product that will allow health exams to be done remotely anywhere in the world with internet access. All of my accomplishments were done without lying through my teeth like the president does constantly.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369603558881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369603613778-48</Id><Topic><Title>Part 3 The Real Truth About the XL Pipeline out of America Gets Front Page..</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369368081410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:01:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets face it, the big oil that supports Neo-Con Pseudo RepubliCon's won't get a pipeline unless the president at least gets his jobs bill intact. Everyone knows by now that most of the refined products of that oil is going outside the US including our enemy China.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369603613778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369604193761-49</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, me too.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1369604193761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369605913190-50</Id><Topic><Title>Fighting Radical Muslim Preachers</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369573292696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the looks of it there appears to be 8 to 10 free radicals on this board, or it could be one poster with a number of alias that registers 8 to 10 thumbs down, We need more clues!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369605913190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 18:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369607302517-51</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% true. Would you have preferred that I was a charismatic phony like Obonzo? Do you not like creative scientific types that have the nerve to take risk by investing in their own ideas? I came from nothing and I am a self-made success. I paid for 100% of all my schooling. I DID BUILD THAT and idiots like Obonzo are the type of people that just get in my way.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369607302517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 18:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369607328983-52</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure he didn't. Ha ha a.</Msg><Username>penmouse68</Username><Timestamp>1369607328983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 18:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369607682131-53</Id><Topic><Title>Part 3 The Real Truth About the XL Pipeline out of America Gets Front Page..</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369368081410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 00:01:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can any of you Obonzo turd polishers tell me if the Illinois pipeline that Obonzo approved was a Pinto?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369607682131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 18:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369608084718-54</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bob, Is it just possible that Mus lims make the news today in the U.S.? My grandfather wasn't sure if the "Krauts" or the "Japs" who were the most vicious people on the earth... which, I guess, would make either the Lutherans or the Buddhists the most vicious religion. The Mus lims were never mentioned. The next generation mention the Chinese, Koreans, and Vietnamese. I was told that the Asians were "naturally adept" at torturing people. The photos of the death camps by the Third Reich are disturbing, as is reading about the kamikaze pilots in WW 2... an earlier version of the WTC missions. Now Google the "16th Street Baptist Church bombing" to see what can happen in Southern Baptist America. Equally cruel.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369608084718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 18:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369608669464-55</Id><Topic><Title>TO THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369581575195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and aain. It would sure be nice if the board twits would stop and appreciate those who served and gave the last full measure. Please take your wingnut rants elsewhere- or at least give it a rest</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369608669464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 18:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369609137193-56</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's only a winner 'cause Karl Rove wanted him in the White House, serving the 1%..</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369609137193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 18:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369609226755-57</Id><Topic><Title>NO MONEY</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369603019556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Billions to the banksters. Billions for prisons. Billions for bloated military contracts.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369609226755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 19:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369609285844-58</Id><Topic><Title>Deliveries as of week 3 May,</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369509804103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your response, just trying to spread the truth. Ready to give up though. Your posts are most informative, I must repeat from a prior post to you. Good luck.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369609285844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 19:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369611346050-59</Id><Topic><Title>Deliveries as of week 3 May,</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369509804103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I can not, but it is common knowledge that Boeing has parked a whole lot of planes they can not sell out in the desert. Someone mentioned that to me just recently. And that has been going on for sometime now.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369611346050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 19:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369611866589-60</Id><Topic><Title>NO MONEY</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369603019556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obonzo would rather support lazy useless turd polishers so they keep voting for him. He also lost billions to his green cronies to build EVs that nobody is buying and solar and wind that can't compete internationally. All his millionaire Hollywood types are getting huge government tax breaks to by $100,000.00 Teslas. It's Obonzo's choice as to where he spends money wisely or wastes money foolishly and he is mostly wasting money foolishly.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369611866589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 19:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369613764562-61</Id><Topic><Title>Fighting Radical Muslim Preachers</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369573292696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More likely: you are simply a doofus sca_ lover</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1369613764562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 20:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369614266287-62</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, I agreed with you that people who ascribe to a "faith" (belief or religion) have done good and have done bad things. What I was pointing out was the more direct attribution of their deity to the reason for their heinous acts. And the Koran feeds that. Racism (white and black against each other) and nationalism (Protestant vs. Catholic) is way more about human lack of trust, politics and power than it is about God. Both racism and nationalism bring about the sin of pride. Killing, specifically based upon belief in God, is what I was poking at. Ergo, the cry of "Allahu Akbar" upon executing such acts. Islam has (at least apparently) an exclusive patent on this. The Crusades may or may not have been the same, but there again, the Bible gives no such instructions to do that. And, except for the specific instruction in the Old Testament to the Israelites to destroy the inhabitants of Canaan and only the inhabitants of Canaan, under a death order by God for their specific sins, the Koran tells folks to destroy non-believers – wherever they may be found and at any time they may be found. It looks like Dr. Saeed chooses to ignore that admonition, as if it does not even exist, but many of these so-called “radicalized” Muslims, are, as I said, being more faithful to their scriptures. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1369614266287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 20:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369617861088-63</Id><Topic><Title>Deliveries as of week 3 May,</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369509804103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you will find a NOT a lot of planes in the desert b - a few planes for which buyer deliberately delayed delivery due to financial problems- since payment is due on delivery c- many planes which have been traded in or ready to be scrapped out or resold. Location is mojave desert in calif a long time - well known scrap yard Aircraft heavy maintenance and storage [edit] The Mojave airport is also known as a storage location for commercial airliners, due to the vast area and dry desert conditions.[5] Numerous large Boeing, McDonnell Douglas, Lockheed, and Airbus aircraft owned by major airlines are stored at Mojave. Some aircraft reach the end of their useful lifetime and are scrapped at the Mojave aircraft boneyard, while others are refurbished and returned to active service.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369617861088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 21:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369623164141-64</Id><Title>Boeing buisness jet</Title><Msg>Saw a picture of the inside of the business jet and let me say---its is beautiful. I would actually choose to sit in there just to relax. Modern, spacious, giant led screen. They did a great job. Should be highly competitive.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369623164141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 22:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369626124651-65</Id><Topic><Title>America is blessed to have Barack Obama as its president</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369582011691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama heads the Party of hate, that was evident whent he DNC booed when God was returned to the plateform. This Obama while Americans sleep has attacked rights of Americans as we sleep. He claimed bipartisan but this guy has used his power to attack Conservitives across America. The Constitution the Bill of Rights are toyed with while Obama says it wasn't me.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369626124651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 23:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>