<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379046499259-1</Id><Topic><Title>God Floods Colorado</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379002684223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did not !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1379046499259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 00:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379047075263-2</Id><Topic><Title>What Happed to all those Global Warming caused Hurricanes?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378914881105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the West Coast the sea level actually drops ( relative to the land ) because the coastal lands slowly rise over long periods of time due to subduction caused by continental drift . We have places on the Puget Low Lands where there are hills abruptly sticking up out of the plains like mole hills on a lawn . These hills were once islands, and you can find multiple ancient beaches on them if you look carefully and do a little digging . Geological truth is stranger than glow-ball warming fiction, and alot more interesting . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379047075263</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 00:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379048493941-3</Id><Topic><Title>What Happed to all those Global Warming caused Hurricanes?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378914881105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not sea level dropping, that's land rising.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379048493941</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 01:01:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379049486835-4</Id><Topic><Title>How it was so Easy for Putin to Checkmate Obama and Kerry</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378992578177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:29:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Putin is playing chess. Obama and Kerry are playing fish.</Msg><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1379049486835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 01:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379051511513-5</Id><Title>America Is Not An Exceptional Nation</Title><Msg>Just look at what our president who won re-election has been up to lately. If we were so "exceptional" King Obama would be back in Chicago organizing the community and "doing a little blow and some weed" right now.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1379051511513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 01:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379072800833-6</Id><Title>Notice that the reason Putin is being criticized</Title><Msg>Notice that the reason Putin is being criticized is that he has blocked the Obama regime from attacking Syria and slaughtering countless numbers of Syrians in the name of human rights. The stuck pigs are outraged that Obama’s war has been blocked. They were so much looking forward to the mass slaughter that they believe would advance their profits and agendas.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379072800833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 07:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379076350093-7</Id><Title>The Rise of Left Wing Intellectualism in our Universities</Title><Msg>Late Friday morning of last week, I got interrupted by a call from Katie Pavlich. It's not like I was working - I haven't worked on a Friday morning since I got tenure back in 1998. It's just that I was cleaning one of my favorite .44 magnums and didn't want to be disturbed at that particular moment. Nonetheless, Katie was having some problems with the folks at UNC - Chapel Hill and she needed some help. So I put down my Smith and Wesson and gave her my best advice. For those who haven't yet heard, Katie was invited by the College Republicans to speak at UNC-CH. But the folks in student government said she was "non-intellectual" and had "no value" as a speaker. So they refused to fund her speech and gave it to some feminists and anarchists instead. (Please pardon any redundancy in that last sentence). Although Katie contacted me for support, I had to be honest with her. I agree with the UNC-CH student government. Katie is a non-intellectual with no value as a speaker. Furthermore, the funding debacle at UNC-CH is entirely her fault. If Katie knew anything about the UNC system, she could have taken any number of measures to ensure full funding of her event. I shared a number of examples with Katie. Just in case you're a conservative woman seeking an audience at UNC-CH, I'm sharing these tips with you, free of charge. - Dress up as a six foot vagina. A few years ago at Appalachian State, which is in the UNC system, a feminist at the Women's Center went parading across campus dressed in a six foot tall vagina costume. She and her fellow feminists managed to get funding for The Vagina Monologues. They were also allowed to advertise for it with the giant vagina costume. Katie could have borrowed that costume and even given her speech wearing it. She would have looked every bit as intellectual as an Appalachian State feminist. Then, the UNC system would have funded her speech in a heartbeat. Sometimes appropriate business attire really makes a difference. This is especially true when you want to come across as a true intellectual. On a side note, UNCW Feminists also managed to get funding to sell little vagina-shaped lollipops when they put on the Vagina Monologues. If Katie were to put in a request to sell these p*ssy pops (that is what they actually called them) at her speech, then she would likely get full funding. It's not a truly intellectually stimulating event unless feminists are walking around licking sugar-coated treats that look like genitalia. - Drop your guns and celebrate "kick #$%$" feminism. Katie needs to get off of this gun kick. Last year, one of my feminist colleagues, Donna King, published a book called Men Who Hate Women: And the Women Who Kick Their #$%$. In it, she advanced the concept of "kick #$%$ feminism." One of the chapters in her book praised a feminist in a Stieg Larsson novel who retaliated against a man who had previously raped her. She accomplished the retaliation by finding him, tying him up, and then shoving metal objects up his rectum. Clearly, Katie's ideas about preventing violence via lawful gun possession are anti-intellectual, even if supported by the work of scholars like John Lott. If Katie wants to be a true intellectual, she needs to renounce guns and convince women to wait until after they are raped to deal with the rapist via vigilantism. No need for guns. All you need is a little rope and a few metal objects to shove up the rapist's rectum once he's safely bounded and gagged. If a feminist intellectual recommends a vigilante course of action, you know it has to be sound. Plus, the word "vigilante" sounds similar to vagina. And that's always re#$%$uring. - Tell UNC feminists that some handguns can also be used as sex toys. A few years ago, UNC Chapel Hill decided that "orgasm awareness week" was of enough intellectual value to merit funding from the university. In fact, they built a temporary vibrator museum right there in the middle of the campus. I told Katie that she should just tell campus feminists that they don't have to be afraid of handguns. Tying it into sex (please, no bondage jokes) is a sure way to win over the hearts and minds of sex crazed, I mean, intellectually gifted UNC feminists. Tell them the guns can also be used as sex toys and you'll get full funding. Tell them that guns can also be used to perform late term abortions (4th trimester and beyond) and they'll make you director of the Women's Center. - Dress up as a gorilla and throw bananas at the audience. A few years ago, our women's center paid for a group called the Gorilla Girls to come to campus. They were some serious intellectuals. They dressed up in gorilla costumes and threw bananas at audience members. I told Katie she should emulate them. Put on a gorilla outfit and throw bananas at students who are there earning extra credit. Hit them in the face with those bananas. I mean, knock the #$%$ out of them. Hit them hard enough and they'll start to agree that they need to be armed with handguns to protect themselves from #$%$ault and battery. - Fly in on a private jet. Arianna Huffington was paid $12,500 to fly into UNC - Wilmington on a private jet. During her tree hugging feminist speech, she lectured the audience about driving SUVs and wasting precious gasoline. Nothing communicates a need for a giant honorarium better than having your own private jet. And people who use a private jet to facilitate a lecture on energy conservation tend to be intellectually gifted, high value speakers. - Stop wearing makeup and shaving your arm pits. I know she's never heard this before but Katie is not ugly. And that's a serious problem for her. These UNC feminists are tough on good looking women. They have a real disdain for makeup and razor blades. If Katie started looking a little more like a French foreign exchange student then she might be taken more seriously by the UNC feminists. In a nutshell, when a woman dresses and carries herself like Katie Pavlich, bad things are bound to happen. She really brought the whole thing on herself and should have sought my advice much sooner. If she had, she would be rubbing elbows with Gorilla Girls and making a down payment on her first private jet. In all seriousness, I believe it’s time for UNC-CH to stop holding itself out as an institution interested in achieving intellectual diversity through the free and open exchange of ideas. And it's past time to get rid of its official motto, Lux Libertas. How about Collis Hypocrisi instead? Mike Adams</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1379076350093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 08:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379076894012-8</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings website has new Phantom Swift drone---incredible--they may have got it 100% right</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1378942991597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 19:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very sorry for the error. I thought it was designed and built in 90 days. The eyes played tricks. They did it in 30 days is amazing. Their design and build process should be shared with the engineers and manufacturing depts throughout Boeing.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1379076894012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 08:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379078525480-9</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of Left Wing Intellectualism in our Universities</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1379076350093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 08:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Evidently in your delusional mind we are all sparties now.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1379078525480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379080383422-10</Id><Title>Can we hit 111 today ;-) OH YEAH !!!!</Title><Msg>The shorts are feeling it ;-)</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1379080383422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379080743260-11</Id><Title>The Rise of right wing anti Intellectualism outside our Universities</Title><Msg>Typical of the dark and middle ages this anti intellectualism resides with uneducated ignorant hateful forces and wannabe feudal economic system backers. Virtually without exception the basic causation of anti intellectualism is fear, greed and ignorance. A half dozen or so posters on this board are locked into pathological anti intellectualism with hate and ignorance permeating their posts. These individuals have failed to accept and embrace the thought, ethics and philosophy of the age of the enlightenment (known as liberalism) and true to their puritan forebearers seem unable to progress to higher thought processes. In the past eras of human evolution these types have generally become extinct over time as will the current crop of anti intellectuals- but alas it could take decades if not centuries</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379080743260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379082060824-12</Id><Title>Sure glad Al Q is on the run and decimated . . . Oh wait !!</Title><Msg>DUBAI (Reuters) - Al Qaeda leader Ayman al-Zawahri urged small-scale attacks inside the United States to "bleed America economically", adding he hoped eventually to see a more significant strike, according to the SITE monitoring service. In an audio speech released online a day after the 12th anniversary of the 9/11 strikes, Zawahri said attacks "by one brother or a few of the brothers" would weaken the U.S. economy by triggering big spending on security, SITE reported. Western counter-terrorism chiefs have warned that radicalized "lone wolves" who might have had no direct contact with al Qaeda posed as great a risk as those who carried out complex plots like the 9/11 attacks. "We should bleed America economically by provoking it to continue in its massive expenditure on its security, for the weak point of America is its economy, which has already begun to stagger due to the military and security expenditure," he said. Keeping America in such a state of tension and anticipation only required a few disparate attacks "here and there", he said +++++ Reuters claimed they were unable to verify the audio-video . .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1379082060824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 10:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379082266143-13</Id><Topic><Title>What Happed to all those Global Warming caused Hurricanes?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378914881105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Land subsidence is occurring on the East Coast and Gulf Coast but the unscientific college English majors in the media report it as ALL sea level rise. Sea level rise has been rising at a rate of 2cm/yr. for at least 120 years in linear fashion. Geophysical Research Letters has a study, "Contribution of the pacific decadal oscillation to global mean sea level trends" indicating that the Pacific Decadal Oscillator has contributed .49cm/year to sea level rise since 1950. This contribution to SLR is significant but it is a natural contributor to SLR that when accounted for would show that man has had no impact on SLR during this period as is often claimed. The long term tide gauge measurements (used to calibrate satellites) show a linear trend of 2cm/year of SLR for the last 120 years with no correlation with increased CO2, just as has been the case of no correlation between increased CO2 and hurricanes or tornadoes.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379082266143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 10:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379082606934-14</Id><Topic><Title>What Happed to all those Global Warming caused Hurricanes?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378914881105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The long term tide gauge record of sea level rise shows no correlation between CO2 increase and sea level rise. Scientists have just found natural contributors like the PDO have been the primary cause of sea level change not man.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379082606934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 10:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379083079295-15</Id><Topic><Title>Can we hit 111 today ;-) OH YEAH !!!!</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1379080383422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next week the odds are better 787-9 should be flying and then we'll throw a Shortfry Party$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379083079295</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 10:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379083207911-16</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of right wing anti Intellectualism outside our Universities</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379080743260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some day we could all be as enlightened as you obviously are. They call that state of affairs a dark age. LMAO.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1379083207911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 10:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379083537228-17</Id><Topic><Title>What Happed to all those Global Warming caused Hurricanes?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378914881105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No longer "Global Warming" talking points sent out by Gore and friends have quietly changed term to "Climate Change" because they kept on getting beat up when forecast were consistantly wrong on the temp side.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1379083537228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 10:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379083904400-18</Id><Topic><Title>What Happed to all those Global Warming caused Hurricanes?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378914881105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Note that the GRACE satellite measurements for ice melt in the Arctic and Antarctic were terribly wrong and had to be adjusted in 2012. After adjustments scientists learned that the Antarctic has been increasing ice mass balance at a rate of 49Gt/year since 2002 and that Greenland ice mass loss was only about half of what had previously been reported. The models for sea level rise had to be adjusted downward because of these errors so the IPCC should be lowering the future sea level rise estimates in their upcoming report. The longest records of Arctic temperatures (Danish Meteorological Institute) recorded 2013 as the coldest summer since records began in 1957. At the same time 2013 also set a record for sea ice extent in the Antarctic which also has been getting colder in the last decade. The major cause of ice mass balance loss in Greenland has been aerosols like soot and black carbon coming from Asia and settling on Greenland ice surface and causing a drop in ice albedo thus increasing surface melt. Cloud cover reduction in the Arctic has also been a factor. It has been predicted by Solar Physicists that we will experience a 30 or 40 year solar minimum starting in 2014 or 2015. It will be interesting to see how a drop of 1.0 W/m^2 in Total Solar Irradiance will affect the Earth's temperature.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379083904400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 10:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379086292578-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of right wing anti Intellectualism outside our Universities</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379080743260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zo - all of the professors were liberal in the 1960s and 1970s but they were traditional liberal intellectuals. There has been a proliferation of anti American radicals, Socialists/Communists and anarchists that have perverted traditional liberal thinking within universities today. JFK was a traditional liberal but I think he would reject radical liberal "intellectuals" like Bill Ayers, John Holdren, Van Jones, etc. that Obonzo finds so appealing and seeks advice from. Consider liberal Rahm Emmanuel, who fits the traditional liberal description, who has made his contempt for radical Progressives known. So your argument doesn't stick man.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379086292578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379086414980-20</Id><Title>Thai Airways inspects Airbus A330 fleet</Title><Msg>Thai Airways orders inspection of Airbus A330s after landing gear collapse warned of in 2011. Article here: http://finance.yahoo.com/news/thai-airways-inspects-airbus-a330-143105135.html</Msg><Username>canthisbetakentoo</Username><Timestamp>1379086414980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379086545362-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of right wing anti Intellectualism outside our Universities</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379080743260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aint gonna happen zombie-- you guys and your would be decendants are going extinct because of your failure to make the right choices- your kind are becoming extinct thruout the third world as we speak. These elements of the population either die off or change their ways and accept the more beneficial ideas of intellectualism to enable them and their decendants to survive</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379086545362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379086665278-22</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of right wing anti Intellectualism outside our Universities</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379080743260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your sour grapes approach isn't going to work censored-- the reason you are an anti intellectual is because you think intellectualism is bad for mankind but you are mistaken and the entire element of the human race who think like you do will fail to survive the coming ages and become extinct</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379086665278</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379086734350-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of Left Wing Intellectualism in our Universities</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1379076350093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 08:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Left Wing Intellectualism is an oxymoron and like a square circle or intellectuals shouting hope and change, hope and change, yes we can.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379086734350</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379087276993-24</Id><Title>Prior the election the black unemployment rate was 19% its now over 22% and climbing. Now who is a racist?</Title><Msg>Obama is doing nothing for blacks, while blacks scream his approval.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379087276993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:47:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379087530979-25</Id><Title>Split Talk</Title><Msg>Does BA have authorization for a split and does it have sufficient shares to do so at say 2:1?</Msg><Username>mlljpl</Username><Timestamp>1379087530979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379088125586-26</Id><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Msg>Think about IRS abuse, EPA abuse, ATF abuse.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379088345270-27</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you don't know much about what actually goes on in Russia. Both countries have a lot of people in their prison systems, but guess which one has more people incarcerated for breaking laws that haven't been written yet.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379088345270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379088481486-28</Id><Topic><Title>Split Talk</Title><Username>mlljpl</Username><Timestamp>1379087530979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They occasionally perform splits, but I thought I read not too long ago that they had no intention of performing one in the near future. When considering splits, dividends have to be considered also.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379088481486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379088853988-29</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess which one goes into a business with guns drawn, seizes their property and shuts down their ability to operate and make a living without ever charging them with a crime and admitting they broke no U.S. Law. It seems their crime was donation money to an opposing political candidate. Has there a law been written for that crime yet.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088853988</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379088882444-30</Id><Topic><Title>Split Talk</Title><Username>mlljpl</Username><Timestamp>1379087530979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When we really start to fly higher maybe they'll think about it but first lets have a buy back. P.S. Love the new high and next week the 787-9 will test fly middle of next week and we might see new highs!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379088882444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379089093757-31</Id><Topic><Title>Thai Airways inspects Airbus A330 fleet</Title><Username>canthisbetakentoo</Username><Timestamp>1379086414980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They were aware of this problem since 2011!!! P.S. the one you a thumbs down must be that waynedickless!!! New High $110.52!!!!!!!!!!!!! :)</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379089093757</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379089283445-32</Id><Topic><Title>Split Talk</Title><Username>mlljpl</Username><Timestamp>1379087530979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are already in buy back mode, they just haven't had much need to implement much of it. They may decide to earmark that cash for something else, like increasing the dividend. They authorized the buy back to support the pps when they had trouble with the 787.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379089283445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379089912540-33</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or sending rodeo clowns to Obama indoctrination camps.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379089912540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379089979863-34</Id><Topic><Title>Thai Airways inspects Airbus A330 fleet</Title><Username>canthisbetakentoo</Username><Timestamp>1379086414980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne or one of his other 3 alias's</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1379089979863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379090116519-35</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why don't you run Putin as the GOP candy for president of the U.S. in 2016? Commie Putz.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379090116519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379090239810-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Leading From Behind?</Title><Username>jerrybrownbucks</Username><Timestamp>1378916239624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 12:17:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama isn't leading, not even from behind.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1379090239810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379090250808-37</Id><Topic><Title>'Obamacare' has saved Americans over $1 billion in 2012</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379087051723</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:44:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something tells me they are using the same kind of math which shows the unemployment rate falling.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379090250808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379090407204-38</Id><Topic><Title>Prior the election the black unemployment rate was 19% its now over 22% and climbing. Now who is a racist?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379087276993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is the white half's fault.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379090407204</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379090617714-39</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He isn't qualified. We know where Putin was born.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379090617714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379090665894-40</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a Republican so I can't speak for them but it may be because Democrats would demand his long form birth certificate and College records. Can't you answer the question putz genna?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379090665894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379090713417-41</Id><Topic><Title>Prior the election the black unemployment rate was 19% its now over 22% and climbing. Now who is a racist?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379087276993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that called a paradox? Blacks should reconsider their allegiance to the democrats, if that's isn't too difficult for them to contemplate.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1379090713417</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379090756106-42</Id><Title>Obamacare was going to save Americans, then the cost went to $880B, then $1.7T then after the Supreme Court looked at it 1.7T plus a tax.</Title><Msg>So far the nation has not insured just one poor person as the president has delayed the full implementation of the legislation. Those who are insured have had to pay pay pay. Boeing insurance was 100% today its 80% coverage co pays have doubled, deductible doubled. Also the nations is in a shift to part time labor to avoid the healthcare legislation. In the end the people who need the healthcare are not going to get it. All this spells is Bad Legislation.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379090756106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379090984475-43</Id><Title>Where is WayneDickhead? $110...LOL...</Title><Msg>Wayne is a sorry POS.</Msg><Username>tallicat9300</Username><Timestamp>1379090984475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379091283989-44</Id><Topic><Title>Heart n Soul of the Democrat Party</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1379090000066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats have always been the party of legalized theft and slavery. Thanks to their success, hard working Americans of all colors are only 1/3 slave and only forced to work 4 months of the year for the government bureaucrats. It only takes about 5% of GDP to fund the legitimate government operations, the other 20% they seize can correctly be labeled legalized theft.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379091283989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379091385688-45</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because you are full of bull!</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379091385688</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379091501831-46</Id><Title>RWNJ's - deluded simpletons?</Title><Msg>Or braind-washed extremeist right-wng Murdoch faux-news media dittoheaded Norquist Grover Pleadging Tea-bagged Koch-suckers?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379091501831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379091604312-47</Id><Topic><Title>RWNJ's - deluded simpletons?</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379091501831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:58:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moore-on,</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379091604312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379091623838-48</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The answer to that would be both of them. But pay attention to Russian politics. Putin keeps threatening a top political candidate with jail because he disagrees with Putin.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379091623838</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379091985900-49</Id><Title>The only Reason Democrats won't Admit Putin to their Party</Title><Msg>He won't quit humiliating Obama.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379091985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379092228980-50</Id><Topic><Title>RWNJ's - deluded simpletons?</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379091501831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:58:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen punk, you have to ask yourselff, what would Mittens Rawmoney do? a. whatever the angel moroni revealed to him b. he have to ask the church elders c. he would have to ask the Koch brothers d. he would have to ask what's his face P. Ryan the 3 hour marathon runner e. take credit for every Obama success f. all of the above Too bad your sole purpose to make Obama a one-term president failed, or that your wish for America to fail rather than for Obama succeed didn't work out either. Guess you are stuck on stupid - trying to find a smoking gun or blue dress for another +1000 days... or you could always become a rational and good American.</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379092228980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379092268082-51</Id><Topic><Title>Where is WayneDickhead? $110...LOL...</Title><Username>tallicat9300</Username><Timestamp>1379090984475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's been hiding or changed his ID thinks it's elonmusk!! I miss that Cheerleader! Do I hear Short Squeeze$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379092268082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379092349135-52</Id><Topic><Title>Split Talk</Title><Username>mlljpl</Username><Timestamp>1379087530979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be OK on hiking the Divi$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379092349135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379092424423-53</Id><Topic><Title>The only Reason Democrats won't Admit Putin to their Party</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379091985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can quitter Palin still see Putins missile from her backyard? Guess she like it the same way you do...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379092424423</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379092536698-54</Id><Topic><Title>Thai Airways inspects Airbus A330 fleet</Title><Username>canthisbetakentoo</Username><Timestamp>1379086414980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 11:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His ears are Ringing off the hook by now even his alias are quiet!! Newer High $110.70+</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379092536698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379092872453-55</Id><Topic><Title>Who has been more cruel to his Countrymen Putin or Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379088125586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the point is Obama ignores the Constitution. Freedom of Speech....in the end when Obama said Open government.....that of course was a lie. This presidency lives a life of hypocrisy too many lies to count. As he has delayed implementation of Obamacare not one poor person is insured while our healthcare costs have soared. Corporate America #$%$ to part time to avoid it. Bad legislation but Obama does not want to talk about it before the next election cycle</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379092872453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379093061737-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare was going to save Americans, then the cost went to $880B, then $1.7T then after the Supreme Court looked at it 1.7T plus a tax.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379090756106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bullongney. Many a</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379093061737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379093333660-57</Id><Title>Democrats call James Madison and Thomas Jefferson Rigt Wing Extremists</Title><Msg>......for having the Audacity to say forced benevolence is not a legitimate government function.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093333660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379093636207-58</Id><Title>The LWNJs Definition of "Right-Wing Extremists."</Title><Msg>People who want Lower Taxes, Smaller Government, balanced budgets and politicians who will obey the constitution.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093636207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379093944401-59</Id><Topic><Title>The LWNJs Definition of "Right-Wing Extremists."</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093636207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you forgot God and freedom, simpleton... Or, as a Great president once said: "I believe in human dignity as the source of national purpose, in human liberty as the source of national action, in the human heart as the source of national compassion, and in the human mind as the source of our invention and our ideas. It is, I believe, the faith in our fellow citizens as individuals and as people that lies at the heart of the liberal faith. For liberalism is not so much a party creed or set of fixed platform promises as it is an attitude of mind and heart, a faith in man's ability through the experiences of his reason and judgment to increase for himself and his fellow men the amount of justice and freedom and brotherhood which all human life deserves I believe also in the United States of America, in the promise that it contains and has contained throughout our history of producing a society so abundant and creative and so free and responsible that it cannot only fulfill the aspirations of its citizens, but serve equally well as a beacon for all mankind. I do not believe in a superstate. I see no magic in tax dollars which are sent to Washington and then returned. I abhor the waste and incompetence of large-scale federal bureaucracies in this administration as well as in others. I do not favor state compulsion when voluntary individual effort can do the job and do it well. But I believe in a government which acts, which exercises its full powers and full responsibilities. Government is an art and a precious obligation; and when it has a job to do, I believe it should do it. And this requires not only great ends but that we propose concrete means of achieving them. Our responsibility is not discharged by announcement of virtuous ends. Our responsibility is to achieve these objectives with social invention, with political skill, and executive vigor. I believe for these reasons that liberalism is our best and only hope in the world today. For the liberal society is a free society, and it is at the same time and for that reason a strong society. Its strength is drawn from the will of free people committed to great ends and peacefully striving to meet them. Only liberalism, in short, can repair our national power, restore our national purpose, and liberate our national energies. What do our opponents mean when they apply to us the label "Liberal?" If by "Liberal" they mean, as they want people to believe, someone who is soft in his policies abroad, who is against local government, and who is unconcerned with the taxpayer's dollar, then the record of this party and its members demonstrate that we are not that kind of "Liberal." But if by a "Liberal" they mean someone who looks ahead and not behind, someone who welcomes new ideas without rigid reactions, someone who cares about the welfare of the people -- their health, their housing, their schools, their jobs, their civil rights, and their civil liberties -- someone who believes we can break through the stalemate and suspicions that grip us in our policies abroad, if that is what they mean by a "Liberal," then I'm proud to say I'm a "Liberal." President John Fitzgerald Kennedy</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379093944401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379094795159-60</Id><Topic><Title>The only Reason Democrats won't Admit Putin to their Party</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379091985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's already a Party member: Communist Party.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379094795159</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:53:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379095200325-61</Id><Topic><Title>The LWNJs Definition of "Right-Wing Extremists."</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093636207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you had to go back to JFK, who was actually a fiscal conservative to find an interesting quote.. You couldn't get anything the left has said in the last 50 that was well written?</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1379095200325</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:00:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379095395717-62</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare was going to save Americans, then the cost went to $880B, then $1.7T then after the Supreme Court looked at it 1.7T plus a tax.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379090756106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree..shut the gov down it down let the market fall. I enjoy reading European legislators poking fun at Obama, even Putin. Now blacks are speaking out against this thug. Economist Thomas Sowell and pediatric surgeon Ben Carson. These are black men that any white man would want to follow. Obama is an expert in nothing and the people who he has appointed have a collective expert rating of 13%. The lowest of any president in our nations history. The economy, healthcare and the foreign front all in chaos.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379095395717</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379095759287-63</Id><Topic><Title>The LWNJs Definition of "Right-Wing Extremists."</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093636207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well...your kind are kinda fonda quoting a putin, whose kgb days goes back to the JFK era... \ n'ect ce pas?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379095759287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379096035441-64</Id><Topic><Title>The LWNJs Definition of "Right-Wing Extremists."</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093636207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by the trial and error method a click near the bottom, and then paste someore but then all you have to say is hate, lies, ignorance, bigotry, and RIGHT-WING IDIOCY IN ESSENCE AND EMDODIMENT - A RWNJ'S WET-DREAM TO THE TENTH FOLD hence even their movement away from YOUR KIND</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379096035441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379096422317-65</Id><Topic><Title>YAHOO Message Boards like Lois Lerner’s IRS</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1379096110393</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:15:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you like the 'new' Yahooty sports page(s) layout? I, for one do not. Please stand up and be counted, instead of reporting me for a TOS violation for the 1000th time.... it must be you, nobody else has such little cajones... as for BA 110 yahoo/wahoo way to go/team exewpt mangement</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379096422317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379097049284-66</Id><Topic><Title>The LWNJs Definition of "Right-Wing Extremists."</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093636207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot JFK gave use tax biggest tax cut of all modern presidents and said " ask not what your country can do for you but ask what you can do for your country.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379097049284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379097123250-67</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of right wing anti Intellectualism outside our Universities</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379080743260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You equate intellectualism with Marxist ideology. What you offer is old news about a failed philosophy. How about we round up these "intellectuals" spend a few years working the fields the way Stalin did, and then see how many want to embrace a Marxist philosophy, assuming they survive as many did not under Stalin? You confuse rehashed failed Marxist philosophy that appeals to you with intellectualism. You ignore that emerging nations are running AWAY from Marxism towards free markets and competition while you, Obonzo and your so called intellectuals run blindly TOWARDS Marxism and away from free markets and competition. Read my post about the Shanghai school system compared to your "intellectual" Obonzo endorsed public school system in Washington DC. There is no intellectualism in your fanatical Marxist dogma only a history of applied failure.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379097123250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379097191766-68</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare was going to save Americans, then the cost went to $880B, then $1.7T then after the Supreme Court looked at it 1.7T plus a tax.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379090756106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"let the market fall" doomsday sayer 1001% in cash preciuos metals and tail-waggers</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379097191766</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379097712931-69</Id><Topic><Title>The only Reason Democrats won't Admit Putin to their Party</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379091985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Putin is too far right for the Democratic Party</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379097712931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379097890446-70</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could be an interesting develpoment of the Trayvon Martin child murder... even if he was momentarilrily under the influence of a gang of thugs on bath-salts at the 7/11 the z-man need to be held accountable</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379097890446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379097999808-71</Id><Topic><Title>Notice that the reason Putin is being criticized</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379072800833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 07:46:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a void maybe a putin kid could be 'president' of syria</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379097999808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379098034981-72</Id><Topic><Title>Notice that the reason Putin is being criticized</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379072800833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 07:46:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>instead of another costly U.S. puppet</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379098034981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379098188940-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a bunch of stuff would have to happen before i draw a red line including your blurred lines</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379098188940</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379098230183-74</Id><Title>Boeing Kickin` #$%$</Title><Msg>I can`t believe all of the BS that is posted on this board! Nothing but a bunch of Loosers! Go Boeing!! DrD</Msg><Username>drdiscretion</Username><Timestamp>1379098230183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379098307676-75</Id><Topic><Title>Dont feel bad that the American Empire is dying</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379030245243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:57:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Koch 'brothers' think they are 'bigger' than the fed(s)... like bonnie and clyde</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379098307676</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379098595025-76</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare was going to save Americans, then the cost went to $880B, then $1.7T then after the Supreme Court looked at it 1.7T plus a tax.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379090756106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at $3 per patient visit unde raygonomoics \i have spred the LOVE 1000 fold n'est ce pas but then was a 'red-necker/red-legger' with</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379098595025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379098668305-77</Id><Topic><Title>THIS IS ERECTION DAY for the DEMOCRAT'S WEINER - Peters out at 7%</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378823113745</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-10 10:25:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wiener said he 'came up short"</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379098668305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379098685314-78</Id><Topic><Title>The only Reason Democrats won't Admit Putin to their Party</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379091985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lololol yeah, and the 8th wonder of the world is spart-c-cuss this 9/11 anniversary went 'well' so far,...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379098685314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379098710653-79</Id><Topic><Title>The only Reason Democrats won't Admit Putin to their Party</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379091985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for a friday the 13th...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379098710653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379098774205-80</Id><Topic><Title>The only Reason Democrats won't Admit Putin to their Party</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379091985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and then there is always the market crashes of september and october to ticke about lol9lol</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379098774205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379099115075-81</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK?? So? What's the problem?</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379099115075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379099680591-82</Id><Title>110.oo</Title><Msg>let me access my memory bank(s)</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379099680591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379099721857-83</Id><Topic><Title>110.oo</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379099680591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:14:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only two to four more episodes \of breaking bad</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379099721857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379099877550-84</Id><Topic><Title>110.oo</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379099680591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:14:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're chidden me...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379099877550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379099887199-85</Id><Title>POLL: Americans' trust in government falls to all-time low...</Title><Msg>Good job Obama and democrats! Less than half of Americans trust the government to handle problems, a all-time low, according to a new poll. Just 49 percent of Americans said they had a great deal or fair amount of confidence in the federal government to handle international problems, according to a Gallup poll released Friday. The previous low was 51 percent in 2007. Which mean people trusted George Bush's government more than they do the corrupt lying Obama administration.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1379099887199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379100071247-86</Id><Title>Grateful Dead - Estimated Prophet / Eyes Of The World / St. Stephen</Title><Msg>got me though more than one gun fight...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379100071247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379100173296-87</Id><Title>Kerry's Russian counterpart mocks him for talking too much...</Title><Msg>Secretary of State John Kerry's negotiations with the Russian Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov got off to a rocky start Thursday, with the Russian mocking Kerry right at the outset. "They got off to a really bad start yesterday --- partly because of the Putin op-ed and partly because Kerry in the opening remarks spoke at length --- and I mean at length --- compared to the unprepared few welcoming comments from the Russian counterpart," NBC News foreign correspondent Andrea Mitchell said on "Morning Joe." "And then the Russian minister said at the end, very tartly, 'Sometimes diplomacy demands silence.'"</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1379100173296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379100267013-88</Id><Title>Liberals Adore Hillary</Title><Msg>So, why not a transvaginal implant to get them even closer?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1379100267013</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379100336174-89</Id><Title>To 'cleanse' the house of representatives of the fRWNJ filth</Title><Msg>we only have to 'clense' one room per 3-5 days</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379100336174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379100690925-90</Id><Topic><Title>Notice that the reason Putin is being criticized</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379072800833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 07:46:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fool - the pigs are Not outraged as you may think and the criticism has been for your benefit</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379100690925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379101135657-91</Id><Title>Who exactly is the CEO of Boeing?</Title><Msg>sometimes we ride alone...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379101135657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379101792740-92</Id><Topic><Title>The LWNJs Definition of "Right-Wing Extremists."</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093636207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh?</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1379101792740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379101923520-93</Id><Title>OH YEAH BABY 111 ;-) sweet ;-)</Title><Msg>How you shorts liken this ?</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1379101923520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379102025464-94</Id><Title>Pimping Putin !</Title><Msg>the Capitalist found a new product to peddle .... and suddenly he's a household name...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379102025464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379102055836-95</Id><Topic><Title>POLL: Americans' trust in government falls to all-time low...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1379099887199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even worse then Bush ...................WOW !</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379102055836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379102116592-96</Id><Topic><Title>Notice that the reason Putin is being criticized</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379072800833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 07:46:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why are you a war monger ? Why do you support Islamic extremists ? Why do you hate freedom ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379102116592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:55:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379102268934-97</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anderson Cooper = CIA = Vanderbilt Dynasty = Spawn of the New World Order google it and start getting educated on who runs the world</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379102268934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379102394749-98</Id><Topic><Title>Pimping Putin !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379102025464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These low life anti Obama everything folks are joke , their new hero is the ex head of the KGB, absolutely pathetic. War has been avoided by the Russian and US working together for a solution I say that`s a win all around for everybody!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1379102394749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379102482051-99</Id><Topic><Title>Notice that the reason Putin is being criticized</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379072800833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 07:46:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot - can't you read - where have i ever said i want war ?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379102482051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379102522759-100</Id><Topic><Title>POLL: Americans' trust in government falls to all-time low...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1379099887199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice spin , I bet you think the Titanic would not of sunk if they had changed the Captain after it struck the iceberg too .</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1379102522759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379102707406-101</Id><Topic><Title>Grateful Dead - Estimated Prophet / Eyes Of The World / St. Stephen</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379100071247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>callouses on my fingers \ \rings toes, nose, and ears tongue I'll be biden that this friday the 13th</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379102707406</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379103193741-102</Id><Topic><Title>False Flag of Syrian Gas attack CONFIRMED by Video footage</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377295105160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-23 17:58:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379103193741</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379103419276-103</Id><Title>Estimated Prphet...</Title><Msg>did Robert Hunter have anything to do with.., and if so did he use a gun ? My plan since I have so many wide and varied OPTIONS since heaven exists here on earth as well as well as in heaven RWNJ's must ar-go f tehmselves let me know when you are sane</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379103419276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379103743648-104</Id><Title>Sparty acknowldges a Syrian 'gas' attack...</Title><Msg>is the first step... even if it don;t look right in the minds eye is kooter libby dead</Msg><Username>skooterlibby</Username><Timestamp>1379103743648</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379103853449-105</Id><Title>boeing</Title><Msg>Read yesterday boeing had mover to #24 on the list of most shorted stocks, alot of traders getting hammered.</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1379103853449</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379104624668-106</Id><Title>More Millennials identify as liberals than conservatives</Title><Msg>.... Hardly any of them (10 percent) support the libertarian-embraced Tea Party. About three-quarters say they despise congressional Republicans. Nearly two-thirds voted for Obama in 2008. Slightly over half approve of him now. Nearly three-quarters of Millennials hate congressional Republicans. 55% trust in the U.S. military, one of the largest state-socialist programs in the entire world, also responsible for, you know, those wars that libertarians supposedly hate. Over a quarter put their faith in the federal government all or most of the time, and 55% “some of the time.” Only 17% answered “never.” And despite all their supposed Ron Paul love, they trust the “globalist” United Nations even more than they do the feds.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379104624668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379104741672-107</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of right wing anti Intellectualism outside our Universities</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379080743260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stalin?? Marx?? you are insane---no country on the planet is following the Stalinist nor Marxists- this is all part of your psychotic thought processes. No modern nation even third world nations consider themselves Stalinist or Marxist with the possible exception of Beylorussia or Cuba- You need psychiatric help. In this day and age there are psycho pharmaceutical approaches available to treat your mental disease. For gawds sake get help and take your meds- don't do it and you are going to be taken off the street and locked up in a rubber room</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379104741672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379104812093-108</Id><Topic><Title>What Happed to all those Global Warming caused Hurricanes?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378914881105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One of them is in the Gulf of Mexico now. It has your name all over it: Ingrid.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379104812093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379105373134-109</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats call James Madison and Thomas Jefferson Rigt Wing Extremists</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093333660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once again we are insulted by the big RWNJ lie about the originators of the Democrat party. Liberalism is a living thing which grows and enlarges thru the years as its practioners gain knowledge and experience. Jefferson being the humanitarian that he was would have given his blessing to all of the modern Democrat nostrums to ease the economically based pain of the masses and would have scolded the super rich for their lack of patriotism and quasi disloyalty to the United States. I have often wondered about your choice of a 'nym-- ie marxbouncers and have long suspected that you are a closet Marxist. We all know that you have used and abused welfare in the past and have seldom held a job- why not get it off your chest and admit your guilt-- you might even find forgiveness for your ignorance and weakness</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379105373134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379105905009-110</Id><Title>OBAMA MUST THINK HE IS "TOO BIG TO FAIL"</Title><Msg>How's that's been working out lately?</Msg><Username>vaiien2</Username><Timestamp>1379105905009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:58:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379105945168-111</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats call James Madison and Thomas Jefferson Rigt Wing Extremists</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093333660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they talked about forced benevolence they were referring to tithing.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379105945168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379106144756-112</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats call James Madison and Thomas Jefferson Rigt Wing Extremists</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093333660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tithing? Oh Really? • In 1794, when Congress appropriated $15,000 for relief of French refugees who fled from insurrection in San Domingo to Baltimore and Philadelphia, James Madison stood on the floor of the House to object saying, "I cannot undertake to lay my finger on that article of the Constitution which granted a right to Congress of expending, on objects of benevolence, the money of their constituents." -- James Madison, 4 Annals of congress 179 (1794)</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1379106144756</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379106351997-113</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You never cease to amaze me Raven..the UN has already come out and said the Rebels did it.....You can also go to You Tube and see the Rebels loading up Chemical Canisters into cannisters as they brag that they "Did It" ...Keep on catapulting the propaganda tho Ravin...maybe you and your bloodthirsty criminals in this administration can get your worthless undeclared war sooner or later...after all...if its a Democrat killing women and women with drones...its a "liberal and loving war"...</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379106351997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379106389601-114</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't understand hooze........What I meant was, as Hillary says, " what difference, at this point, does it make"?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1379106389601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379106910530-115</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats call James Madison and Thomas Jefferson Rigt Wing Extremists</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093333660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thomas Jefferson backed up Madison by declaring, "Congress has not unlimited powers to provide for the general welfare, but only those specifically enumerated." Check out Article 1, Section 8 of the constitution and you will see which ones were specifically enumerated.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1379106910530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379107512931-116</Id><Topic><Title>Pimping Putin !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379102025464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 15:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The enemy of Obama is my friend"--new Teabagger Official Slogan.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1379107512931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379107792963-117</Id><Title>Thomas Jefferson on Wealth Redistribution</Title><Msg>"To take from one, because it is thought his own industry and that of his fathers has acquired too much, in order to spare to others, who, or whose fathers, have not exercised equal industry and skill, is to violate arbitrarily the first principle of association, the guarantee to everyone the free exercise of his industry and the fruits acquired by it." -- Thomas Jefferson, letter to Joseph Milligan, April 6, 1816</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1379107792963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379108058955-118</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the Raven has a new war cry and a rebel yell......(Billy Idol)......to help hide his hyochrissy and shame......and besides, he thinks it's very, and I do mean very, trendy.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1379108058955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379108094680-119</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see any link to verify what you are claiming....</Msg><Username>pauln277</Username><Timestamp>1379108094680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379108123065-120</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tough talk from a couch potato private............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1379108123065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379108425532-121</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's too bad you always let your fevered rhetoric get in the way of explaining your position. As you know, but have conveniently forgotten in your brain-dissolving hatred, I have posted here that I opposed a U.S.-only military strike on Syria. I know how you must have bated to hear that; you hate everything and everyone except the lamebrains who post in support of your fantasies.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379108425532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379109094447-122</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats call James Madison and Thomas Jefferson Rigt Wing Extremists</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1379093333660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 13:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You only ever cite Madison when it suits you. How do you right-fringers explain this: "Madison campaigned for the Embargo Act of 1807, which prohibited American vessels from traveling to foreign ports and halted exports from the United States. Hugely unpopular, this measure proved to be an economic disaster for American merchants."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379109094447</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379109423567-123</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty acknowldges a Syrian 'gas' attack...</Title><Username>skooterlibby</Username><Timestamp>1379103743648</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in the 'pipeline'</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379109423567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 17:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379110101494-124</Id><Title>$111.95 after hours EOM</Title><Msg>EOM</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1379110101494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 18:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379110688527-125</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well the medical examiner had problems with consistency in his testimony and changed his mind on several issues according to the prosecutors. It looks to me like the ME was chosen to be the fall guy as Dems always have a fall guy to blame in failure. I guess Zimmerman can change his testimony too and claim that his head being bashed on the concrete made him delirious and like Hillary during Whitewater, he can't recollect how he shot Trayvon Martin. The verdict of innocence is public record and that isn't going to change. I can see where you might use this story as part of your race baiting initiative to keep the race baitable twits in Obonzo's camp as he crashes and burns.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379110688527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 18:18:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379112453926-126</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@ "Ban did not say that Assad's forces carried out a suspected chemical arms attack near Damascus investigated by UN experts. But he said the Syrian leader has "committed many crimes against humanity."" So the UN is not supporting Obonzo in Obonzo's version of the story that Assad was responsible for chemical use. One has to wonder how much of the Chicago Way political pressure/influence = $$$$, Oboonzo used on Ki-moon to give this half hearted indictment of Assad? This is quite laughable and the end result is that Obonzo still has no UN backing and no UN resolution and is still in a lurch, and as far as calling Assad a war criminal, that term has been applied equally to Obonzo on the world stage and in 1 million hits on google when you search for "Obama is a war criminal". Duh...........</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379112453926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 18:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379113247192-127</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA MUST THINK HE IS "TOO BIG TO FAIL"</Title><Username>vaiien2</Username><Timestamp>1379105905009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:58:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This President thinks he has Goldman Sachs written all over himself! No one adores this President more than this President!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1379113247192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379114777321-128</Id><Topic><Title>White House Petition Asks Obama to give Putin his Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379114343011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:19:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really identify with any and all idiots, don't you Loon?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379114777321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379115482786-129</Id><Title>GREAT TOM BROWN AND WAYNEDICK-FEB.....</Title><Msg>Waynedick said that the great tom brown indicated once boeing matches previous high of $ 107+ it will reverse and boeing will go back to $ 70's within a year. That's what bigidickwaynedick said! ....lmao....lmao....taht's my bigdickwaynedick...(now with a new id elon musk something! )i agree $ 70's but after 2 for 1 spilt within 12 to 18 months.</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1379115482786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379115803409-130</Id><Topic><Title>White House Petition Asks Obama to give Putin his Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379114343011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:19:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dog gone it, I forgot again, why did they give Bozo a Nobel Prize in the first place? It wasn't for turning lead into gold, was it?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1379115803409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379115972741-131</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I do lose I don't act like a spoiled child and blame others like Obonzo has done his entire life. Do you consider Obonzo as a "winner" in his current handling of Syria?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379115972741</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379117811309-132</Id><Topic><Title>White House Petition Asks Obama to give Putin his Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379114343011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:19:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, chris_genna2.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1379117811309</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 20:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379118869265-133</Id><Topic><Title>Satifaction</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379116149980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the snake was multi-colored \ king snake IAM not gonna kill a multi-colored snake nAMD aSSAD UNTIL tOADAY</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379118869265</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 20:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379119043875-134</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Obama had some bad advice (probably from the Pentagon, who can never resist trying out their toys, or some holdover neocons in the woodwork of the situation room. I think he felt duty-bound to do what he thought was the right thing to do given a breach of the chem weapons treaty, even if he had to go it alone -- you would call it brass balls if he were a Repugnantcon. I think his posturing brought Russia around to the things it could lose if the treaty were not upheld. (How do you spell Kazakhstan and Chechnya?) I saw Putin's offer as potentially getting Obama out from between a rock and a hard place, and I respect him for finally knuckling down to some honest diplomacy. (Though I can detect nothing happening YET.) But I don't see Putin as one-upping US (yes, it's US, not just Obama) and I don't see our president as the kind of craven and inept clown you would like to think he is, or would like others to think he is. His demeanor throughout this whole "crisis" is 1,000 times better than the last gunslinger we had in the Oval Office. I wish him the best because. as LBJ might have said, he has all our peckers in his pocket. Why do you think YOURS is not?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379119043875</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 20:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379119801594-135</Id><Title>DTRI8KE A RUSSIAN IN MOSCOW</Title><Msg>IN THE FACE \AND COVER IT IT FILM</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379119801594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 20:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379119854944-136</Id><Topic><Title>DTRI8KE A RUSSIAN IN MOSCOW</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379119801594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 20:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHEN THR WOOFR COMES DOWN \ BY HTE ROLLING STONES</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379119854944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 20:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379119938665-137</Id><Topic><Title>DTRI8KE A RUSSIAN IN MOSCOW</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379119801594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 20:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TANX ALOT</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379119938665</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 20:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379121038154-138</Id><Title>BA/Airbus deliveries thru 9-13</Title><Msg>Per planespotters database: BA= 19 planes Airbus= 14 planes</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1379121038154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379121203435-139</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no loser because the game is not over yet. It is true that Putin covets the Nobel Peace Prize.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379121203435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379121421498-140</Id><Title>Earnings Monday comes as a surprise heard Cramer say he expects a beat plus has room to continue to run!</Title><Msg>Didn't realize we had earning's already anyone have a opinion on the outcome?</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1379121421498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:17:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379122917148-141</Id><Title>"Free Markets" are an Oxymoron</Title><Msg>Published on Friday, September 13, 2013 by Common Dreams The 4 (or 5) Worst Market Failures in Human History by Stan Sorscher I'm a capitalist for one reason: to raise living standards in my community. A familiar mantra of capitalism guides me: Markets are powerful and efficient. I'm also a realist, so I temper that mantra: Markets are powerful and efficient. And markets fail. Market failure is an established, well-understood field of study in mainstream economics. Generations of economists accept the basics of market failure. However, American economists turn their heads away at the mention of it, because it sounds like heresy. Consider the four biggest market failures in human history: •Climate change: $40 trillion, so far •Health care in America: trillions per year, ongoing •The housing-financial asset bubble: at least $8 trillion •Free trade: $8 trillion, so far According to the chief economist for the World Bank, Nicholas Stern, climate change is the greatest market failure in human history. Greenhouse gas emissions are a classic externality, where everyone on earth subsidizes oil companies and consumers of fossil fuels. Fossil fuels are under-priced by $40 trillion -- a rough estimate of the cost that future generations will pay for damage we're doing to the Earth. Health care in America wastes roughly $1 trillion per year, compared to other wealthy countries, and the problem is steadily worsening. First, health care is not a market. A market involves buyers and sellers. In American health care, we're not really sure who is a buyer and a seller. Figure 1. Find the buyer and the seller in American health care. As a result, market incentives are badly misaligned. Very few patients shop around for deals. After the doctor says the word "cancer," most people lose their shopping instincts. The housing and financial asset bubble is a classic market failure. Mortgage brokers misled home buyers into bad mortgages. Banks bundled unaffordable mortg</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1379122917148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379122988950-142</Id><Title>In the Soviet of Seattle - use of word CITIZEN is Offensive</Title><Msg>Back in August .. A memo sent out to Seattle Public Affairs Officers this week listed new rules that included a ban on the words “brown bag” and “citizens” due to their “offensive nature.” In a report entitled “On ‘brown bags, ‘citizens’ and language” by Elliott Bronstein of the Office for Civil Rights, Bronstein goes on to say that both terms are potentially offensive, especially “brown bag” since Black American’s skin was compared to brown paper bags 100 years ago. “The term ‘brown bag’ doesn’t bother everybody, but . . . there is a history behind the use of it,” Bronstein told the Seattle PI. The City of Seattle has used the phrase “brown bags” for years, a term referring to meetings where participants bring a lunch from home, usually in brown paper bags. Bronstein suggested that “lunch-and-learn” and “sack lunch” are more viable options. Bronstein went on to call for the end of the word “citizens” which could be offensive to people who aren’t legal citizens, noting the city’s decision to change the Citizens Service Bureau into the “Customer” Service Bureau several years back. +++ perhaps the preferred words are COMRADE- GRUNT - PEASANT - SHEEP - PROLETARIAT ? AND Washington state’s governor Jay Inslee signed legislation earlier this year to make Washington statutes “less sexist” by changing words that included “man” in them. “Freshman” became “first-year student” and “penmanship” became “handwriting.” How about new students being called Young Pioneers ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1379122988950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379123015651-143</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings Monday comes as a surprise heard Cramer say he expects a beat plus has room to continue to run!</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1379121421498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:17:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was Cramer correct and do we report Monday inquisitive minds want to know?</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1379123015651</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379123055336-144</Id><Topic><Title>"Free Markets" are an Oxymoron</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1379122917148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:41:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The housing and financial asset bubble is a classic market failure. Mortgage brokers misled home buyers into bad mortgages. Banks bundled unaffordable mortgages into bogus securities and sold them to investors. Rating agencies provided false security to investors. Herd mentality and massive group-think inflated the asset bubble. Losses in housing values alone exceeded $8 trillion. We should add costs for the recession, millions of foreclosed homes, personal bankruptcies, lost opportunities, millions of workers unemployed and careers damaged permanently. Markets rewarded bad behavior and punished millions who behaved responsibly. Free trade is a market failure, but it is also an intellectual failure for the economics profession, and a policy failure on the part of elected officials. Our cumulative trade debt since NAFTA is well over $8 trillion. Our economy is de-industrializing, with thousands of factories closed, millions of jobs lost, and no improvement in sight. Free trade has enjoyed inexplicably unassailable reverence since David Ricardo introduced it in 1817. It was unrealistic in 1817, and it is unrealistic today. It starts with hopelessly idealized assumptions, applied blindly in the complex global economy, where trading partners and multinational companies exploit those assumptions for their own purposes. We were promised mutual gain, but we suffer huge deficits, concentration of wealth and power among trade's "winners" and loss of bargaining power, de-industrialization and stagnant wages for the rest of us. If the study of free trade were moved from economics departments in universities to mathematics departments, it would be discredited on logical grounds by the end of the first day. Similarly, its half-life in a physics, astronomy, or chemistry department would be a week or two -- the time it would take to send graduates students to the lab to collect data. It is worth noting that conventional free trade theory is considered largely irrelevant in business schools, where students learn the realities of how to move capital and production around the world. Worse by far, our so-called free trade agreements are really designed to protect and enrich global companies. These agreements toss aside democratic checks and balances, weaken civil society and erode the middle class. Under the right conditions, markets will, in fact, produce broad-based well-being. In 1776, Adam Smith argued that beneficial market control occurred when merchants in the village were personally connected to the well-being of their neighbors, who lived and shopped in the village. Social and economic cohesion would prevent market failure. But globalization, as we've managed it, de-couples modern corporate decision-makers from any obligation or connection to communities anywhere. The test of a market economy is whether it raises living standards. We fail that test when we look at growing inequality and reduced career prospects for the next generations of Americans. As a society, we have stopped sharing the gains from productivity and trade. Almost all new income goes to the top 1 percent -- more than $1 trillion per year. Some economists object that inequality is beyond the narrow scope of economics, so it's not "really" a market failure. Granted, our looming inequality has broad dimensions -- social, political and moral, as well as economic. However, when economists duck responsibility for inequality, they are really acknowledging that free markets and free trade will predictably create inequality, without strong intervention in the form of public policy and social values. That sounds like market failure to me. Here's the take-away message. The narrow orthodoxy of free markets and free trade says that markets will solve all our problems, and government intervention is bad. Look at politics in America, today. Unfortunately, the real world is a very large system with many interacting forces and interests. Markets fail. A legitimate purpose of public policy is to intervene in markets to prevent market failure. Public policy has a necessary role in protecting the environment, human rights, labor rights, education and public health, managing growth, regulating markets, and managing global trade. That's capitalism for realists. Stan Sorscher is on staff at Society for Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace (SPEEA), a labor union representing aerospace engineers, scientists and technical workers, and is President of the Washington Fair Trade Coalition. He is active in trade, economic development, and other public policy issues.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1379123055336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379123302057-145</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@ "yes, it's US, not just Obama" He is a craven inept clown and his record demonstrates it. Who said "I Got Bin Laden" rather than "we" got Bin Laden or the "Navy Seals" got Bin Laden? Good leaders give credit to others when things go well and good leaders don't blame others when things go wrong. Obonzo does just the opposite. With Obonzo it's always about him. I've seen his empty suit politics and his lack of executive skills for to long. I've seen his phony act since the day he entered politics and I have not seen a change in his behavior. He is still the same guy that voted "Present" most of his career as an Illinois pol. His ego and arrogance is what led him into this Syrian mess and while he seems to have motivated you to feel inclusive in his stupidity, ego and arrogance I am immune from years of exposure to his stupidity ego and arrogance.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379123302057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379123368916-146</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's sons beat Shorty to death in his car.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379123368916</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379123750585-147</Id><Topic><Title>Satifaction</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379116149980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 19:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WITHOUT PROOF</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379123750585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379123773355-148</Id><Topic><Title>The Rise of right wing anti Intellectualism outside our Universities</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379080743260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadly there are enough of these morons in congress to severely limit funding for scientific research and put a chill on scientists ability to pursue several fields deemed "unacceptable". We are on the path to third world status if they aren't stopped.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1379123773355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379124069021-149</Id><Topic><Title>RWNJ's - deluded simpletons?</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379091501831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:58:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank goodness we still have a Republican controlled House of Representatives and a Supreme Court to try and keep, as you say "a rational and good America", or at the or at least some semblance of it.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379124069021</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379124113072-150</Id><Title>hello was cramer wrong or right do we report monday or did i add today for the wrong reason?</Title><Msg>serious when i heard boeing was reporting i didn't hesitate just jumped,now that i have had time to think about his statement on his show i believe he could of been wrong someone give me a answer to my post thanks.</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1379124113072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379124380100-151</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America had a lynch rate of ~100 hangings per year in 1900. "In Winchester, Tennessee, a maddened crowd of whites burned a black man at the stake and sold slices of his roasted liver." Theodore Rex by Edmond Morris Guess you and your ilk were born 100 years too late, you missed out on your slice! Oh for the good old days.........</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1379124380100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379124569709-152</Id><Title>THESE BOYS</Title><Msg>der Beatles not a one wanta t beat my #$%$ \over The Revolution or The Constitution</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379124569709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379124615813-153</Id><Topic><Title>hello was cramer wrong or right do we report monday or did i add today for the wrong reason?</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1379124113072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>report earnings Monday? No.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379124615813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379125053306-154</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But, the truth is, not all who were lynched were black. In the late 1800's and early 1900' many communities of divided opinions resorted to terror tactics and lynchings to sway the other side. And in many rural areas people caught thieving or rustling or even thought to be guilty of those or any other unacceptable activities were sometimes lynched: black, white, or any other color.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379125053306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379125502117-155</Id><Topic><Title>hello was cramer wrong or right do we report monday or did i add today for the wrong reason?</Title><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1379124113072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well I had just flew in and was waiting in the airport tuned in to cnbc heard Cramer say we were reporting I jumped the gun,I will blame it on jet lag anyway I bought so my position is 300 more oh well maybe it was meant to be?</Msg><Username>skipaway</Username><Timestamp>1379125502117</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379125659068-156</Id><Title>The foggy-bottom boys</Title><Msg>this is gonna make us bigger than Obama and the most girl who made peace signs cross-legged with the sawdust in the main floor of the gym apparently it was an apparition or I have to chew my words carfully./. aren't you....</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379125659068</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379125800389-157</Id><Title>does hooz lie half of the time or all of the time the answer</Title><Msg>consensus is 1 guy said half the time, 10000000000 said all of the time. The answer is ALL OF THE TIME</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379125800389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379125970025-158</Id><Topic><Title>RWNJ's - deluded simpletons?</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379091501831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 12:58:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aIl I would have to do is ask an english teacher about your sentence structure...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379125970025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379126045475-159</Id><Title>WHY do liberals demonize those who don't think like they do. Why does a president send out IRS attack dogs</Title><Msg>even to the Billy Graham non profit using thuggery twice in 6 months. Why does a president send out IRS attack dogs and get away with it.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379126045475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379126284789-160</Id><Title>Toys in the attic?</Title><Msg>Any mre questions ?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379126284789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379126518677-161</Id><Title>two experts one a scholar economist the other a MD oppose Obama on ideology on the Economy and Healthcare what they common?</Title><Msg>all black, but the two are experts in their fields when Obama is a community watch dog. A lot like Zimmerman.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379126518677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379126604984-162</Id><Title>Zacks still has Boeing on</Title><Msg>HOLD</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379126604984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379127180147-163</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA MUST THINK HE IS "TOO BIG TO FAIL"</Title><Username>vaiien2</Username><Timestamp>1379105905009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:58:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too big to fail, too small to succeed . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379127180147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 22:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379127743667-164</Id><Topic><Title>Sure glad Al Q is on the run and decimated . . . Oh wait !!</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1379082060824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 10:21:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B.O. built a nice cozy animal refuge for them in Libya . He tried to do the same thing in Egypt, but the Egyption military has other ideas . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379127743667</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379127947580-165</Id><Title>Can I be xcused from the table...</Title><Msg>where xactly are we three going ? to throw some apricots off a tree onto passingy autmobiles and digesting for fun otto what do you mean I have to run ding ding ding ding ding ding splat \because it was \my apricots 3,2,1 we also most successfully play3d Sink The Bismrak for fun...this time is\ is not apricots</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379127947580</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379128625418-166</Id><Topic><Title>Can I be xcused from the table...</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379127947580</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did I sat splat whe I meant ding ding ding afterall only one can hld nine apricots in hs hands and time his throws and they say new CEO of yahooty is cool \throbbing</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379128625418</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379129120723-167</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon was SHOT in the BACK??</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379097169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 14:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Between 1882 and 1968 1,297 whites were lynched vs 3,445 blacks (especially in the old Confederacy). Blacks were/are ~10% of the US population. You do the math. faculty.berea.edu/browners/chesnutt/classroom/lynchingstat.html</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1379129120723</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379129426069-168</Id><Title>A black Corvette with 10 dings in it....</Title><Msg>apparently I was correct in my estimates of time a n distance and "beat the chid outta me" shoulkd they'catch me" half a night wasted</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379129426069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379129510648-169</Id><Title>Airbus stock price increase year to date 51% Boeing 47%, 3 years Airbus up 144%,Boeing loser at only76%</Title><Msg>For Boeing, the answer to that question will always depend on the commercial airliner market. That division accounts for two-thirds of Boeing's revenue and more than 80% of operating profit, which turns its government contracts into a nearly irrelevant sideshow for investors. , Boeing is betting big on the 787 Dreamliner jumbo jet. -- if two crucial assumptions play out as planned. One is that the competition doesn't catch up to Boeing's technological advantage right away. Largest rival Airbus has been working on a similar design known as the A350 since 2004. The A350 made its first test flight this summer and enters airline service in 2014, which gives Boeing about a year's worth of exclusive sales in this category. The other vital assumption is that the Dreamliner is, in fact, fit to fly. Battery problems have caused fires on three Dreamliners this year. That's bad for Boeing in at least two ways: Airlines might hold back on 787 orders until Boeing proves that the fire hazards are long gone, and consumers might worry that Dreamliner flights are not safe. These fears can linger long after the actual danger is gone.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1379129510648</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379130011349-170</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad for you. Letting yourself be ruled by a craven inept clown. A real man would move to Russia and be ruled by Putin. Hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379130011349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:40:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379130019040-171</Id><Title>787 lemon or as Boeing says "“committed to improving the 787’s in-service dispatch reliability</Title><Msg>The Norwegian low-cost carrier has two 787s, and has six more on order. A week ago, the first was grounded for five days after a power supply issue to the electric brake system showed up during routine maintenance on the ground Five days later, that was fixed, but on Saturday the carrier’s second 787 developed an apparently unrelated power supply problem, this time connected to the jet’s central computing system. In a statement, a Boeing spokesman said the company is “committed to improving the 787’s in-service dispatch reliability ...(with) a significant focus on component reliability improvements</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1379130019040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379130171638-172</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, Obama gave FULL credit to the military team who went in and got Bin Laden. You're entitled to your opinion, but not your own facts.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379130171638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379130285660-173</Id><Topic><Title>In the Soviet of Seattle - use of word CITIZEN is Offensive</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1379122988950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 21:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need some new things to get mad about, Don. But this, however novel, isn't it. You do know the NMFS started calling fishermen fishers back about 1842, don't you? Silly, but hardly anything to start a revolution over.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379130285660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379130356778-174</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, he has to get his own -- not Obama's ;-D</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379130356778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379131019628-175</Id><Topic><Title>C'mon, Vlad. We're waiting to see if you put your hammer where your sickle is.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379105525543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 16:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My ideal and my goal, as it should be for all men willing to fight for freedom, is to not be ruled by ANYONE. You suggest that since I don't want to be ruled by Obonzo that I should go be ruled by Putin. I don't want to be ruled by Obonzo or Putin as neither case is acceptable. Here you once again demonstarte limited and linear thinking. Even in your comments you illustrate that you think in terms of being ruled and it speaks to your subconscious want and need to be ruled. I reject your thinking.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1379131019628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:56:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379131198005-176</Id><Title>I have akways windered why they CHOSE kneel armstrong over donwshuper</Title><Msg>but not very often</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1379131198005</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-13 23:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>