<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371528241448-1</Id><Topic><Title>The Cowardly Character Assassination of Sarah Palin</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371492187764</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She would not have sold guns to Mex drug lords, flushed billions on solar Solidras down the crapper, jacked into phones &amp; e-mails of millions, used the IRS, EPA, Labor Dept, etc as a hit team against those who disagree, abandoned those in Benghazi, spent endless hours playing golf, promoted policies of high unemployment &amp; low GDP, and she can put a baseball over the plate.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1371528241448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371529387845-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Cowardly Character Assassination of Sarah Palin</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371492187764</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bozo palin would have done all those things you bray about if she had to to serve the super rich- George H W Bush's idiot son would have done it also----- straighten up for a change and stop acting like the village idiot you are</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371529387845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371529436075-3</Id><Title>103.03 1.20(1.18%) 4:00PM EDT|After Hours : 103.38 0.35 (0.34%)</Title><Msg>all lights are Green all systems are Go except for a couple three things... 1. Tuesday will be a sell off 2. based on the supposed threat of Ben(jamin) Bernanke 3. and the most evil #$%$ Chieney raising his ugly head, after living a long and fruitless evil life, putting himself to the front of the line for a heart transplant ahead of a 12 yer old, so he could utter "Snowden is a traitor" and lie some more about 9/11, saying that"if he had the NSA phone monotoring program, 9/11 would not have happened", when in fact the NSA phone monitoring program was intiated seven months before 9/11 under his 'watch'... 4. nevermind</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371529436075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371529564192-4</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not a question of "need," Sparty. It's all about FREEDOM!! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371529564192</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371529616300-5</Id><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Msg>28 replies to spartaloon ? am I missing something...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371529616300</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:26:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371530065983-6</Id><Topic><Title>How is Obonzo different from Bush?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371487194039</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 12:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've got a feeling (to parahrase one of the great Beatles, sir Paul McCartney, who singlehandedly put Burt Bcharach. Elton, Hamlisch, Rogers, and some of the B's = Bch, Beethoven tp shemp-;and if he wanted to... you would suck Randy paul's pud based on disinformation</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371530065983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371530534211-7</Id><Topic><Title>Lots of awards for Boeing today-- must read message</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371461684147</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 05:34:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think BA should claim the Ryanair order as new and firm it up with 175 aircraft plus 200 MAXs.</Msg><Username>mental_dwarf1</Username><Timestamp>1371530534211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371530627823-8</Id><Topic><Title>Lots of awards for Boeing today-- must read message</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371461684147</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 05:34:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, British Airways will be firming up 18 787s, plus 100 787-10xs, China Airlines needs to firm up 31 aircraft, etc. Couple of these are 747-8s.</Msg><Username>mental_dwarf1</Username><Timestamp>1371530627823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371530706474-9</Id><Title>CNBC got whta's is face - Mcnery tgalking about Boing at the paris airshow loser</Title><Msg>in the middle of the night on the Left coast should I listen or tune into the la st of the free HBO/MAX/Starz weekerend show nothing except old blind macular degeneration guy's film about being Behind The Curve without drawing from a holster and shooting the Timberlake kid for what;s her face... whatever McNerny says about the suppliers, goes...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371530706474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371531070358-10</Id><Topic><Title>Blacks, Fatherhood and the Democrat's Policies</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371479995685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:39:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, it is a mess created by classism and racism from several generations ago and hard to correct, as the answers are as simple as eliminating welfare. I don't know if 75% of black males are irresponsible, but regardless that number is too high. Black women are amongst the strongest people in the world, but most of the black males I know are responsible and hard working. Long term welfare is a problem in this country, just as much as outsourcing every industry and allowing the government to create jobs through massive deficit overspending.</Msg><Username>mental_dwarf1</Username><Timestamp>1371531070358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:51:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371531528898-11</Id><Topic><Title>Blacks, Fatherhood and the Democrat's Policies</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371479995685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 10:39:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kindasleax\zy rice what say ewe 'bout a member od Augusta and Cypress Point gofer premoted by Bushco from Nat. Sec Advisor for 9/11 to Sec.State ??? pparent;ly she has never been married or born a child still 12 times the womanof jane4whoite peoples's?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371531528898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371534332211-12</Id><Title>Exactly right- the Obama Administration compares favorarbly to some of the great ones</Title><Msg>especially when compared to the republicanfascists even the most evil Chieney said so...</Msg><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1371534332211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 01:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371534498424-13</Id><Topic><Title>Exactly right- the Obama Administration compares favorarbly to some of the great ones</Title><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1371534332211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 01:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raygun wrought the AIDS virus +++ = how many? Chieney wrought worse = how many?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371534498424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 01:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371534928517-14</Id><Topic><Title>103.03 1.20(1.18%) 4:00PM EDT|After Hours : 103.38 0.35 (0.34%)</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371529436075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just when I was thinking to add some $99 share(s) to my $26 portfolio shares</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371534928517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 01:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371535827746-15</Id><Topic><Title>From Fox News to Rush: Secrets of the right’s lie machine</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371416744907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But if there is a basic premise that unites Limbaugh, the folks on Fox, and the vast infrastructure of regional right-wing talkers, it is this: conservatives should never bend to the demands of the voters; voters should be made to bend to the demands of conservatives. To that end, conservative media actively campaign against any proposal that might renew actual journalism. The conservative media and dollarcrats oppose all policy measures to address the journalism crisis, from increasing postal subsidies, enhancing public media, or breaking up monopoly media firms to create more competition. To the conservatives and to Dollarocracy, " You can bet your sweet bottom that if a nail was meant to be hit on the head, it was not fabricated by a right-wing nut non-union worker... believe when I say to you the poster above the factory urinal read: A Job Well Done Is It's Own Reward but then I believe Management put it there since they had little else to do....</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371535827746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 02:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371536392793-16</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC got whta's is face - Mcnery tgalking about Boing at the paris airshow loser</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371530706474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:45:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is good for us...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371536392793</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 02:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371538668699-17</Id><Topic><Title>Paris Air Show- Vote on Boeing vs Airbus Stock Price</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371247771854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing outgained Airbus by 310% (1.18% vs .38%) today percentagewise and the Wayneker is dumb.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1371538668699</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 02:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371541087649-18</Id><Topic><Title>103.03 1.20(1.18%) 4:00PM EDT|After Hours : 103.38 0.35 (0.34%)</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371529436075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As they used to say UP in the Great White North in Canaduh well, good on you no sticky wickets for ZBOING is not exactly true...</Msg><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1371541087649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371541111868-19</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*whoosh!* That sailed right over his head...</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1371541111868</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371541155716-20</Id><Title>US Secrets to China Via the Tele Aviv Super Highway</Title><Msg>The Chinese Embassy in Israel is located at 219 Ben Yehuda St. in Tel Aviv. The four-story residential building turned into offices houses 50 accredited diplomats and dozens of employees with non-diplomatic status, making it the fifth largest embassy among the 83 nations that have permanent diplomatic missions in Israel. The fate of Israeli arms sales to China was IAI’s Phalcon project, designed to convert a Russian-made Ilyushin transport plane into an early warning spy in the sky for the Chinese Air Force. The second deal, also involving IAI, was for the upgrading of the Harpy attack drones that it had previously sold to China. The administration of then US president Bill Clinton, which perceived China as an emerging superpower adversary, set an ultimatum for Israel – to cancel the Phalcon project and not to upgrade the Harpies. Israel protested but gave in to the pressure of its strategic ally (free technology) and financial benefactor. “The Chinese operate endlessly in Israel,” a senior source who is familiar with the topic told me. “They operate with a variety of methods. They try to obtain data from open sources. They try to recruit and run agents in the most sensitive fields: military industries, the army and air force, the intelligence community and high-tech companies.” The Chinese Embassy in Tel Aviv houses electronic and other equipment that enables them to bug Israeli communications and decipher coded messages – an art known as signal intelligence, or sigint. the Chinese embasy penetrates computers and network systems at top-secret sites, such as Israel's Dimona nuclear reactor and at the security services and military industries. Israel as an opportunist or a so called "ally" is obvious courting the enemies of America.</Msg><Username>netanyehoo</Username><Timestamp>1371541155716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371542018479-21</Id><Topic><Title>103.03 1.20(1.18%) 4:00PM EDT|After Hours : 103.38 0.35 (0.34%)</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1371529436075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand this kinda talk... you are a\ tri-serviceE1 - E-9 most valuable asset something about a 17 hour MAC flight, and another 39 hours to here and you8 have isolated the problem... You have come to the right chair at the right time. Should a feather touch it would you grab the ceiling with your claws? That would be: Yes hmmm... perhaps,,,, then I won;t touch IT with a feather... Can I just take a gander at IT ? Totally pre-Tigger man, an hour booked...when the job is completed under three chocka, none of the otter stuff... as for BA should $99 appear on your radar screen, you might wanna nibble to above $110 again</Msg><Username>spartaloon</Username><Timestamp>1371542018479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371542322457-22</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope the NSA metadata phone collection system inititiated by the most evil Bushco/Chienyburton does not snag bepop_arugula as much as I dislike the actual arulgula we shall he what they post sweet dreams and peace/Bwell</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371542322457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371543091787-23</Id><Title>Israel Financial Benefactor secretly sells out US in nuclear weapons to China</Title><Msg>Israel was recently caught secretly selling nuclear US technology to America’s enemies in breach of a long-established agreement. The joke is, that these are American weapons are paid for by American tax-payers who generously subsidize Israel, going to a rising Communist superpower. Now what’s wrong with all this? Well the answer is easy, everything is wrong. All was discovered as the “Iron Dome Defense Missiles” Seized by Finland, labeled “Fireworks” from Israel was captured. The ship contained 69 of the brand new Patriot Missiles and was bound for China. Finland says cargo ship can sail again, but without its 69 missiles, explosives or it’s Ukrainian captain. The captured ship that was held in a Finnish port after authorities discovered 69 surface-to-air missiles and 160 tons of explosives on-board has permission to travel again, but without those materials or its captain, a port official said. The M/S Thor Liberty was headed to China and had docked in the southern Finnish port of Kotka to pick up anchor chains when Finnish Police last week discovered and seized the missiles and explosives on board.” Finnish authorities have confirmed the seizure of 69 Patriot missiles manufactured by Raytheon Corporation. Israel’s relationship with its closest ally, the United States, seems to have hit a rough patch, with Washington apparently upset with Israel’s clandestine dealings with China. The spat is not new it has its roots in a decade-old issue. It is an explosion into the public domain of a row that has been going on for a few years. The quarrel is over Israel’s alleged concealing from Washington of an upgrade of a major weapons system it sold to China more than a decade ago. The United States claims that by upgrading the system, Israel violated its commitment not to transfer US technology to China without Washington’s permission. Israel, however, insists that the upgrade was really just routine maintenance of a system that had been sold to China with US approval.</Msg><Username>netanyehoo</Username><Timestamp>1371543091787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 04:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371544276438-24</Id><Title>Great news--Rynair shareholders approve the March $16 Billion Dollar Boeing Award</Title><Msg>Purchase will be for 175 planes!</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371544276438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 04:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371544331981-25</Id><Topic><Title>Great news--Rynair shareholders approve the March $16 Billion Dollar Boeing Award</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371544276438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 04:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forgot right now what planes the order is for</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371544331981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 04:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371547033499-26</Id><Title>A Joni Mitchell song</Title><Msg>I came upon a child of god and this he told me.. life is but for learning screaming guitar(s)</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371547033499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371547846446-27</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's just a large sloth and believes what ever his party tells him.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371547846446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371548058332-28</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle O entourage takes 30 rooms at posh hotel...</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371498576175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 15:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make a good but licker.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371548058332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:34:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371548716861-29</Id><Topic><Title>US Secrets to China Via the Tele Aviv Super Highway</Title><Username>netanyehoo</Username><Timestamp>1371541155716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is Obonzo thinking? He could have sold US secrets directly to the Chinese like Clinton and Gore did and cut out the middle man.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371548716861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 05:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371555458558-30</Id><Title>Obonzo shoots the Constitution in a parody of Joe Manchin shooting Obamacare</Title><Msg>The NRA is running ads against Joe Manchin the West VA Dem who supports Obonzo's gun control efforts. I think the NRA should consider an "Onion" style parody of Joe Manchin's campaign ad where Manchin shot Obomacare hanging from a tree. The NRA parody could incorporate the hilarious picture of Obonzo with a shotgun and show Obonzo aiming his shotgun at the US Constitution hanging on a tree followed by a video close up of the Constitution being blown to smithereens by buckshot. The ad would then show a band of Mexican drug dealers that got guns via "Fast and Furious" scowling at the camera saying "Background checks? We don't need no stinkin' background checks". The next scene in the ad would show guns being passed out to al-Qaeda members with autographed pictures of Obonzo that say "Compliments of your friend Barack". The al-Qaeda members would immediately aim the guns into the air and fire them while screaming "Death to America!" The next scene would show part of Joe Manchin's original ad but replace Obamacare on the tree with the Constitution with Manchin now putting a bullet through the Constitution. The ad would close with one of those deep announcer type voices saying, "Manchin, he's lost aim of the rights and protections that are important to West Virginians" Now that would be an entertaining ad.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371555458558</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:37:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371555499058-31</Id><Topic><Title>US Secrets to China Via the Tele Aviv Super Highway</Title><Username>netanyehoo</Username><Timestamp>1371541155716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually you should be asking "what was George H W Bush's idiot son thinking" since the deal originated ten years ago during his reign-- Oh you thought you could hang it on Obama ? Well keep throwing that mud some of it is bound to sticke right?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371555499058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371556472982-32</Id><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Msg>.....you're MISLEADING the country" Charlie Daniels</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371556762763-33</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They need to K loader then strap and ratchet down the Raven in Chinook Helicopter to get his #$%$ airborne</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556762763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:59:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371558310271-34</Id><Title>Washington is Insane</Title><Msg>dubya dubya dubya.infowars.c*m/washington-is-insane/ (dubya = w) and (*=o)</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371558310271</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371559984704-35</Id><Topic><Title>US Secrets to China Via the Tele Aviv Super Highway</Title><Username>netanyehoo</Username><Timestamp>1371541155716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ZO - I read the entire article dingbat and it states that Israel complied with the wishes of the Clinton administration and shut down its weapon sales to China. Israel is NOT helping China anymore and China is getting tech secrets directly from the USA as well as Israel by cyber warfare and hacking. "There have been increasing reports in the international media about China’s spy activities in the US. A special report by the Pentagon, which was partly leaked to The Washington Post, revealed that Chinese espionage activities have reached the level of an unstoppable epidemic. Today, it is no longer classical espionage, that is the recruitment of human sources to become agents, though Chinese intelligence officers have been caught in several cases of doing this on American soil. Nowadays, however, Chinese collection efforts are focused on what is known as cyber warfare. It is the effort to undetectably infiltrate databases and computers, and steal the stored and hidden secrets. China has also been involved in penetrating computer systems that operate strategic sites, such as power stations and banks, to practice its sabotage capabilities and to test the cyber defense measures of the US." So Bush had nothing to do with tech leaks to China and Israel is being a good partner to the US and complying with US wishes since the mid 1990s according to the article.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371559984704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371560257554-36</Id><Topic><Title>US Secrets to China Via the Tele Aviv Super Highway</Title><Username>netanyehoo</Username><Timestamp>1371541155716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 03:39:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's the other aspect of big govt socialist governance. They run out of money to pay for their socialist expansion, and cutback on intelligence gathering to pay for it. Clinton cut out intelli bigtime, and it led to poor intelligence regarding Iraq.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1371560257554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371560463301-37</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares what Charlie Daniels says, why do you think his opinion matters any more than any other citizen?</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1371560463301</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371561108709-38</Id><Title>747 demand</Title><Msg>PARIS (Reuters) - Korean Air Lines is set to announce an order for five more Boeing 747-8 jumbo jets at the Paris Airshow, sources familiar with the matter said on Tuesday. The order is for the passenger version of the aircraft, according to the sources.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371561108709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371561289814-39</Id><Topic><Title>Great news--Rynair shareholders approve the March $16 Billion Dollar Boeing Award</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371544276438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 04:31:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>737-800 next generation</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371561289814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371563162169-40</Id><Title>Come on 104 ;-)</Title><Msg>then 105 then 6 see the pattern ;-) JUST KEEP GOING :-)</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1371563162169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371563643723-41</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Charlie is not a legend more like a drunk who got lucky with one song about the Devil.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1371563643723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371564498540-42</Id><Title>$103.63 NEW HIGH GO BOEING$$$$$$$</Title><Msg>Short are going NUTS and trying with their last breath but BOEING will continue making$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371564498540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371567406043-43</Id><Topic><Title>Washington is Insane</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371558310271</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 08:25:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's your grand mufti, maobama, and his dumb gov't (OPM) dependent party who'da thought a phony/community agitator wouldn't work out so well</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371567406043</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371568057833-44</Id><Title>Boeing Nets Orders For 102 787's</Title><Msg>LE BOURGET, France (AP) -- Boeing Co. won major orders from five customers for a stretched-out version of its popular 787 Dreamliner jet at the Paris Air Show Tuesday, further evidence of a strengthening market for more expensive long-haul jets. Boeing announced the formal launch of its 787-10 program at the Paris Air Show on Tuesday and says it already has commitments for 102 jets from five customers: Air Lease Corp., Singapore Airlines, United Airlines, International Airlines Group and GE Capital Aviation Services. The new 787-10 lists at $290 million, making the deal worth nearly $30 billion at full price, although customers often negotiate deep discounts. United remains the only U.S.-based airline to fly the 787, which is steadily winning customers after being beset with problems concerning lithium-ion battery on two Japanese carriers. The plane, like its newest rival the Airbus A350, uses lightweight materials and new engine technology to cut down on fuel consumption at a time of rapidly increasing jet fuel prices. Boeing has said passengers will notice bigger windows and an adjustment in cabin pressure which means they will not suffer from jet lag as badly as on other aircraft. The original 787 can seat between 210 and 250 passengers. Boeing has started building a longer version, the 787-9, that would hold between 250 and 290 passengers, while the 787-10 would seat between 300 and 330.</Msg><Username>dellgeorgesr</Username><Timestamp>1371568057833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371568676879-45</Id><Topic><Title>747 demand</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371561108709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:11:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets hope this airplane starts to sell- transports would be ok too though</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371568676879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371568974707-46</Id><Title>Desecrating the Flag !</Title><Msg>lil Wayne - you little Doosh</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371568974707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371570576864-47</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PLEASE get a life. So you won't have to quote Charlie Daniels among 1,000 other reasons.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1371570576864</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371570920286-48</Id><Topic><Title>$103.63 NEW HIGH GO BOEING$$$$$$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371564498540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WAYNEDICK-FEB HAS 2 THUMBS DOWN! LOL!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371570920286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371572309153-49</Id><Topic><Title>Desecrating the Flag !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371568974707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:22:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>following in the footsteps of our not so dear leader, barack hussein... now that he's mucked it up iran (no help to protestors), egypt, iraq, libya...he plans to throw weapons on the fire in syria, and wants to break bread with the taliban (over human/women's rights n such) before his scheduled withdrawl.... "The Pentagon has no plans to suspend or cancel purchases of helicopters for Afghanistan's air force from the same Russian firm that is allegedly sending attack helicopters to Syrian President Bashar al-Assad's loyalist military." a global disaster that rivals all others in terms of wealth, and liberty/prosperity, and opportunity destroyed, his legacy will live on with his illegal luvin supremes and lawless appointments.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371572309153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371572578079-50</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you have no more insane rambling to regale us with, Loon, you can always just smear feces. Actually, I just occurred to me there's no difference.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371572578079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371572759308-51</Id><Title>I Would Have Been 71 Today...</Title><Msg>Had I not died in a motorcycle accident in 1966. Fortunately, the technology was available to take a man named Mitch Campbell and perform plastic surgery on him to make him look just like me. And then to teach him to play bass left-handed and also keyboards. And then to perform surgery on his vocal cords so that he sounded just like me... and, finally, they taught him to write songs just as I did. If you don't believe all of this, visit any of the various "Paul is Dead" boards available. If you do believe all of this, seek help immediately... and then become a birther.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371572759308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371572821328-52</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post, Chris Genna.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371572821328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371573439882-53</Id><Topic><Title>$103.63 NEW HIGH GO BOEING$$$$$$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371564498540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 10:08:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>News Flash New HIGH $103.63$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371573439882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371573500948-54</Id><Topic><Title>747 demand</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371561108709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 09:11:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Friday the Orders will be BIG$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371573500948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371573606037-55</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty has drawn lessons he feels compelled to share with us from "V for Vendetta," "The Return of the King," "48 Hours," and innumerable Looney Tunes. This one pretty much tops them all. Why is it I associate Charlie Daniels' name with bourbon. Is he a relative of Jack's???</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371573606037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371573767655-56</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who here gives a $ht what Sean Penn or George Looney has to say? I know I don't!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1371573767655</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:42:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371574413163-57</Id><Topic><Title>Israel Financial Benefactor secretly sells out US in nuclear weapons to China</Title><Username>netanyehoo</Username><Timestamp>1371543091787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 04:11:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The board's numero uno Israel hater propagandist is back with a new nick - netanyehoo, in full swing spreading his regular BIG LIES about Israel. He hopes to find fools on this board to believe him.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1371574413163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371574795837-58</Id><Topic><Title>Israel Financial Benefactor secretly sells out US in nuclear weapons to China</Title><Username>netanyehoo</Username><Timestamp>1371543091787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 04:11:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean sparty? i think he may be of mobro descent. course j ews in the US seem to israels worst enemy, especially in their unwavering support of dumbocrats...free stuff before God and Country</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371574795837</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371575164288-59</Id><Topic><Title>ANYONE KNOW WAYNEDICK-FEB'S AGENDA?</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371145636800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 13:47:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>foulmoutharbor , please, your a a armchair psychologist now? foulmoutharbor, really, why not tell the truth, "and yahoo restored the ignore option," it never was gone. foulmoutharbor you seem highly interested in talking about me in a negative way to boost up your credibility and opinions, on Boeing. foulmoutharbor, when you have the facts on your side you argue facts, , when you do not you pound the table and call names.Over time Airbus shareholders are better off than Boeing shareholders, this year to date Airbus stock holders are up 46% and Boeing shareholders are less at 37% so you are saying your happy earning 9% less in 6 months. For3 years Airbus shareholders are better than boeing shareholder by 117% so you happy making over 117% less in 3 years than airbus shareholders , You better actually put me on ignore as you need to ignore this fact if your going to pump Boeing stock as it is second place in the duopoly . The dividends are about the same 1.09 boeing and 1.03 Airbus so just .6% difference not a significant factor. The meat of profit is single aisle and Airbus is killing Boeing right now at Paris on that plane order size end of story wayne now go back to ignor if you really will stop the pretend game of your ok and I am not</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371575164288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371575253500-60</Id><Topic><Title>Desecrating the Flag !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371568974707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 11:22:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you and hussein have a lot alike</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371575253500</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371576915545-61</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So many things sail over his head.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371576915545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371577956545-62</Id><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Msg>Bill Ayers discusses Obama's presidency with Tom Bevan and Charlie Stone and says Obama should be tried with war crimes. See the video at real Clear Politics.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578106671-63</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come on, barack is like bill ayer's step brother, his parents fostered barack</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371578106671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371578188342-64</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and bill writes his books, barack is like their creation</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371578188342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371579084128-65</Id><Title>pe 20? 50%overvalued</Title><Msg>crash next</Msg><Username>behindtruth2003</Username><Timestamp>1371579084128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371580172326-66</Id><Title>Boing gets big order at the Paris Air Show</Title><Msg>Both Boeing and Airbus got over 6,000 orders each. But the 787 takes the lead. Airbus CEO praised Boeing's technology and the 787. The Boeing announced plans for building the 787-50 which will carry over 300 passengers. The Boeing 787 cuts travel time and fuel costs. It's a comfortable, luxurious plane. Boeing currently trading over $103.</Msg><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1371580172326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371580378842-67</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looney tunes are songs you tried to write. Loosen your panties a bit and you might not sound like your head is full of sawdust.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371580378842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371581155485-68</Id><Title>Obama couldn't Care Less about the Mediocre Class</Title><Msg>He hob knobs and get's his campaign donations from the top one half of the top 1% then he shovels multiple times their donations back to them in the form of grants, no obligation loans, stimulus funds and subsidies.......all paid for by mediocre class workers. He also panders to the dependent class with record payouts for welfare, food stamps, disability claims and years unemployment compensation all paid for again by......you guessed it.....mediocre class workers.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371581155485</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371581323607-69</Id><Title>OHH MY New HIGH $104.12!!!</Title><Msg>Suck on that waynedicless airbusted is holding up a PICTURE of the a-350 and No takers while BOEING'S 787 is flying allover the place CASHING IN ON ORDERS$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371581323607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371581550225-70</Id><Title>Blaming the Past</Title><Msg>People love the past. It provides convenient excuses for all manner of individual or group shortcomings. Academic "experts", politicians and race hustlers use history as a coverup. They point to the ugly facts of slavery, Jim Crow and discrimination as explanations for the high rates of black illegitimacy, crime and family breakdown. The connection between slavery and discrimination and what we see today is hardly ever challenged. But challenge it we must. Only 40 percent of black children live in two-parent households. The illegitimacy rate among blacks stands close to 70 percent. The "legacy of slavery" explanation for today's weak black family structure loses all manner of credibility when one examines evidence from the past. Even during slavery, most black children lived in biological two-parent families. One study of nineteenth century slave families (Herbert Gutman, The Black Family in Slavery and Freedom: 1750-1925) found that in up to three-fourths of the families, all the children had the same mother and father. In New York City, in 1925, 85 percent of kin-related black households were double-headed. In fact, "Five in six children under the age of six lived with both parents." Both during slavery and as late as 1920, a black teenage girl raising a child without a man was rare among blacks. Historian Herbert Gutman, also found in analyzing data on black families in Harlem between 1905 and 1925, that only 3 percent of all families "were headed by a woman under thirty." Thomas Sowell found, "Going back a hundred years, when blacks were just one generation out of slavery, we find that census data of that era showed that a slightly higher percentage of black adults had married than white adults. This fact remained true in every census from 1890 to 1940." In absolute numbers, blacks commit most of the crime in the U.S. Blacks account for half of all the arrests for assault and rape and two-thirds of arrests for robbery. Blacks are disproportionately more represented in all categories of felonies, except those requiring access to large sums of money such as embezzlement and stock fraud. Criminologist Marvin Wolfgang says, "For four violent offenses - homicide, rape, robbery and aggravated assault - the crime rates for blacks are at least 10 times as high as they are for whites." Close to ninety percent of the victims of black criminals are black. Crime turns neighborhoods into economic wastelands forcing poor people to bear the cost of traveling to suburban malls to do routine shopping or pay the high prices at local "Ma &amp; Pa" shops. If they manage to buy a home, that home is worth less because of crime and wanton property destruction. Poor people are most dependent on law and order for safety and welfare. Wealthier people have the financial resources to protect themselves such as purchasing alarms, hiring private guards. An often overlooked crime cost is that people who are the most upwardly mobile people are the first to leave. Their replacements are not as mobile or care less about neighborhood amenities. The people who leave take with them the social leavening that contributes to vital and stable communities. The "politically correct" theory is that poverty and discrimination is the cause of high crime rates. During my youth, the 1930s and 1940s, black neighborhoods were far safer than today. It would be preposterous to suggest back then there was less poverty and discrimination. The level of social pathology seen in many black communities is unprecedented and has nothing to do with a so-called legacy of slavery, unless we're willing to say that slavery has a delayed reaction of four or five generations. Walter E. Williams</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371581550225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371581607298-71</Id><Topic><Title>ANYONE KNOW WAYNEDICK-FEB'S AGENDA?</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371145636800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 13:47:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Falmouth seems you hit a Nerve with wayne BABY!!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371581607298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371582385520-72</Id><Title>Boeing Airbus and pshchology which is better and the gang</Title><Msg> foulmoutharbor The meat of profit is single aisle and Airbus is killing Boeing right now at Paris on that plane order size ! . foulmoutharbor, when you have the facts on your side you argue facts, , when you do not you pound the table and call names, please, your a armchair psychologist? Over time Airbus shareholders are better off than Boeing shareholders, this year to date Airbus stock holders are up 46% and Boeing shareholders are less at 37% so you are saying your happy earning 9% less in 6 months. For 3 years Airbus shareholders are better than Boeing shareholder by 117% so you happy making over 117% less in 3 years than airbus shareholders foulmoutharbor, really, why not tell the truth, "and yahoo restored the ignore option," it never was gone. foulmoutharbor you seem highly interested in talking about me in a negative way to boost up your credibility and opinions, on Boeing., You better actually put me on ignore as you need to ignore this fact if your going to pump Boeing stock as it is second place in the duopoly . The dividends are about the same 1.9 Boeing and 1.3 Airbus so just .6% difference not a significant factor. now go back to ignor if you really will stop the pretend game of your ok and I am not o falmouthharbor • Jun 13, 2013 2:31 PM Flag “Not sure what drives him . Clearly he has problems with low self image that drives him to tell us all how smart he is and what great decisions he has made (?). He does seem a bit obsessed with painting a negative opinion of Boeing. I am just happy that Yahoo has restored the ignore user function so his posts (and others on ignore) no longer clutter up the message boards.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371582385520</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371582437343-73</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Airbus and pshchology which is better and the gang</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371582385520</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>should be psychology for BHT to understand they spael god dowt u no</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371582437343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371583339181-74</Id><Title>1 buck from historical all time high..</Title><Msg>Taking off, 787..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1371583339181</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:22:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583394341-75</Id><Topic><Title>1 buck from historical all time high..</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1371583339181</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even cavemen know it is going to be broken...</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1371583394341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371583540509-76</Id><Title>YEAH 104 !!!! LOVE IT !!!!</Title><Msg>JUST KEEP GO UP UP UP !!!!</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1371583540509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583772439-77</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a lard #$%$.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371583772439</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583851867-78</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Careful, you are insulting the Kent Ravens boyfriend.......</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371583851867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:30:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371583954508-79</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be one of the DFCs around..............dumber than dirt.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371583954508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584006239-80</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissy's alias congratulating Chrissy...........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371584006239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584425398-81</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you "loosen your panties"? Do yours have straps with buckles? People who don't wear kinky clothes want to know.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371584425398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584535292-82</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee Floyd; only 4 successive posts about me? You're either losing your edge, or else falling out of love with me.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371584535292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:42:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584598064-83</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, who cares about a citizen's opinion when we got big brother to tell us what to think and do.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1371584598064</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:43:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584677223-84</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looney Tunes are cartoon, mediocre, filled with ridiculous characters like you.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371584677223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371584726355-85</Id><Title>A Nice short Sqeeze about now would Kill the shorties$$</Title><Msg>Their better cover like their doing at Boeing 787 Engine Maker GE$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371584726355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371584742296-86</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are Ayers, Bevan and Stone? Guys you met at the bar, grumbling in their beer?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371584742296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371584839764-87</Id><Title>Shouldn't We Abolish the IRS?</Title><Msg>....and replace it with a flat tax or the FAIR TAX. No Deductions, no loopholes.....everyone....and I do mean EVERYONE should pay the same rate. People should be punished because they refuse to be mediocre, a member of the dependent class or a societal leach.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371584839764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585023768-88</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are people who know Obama best.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371585023768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371585046683-89</Id><Title>7 dead and 41 wounded over the weekend in "gun free" Chicago</Title><Msg>Preventing law abiding citizens from access to guns in Chicago is really paying off. Chicago serves as the role model for Obama gun policy.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371585046683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371585918957-90</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...people who know Obama best" sitting in a bar grumbling in their beer?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371585918957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371586296320-91</Id><Title>Fox commentator paid $50,000 to tout stock</Title><Msg>Most investors can’t tell the difference between “sponsored investment research” and independent analysis, and that’s exactly what the “sponsors” — typically small companies paying for a marketing campaign that will inflate their stock activity and value — are counting on. The difference gets even tougher to figure out when the sponsor hires someone who is known for giving independent commentary colored only by their own feelings and research. Enlarge Image Tobin Smith’s newsletter Think of it like a big honking commercial, with a celebrity endorser. Last week, that bought-and-paid for stock endorsement was a 20-page mailer about Petrosonic Energy /quotes/zigman/12888469/quotes/nls/pson PSON -20.90% , supported by an e-mail campaign, featuring Tobin Smith, a money manager who has been a fixture on the television news shows for 15 years, and who today is a regular on the Fox networks, describing himself on Twitter as a “guest anchor.” According to Fox, he is “a contributing market analyst for FOX News Channel and a regular panelist on ‘Bulls &amp; Bears.’” (Fox, like MarketWatch, is owned by News Corp.) While investors might have ordinarily treated the “special edition” of the new Next Big Thing Investor newsletter — Smith’s latest, just-started investment newsletter — like junk mail or spam, Smith’s name and his smiling, personable countenance had some investors doing a double-take, at least judging from the e-mails I received on the subject. The people who contacted me considered buying the stock entirely based on Smith’s say-so, and the credibility he exudes in his Fox appearances. They didn’t appear to read the disclaimers of the campaign; had they bothered, they would have quickly found it was paid advertising for which Smith’s company pocketed $50,000. This is a unique case because of how recognizable Smith is, and it brings into focus credibility questions that I’ve found most investors fail to answer even as they are deciding who they can trust. Fox’s official policy is that “no Contributor to FBN, nor his/her firm, and/or family members are allowed to accept financial consideration of any kind whatsoever to issue research, advertisements, or to otherwise promote individual stocks or securities,” a spokesman says. However, the network, which was unaware of Smith’s efforts on Petrosonic’s behalf until I contacted them, would not comment on the matter. Asked whether he violated Fox’s rules, Smith said, via text message, “that policy was added late last year … my contract was not subject to that clause …” He went on to say he was “adding it to my existing contract ASAP.” Petrosonic could not be reached for comment. The campaign started with Petrosonic — there’s a disclosure in the company’s annual report noting that it hired a firm “that provides strategic investor relations services” — but the issue here is not so much about what is being touted as by who is doing it, why they are doing it, and whether the audience can tell the difference between independent analysis and advertising cloaked in the guise of analysis. Smith told me it’s actually better to have the company — rather than a third-party with a big wad of shares — backing these campaigns because it’s more “like public venture capital” than a play to pump the stock. Either way, the Petrosonic blitz last week helped the stock gain roughly 20%. Getty Images Enlarge Image Tobin Smith on set at Fox Business News And with Petrosonic up over 40% year-to-date and more than 135% in the last year, anyone who can’t see past the smiling face of the popular, charismatic Smith might think the stock really is “the investment opportunity of your lifetime,” as it’s described in the flyer. For one, there’s the company’s lack of revenues, as in zero, according to filings, though Petrosonic did issue a press release late last week about how the company — which says it has a unique process for upgrading heavy oil — is now generating revenue from its plant in Albania. Also overlooked in the hype are Petrosonic’s rising losses, negative cash-flow and the “going-concern letter” from auditors who think there is “substantial doubt” in Petrosonic’s ability to survive. In its regulatory filings — where all of those conditions are readily evident — Petrosonic notes that the business will fail if it can’t generate adequate cash/financing; those concerns aren’t mentioned in Smith’s “special report.”</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371586296320</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:11:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586309902-92</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't We Abolish the IRS?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371584839764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whoa, now that's a stupid post. I'd say the supidest post of the day -- congrats, mmoorroon.</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1371586309902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586393170-93</Id><Topic><Title>I Would Have Been 71 Today...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371572759308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" If you do believe all of this, seek help immediately... and then become a birther." Now that says it all.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371586393170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586520192-94</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Highest Nuber of Thumbs Down Ratings One can Get</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371494389014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 14:39:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enlisting is for LOSERS.</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1371586520192</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371586521340-95</Id><Title>Not many feminine men on here today</Title><Msg>Is 7 "I don't like yous" the best you sissies from the San Francisco and Seattle areas can do?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371586521340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586761751-96</Id><Topic><Title>Not many feminine men on here today</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371586521340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a frustrated repressed bottom who hasn't gotten any in a few months. Am I right?</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1371586761751</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586788295-97</Id><Topic><Title>I Would Have Been 71 Today...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371572759308</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 12:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's dumb .......no one would have gone to all that trouble......they would have just bought a fog horn.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371586788295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371586872635-98</Id><Title>Big Brother alert: Cameras in the cable box to monitor TV viewers</Title><Msg>Cheryl K. Chumley Washington Times June 18, 2013 It hardly gets more Orwellian than this. New technology would allow cable companies to peer directly into television watchers’ homes and monitor viewing habits and reactions to product advertisements. The technology would come via the cable box, and at least one lawmaker on Capitol Hill is standing in opposition.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371586872635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586969689-99</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The New World Order prefers to give Barry Soetoro a Peace Prize...when Childrens arms and legs are torn off during "kinetic military action" those drones are delivering loving Peace bombs don't ya know</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371586969689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371586980132-100</Id><Topic><Title>Shouldn't We Abolish the IRS?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371584839764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 15:47:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you ever rise to the level of mediocre you will realize you are the stupid one.......but I don't think there's much danger of that ever happening.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371586980132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587058111-101</Id><Topic><Title>Music Legend to Obama : "You're not leading the country...........</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371556472982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 07:54:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL...you got that right</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371587058111</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587258763-102</Id><Topic><Title>Big Brother alert: Cameras in the cable box to monitor TV viewers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371586872635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:21:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave it to a knee-jerk reactionary grandstanding lawgiver to "stand in opposition" to something that might happen, which could easily be fixed with a piece of masking tape. (Masking tape masks; get it?) Har har har har har</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371587258763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:27:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371587556186-103</Id><Title>Dreamliner aborted take off in HongKong</Title><Msg>Ok i am stucked in HKG right now and me and all other passengers of flight qr 813 because Boeings wonderwapon Dreamliner has technical problems we were just before the runway when the chief pilot informed us that we have to go back to the gate. after 30 minutes waiting in the dreamliner they informed us to leave the.dreamliner and all passengers are.now back at the departure hall since 3 hours.</Msg><Username>eurasam</Username><Timestamp>1371587556186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:32:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371587859776-104</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner aborted take off in HongKong</Title><Username>eurasam</Username><Timestamp>1371587556186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:32:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS and you now it SHORTIE so Cover before you lose it all$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371587859776</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371588273900-105</Id><Title>‘Free at Last!’ Louisiana State Senator Explains Why He Left the ‘Government Plantation’</Title><Msg>Louisiana State Sen. Elbert Guillory, formerly a Democrat, recently — and enthusiastically — joined the Republican party. Weeks after announcing his bold move, Guillory has released a video explaining why he is now with the GOP. The powerful video is titled, “Why I Am a Republican.” Louisiana State Sen. Elbert Guillory, formerly a Democrat, recently — and enthusiastically — joined the Republican party. Weeks after announcing his bold move, Guillory has released a video explaining why he is now with the GOP. The powerful video is titled, “Why I Am a Republican.” In the video, Guillory says it is the Republican Party that actually has the best interests of the black community in mind. He argues Democrats relentlessly push an agenda intended to exert control over blacks, not lift them out of poverty. “You see, in recent history, the Democrat party has created the illusion that their agenda and their policies are what’s best for black people,” Guillory said. “Somehow it has been forgotten that the Republican party was founded in 1854 as an abolitionist movement, with one simple creed: that slavery is a violation of the rights of man.” The former Democrat explained that Frederick Douglass called Republicans the “party of freedom and progress.” He also pointed out that former Republican President Abraham Lincoln signed the Emancipation Proclamation and Republicans in Congress wrote the Thirteenth, Fourteenth and Fifteenth Amendments. “The Democrats, on the other hand, were the party of Jim Crow,” Guillory added. “It was the Democrats who defended the rights of slave owners.” He went on: “You see, at the heart of liberalism, is the idea that only a great and powerful big Government can be the benefactor of social justice for all Americans. But the left is only concerned with one thing: control. And they disguise this control as charity.” Guillory claimed entitlement programs like welfare and food stamps were never designed to “lift black Americans out of poverty,” but rather to control them. Further, the welfare programs haven’t even helped blacks at all as they are still “as poor as they’ve ever been,” he argued. “But most importantly, it is the idea that the individual must be free to pursue his or her own happiness, free from Government dependence, and free from Government control. Because to be truly free, is to be reliant on no one, other than the author of our destiny,” Guillory continued, pointing to God. “These are the ideas are at the core of Republican party… My brothers and sisters of the American community, please join me in abandoning the Government plantation and the party of disappointment.” “So that we may all echo of one Republican leader who famously said, ‘Free at last, free at last. Thank God almighty, we are free at last,” he concluded.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371588273900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371588528474-106</Id><Topic><Title>Not many feminine men on here today</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371586521340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you speak with a lisp and gesture with a limp wrist? Are you from around San Francisco or Seattle?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371588528474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371588905484-107</Id><Title>Boeing Wins Second Multibillion-Dollar Chinook Order</Title><Msg>In a news release last night, DoD announced that it has awarded Boeing a firm-fixed-price, multiyear contract worth up to $3.4 billion for the production of remanufactured and new-build Chinooks. To be clear, this new contract is not the anticipated "option" to buy an additional 38 helos discussed in last week's contract. Rather, this is an entirely new order placed "in support of foreign military sales for Turkey and United Arab Emirates."</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371588905484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371588995989-108</Id><Topic><Title>Not many feminine men on here today</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371586521340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I speak a gravelly Brooklyn dialect, and my wrist is firm enough to put you down for the count, Have you always had such a big mouth, WIMP?</Msg><Username>alan_gonquin_is_queer</Username><Timestamp>1371588995989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589030452-109</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ayers was one of the #$%$ leaders of the Weather Underground radicals which are the foundation for modern progressives. You should be familiar with WU as they founded one of your favorite blogs 'Common Dreams' or 'Communist Dreams' as I refer to it. ;-) #$%$ Ayers was a good Hyde Park Chicago Marxist progressive buddy of Obama's and they both served on the BOD of the Annenberg Charter School Project in Chicago. Ayers comments are in the Washington Post (the Washington Post is not a bar and does not serve beer) and you can read them for yourself at the Washington Post if you are not too drunk or too lazy.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371589030452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371589372187-110</Id><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Msg>Maybe it was $40 trillion in regulations “We wanted flying cars, instead we got 140 characters” is the pithy and tweetable way the Founders Fund, a San Francisco-based venture capital firm, asks the question, “What happened to the future?” How did it get away from us? Maybe we regulated away the sci-fi future that our never-happened tiger years would have brought us. A 2013 study from economists John Dawson of Appalachian State University and John Seater of North Carolina State University, Federal Regulation and Aggregate Economic Growth, estimates that the past 50 years of federal regulations have reduced real GDP by roughly two percentage points a year, or nearly $40 trillion. Instead of the US economy growing by just over 3% a year since World War Two, it would have grown by over 5% a year. “That is, GDP at the end of 2011 would have been $53.9 trillion instead of $15.1 trillion if regulation had remained at its 1949 level,” the authors conclude. (And by the way, the study does not attempt to quantify the costs of the Affordable Care Act or Dodd-Frank financial regulation.) Imagine a US economy four times as big — four times as wealthy — as the one today. Basically, we would have the US economy of 2080 right now. Instead of regulation to reduce air and water pollution, maybe nanobots would be doing the job for us. And maybe we would have flying cars, such as the one depicted cruising above 2019 Los Angeles in the film Bladerunner (to</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589531358-111</Id><Topic><Title>Not many feminine men on here today</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371586521340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Little sissies makey cheapy talk.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589531358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371589916338-112</Id><Title>how much aluminum in the new dreamliner</Title><Msg>just looking for facts thanks in advance</Msg><Username>jwmjohny6</Username><Timestamp>1371589916338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371589964325-113</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting fact on Apache Longbow</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371524805323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-17 23:06:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats gotta be a force muiliplyer. So fast and the prioritize aspect is great. Shoot at a tank, not a trash truck for example.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371589964325</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590289504-114</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Ayers? You don't know your own fellow lefties? Ayers was Obama's buddy, the terrorist that took part on the NY bombing, and said he regretted he wasn't more successful. Obama said he vaguely knew Ayers even though he was a neighbor, and even though Obama sat on the same socialist boards with Ayers.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1371590289504</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590600953-115</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it was because NO ONE wanted traffic jams and midair collisions over their house. It ain't rocket science -- just go to a mall or big box parking lot, get out and walk to a good vantage spot, and watch for 30 minutes. Do you want "THOSE PEOPLE" hot-dogging in the sky over your kids' playground? I'm glad there's an FAA and a billion regulations that make it a wee bit tougher from some Mittens Romney to finance that lunacy by laying off workers. Then the financial hotshots can pee and moan about Obama and find some equally profitable place to invest the money they've stolen or borrowed.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371590600953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371590614272-116</Id><Title>another chinook order</Title><Msg>In a news release last night, DoD announced that it has awarded Boeing a firm-fixed-price, multiyear contract worth up to $3.4 billion for the production of remanufactured and new-build Chinooks. To be clear, this new contract is not the anticipated "option" to buy an additional 38 helos discussed in last week's contract. Rather, this is an entirely new order placed "in support of foreign military sales for Turkey and United Arab Emirates." What's more, this one could be even bigger as the "optioned" version of the contract let out by the U.S. Army last week. According to DoD, the Turkey/UAE contract has options of its own attached, which, if exercised, could increase the total contract value to just under $5 billion, versus a potential value of roughly $4.8 billion on last week's U.S. Army contract.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371590614272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371590746786-117</Id><Title>Air Lease Corp commits to 30 787-10x's and 3 more 787-9x's</Title><Msg>Keep on coming boys, your doing great. Not sure of value of award</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371590746786</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371590760343-118</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I leave it to right-fringers to obsess about people whose politics they know only from some H.S. "news" site. (The "H" is for horse.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371590760343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371590920559-119</Id><Title>Korean Air today ordered 5 747-8 and 6 787-300er---- $3.36 Billion dollar award</Title><Msg>like that we got some 747-8 wins. Highly overlooked plane.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371590920559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591147375-120</Id><Topic><Title>another chinook order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371590614272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:23:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I strongly feel we will see more Chinook orders------great helo for sure. Stood the test of time with honors!</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371591147375</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591451561-121</Id><Topic><Title>another chinook order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371590614272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:23:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, for the sake of our brave fighting war profiteers, let's hope for more quagmire wars soon! Two, three, many Afghanistans! to coin a phrase.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371591451561</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591473628-122</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A fair amount of Obonzo supporters are progressives that have become self-loathing anti-human regressives that view humans as a planetary disease and don't want growth and in fact want to see population reduction through mandatory abortions and sterilization. I engage in discussion with these regressives at Mother Jones, Huffington Post, The Guardian, etc and they worship anti-science, anti-growth and human hating people like Rachel Carson, Paul Ehrlich and John Holdren. For them the ideal growth rate target is a negative 5% with human population being killed off and limited to 1 billion people. I agree with the analysis of GDP and at this point in his second term Reagan attained a 5.6% GDP. Unfortunately we have Obonzonomics which throws taxpayer money away on losing companies like Fiskar who builds electric cars that only Leonardo Dicrapio and other Hollywood regressive douchebags can afford while losing $35,000.00 per car. It's all good if you're one of Obama's crony capitalist buddies, but Obonzo is doing his best to slow growth for the rest of us.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371591473628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591516429-123</Id><Topic><Title>how much aluminum in the new dreamliner</Title><Username>jwmjohny6</Username><Timestamp>1371589916338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:11:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20% of plane weight is aluminum, 50% is composit,</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371591516429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371591791117-124</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What else would you expect people who know Obama best to do? Get a job? not a chance.......maybe organize a community protest for more fee stuff to sell at the LGBTDFC fund raiser.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371591791117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371592154722-125</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna was awarded a 'Pull it sir' Prize for his work at the Kent Bath House but he can only dream of being talented enough to be writing at some regressive H.S. site. ROTFL BTW, when did Genna determined that the Washington Post is a fringe H.S. site, because that is where I read Bill Ayers comments? lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371592154722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371592413031-126</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....Chrissie is a perfect example of how backward thinking the progressives are. He has the same mentality of the people who didn't want that dangerous thing called electricity wired into their homes and sure didn't want those new fangled things call automobiles spewing smoke and scaring the horses on the roads.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371592413031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371592616445-127</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent posts..........Genna is one of the dumbest posters on here.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1371592616445</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371593019405-128</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" that have become self-loathing anti-human regressives that view humans as a planetary disease" Anybody who knows you would have that view.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371593019405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371593158831-129</Id><Title>War against Issa heats up, as Cummings releases IRS transcript</Title><Msg>Issa's IRS "scandal" flops Slamming Issa's leaks, Cummings says “not one witness…has identified any involvement by any White House officials” By Joan Walsh The internal war between House Oversight Committee chair Darrell Issa and ranking Democrat Elijah Cummings blew up again Tuesday, when Cummings released the full transcript of a five-hour interview with the conservative Republican IRS screening manager who said the very first Tea Party case was flagged by one of his own staffers, and denied any White House knowledge or involvement with the controversial screening policy. Part one is here; part two is here. You’ll recall that Cummings had previously charged Issa with misrepresenting the Committee’s findings when he charged that the investigation was uncovering evidence that pointed to “Washington” involvement. Cummings demanded that Issa keep an earlier pledge to release all of the transcripts of committee interviews to date. Issa refused, calling Cummings “reckless” and “irresponsible” for sharing a partial transcript of the Republican screening manager’s interview, and insisting any further disclosure of interviews would “undermine the integrity of the Committee’s investigation.” Of course, Issa himself then leaked the transcript of an interview with IRS agent Holly Paz, a Washington, D.C. based supervisor who reviewed some of the applications, to USA Today, Reuters, the Wall Street Journal, the Associated Press and Politico. (AP also got to look at transcripts of interviews with agents Gary Muthert and Elizabeth Hofacre). Issa seemed to think Paz’s testimony somehow proved that political meddling indeed came from “Washington,” neglecting the fact that the IRS is based there, and the Cincinnati screeners followed internal procedure by consulting Washington based supervisors. But as AP reported, Paz “provided no evidence that senior IRS officials ordered agents to target conservative groups or that anyone in the Obama administration” was involved. (Media Matters breaks down the entire Paz story here.) “Rather than working together in a bipartisan manner, Cummings wrote to Issa, “you apparently directed your staff to spend the weekend engaging in the same activity you condemned as “reckless” less than a week earlier.” Cummings’ Oversight committee staff had already released partial transcripts of the Cincinnati screening manager’s testimony, but Tuesday’s full transcript provides more detail. From Cummings’ summary of the testimony of the self-described “conservative Republican:” The Screening Group Manager explained that the very first case at issue in this investigation was initially flagged by one of his own screeners in February 2010. He told us he agreed that this case should be elevated to IRS employees in Washington because it was a “high profile” application in which the organization indicated that it would be engaging in political activity. He explained that he initiated the first effort to gather similar cases in order to ensure their consistent treatment, and that he took this action on his own, without any direction from his superiors, and without any political motivation. He also confirmed that one of his screeners developed terms subsequently identified by the Inspector General as “inappropriate,” such as “Patriot” and “9/12 project,” but that he did not become aware that his screener was using these terms until more than a year later. The manager’s testimony explains why some of the Tea Party applications wound up in Washington – although I’ve always had a hard time understanding how anyone could use the location of the federal government as a synonym for political meddling without any other proof. Cummings concludes: These facts are a far cry from accusations of a conspiracy orchestrated by the White House to target the President’s political enemies. At this point in the investigation, not one witness who has appeared before the Committee has identified any involvement by any White House officials in the identification or screening of Tea Party applicants for tax exempt status, and the Committee has obtained no documents indicating any such involvement. As Cummings notes in his letter, the dueling transcript leaks by Issa and Cummings is understandably causing some people, even Republicans, to demand that the committee release the full interview transcripts. “Let’s see everything. Let’s see it all. And let’s see all the transcripts and you know let’s have a fair, objective analysis of this,” Sen. Rob Portman told a Cincinnati television station. I doubt that Issa will find Portman any more persuasive than he does Cummings. But it’s nice to see Cummings try to keep Issa honest, even if that’s close to impossible.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371593158831</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371593250361-130</Id><Topic><Title>‘Free at Last!’ Louisiana State Senator Explains Why He Left the ‘Government Plantation’</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371588273900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 16:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool video. When will the talk shows get people like this for guests and discuss why Democrat policies have only served to make African Americans dependency slaves of the government plantation for 60 years?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371593250361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371593403893-131</Id><Title>Air Lease's Hazy Says Boeing 787-10 Beats Airbus on Fuel</Title><Msg>Steven Udvar-Hazy, the self- proclaimed godfather of aircraft leasing, said Boeing Co.’s stretched Dreamliner has better fuel economy over Airbus SAS’s A350-900, making the new 787 attractive to airlines</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371593403893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371593475808-132</Id><Topic><Title>Air Lease's Hazy Says Boeing 787-10 Beats Airbus on Fuel</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371593403893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to see it in print especially from Steven Udvar-Hazy</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371593475808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371593664849-133</Id><Title>Boeing Sees Larger 787 With Chance to Boost Orders by 60%</Title><Msg>Boeing Co. said its stretched 787 Dreamliner promises to match sales of the smallest variant, boosting the plane’s order tally as much as 60 percent, as it expanded its wide-body lineup to blunt an Airbus SAS challenge</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371593664849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371594057047-134</Id><Title>And Now, For Your #$%$ Moment of the Day</Title><Msg>GOP lawmaker: Extreme abortion ban justified because of masturbating fetuses Rep. Michael Burgess has seen fetuses with "their hands between their legs" as early as 15 weeks, he says By Katie Mcdonough Rep. Michael Burgess, R-Texas, said on Monday that he supports the proposed federal ban on abortion at 20 weeks because he has personally witnessed male fetuses with their hands “between their legs” pleasuring themselves at 15 weeks. “There is no question in my mind that a baby at 20-weeks after conception can feel pain. The fact of the matter is, I argue with the chairman because I thought the date was far too late. We should be setting this at 15-weeks, 16-weeks,” said the former OB-GYN during the House Rules Committee debate on the “Pain-Capable Unborn Child Protection Act.” “Watch a sonogram of a 15-week baby, and they have movements that are purposeful,” he continued. “They stroke their face. If they’re a male baby, they may have their hand between their legs. If they feel pleasure, why is it so hard to believe that they could feel pain?” Burgess’ theory about “masturbating” fetuses isn’t the only outrageous comment presented as fact to provoke outrage (and some head scratches) during the lead-up to the House debate on the doomed measure; on Wednesday of last week, bill sponsor Rep. Trent Franks, R-Ariz., remarked that an exception to the ban in cases of rape or incest was unnecessary “because, you know, the incidence of rape resulting in pregnancy are very low.”</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594057047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371594180830-135</Id><Title>It's War!</Title><Msg>Bachmann: Karl Rove is not with the GOP base Bachmann was hitting back at Rove's comment that she "did nothing" as chair of the Tea Party caucus By Jillian Rayfield Rep. Michele Bachmann, R-Minn., doesn’t care what Karl Rove has to say about her, because the “base of our party is not where Karl Rove is, to be honest with you.” Speaking on Laura Ingraham’s radio show, Politico reports, Bachmann was responding to Rove’s criticism after she announced she would not run for reelection in 2014, which he said was a good thing. “Michele Bachmann was the chairman of the congressional Tea Party caucus and in that position did nothing,” Rove said. “The base of our party is not where Karl Rove is, to be honest with you,” Bachmann said Tuesday. “I think that perhaps he wants to be the conscience of the Republican Party.” “It is bizarre,” Bachmann added. “On one hand, the Tea Party was doing too much. And now they’re saying they’re not doing enough.”</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371594234904-136</Id><Topic><Title>another chinook order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371590614272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:23:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong, its to enable our soldiers to fight the fight and come home quicker and safer. The ancient thinking that we start wars for profit is crazy.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371594234904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371594405442-137</Id><Topic><Title>It's War!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rove's deep seated problem stems from his progressive philosophy. He's as republican as John McCain.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1371594405442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371594661543-138</Id><Topic><Title>how much aluminum in the new dreamliner</Title><Username>jwmjohny6</Username><Timestamp>1371589916338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:11:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To add to falmouthharbor message it seems there is also 15% titanium and 10% steel----was just curious what made up the other materials. Expected to find a little more titanium, but too expensive. I think the titanium is to connect to the composite material?? Is that correct anyone??</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371594661543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:31:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371594833740-139</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Sees Larger 787 With Chance to Boost Orders by 60%</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371593664849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:14:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My first take on the A350 was why such small windows? After that I saw the interior on a video which was not that impressive. I feel also that the 787-10 will be hugely successful. I think over 100 orders already at kick-off</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371594833740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371595071146-140</Id><Title>You can always tell when little Chrissy gets his</Title><Msg>panties in a wad over a post, he brings out all his aliases to make it appear as though he has real "friends" on his side.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1371595071146</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371595121467-141</Id><Topic><Title>how much aluminum in the new dreamliner</Title><Username>jwmjohny6</Username><Timestamp>1371589916338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:11:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quite a few parts of all sizes are titanium, but a large part that is titanium is the landing gear beam.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371595121467</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371595174385-142</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has many awards and decorations for his service at the KBH.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1371595174385</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371595199377-143</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Progressives are DFC's.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1371595199377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371595286630-144</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, For Your #$%$ Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594057047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope they don't go blind before they're born.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1371595286630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371595520330-145</Id><Topic><Title>You can always tell when little Chrissy gets his</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1371595071146</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:37:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He does have a lot of people who support him. Like me.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1371595520330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:45:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371595640234-146</Id><Title>$2.8 Billon dollar award from Qatar Airlines for nine 777- 300ER</Title><Msg>In addition to the above award Boeing has won a significant contract for the upgrade of four French E-3F Airborne Warning and Control System (“AWACS”) aircraft. The contract is valued at $354 million.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371595640234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371597060135-147</Id><Title>Boeing to help sell Embraer KC-390 military transport plane---to help the sale of fighters to Brazil?</Title><Msg>Is that the only immediate benefit I see , which is indeed large, is for the sale of the fighters to Brazil--could be the first of more orders. I know Boeing only is in charge of selling in United States, United Kingdom, and some Middle Eastern countries. Is the fighter sale the reason, do we get a commision for each sale, and more importantly are we ever making a transport to replace the C-130 and C-17??</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371597060135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598158395-148</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, For Your #$%$ Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594057047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just when you thought the practice of denying science in favor of one's harebrained assumptions had reached its lowest point, someone (usually a southerner) lowers the limbo bar again. Only a cockroach could get under now. (Pun intended. :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371598158395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:29:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598342417-149</Id><Topic><Title>BILL AYERS: Obama should be tried for 'war crimes'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371577956545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was referring to the places where right-fringe wackos (such as yourself) learn all about how communistic these people are. Critical reading skills, smar tass; critical reading skills.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371598342417</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598432306-150</Id><Topic><Title>another chinook order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371590614272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:23:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who puts thumbs down on a vechile to protect our troops and get them out of there as soon as possible. I got three thumbs down from, you guessed it, the shorts</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371598432306</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598611900-151</Id><Topic><Title>It's War!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well ... at least bat**it Bachmann did not suggest Rove should be investigated for his anti-American attitudes. Maybe the drugs are working and she's getting better!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371598611900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598742897-152</Id><Topic><Title>It's War!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A pinko questions Rove's strong pro-american sense of values? HAHAHA</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1371598742897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:39:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598755669-153</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did I really say all that? Hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371598755669</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371598910130-154</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, For Your #$%$ Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594057047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Only a cockroach could get under now. (Pun intended. :-)" Nicely done.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1371598910130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371599163737-155</Id><Topic><Title>It's War!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's like choosing between a Python and a Cobra - they're both snakes.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1371599163737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371599640278-156</Id><Title>Tom O"Brien on Boeing stock price today and the Boeing advertisement show</Title><Msg>. Tom O'Brien, is a national stock market expert , who is famous for timing the individual stock prices . Today, Mr. O'Brien covered Boeing , and pointed out that Boeing stock price now is just about "dead on the vine" saying the volume is going down over time. Mr. O'Brien indicated the last time Boeing was a 107 dollar stock was in 2007 and it will now ring the bell at the previous high and maybe get some more but then Boeing stock price will retreat over time to the 71 dollar range . In other words it not going to 130 or 150 it is close to over. For any user of the Boeing financial blog, as you can see there is a core of six Boeing barkers, the doggy, bow wow self proclaimed , Boeing advertisement salesmen, for Boeing who are selling Boeing stock to potential customers. These six people are loud and colorful and like a circus barker stand at the Boeing financial page all day long barking come on in and get some Boeing stocks. Showing news stories and dogging any other opinion with personal attacks For the year to date the competition between the two major competitors, Airbus stock is better .When you have the facts on your side you argue facts, , when you do not have the facts on your side, you pound the table and call names. Airbus is for the year to date up or better than Boeing at a 46% gain to 38% for Boeing, a 7% advantage to Airbus shareholders, For long term investment over the past 3 years , Airbus is better stock gain for their investors by 117%. Remember , the Boeing barkers the doggy bow - wow is to cover their bad position on Boeing , so they pound the table and call names.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371599640278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 19:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371600502316-157</Id><Topic><Title>how much aluminum in the new dreamliner</Title><Username>jwmjohny6</Username><Timestamp>1371589916338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:11:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And some materials that people don't think about but which add up to tonnage are carpet, upholstery and paint.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371600502316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371601056774-158</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flying cars will never be practical you would get many complaints from the folks up the block when you crash it in the street. They would be noisy buzzing around everywhere.you would have drunk all people will build some toys but a production flying car for everybody l Doubt it . the Jetson`s were cool though. Just think of all the Federal Regulations there would have to be.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1371601056774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371601161882-159</Id><Title>♫♫♫♫ No MUSIC? BUY PREFERREDS...before it's too late...5-8% dividends</Title><Msg>stay OUT of the insane "common" market boys...she's heading SOUTH soon......</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1371601161882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371601211675-160</Id><Topic><Title>It's War!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the python will love you to death.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371601211675</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371601563221-161</Id><Topic><Title>It's War!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whoosh, jokeydokey. Whoosh.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371601563221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371606249050-162</Id><Topic><Title>It's War!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371594180830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was thinking more like a clown and a vampire.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1371606249050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 21:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371607262757-163</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another insane screed from chemical_ali_infested! Climate change denial expert pretending to hold a sane discussion with himself.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1371607262757</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610410260-164</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think of all the things we use today that was invented by those before us that couldn't be done today. If the airplane was invented today, could it legally fly, probably not. Lib lawyers and gov agencies would shut it down. Same with autos, electricity, candy, nuke power , beer, etc.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1371610410260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371610721101-165</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You use the word "HEAD" a lot...is that the password at the Kent bath house</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371610721101</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 22:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371611149296-166</Id><Title>Why the New World Order has been winning so far !!!!!</Title><Msg>“The powers of financial capitalism had another far-reaching aim, nothing less than to create a world system of financial control in private hands able to dominate the political system of each country and the economy of the world as a whole. This system was to be controlled in a feudalist fashion by the central banks of the world acting in concert, by secret agreements arrived at in frequent meetings and conferences. The apex of the systems was to be the Bank for International Settlements in Basel, Switzerland, a private bank owned and controlled by the world’s central banks which were themselves private corporations. Each central bank…sought to dominate its government by its ability to control Treasury loans, to manipulate foreign exchanges, to influence the level of economic activity in the country, and to influence cooperative politicians by subsequent economic rewards in the business world." - Carroll Quigley author of "Tragedy and Hope."</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371611149296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371611311847-167</Id><Topic><Title>Why did we get 140 characters rather than flying cars?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371589372187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well over the course of history think of all the things that have been invented that failed , Flying cars is one of them. Remember the gyro copter ? pretty similar. It just would not be practical and some yahoo`s would probably get tired of you flying over their house and put a few rounds of buckshot in your flying car.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1371611311847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371611668196-168</Id><Topic><Title>Why the New World Order has been winning so far !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371611149296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:05:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other than posting conspiracy theory`s forever on Yahoo thinking you`re going to make a difference what can you going to do about it?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1371611668196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371611841941-169</Id><Title>Flying Cars</Title><Msg>Reminds me of the Republican agenda:-)</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1371611841941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371612793433-170</Id><Title>Texas Qoutes for the Day</Title><Msg>You know the good part about all those executions in Texas? Fewer Texans. You may all go to Hell, and I will go to Texas. Davy Crockett Calling a taxi in Texas is like calling a rabbi in Iraq. I'm from Texas, and one of the reasons I like Texas is because there's no one in control. The Clinton administration launched an attack on people in Texas because those people were religious nuts with guns. Hell, this country was founded by religious nuts with guns. Who does Bill Clinton think stepped ashore on Plymouth Rock? Some folks look at me and see a certain swagger, which in Texas is called 'walking.' Texas women have an amazing sense of purpose when they lose it. They're the best girls in the world - they're loyal and fun, but when they get mad, they'll try to kill you. Next time I tell you someone from Texas should not be president of the United States, please pay attention. Texas will again lift it's head and stand among the nations. It ought to do so, for no country upon the globe can compare with it in natural advantages. I dearly love the state of Texas, but I consider that a harmless perversion on my part, and discuss it only with consenting adults.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1371612793433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 23:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>