<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370406588306-1</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>never been in jail, never missed a child support payment, work for aliving, my son's always supported thier families never ran away. Got 10 grandkids, a great relationship with each and everyone. White guys love thier kids, black guys run off, so white guys got to pay for black guys family. Deadbeats, black guys know it and white guys know it thats why Obama wants to take money away from white guys, cause he knows it. Blacks are deadbeats. I have black friends that say it too. Deadbeat. get a job lazy ignorant hussler, drug pusher, moocher, be proud come out you #$%$.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370406588306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370406799973-2</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In fact, at one point the unrepentant folks cry out for the rocks to fall on them to hide them from the face of the One bringing on that judgement (Rev 6:16). So be it written for bulky-bob -further prog and the obamanites, the One knows your ways...</Msg><Username>furtherprog</Username><Timestamp>1370406799973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370406988334-3</Id><Topic><Title>Illinois state pension fund $100B in the red. Dem sell themselves out for the Union vote. The Liberal economy as we saw in Greece</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370387750151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:15:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Illinois is going to lead the way with bankruptcy. All these crying #$%$ are going to get a pay raise when that happens, its going to have a 0 at the beginning and at the end written on the proud #$%$ with the loser econimics they have been pushing. Pensions go to a big 0, can't wait for that to happen. Soup lines in Illinois just around the corner.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370406988334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370408298899-4</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris - I'm a bit puzzled by your response. You were one of many hundreds of persons who did deliberately go in harms way tto retrieve or help those who were in danger and had been hurt, and to NOT leave them behind. And I'm sure the odds were NOT in your favor. IMO- it would be demeaning to say you ' simply tried' - nothing simple about it - or " at least you tried". You knew the risks and the probable odds and went anyhow. THANK YOU !! AND ALL THE OTHERS !! OTOH - the current disaster in chief or his lackies ' didn't bother to "try' because it would take too long or ( paraphrased ) ' did not want to have others go in harms way without more detailed info ' , yada yada yada and they were smart enough to know that then attack would be over BEFORE they could get organized?? Whether or not such rescue efforts were all successful is not the issue here, But FAILURE to try IS the issue. And abhorrent to most . .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370408298899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370408390615-5</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$sexually is an abomination to God. Woman was made for man, so did God make a mistake? but wasnt creation Gods creation. Obama ran to the Grahams trying to get buy in for Obamas #$%$ agenda. Two pieces of legislation is creeping thru the Congress. Obama is not of God when considering Scripture Obama is of Satan. He is a deceiver, liar, telling half truths. Americans all know he sent the IRS, Obama went after the Press, we all know Obama is a sociopath and a thug acting out when he does not get his way.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370408390615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 00:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370409442128-6</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a little background on dr in out, he is, or was, a fugitive, a gay pedophile, a ne silver spoon lib, his hero's include che guevara and hugo chavez.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370409442128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 01:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370412136656-7</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe this will help you: "He replied, 'Go your way, Daniel, because the words are rolled up and sealed until the time of the end. Many will be purified, made spotless and refined, but the wicked will continue to be wicked. None of the wicked will understand, but those who are wise will understand.' " (Daniel 12:9, 10) If you cannot explain this, then its included warning is about you.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1370412136656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 02:02:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370413437755-8</Id><Title>Obama Astounded to Discover that He is Married</Title><Msg>From Peoples cube - President Obama, in a press release this morning, revealed that he was "surprised" to discover that he has apparently been married for quite some time. "The first I heard of it was when I saw a CNN report on my wife...uh..."Michelle," apparently...delivering an address to the National Coalition of Lobster Producers," said the President. "This was as much a surprise to me as discovering rogue agents in the IRS was when I found out about that by watching CNN too." Presidential spokesperson Jay Carney was quick to point out that there are several layers of bureaucracy in any marriage, and that nobody on the White House Staff was aware of the marriage until CNN broke the story on March 22, 2013. Evidence suggests that the marriage has been an on-going situation, as the President has also learned that he has two children, although their names, genders, and exact ages were not provided in the press briefing. "I think it important to note," Carney told reporters, "that at least one and possibly both of these children were already in place at the time the previous administration occupied the White House." It is possible that one or perhaps both were conceived during a Republican administration, or when there was a Republican majority in Congress. New reports of this heretofore unknown First Lady have been surfacing, including some disturbing allegations of lavish spending on travel and accommodations over the past four years. When questioned by reporters on the subject, Carney replied that while "such wild allegations were inevitable in an era of Republican overreach," the President himself rarely accompanied the First Lady and had thus been completely unaware of any travel, if indeed any travel had taken place. The Justice Department has announced it will be investigating possible leaks related to the revelation of the First Lady's existence on CNN.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1370413437755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 02:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370415506040-9</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. Read it and it is good. We've been buying insurance in OR. e-insurance, sort of like the exchanges. We've had a state health plan up and running way longer than Romneycare.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370415506040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 02:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370415604541-10</Id><Title>2000th Apache produced---thats alot of birds for sure</Title><Msg>Constantly upgraded and a proven powerhouse-----recently made better by new armament etc. Its been quoted to be one of the most hated and feared weapon. It pops up, fires, and goes. Protected from direct line of sight. Like that heli alot I must say</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370415604541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 03:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370415607988-11</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come on! It would be like being an only child: no one to fight with.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370415607988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 03:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370416383739-12</Id><Topic><Title>2000th Apache produced---thats alot of birds for sure</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370415604541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 03:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$20 million apiece. That's what NIST spent giving us half a report on the collapses of the World Trade Center. Wikipedia says 31 Apaches were lost in Iraq, 16 due to hostile fire. Wikipedia says 14 Apaches have been lost in Afghanistan, none due to hostile fire. So 3X as many are lost to accident as to hostile fire. What's that about?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370416383739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 03:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370416481116-13</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris, you must be the resident of a sucky state.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370416481116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 03:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370416675654-14</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're saying that an Imperial agenda depends on federal resources.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370416675654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 03:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370416853269-15</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jon Turley says Holder should be fired.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370416853269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 03:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370421014903-16</Id><Title>TSLA business model or Boeing business model which is better</Title><Msg>Elon Musk, the chief executive of electric carmaker Tesla Motors Inc, criticized the traditional way of selling cars in the United States and indicated the traditional sales or business model would hamper the 10-year-old U.S. automaker's growth prospects.Tesla is pushing to sell its Model S electric sedan directly to consumers rather than relying on a network of independent dealers. "It didn't work for Fisker, didn't work for Coda. In the last 90 years, when did it work?" Musk said at the meeting in Mountain View, California that was also broadcast online. "We have to do this directly." Boeing wants to cut labor cost but is not going to China why not/ I know/ China would learn from Boeing then replace the CEO's with low cost Chinese CEOs very simple . The greed of Boeing Executives is the problem, they want cheaper wages but can not go to where the real cheap labor is because they would be replaced very soon. NC labor is 100 per day while Chinese labor is 50 per month ,end of story. Face it the Chinese can now make anything better and cheaper than the USA and especially NC.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370421014903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 04:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370424895768-17</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you get it by now? He's a DFC. Do I have to spell it out for you????? A REAL card carrying DFC!!!!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370424895768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 05:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370424960824-18</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you move to China, little DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370424960824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 05:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370425079650-19</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your posts aren't very patriotic. In fact, you sound like a DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370425079650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 05:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370425240269-20</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a real card carrying DFC!!!!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370425240269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 05:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370425375312-21</Id><Topic><Title>12 bags of RWNJ/squirrel food</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370391397419</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you go off your meds or overdose on them? You sound like a DFC gone crazy!!!!!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370425375312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 05:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370425446114-22</Id><Title>This board has a few DFC insurgents posting 24-7</Title><Msg>and YOU know who YOU are.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370425446114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 05:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370431300524-23</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would YOU, of all idiots, know about God™? Talking about homosexuality, you sure do sound like a repressed homosexual yaself, morroon.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1370431300524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 07:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370434053955-24</Id><Title>Cell Phone Rudeness</Title><Msg>I fly frequently and notice it all the time. Passengers have there smartphones on after the announcement to shut them off has been given. These passengers may end their call as the plane takes off but they are not shut down, the passengers continues to play with them when they should be turned off. Many passengers don't know how to shut off the phone. They leave them in sleep mode. Often flight attendents pass by not noticing what the passengers hold in their hands. Its a common situation and if not a danger its rudeness to fellow passengers.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370434053955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370434132914-25</Id><Topic><Title>This board has a few DFC insurgents posting 24-7</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370425446114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 05:44:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, A few of them slipped through the wire but they're easy to spot.........they all speak with a lisp, have limp wrists and wave their pinkies at each other.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370434132914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:08:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370434787637-26</Id><Title>God Destroyed Sodom And Gomorrah.....and He's sending a Warning to...........</Title><Msg>......the Kent bath house. Chrissie and Hooze better wake up.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370434787637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370435095312-27</Id><Title>Susan Rice Lies about Benghazi - Gets Big Promotion</Title><Msg>People not willing to Lie for Obama will go nowhere in his administration. Ask any whistle blower.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370435095312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:24:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370435367512-28</Id><Title>President Transparency's Spokesman: No Comment on Secret White House Email Accounts</Title><Msg>Since President Obama's EPA administrator, HHS Secretary, and nominee for Labor Secretary have all been exposed for using pseudonymous email accounts as an end-run around transparency efforts, have any officials inside the White House employed the same trick? Sorry, the spokesman for the "most transparent administration in history" won't comment on that: Carney wants you to remember that White House internal correspondence isn't subject to FOIA requests (which isn't the case re: Jackson/Sebelius/Perez), so it's a moot question. Fox's Ed Henry follows up anyway, and Carney declines to answer. Why? If White House honchos are immune from truth-seeking FOIA requests, shouldn't they have no use for secret emails identities, and shouldn't Carney's lay-up answer be "no"?</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370435367512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370435414821-29</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don -you are correct for the future-"It is about sending a strong message to every American that, should they ever face danger abroad in the future, the American military will come to their aid. " We all know mistakes were made in Benghazi. What Congress is doing now is not making preventive proposals. This tragedy is being used for purposes of political gain under the guise of seeking more information for the families.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370435414821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370435779475-30</Id><Title>God will destroy the mediocreclassguy too</Title><Msg>get down on your knees liar- pray for forgiveness</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370435779475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370435884565-31</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you guys dont need states in Canada do you HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR H</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370435884565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370436476283-32</Id><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting</Title><Msg>Baghdad Democrat Jim McDermott blamed tea party groups for IRS targeting. He said if they hadn't exercised their rights and applied to the IRS then the IRS would not have had to indiscriminately target them. This says a lot about Washingtonians who keep electing this anti-American buffoon over and over again. Maybe Washington state Democrats are hoping he'll someday rise to the stature of Democrat Sheila Jackson Lee. He's already pretty close.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436476283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:47:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370436690961-33</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>States are able to balance budgets and some operate just fine without income taxes.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436690961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370436703219-34</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can a libtard get things so considtently backasswards. What drugs do you pinkios take? I may need some of those some day. States are where the standard of living is. RED states mean quality of life, and BLUE states mean you work for the state, and eat dirt unless you are wealthy. Red states attract businesses, and create jobs with good economic policy growing the private sector. Blue states are a high debt govt bureaucratic nitemare that bilks the folks raising taxes to support socialism, and drives people, and businesses out of the state. So what commune do you live in?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370436703219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370436885398-35</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436476283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who listens to a friggin democrat? Obama is about to hire Rice as his security advisor? Just can't get rid of his #$%$ed acompolices. One Rice, Bush's Rice was a highly educated, competent public servant who still serves on pulbic boards benefiting the folks. The other Rice, Obama's Rice, is a #$%$, and a liar, but she qualifies as the perfect Democrat.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370436885398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370437234843-36</Id><Topic><Title>God will destroy the mediocreclassguy too</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370435779475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:36:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima , I'm so sorry I left you off the Kent bath house list.......it's obvious you're feeling left out.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370437234843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370437271505-37</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436476283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dopey joe in addition to being the worlds dopyest you are obviously a race baiting racist with hate oozing out of your pores- you wouldnt get ten steps trying to voice your attitude in public- either you would end up in Leavenworth for sedition or the Black Panthers would find you and we wouldnt ever have to smell your red nekk carcass again</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370437271505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370437516836-38</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436476283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Tdouchebagger front groups werent trying to commit criminal tax evasion they wouldnt be under the IRS scrutiny- but without exception these groups have applied for tax exempt status- never mind that they would be breaking the law if they got that status. The only reason the IRS thing has surfaced is because all of a sudden TParty Patriots, Americans for Prosperity and Freedom Works began to believe they were under the scrutiny of the IRS and FBI so they are trying to mask their guilt by blaming the IRS and FBI for persecuting them</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370437516836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370437892448-39</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436476283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post, bro. Spot on.</Msg><Username>lucid_luke</Username><Timestamp>1370437892448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370438993576-40</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436476283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lucid_luke (sparty in hoodie)</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370438993576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370440036853-41</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436476283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rainbow Coalition, NAACP, Media Matters, ACORN, Al Sharpton's National Action Network and a thousand more anti-American left wing idiot farms were expeditiously approved as non profit entities..........naw, nothing political about any of these groups.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370440036853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:47:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370440255325-42</Id><Title>States are not needed Unless you want the USA to be a communist country.......</Title><Msg>......run by a dictatorship like Genna advocates for the country.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370440255325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370440509578-43</Id><Title>Is there a Sign at the White House that says only Tax Cheats and Liars may Apply?</Title><Msg>.....that seems to be the prerequisites for joining and advancing in the Obama administration.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370440509578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370440669316-44</Id><Topic><Title>God Destroyed Sodom And Gomorrah.....and He's sending a Warning to...........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370434787637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:19:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God isn't nearly as confused about a non-existent bath house as you are.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370440669316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 09:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370440831629-45</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370436476283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:47:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>turns out abusing Federal power and rampant fraud in dumb districts was an absolute requirement if dumbos were to throw the election in barack's favor...4 states, 333,908 votes Romney lost New Hampshire’s 4 electoral college votes by a margin of 40,659 Obama won with 368,529 to Romney’s 327,870. Romney lost Florida’s 29 electoral college votes by a margin of 73,858 Obama won with 4,236,032 to Romney's 4,162,174. Romney lost Ohio’s 18 electoral college votes by a margin of 103,481 Obama won with 2,697,260 to Romney’s 2,593,779 Romney lost Virginia’s 13 electoral college votes by a margin of 115,910 Obama won with 1,905,528 to Romney’s 1,789,618. Add the 64 electoral college votes from this switch of 333,908 votes in these four key states to Romney’s 206, remove them from Obama’s 332, and Romney defeats Obama 270 to 268.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370440831629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370440853796-46</Id><Title>GOV'T MOTORS BAILOUT: $10 BILLION LOSS</Title><Msg>Treasury, UAW health care trust will sell 50 million shares of GM stock Washington — The U.S. Treasury said Wednesday it plans to sell 30 million additional shares of General Motors stock in a new public offering in conjunction with GM’s return to the S&amp;P 500 index on Thursday. The United Auto Workers Retiree Medical Benefits Trust — which holds about 14 percent of GM — will also participate by selling 20 million shares, making the total offering size 50 million shares. It represents about 12 percent of Treasury’s outstanding GM stock. The move may mean that Treasury completely exits in 2013, rather than by the end of March 2014. The return to the S&amp;P will prompt significant demand for GM shares and the stock has recently traded near its highest level since February 2011. GM is filing a new prospectus ahead of the sale. The Treasury sold nearly 20 percent of its remaining shares in General Motors Co. in the first three months of the year, the Detroit automaker disclosed Thursday. The Treasury, which initially held 60.8 percent of GM as part of the U.S. $49.5 billion bailout, now owns just 16.4 percent, or 241.7 million shares. In December, the Treasury sold GM 200 million shares of its stake for $5.5 billion to reduce its stake to 300 million shares. In total, Treasury has recouped $30.6 billion. At current trading prices, Treasury would lose around $10 billion on its GM bailout.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370440853796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370440860246-47</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whoosh, poordumb. Whoosh.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370440860246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:01:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370441006082-48</Id><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Msg>......he is a good little DFC.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370441062444-49</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pdb - hold that thought</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370441062444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370441284155-50</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not if you prefer one dumb oligarch ruled commune, the collective host for dem parasites will just be a little thinner, huh chrissie</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370441284155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370441398534-51</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stikdik prefers crooks in gov't, he's dependent on em</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370441398534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370441523985-52</Id><Title>'It's not a recovery. It's not even normal growth. It's bad'...</Title><Msg>The country's tepid growth in its gross domestic product isn't creating enough good jobs to build a strong middle class, according to a UCLA report released Wednesday. "Growth in GDP has been positive, but not exceptional," UCLA economists wrote in their quarterly Anderson Forecast. "Jobs are growing, but not rapidly enough to create good jobs for all." The report, which analyzed long-term trends of past recoveries, found that the long-anticipated "Great Recovery" has not yet materialized. Real GDP growth — the value of goods and services produced after adjusting for inflation — is 15.4% below the 3% growth trend of past recoveries, wrote Edward Leamer, director of the UCLA Anderson Forecast. More robust growth will be necessary to bring this recovery in line with previous ones. "It's not a recovery," he wrote. "It's not even normal growth. It's bad." That has long-term implications in the face of technological advancements that continue displacing workers, Leamer said. And the country's education system isn't adequately developing the workforce of the future, he said.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441523985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370441755524-53</Id><Topic><Title>'It's not a recovery. It's not even normal growth. It's bad'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441523985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is the perfect liberal model that will happen everytime it is implimented. Europe is the perfect example as well. They sacrifice the private sector that creates real jobs that pays the public sector bills by growing the public sector extensively, impliment high regulation, and taxation to pay for it, and the private sector goes gunny sack. Businesses and jobs leave, and the govt continues to grow debt until it goes under.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370441755524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370441829592-54</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a big admirer of Chairman Mao and Uncle Ho</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370441829592</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370441901693-55</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't give yourself away, mediocremind. All you know about DFCs is that they make you very jealous. In fact, we might call it "DFC envy."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370441901693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370441906052-56</Id><Topic><Title>'It's not a recovery. It's not even normal growth. It's bad'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441523985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>growth in debt is outpacing growth in gdp four to one...which means we're depleting wealth faster than it's being created meanwhile dumb activists, i mean parasites, continue to tax, litigate, and regulate, ranchers, farmers, and businesses, large and small, out of business</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370441906052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370442031468-57</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's DFC chrissie? fried chicken?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370442031468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370442174086-58</Id><Topic><Title>'It's not a recovery. It's not even normal growth. It's bad'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441523985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The country's education system isn't adequately developing the workforce of the future". You know that the education system is actually developing the workforce that the PTB want for the USA. Unfortunately it's a government dependant, dumbed down workforce, that will believe whatever they are told, no matter how silly. 1984 just got here a little late.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1370442174086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370442454461-59</Id><Topic><Title>'It's not a recovery. It's not even normal growth. It's bad'...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441523985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:12:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one would conclude the education collective is overpaid and underperforming., huh sparty...so much for non competitive work rules</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370442454461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370443082674-60</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am always amazed at how a pathetic coward like yourself, censored, who avoided military service, has the audacity to call a war hero "chrissie." It's unbelievable.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1370443082674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370443334747-61</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Distinguished Flying Cross. How's that 2nd shift assistant manager salad bar job going?</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1370443334747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370443669939-62</Id><Title>Report: US hasn't seen expected 'Great Recovery'</Title><Msg>An economic forecast says the country's expected "Great Recovery" hasn't materialized and the economy's fallen short of even normal growth. The Los Angeles Times reports the gloomy picture appears in the quarterly UCLA Anderson Forecast released Wednesday. It says that real gross domestic product growth - the inflation-adjusted value of goods and services produced - is well below the 3-percent growth trend of past recoveries. The forecast says the country isn't creating enough good jobs.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370443669939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370443789429-63</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA business model or Boeing business model which is better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370421014903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 04:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayneker says, "...the Chinese can now make anything better and cheaper than the USA..." So, it doesn't take a highly skilled overpaid union work force to build airplanes? BTW, Tesla down 21% since the 1st of May and Boeing is up 8.8%.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370443789429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370444132098-64</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We do not need a federal government whose only purpose for existence in today's world is to add another layer of monopolistic power to limit individual liberty while confiscating the property of hard working men and women so it can be transferred to people who didn't earn it in exchange for their votes.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370444132098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370444356827-65</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DFC stand for Dumb F******Communist.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370444356827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370445215031-66</Id><Title>Defending an Administration of Liars and Cheats</Title><Msg>No one went to jail for Fast and Furious although there were obvious lying and it caused the death of Americans. No one has gone to jail over Benghazi although there were obvious lying and it caused the death of at least 4 Americans. No one has gone to Jail over the trampling of reporter's first amendment rights by this administration. No one has gone to jail over the IRS's abusive practice of using it's power to suppress and silence political opposition. Yet, you have the political party who put this administration in power fearlessly defending this administration and it's activities that are more akin to that of third world dictatorships than what this country should stand for.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370445215031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370446152852-67</Id><Topic><Title>Defending an Administration of Liars and Cheats</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370445215031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha - you toads can't stand that someone else is in charge !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370446152852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370446444103-68</Id><Topic><Title>Cell Phone Rudeness</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370434053955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AirTran just kick 100 high school students off a flight for not turning off their cell phones. The Rabbi of the school that the kids attend said it was unjustified.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370446444103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370447010782-69</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both Canada and China have Provinces, as well as territories.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370447010782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370447348781-70</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA business model or Boeing business model which is better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370421014903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 04:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW if tsla is down 21% since may1 not the date I said to buy that was May 3 and it was up 100% in 16 days and I called the top short squeeze and got out, and said so too. too stupid to read my user posts fool, if your still in TSLA , freevertass then you are still up 79% in just one month then see how you can't win BHT, ha ha Boeing closed on may 1 at $91.18 right now its at $99.31 a gain of 8.9% so that is not 79% gain since may 1 is it fool your still paying texas holdem with that very short stack ha ha BTW I am all out except for day trading TSLA now until it breaks out of the Bollinger band up or down but you are too stupid to know how to trade a stock I love to tell you that because your ego will not allow you to make money off me your hate over rules your common sense ha ha too stupid to make 1005 in 16 days and too stupid to realize by your own figures TSLA is up 79% ha ha fool</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370447348781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370447411855-71</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA business model or Boeing business model which is better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370421014903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 04:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1005 s/b 100%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370447411855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370447432934-72</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I can't think of a thing they can do that a federal government cannot do better!!" States can provides better educations for far less costs with schools that keep from turning out ignorant victims such as chris_genna like they did before there was ever a Federal Department of Education.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370447432934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370447651910-73</Id><Topic><Title>Defending an Administration of Liars and Cheats</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370445215031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>someone else is always in charge.....that's the problem.....#$%$'s like you need to have someone in charge of managing your life because you don't have enough gray matter to manage it yourself.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370447651910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370448184049-74</Id><Title>POLL: 56% View Feds As Threat to Individual Rights...</Title><Msg>The Internal Revenue Service scandal is just one hot-button issue that the Obama administration is facing. The other is the government investigating reporters. And new poll new numbers indicate, many Americans are not happy with the Justice Department snooping on the press, CBS 2’s #$%$ Brennan reported Tuesday. Americans are very supportive of freedom of the press, but a Rasmussen poll finds they are also very worried about how it’s applied and suspicious of the Justice Department investigating reporters. When asked, “Was the Justice Department primarily trying to intimidate the media or protect national security?” those polled said: * 43 percent say it was an attempt to intimidate the press * 34 percent say it was primarily out of concern for national security * 23 percent say they are not sure “It is partisan, absolutely. Democrats right now say there is too much freedom of the press. Republicans now say there is too much concern about national security. If George W. Bush was in the White House those numbers would be reversed,” pollster Scott Rasmussen said.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370448184049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370448304968-75</Id><Topic><Title>Susan Rice Lies about Benghazi - Gets Big Promotion</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370435095312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:24:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This #$%$ can't discern the difference between a protest and a terrorist attack and she's in charge? Maybe she has pictures of Obonzo having a fling in Vegas. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370448304968</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370448329122-76</Id><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Msg>"Since the American-led invasion of 2003, Iraq has become one of the world's top oil producers," the Times reports, "and China is now its biggest customer." Almost half of Iraq's oil production already is shipped to China, and those once vilified commies, reincarnated as today's robber barons, are bidding for an even larger stake in Iraq's oil field production. The Cold War is indeed over, but China's red capitalists have won. While the United States remains mired in the outdated task of establishing military hegemony through a vast network of advanced bases and sophisticated weaponry, the Chinese have emerged as the world's most nimble entrepreneurs, shrewdly covering their bets without the distraction of patriotic flag waving. "We lost out," Bush Defense Department official Michael Makovsky admits to the Times. "The Chinese had nothing to do with the war, but from an economic standpoint, they are benefiting from it, and our Fifth Fleet and air forces are helping to assure their supply."</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370448330518-77</Id><Title>Topping?</Title><Msg>Interesting pattern, BA has failed to hold above 100 three times now. Every time it dropped below 100 before there has been a quick burst of buying early the next day probably due to hedge/mutual fund or Boeing buyback programs. Didn't happen today. Wonder if the buy programs are starting to run out of steam? I still think that BA will hit the 120 range eventually but it may be later instead of sooner.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1370448330518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370449040570-78</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doesn't matter who buys it, or who sells it, more supply benefits ALL (in terms of price). nice try spazticus, if barack hussein and his dumb comrades would allow more production we could sell more to highest bidder and thereby narrow the trade and DEBT deficit</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370449040570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370449443432-79</Id><Topic><Title>Defending an Administration of Liars and Cheats</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370445215031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yack, yack, yack. Yada, yada.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1370449443432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370450094687-80</Id><Topic><Title>Defending an Administration of Liars and Cheats</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370445215031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote for people like O and this is what you get. The truth is actually much worse that the few stones turned over so far. They are counting on being able to stone wall the truth, and with Americans as dumb as the ones posting below they may very well be able to cover-up everything. We still know few facts! The O administration is expert at disinformation and lies.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370450094687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370450160125-81</Id><Topic><Title>Defending an Administration of Liars and Cheats</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370445215031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bebop's a defender...of liars n cheats birds of a feather</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370450160125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370450724766-82</Id><Topic><Title>Defending an Administration of Liars and Cheats</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370445215031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see this as George Soros directed effort. He and his billionaire buddies, and his net work of leftist media outlets. Soros came close in losing to Bush. The timing of putting his puppet, BO in the White House worked out for him. I've listened to Soros speak to many times, and give his anti-capitalist rant blaming the USA for the worlds problems, and what he wanted as solutions to not clearly see his socialist footprint on all of this.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370450724766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370451089028-83</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody, including you, has acknowledge any difference of opinion to the Obonzo game plan. If I have missed you or one of the aliases calling for Holder to be fired, provide a link. You are a PR shill to the nth degree for Obonzo. Your view that only the Dems have differences of opinion is myopic and hypocritical as according to past posts here by hooz and aliases, Repubs are in disarray and fighting amongst themselves. Do you disagree that such infighting constitutes differences in opinion? Once again you post as if you live in a thought bubble insulated from reality.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370451089028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370451611828-84</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i thought bush's war was all stealing their oil ahkmed, i mean stikDIK, err spart? you change your mind moore-on? far as know there are no laws or penalties against selling oil to china, nor BUYING products from china...they're not on barack hussein's very short (4 nation) terrorist list. earth to ahkmed, it's a world market, furnished like your public housing</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370451611828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370451733059-85</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty, err ali, is still tuned in to keith olbermann....he get a job with al jazeera (formerly gore) TV?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370451733059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370451870402-86</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>China benefits, and has to SMILE at their democrat supporters in this country that continue to deny fossil fuel generation in favor of govt sponsored corrupt green energy that can not supply the needed energy we need to compete against China. The leftists in the country should be getting a govt check from China for their support for creating China as the new super power.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370451870402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370452675801-87</Id><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Msg>in favor of laissez-faire, the free market, and the gold standard..... centered on the unalienable rights of the individual, freedom of speech, freedom of the press, freedom of religion for all belief systems, right to due process and equality under the law as a common foundation across America...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370452922386-88</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bushco lover - how many died so you and china could reap the rewards ?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452922386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:22:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370453366332-89</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a low information dolt who doesn't seem to get the significance of someone like Olbermann calling for Obonzo's resignation/firing. Are you a double agent secretly supporting Obonzo and sharing hugs with Genna in the Kent bath house?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370453366332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:29:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370453802573-90</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>liberals n their brethren m uslim made disasters were whining bout half a million kids dying resultant of saddam sidestepping sanctions to divert oil for food to palaces/bunkers/weapons. they were great about whinning when he was murdering/torturing near 10,000K per year. they remain tight lipped about saddams terrorist training camps and wmd turning up in syria damned if you do, damned if you don't, libs n their mobro allies will whine either way, huh spart, i mean ahkmed</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370453802573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:36:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370453966097-91</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i would expect olbermann to behave like a jilted luver, msdnc and al jazeera gore threw him overboard he's still a lap dog for dumb causes</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370453966097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454039514-92</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stikDIK, err sparty, makes it up as he goes along</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370454039514</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454153434-93</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They used to be the standard of freedom, but their tolerance for Obama's crypto-fascistic agenda shows them to be hypocrites.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370454153434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454325713-94</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Olberman was fired by Al Gore, don't forget.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370454325713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454391202-95</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>states can ignore the constitution allowing the red neckks to commit about any crime that strikes their fancy- like slavery-- been done before BTW not only do you not know anything about government- you know nothing about economics just what do you know??</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370454391202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454405080-96</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>though their labels serve to deceive, progressives (err unlimited gov't do as i say central planners) were NEVER the standard bearers of freedom, they are in FACT antithetical to freedom</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370454405080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454446573-97</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't about stealing the Iraq oil. It was about taking it off the market to constrict the supply and raise prices. Also to stop Saddam from selling oil for Euros.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370454446573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454507616-98</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>which oligarchs did you have in mind sensless?? Charlie Koch? Richard Mellon Scaife? The Duponts? the Waltons? let us know you narrow minded bigot</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370454507616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454551161-99</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Madeleine Albright validated the estimate of 500,000 dead kids, and said "It was worth it". See the Youtube video "Monster Madge"</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370454551161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454597272-100</Id><Topic><Title>Defending an Administration of Liars and Cheats</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1370445215031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 11:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weve had administrations of liars and cheats like the Nixon, Raygun, Bush I, Bush II admins- jist which one did you have in mind</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370454597272</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454701649-101</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>riiiiiighhhhttttt, the ever changing story, i mean narrative....still doesn't make sense you know what makes sense, not producing oil to keep world prices high as a payoff to saudi foster parents, with added bonus of screwing 100s of millions of Americans in the process.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370454701649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370454989045-102</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" tolerance for Obama's crypto-fascistic " took years to get things this fk d up - we need more time to resolve</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370454989045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370455504685-103</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIARS !!! " The sanctions against Iraq were a near-total financial and trade embargo imposed by the United Nations Security Council on the nation of Iraq. They began August 6, 1990, four days after Iraq's invasion of Kuwait "</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370455504685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:05:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370457976203-104</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA business model or Boeing business model which is better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370421014903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 04:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Chinese labor is 50 per month ,end of story." Not end of story. As usual, Wayne spreading disinformation on the board to support his theories. "more recent numbers from a Japanese survey that put the average base monthly wage in Guangzhou at $352 a month and $317 in Shenzen." Google "bloomberg china wages" for article on 3/27/2013</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370457976203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370458498780-105</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What they can do better is experiment with marriage laws, marijuana laws, death penalty laws, gun laws, corporate regulation, public education. If you don't like what your state is doing, you can move to another state.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370458498780</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370458709470-106</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick, Are you related to Rip Van Winkle by any chance? And have been asleep for the last 4 years, 137 days, and 3 hours? Since "Progressive" liberals have "taken over" the White House and U.S. Senate: 1. Drone killings of Americans without "due process" as well as 2000 other human beings 2. Use/abuse of IRS to target, abuse, and harass "non-progressives" 3. Take-over of General Motors and Chrysler 4. Secret email accounts 5. Amassing one billion bullets for who knows what reason 6. Massive supplying of assault weapons to Mexican Drug Cartels 7. Subverting the 2nd Amendment to the Constitution 8. Assault on religious freedom 9. Massive increase in taxes 10. Abandonment of our embassy personnel to terrorists 11. Reduction of naval carrier task force availability from a peak of eight to three 12. Four terrorist attacks on U.S. soil 13. Consistent and pervasive and unrepentant lying by administration officials as well as the President 14. Harassment and intimidation of the Press and its First Amendment rights Obama is doing what he said he would do: "transform America". I suggest that you herald the new era of fascism and socialism as that is the direction he is taking the country.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1370458709470</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 14:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370458835610-107</Id><Title>Can Anyone Tell Me Why Complete Losers Post To Stock Message Boards</Title><Msg>What Zeros They Must Be</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1370458835610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370459916294-108</Id><Topic><Title>Can Anyone Tell Me Why Complete Losers Post To Stock Message Boards</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1370458835610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:00:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speak for yourself, FACEHOLE.</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1370459916294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:18:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370460157100-109</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bulky thats distorted thinking - you still have your rifle, your bible and the freedom to express both... plus your handlers have freedom to elude the tax-man !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370460157100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370460197247-110</Id><Topic><Title>Can Anyone Tell Me Why Complete Losers Post To Stock Message Boards</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1370458835610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:00:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you don't know? So what side of a head of lettuce do you think your IQ is?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370460197247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370461032863-111</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More time? It was Obama's treaty obligation to investigate and prosecute torturers in the Bush administration--"looking forward" and ignoring it was not an option. How much time do you need to investigate blatant violations of the law? Bush admitted the illegal wiretaps on national TV, and he admitted the tortures in his book.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370461032863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370461337615-112</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right. So the easiest way to get the feds ofdf our back is to close the 800 military bases overseas and redeploy the DoD to the mission of defending our own borders, which could be accomplished with only 20% of the current military budget. So get cracking!</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370461337615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370462717415-113</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an anarchist as long as it gives you the freedom to commit crimes of your choice one of which is violation of the Civil Rights laws of 1964-65, another is tax evasion tho the amount of tax you owed never amounted to more than 25-30 bucks. You also are an saskissser and would gladly do what the uber rich wanted you to do----for Gawd knows what reason</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370462717415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370462746339-114</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got to ya did i- har har har har har har har har har har</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370462746339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:05:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370462870575-115</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Say there I doubt that Gold Standard- hadnt you better rethink that one</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370462870575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370463549097-116</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. Drone killings of Americans without "due process" as well as 2000 other human beings These jerks were combatants and thats why they got killed- try not to stand too close to your buddies there fatso- you could be collateral damage 2. Use/abuse of IRS to target, abuse, and harass "non-progressives" The douchebagger orgs like TParty Patriots, Americans for Prosperity, Freedom Works etc are guilty of tax evasion which is a federal crime and the IRS is in their rights to scrutinize as much as needed to prosecute. 3. Take-over of General Motors and Chrysler Seems to me like GM and Chrysler expect to pay their loans and buy back assets by the end of this year- hardly a take over if you are still of sound mind which I doubt 4. Secret email accounts No ones email account is able to evade the FBI or any other serious law enforcement org 5. Amassing one billion bullets for who knows what reason They gotta buy bullets sometime- and in bulk quantity. You paranoid psychotics just cant handle that one can you- Also it means they are going to be able to bring in the crooks even if it takes a gunfight 6. Massive supplying of assault weapons to Mexican Drug Cartels Stop bashing Junior- the creator of Fast and Furios- hes not responsible- hes too dumb 7. Subverting the 2nd Amendment to the Constitution So you dont want background checks- so you can continue to sell guns to criminals and psychos 8. Assault on religious freedom Any breach of the First Amendment would long ago have been ruled against by the RWNJ Supreme Court and prosecuted 9. Massive increase in taxes The insane Bush tax cuts are still in place- this stat</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370463549097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370463856481-117</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"fatso"? All of your arguments are negated by your tone - as well as you are not correct on any of them.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1370463856481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 16:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370466169694-118</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SD - in your neck of the woods - sister is code for free poozee !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370466169694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370466659330-119</Id><Title>my guess Obama will trash the White House like Clinton but will he also pardon all his felon buds across America</Title><Msg>I suspet he will while the liberal horde cheers.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370466659330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:10:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370467066461-120</Id><Title>“SHE GOT IN MY FACE”</Title><Msg>She lacks the behavior, manner, style or class considered proper for a First Lady (not to mention vocabulary).</Msg><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1370467066461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370467187247-121</Id><Title>is Obama helping or hurting the recovery? according to Bernanke the leading economic expert of the land</Title><Msg>Obamu is hurting the recovery. This is why. Obama has no poliicies that support a recovery. Second the 8% payroll tax is killing job growth.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370467187247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370467848273-122</Id><Title>what is better ACAD,TSLA or Boeing and being competive in pay at Carolina compared to China hype or real?</Title><Msg>A frequent BHT, spartacus99991 , has pointed out that the Chinese make an average month pay of $350 dollars and I guessed 50 , so is my point invalid? I said , if Boeing really wanted cheap labor, then Carolina is not competitive. Boeing web page states the average Carolina worker makes $53000 per year. That means Boeing is not going to be able to compete with their high wages in Carolina or maybe they just want to illegally get rid of unions hum? so Boeing pays their workers 1162% more per year . The only reason Boeing is not in China is, the Boeing , CEO would be replaced as soon as the Chinese learned how overpaid and greedy he is . End of that story. Now Boeing stock price is down over a percent like yesterday no surprise . I said when the TSLA squeeze was done we are in for a stock market pullback not shock to a trader who reads a chart it is obvious. So now Boeing stock price has lost shareholders money , it is and down from 32% year to date stock price increase to 30%. But my stocks ACAD and TSLA both were up on a major down day. For the year to date , ACAD is now up from 212% a few days ago to a gain now to 216% gain that is a 4 dollar gain during a overall stock market retreat of 4%. TSLA is up slightly today and after the 16 day 100% stock price gain. I called it the day it did the squeeze to get out. As a BHT , if you want to be a liar, you can say it is down , yep you would only be up 79% since May1 as another hack said today ! I made my comment on May 3 but who is nitpicking the bottom line is TSLA is up 182% year to date and Boeing is not get it Boeing less gain So a 100k investment in TSLA 282,000 dollars today and Boeing would be 130,000 dollar which is better would be 2end of story. As far as TSLA as I said you can day trade it or wait until it breaks above the narrow trade range on the Bollinger band . You BHT are really stupid ha ha Keep trading your ego and I will trade the stock chart !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370467848273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370469188842-123</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA business model or Boeing business model which is better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370421014903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 04:30:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne actually bothering to correct one of his errors. Can the Apocalypse be far behind?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370469188842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370469290912-124</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Progressives worry about locked doors, liberals about glass ceilings, which is why liberals thought Obama's election would create a post-racial society.Too many liberals are infatuated with symbolism such as electing a black president, while ignoring the real problems most minorities face in everything from the job market to dealing with the law. Such as, 19+% black unemployment rate as the liberal gov. reports a falling rate even some liberals cities like Seattle reporting full employment. Falling unemployment while welfare numbers are soaring only makes sense if you want to believe otherwise when the facts spell the opposite.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370469290912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370469541833-125</Id><Topic><Title>Can Anyone Tell Me Why Complete Losers Post To Stock Message Boards</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1370458835610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 15:00:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess you knew I was talking about you...lolololololololololoololol</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1370469541833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370471245264-126</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty err ali err spaz err censored err fascist err bumper err al Jazeera err islamospaz err spartacensored</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1370471245264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 18:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370471294154-127</Id><Topic><Title>China Benefits From Bush's War !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370448329122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 12:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err ahkmed err stikDIK err spart err very short terrorist list: bumper fascist censored</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1370471294154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 18:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370471651402-128</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another classic from gregjanetommax: actually using "spell" in a post.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1370471651402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 18:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370472075416-129</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Progressive liberals shouild be on the FBI's list, and on the watch list of every decent Pro-American. They are bent on destroying your health and welfare.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370472075416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 18:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370473265333-130</Id><Topic><Title>Progressive liberals are the standard of freedom !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370452675801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you in favor of laissez-faire and the free market, you would be against a government mandated minimum wage. Have you ever posted that you are against any minimum wage or is this an attempt at comedy?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370473265333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:01:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370473329809-131</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a real DFC would want to do away with states.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1370473329809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 19:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370476808886-132</Id><Topic><Title>“SHE GOT IN MY FACE”</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1370467066461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She was just trying to identify with their base, low info, low IQ types.</Msg><Username>susank875</Username><Timestamp>1370476808886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:00:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370477383795-133</Id><Title>new drone funding</Title><Msg>At first glance, the $6.8 million contract that Boeing just won from America's Missile Defense Agency probably sounds more like a rounding error than an actual, material event in the life of this $75 billion company. But it could become material in time. On Wednesday, the Pentagon announced it was quadrupling the size of Boeing's original $2.2 million contract to do "instruments and payloads" work on an unnamed "experimental prototype aircraft." The Pentagon's contract also specifies that Boeing will "gather, analyze, and report flight test data to characterize potential payload environments" over the next five months.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370477383795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370478554986-134</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. In your case, it's dumb frickin capitalist. In my case, it stands for Distinguished Flying Cross, which I got for putting my actions where my beliefs were. Unlike any of you bozos who can't bear to contemplate that simple step.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370478554986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370479104552-135</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, LD. And while agree with your opinion of censored/bumper 98%, I have to point out that I have never called myself "war hero." I leave that to floyd and other armchair wannabees. Call me "combat veteran." That more closely accurately describes my somewhat limited career as a Citizen Soldier.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370479104552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370479738019-136</Id><Topic><Title>Kerry: US Will Sign UN Gun Control Treaty</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370293201179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 17:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, 0 for 9. Couldn't even get your other IDs working for you?</Msg><Username>seanesq2001</Username><Timestamp>1370479738019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:48:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370480831467-137</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tsk Tsk. Such vitriol.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370480831467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370480848565-138</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>American armed forces do try to leave no one behind, but over the centuries, many troops and civilians have fallen behind or found themselves behind enemy lines. Many people spent years as captives in VietNam. The US knew they were there, but had to wait. Remember, that was not a declared war, at least not as far as US participation, therefore, certain actions could not be taken. And as we know now, many actions that were taken would not have been considered legal under the rules of warfare. There have been many times in history that the armed forces could not or would not be able to immediately remedy a situation.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370480848565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:07:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370481156218-139</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had trried to respond to Don on this topic but Yahoo has a problem with honest opinion, I guess. I also composed a response to your post about single kids re abolishing states; I don't know what Yahoo disliked about thas one. Perhaps they only want trolls and counter-trolls on this board.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370481156218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370481502225-140</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're coming through loud and clear on this board.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370481502225</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:18:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370481996299-141</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHRIS - If you ( or anyone) tries to put in a link, or copies very much from another site in one post- it first looks like it is ok, but then when you check it does not appear. Probably a few buzz words or phrases that trip the robo cops. Yapoo does not have a problem with BS so called ' opinions" my guess is that whatever filter is used just barfs at times</Msg><Username>dwshup3</Username><Timestamp>1370481996299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 21:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370484318823-142</Id><Topic><Title>Cell Phone Rudeness</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370434053955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 08:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Rabbi has a point all US air carriers are generally lax in enforcing the rule requiring the shutting down of electronic equipment for takeoff and landing. Unless the rule is generally enforced this one instance of selective punishment on this large group of high school students in kicking them off the plane is unjust. The airline needs to answer why did it resort to collective punishment of all the high school kids on the flight for the conduct of a few. Collective punishment does not sound fair.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370484318823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 22:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370484871529-143</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I nearly always say "Sir" when meeting Distinguished Flying Cross recipients. My father earned some decorations in WWII and I was taught something about respecting decorated military veterans. This board is infested with chicken hawks, racists, doofuses (doofi?), homophobes, and conspiracy kooks, so thank you for providing some sanity and being something we can respect.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1370484871529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 22:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370486822909-144</Id><Topic><Title>new drone funding</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370477383795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 20:09:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully they obtain their design goal of staying aloft for 4 days at 65,000 feet. Think they will as things are progressing well. Payload 450lbs for sensors should do it for now---plans to try to reach 2,000lbs payload and staying aloft for more than 1 week.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370486822909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 22:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370486981164-145</Id><Title>Remember Obama's plan for his next term?</Title><Msg>Foodstamps, even Foodstamps in Mexico, any where just get elected. Bernanke was right Obama has no policies to support a recovery. The 8% payroll tax is killing job growth, but did you see Rand Paul policies? Paul is trying to help America with his plan. Obama's tax and foodstamps isn't going to cut it. $17T and climbing. http://www.randpaulreview.com/2013/06/rand-paul-a-clear-vision-to-revitalize-america/ Every American wants a job until Obama showed up.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370486981164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 22:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370488219617-146</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you like Cronie Capitalism over Capitalism. Choosing winners on the cronie instead of merit. President can choose but the rest of us go to jail. So spending your money for little or no output like Solyndra and the other Cronie Capitalism that went bankrupt on the tax payer dime.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370488219617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370488285460-147</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my put, you might be a hero but you're also stupid. Fess up, you're stupid come out and be proud.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370488285460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370488351047-148</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, charts; but as a civilian for the past 42 years, I also respond to "Hey, you." :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370488351047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370488760553-149</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's high praise, tommix, considering YOUR IQ.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370488760553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370488865262-150</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's no crony (note correct spelling) capitalism quite like Halliburton under VP D.less Cheney.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370488865262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370489427370-151</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congrats, alb, you seem to be the only one here who took my post in the spirit I intended. What surprised me is how SERIOUSLY those trolls took my counter-trolling. I find the reaction to my suggestion that we abolish state government strongly reinforces my suspicion that half the posts here are placed by about three TRUE BELIEVERS who only print outrageous ideas to advance an ultra-con servative/warped lib ertarian agenda.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370489427370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370489547653-152</Id><Topic><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well ... greatly abbreviated, it finally passed the board...</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370489547653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370489613382-153</Id><Title>I think this works. Libtard gas is $4.00 a gal. GOP gas is $1.83 put your pocket book where your mouth is!</Title><Msg>and I'll say Libtards win. See it my way and be a winner</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370489613382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370489959131-154</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so Obama is not chosing winners and losers, except in his case he can't pick just one Green Energy winner not going to bankruptcy. Get off drugs and take another look at the spelling. Stupid is as stupid does.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370489959131</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370490149666-155</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know my IQ, to high to be brainwashed like you libtards. Take a look at the the #$%$ in Greece who swallowed the political left. Now take a look at thier gov. pensions, cut in half. All crying and weeping today.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370490149666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370490357300-156</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just TO funny.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370490357300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370490671666-157</Id><Topic><Title>I think this works. Libtard gas is $4.00 a gal. GOP gas is $1.83 put your pocket book where your mouth is!</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370489613382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:33:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sure can cherry-pick your data. When I bought a Ford Escape in late 2008, Bushgas was certainly no $1.83. ou shouldn't taslk about others' drugs when YOURS work such wonders for you!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370490671666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370491103261-158</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Genna Doesn't want States, He prefers a Dictatorship........</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370441006082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know my IQ, to high Classic.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1370491103261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 23:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>