<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364097809452-1</Id><Topic><Title>BA will hit 90 by Friday..</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363636610950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA will crash by Friday, 70 coming</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364097809452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364098363088-2</Id><Topic><Title>5 experimental 787 aircraft flew for 2 years no battery problems</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807695147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Son open your eyes to learn the way. Go wrong way will lead you to hell.</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364098363088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364098431637-3</Id><Topic><Title>All Planes Grounded. Powerful Storm Coming: Ray LaHood.</Title><Username>hoptrannc</Username><Timestamp>1364091747595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 22:22:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks....</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364098431637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364098594452-4</Id><Topic><Title>MATCH OF THE YEAR: RAY CONNER THE BULL VS RAY LAHOOD THE BEAR. WHO CARES ABOUT GOLBEDYGOOK</Title><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364090094139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 21:54:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ray Connery the Bull may be in upper hand with strong dollar swing.?</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364098594452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364098726980-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ray Conneer the Bull with $ / Ray LaHood the Bear with Power punch.</Title><Username>meinfdia</Username><Timestamp>1364085287723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 20:34:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed , money talk , Ray the Bull will win.</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364098726980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364099089319-6</Id><Topic><Title>BA will hit 90 by Friday..</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363636610950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lazy sleepy birds. Keep on dreaming</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364099089319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364099184652-7</Id><Topic><Title>FengShui/Aviation</Title><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1363965781256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 11:23:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for advices Golbedygook.</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364099184652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364099442177-8</Id><Topic><Title>Feng Shui in Aviation.</Title><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1363851414745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 03:36:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks cagook</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364099442177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364099604374-9</Id><Topic><Title>BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY!</Title><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1363632899145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 14:54:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not till the match of the year next week bet. Ray Conner the Bull vs. Ray LaHood the Bear.</Msg><Username>bigbirdisaneagle</Username><Timestamp>1364099604374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364099766315-10</Id><Title>Boeing To loose another All Boeing customer , how is that cheap outsourcing working for you Now CEO!</Title><Msg>TOKYO (Reuters) - Japan Airlines Co may buy about 20 A350 jets from Airbus for around 400 billion yen ($4.23 billion), the Nikkei daily reported on Sunday, a move that would reduce its reliance on Boeing . The Japanese carrier is considering using A350-1000 jets on flights to Europe and the United States to replace its Boeing 777 jets, and is set to make a final decision on the purchase by around June, the newspaper said, without citing sources. Japan Airlines and Airbus could not be immediately reached for comment. The deal for the 350-seater planes would be the first with the European aircraft maker and includes a simulation facility for pilot training. Japan Airlines is set to retire its lone McDonnell Douglas MD-90 jet after a final flight on March 30, leaving it with a fleet of more than 100 aircraft, all manufactured by Boeing, the report said. The carrier's seven Boeing 787 Dreamliner jets have been grounded since mid-January after problems with its lithium-ion battery. IN financial related update, Boeing stock price has gained only 16% gain in three years , Boeing is one of the Dow Jones Stocks , the Dow Jones average is up 33% in 3 years, Airbus stock price has gained 162% in the last 3 years but it gets worse fore Boeing investors. The outsourcd 787 is 3 years late 33 billion over budget and the control and understaning of why the failure of the 787 has taken place is in the hands of the cheap contractors.They engineered and produced the parts. The Boeing investor has to pay like an insurer for any failurre on the contractors' performance. However the Boeing CEO is not worried, he gave himself a 20% performance Bonus on the stockholders investment !BA stock price gain YTDis up 12% while Airbus stock price gain YTD 35% . , Japan which was as a country for decades a 100% Boeing customer and a parts supplier is going with Airbus planes due to the failure of Chicago Management team So how's that outsourcing working for you now !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364099766315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:36:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364099882769-11</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing To loose another All Boeing customer , how is that cheap outsourcing working for you Now CEO!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364099766315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:36:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's give McNerney a raise!</Msg><Username>av_week_reader</Username><Timestamp>1364099882769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364102277495-12</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing To loose another All Boeing customer , how is that cheap outsourcing working for you Now CEO!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364099766315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:36:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, maybe they screwed Boeing on the 787 battery deal. Ever flown on an AirBus. I flew AirBus for years and they really suck. Boeing builds the better aircraft. No doubt about it!</Msg><Username>barbing1965</Username><Timestamp>1364102277495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 01:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364103264071-13</Id><Title>Obama's Popularity Lower than George Bush in the Mid East</Title><Msg>Without the benefit or a drooling media Obama is perceived for what he is -- a big phoney "Despite Barack Obama's promises to salvage America's reputation abroad from all the damage supposedly done by the Bush administration, a survey shows support for the United States in several Middle East countries has dipped below its level from George W. Bush's final year in office. According to the Pew Research Center's Global Attitudes Project, "confidence in Obama" in Muslim countries such as Egypt, Jordan, Lebanon, and Pakistan fell from 33% to 24% during his first term alone. Approval of his policies fell even further--from a high of 34% to the current low of 15%."</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1364103264071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 01:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364103300874-14</Id><Topic><Title>Never knew 10,500 737's produced--impressive--3,100 backlog</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1364018869100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 02:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's more impressive is that Boeing built 365 B-17s in World War 2 in 1 month!</Msg><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1364103300874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 01:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364105940141-15</Id><Topic><Title>Ray Conneer the Bull with $ / Ray LaHood the Bear with Power punch.</Title><Username>meinfdia</Username><Timestamp>1364085287723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 20:34:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS.....Ray LaHood the Bear with Power Punch will be in controlled</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364105940141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:19:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364106512834-16</Id><Title>Barbing1965 says Airbus planes suck? and see you at $150 Boeing stock humm Boeing hack alert</Title><Msg>barbing1965 • Feb 2, 2013 5:39 PM(saturday) you said on Feb 2, 2013, • "I still see Boeing at 150. Problem here is once Boeing fixes the problems with the 787, and they will, Boeing will be on cruise control. Boeing is going where no company has gone before them. It's called bleeding edge"On February 4 ,2013(monday) Boeing stock was $75.21 Friday the close is 484.82 THAT IS A GAIN OF 12% OR JUST IN LINE WITH THE FLAT YEAR TO DATE DEAD CAT BOUNCE NO UP NO DOWN STOCK PRICE A WORTHLESS STOCK TO BE INVESTED IN IS BOEING I think you mean leading edge. Barbing1965 you can toss a blanket over the duopoly as far as airplanes produced and orders over the last several years . The number of planes made and ordered and delivered is insignificant, it is the delay, the cost to build and the profit margin known as the , cost of doing business, customer satisfaction &amp; profit. .Barbing1965, the one difference between Boeing and Airbus is the return on investment for the aircraft makers stock holder. So YTd Boeing has made each shareholder 12% return, Airbus has made 35% The Dow Jones average is up 33% for any ETF holder. For 3 years Boeing has made 16% for any Boeing shareholder and for Airbus shareholders got a profit of 162% So Barbing1965 you have been trashing Airbus for a long time now and you attack any other opinion. !Barbing 1965, Boeing Executives say Airbus makes a quality Airplane so apparently your opinion is in disagreement with Boeing top Brass. Airbus also thinks Boeing makes great planes too. . BARBING1965 HACK ALERT YOUR STATEMENTS ARE CONSISTENT YOU ARE ATTEMPTING TO SPIN AND TWIST THE TRUTH ABOUT BOEING AS AN INVESTMENT</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364106512834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:28:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364106617064-17</Id><Topic><Title>Barbing1965 says Airbus planes suck? and see you at $150 Boeing stock humm Boeing hack alert</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364106512834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:28:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TYPO ERROR 484.82 SHOULD BE $84.82</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364106617064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364106895269-18</Id><Topic><Title>Never knew 10,500 737's produced--impressive--3,100 backlog</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1364018869100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 02:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed but still thumbed you down cause I short BA. 1. What goes up must come down. 2. Problems with sleepy birds don't want to fly. Very costly to BA...3. Will be long term fix, not in weeks. NTSB want root cause not band aid solution.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364106895269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364107068452-19</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing To loose another All Boeing customer , how is that cheap outsourcing working for you Now CEO!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364099766315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:36:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe raise him out of the CEO chair and out the golden parachute door and outsource his job to a Harvard MBA graduate located in India who will work cheaply</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364107068452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364107394556-20</Id><Title>OUCH....</Title><Msg>Boeing To loose another All Boeing customer</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364107394556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364108195323-21</Id><Topic><Title>Never knew 10,500 737's produced--impressive--3,100 backlog</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1364018869100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 02:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, you did beat me. That is incredible when you think of it. Heard once the old I think Northrop building they rolled in one side of this long building and came out an incredible rate---dont know the plane though.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1364108195323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364108473075-22</Id><Title>sell</Title><Msg>sell, sell, sell</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364108473075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 03:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364117576573-23</Id><Title>What do Cessna, lithium batteries and the 787 Boeing plane share ? except for stock price ?</Title><Msg>The Cessna Aircraft Company of Wichita, Kansas, USA, has been the most productive aerospace company, Cessna total production of 192,991 aircraft through the end of 2009. Boeing stockholders have gained 12% YTD Ouch ! , Airbus stockholders have made 35%, YTD For 3 years Boeing stock holders have made only 16%, woof and Ouch ! Airbus stockholders have made 162% Next month Airbus will start to buy back 15% of the Airbus stocks to compete with Boeing stock price manipulation. The Dow Jones Average on a ETF investment is up is up 33% for 3 years . Cessna is owned by Textron symbol TXT their investors are up by 24% YTD and for 3 years have made 44%. So for Boeing investors that is a big woof woof ,woof and ouch ! Now unlike Boeing's top brass making a battery and smoke fire box that will double the original weight of the lithium batteries , Cessna simply replaced their same condition lithium ion firestarter with nicad batteries and were fine , So a real Big woof,woof, woof for the Boeing Board room power point rangers It flies in the Board room but it stays on the ground in Everett. The FAA says it has reviewed Cessna Citation Service Bulletin SB525C-24-05, dated September 29, 2011. The service information describes procedures for replacing lithium-ion main aircraft batteries, Cessna P/N 9914788-1, with Ni-Cad or lead acid batteries. The agency is issuing this AD following evaluation of all the relevant information and determined the unsafe condition(fire and smoke ) described previously is likely to exist or develop in other products of the same type design. The AD requires accomplishing the actions specified in the service information described previously. Within the next 10 hours time-in-service after the effective date of this AD or within the next 7 days after the effective date of this AD, whichever occurs first, replace the lithium-ion main aircraft battery, P/N 9914788-1, following Cessna Citation Service Bulletin SB525C-24-05, dated September 29,</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364117576573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 05:32:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364126057916-24</Id><Title>LOT 787 scheduled for a test flight today (sunday)</Title><Msg>The paine field blog posted the info last night. Hope the flight goes well.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1364126057916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 07:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364126993032-25</Id><Title>The party of the, "chronically needy" and the entitled illegals is in control.</Title><Msg>The country is screwed. We recognize that, left to their own devices, politicians will/have destroyed the country. Every white christian with a work ethic is on their own.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1364126993032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 08:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364127220732-26</Id><Title>LOT 787 grounding has "made the company"nearly insolvent" due to Boeing outsourcing failure</Title><Msg>LOT found itself undergoing constant management change in the late 2000s due to worsening financials and reductions in market share. After placing orders for several Boeing 787 aircraft and taking delivery of two, the carrier has found itself "nearly insolvent" due to the January 2013 grounding of the 787.[6]</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364127220732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 08:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364127342574-27</Id><Topic><Title>What do Cessna, lithium batteries and the 787 Boeing plane share ? except for stock price ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364117576573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 05:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets hope foulmoutharbor, spartacus99991 and custerious can donate money to LOT so the company does not go bankrupt due to the failure of the Boeing 787 and the costly delays .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364127342574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 08:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364131262746-28</Id><Topic><Title>DHS Won't Answer Congress On Billion Bullet Purchase</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364090881972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 22:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364131262746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 09:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364131423279-29</Id><Topic><Title>third world rising, superpower fading</Title><Username>ericwaldron11433</Username><Timestamp>1364050710620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 10:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A little story here. Until China loosens their control over their people, China is going to resort to stealing american technology. America is the greatest "Think Tank" in the world and China is a copy cat!</Msg><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1364131423279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 09:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364132426669-30</Id><Topic><Title>sell</Title><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364108473075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 03:01:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree, Fridays action painted an obvious bear lag on the daily line chart. Get ready for a nose dive Monday and all week. I've patiently waited now its time for my shorts to get pai. Ol</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1364132426669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 09:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364132731108-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Popularity Lower than George Bush in the Mid East</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1364103264071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 01:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're saying that Muslims like GWB more than they do Obama? Interesting.</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1364132731108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 09:45:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364133262837-32</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing To loose another All Boeing customer , how is that cheap outsourcing working for you Now CEO!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364099766315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:36:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try McNurdy!</Msg><Username>wonder_dink</Username><Timestamp>1364133262837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 09:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364134195757-33</Id><Title>With the World teetering on the precipice of Economic Collapse</Title><Msg>What does Obama do....go on the trail to take Americas guns....think about that 1.6 billion rounds DHS just bouht , all the armoured vehicles for urban warfare..the NDAA, the Drones flying in American airspace....use some independent thought and what does it add up to ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364134195757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364134696902-34</Id><Topic><Title>third world rising, superpower fading</Title><Username>ericwaldron11433</Username><Timestamp>1364050710620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 10:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that may be true, but travel to the best universities, and all the top students are indians and chinese, they will tell you their countries were raped, pillage and denied by colonialists, what you thinks of that ?</Msg><Username>garygirdhari</Username><Timestamp>1364134696902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:18:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364134813876-35</Id><Topic><Title>Ray Conneer the Bull with $ / Ray LaHood the Bear with Power punch.</Title><Username>meinfdia</Username><Timestamp>1364085287723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 20:34:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Change my mind to Ray Conner the Bull with dollars upper cut. Easy money last 2 week. Bull will win the second round.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364134813876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364134920590-36</Id><Topic><Title>OUCH....</Title><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364107394556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 02:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go to Boeing for a Band aid solution</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364134920590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364135737434-37</Id><Title>Paralyzed Iraq veteran plans to starve himself to death blaming Bush and Cheney</Title><Msg>The Iraq veteran who can no longer go on: Husband, 33, who was paralysed by sniper bullet four days into deployment plans to starve himself to death almost a decade on Army veteran Tomas Young enrolled in the Army two days after 9/11 Deployed to Iraq in 2004 and paralyzed by sniper's bullet four days later Mr Young plans to refuse nourishment as he is in constant pain Veteran has written his last letter to George W. Bush and #$%$ Cheney shaming them for killing thousands in the war An Iraq war veteran who has lived with extensive injuries since being paralyzed during the conflict has admitted that he no longer has the will to live. For nearly a decade, veteran Tomas Young, has been living in chronic pain after being paralyzed by a sniper's bullet four days into his first assignment in the Middle East. Now the married 33-year-old, who can no longer eat solid foods, plans to refuse nourishment as he is tired of the exhaustive struggle that his life has become.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364135737434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364136616713-38</Id><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Msg>"But the day of the Lord will come like a thief. The heavens will disappear with a roar; the elements will be destroyed by fire, and the earth and everything in it will be laid bare. Since everything will be destroyed in this way, what kind of people ought you to be? You ought to live holy and godly lives as you look forward to the day of God and speed its coming. That day will bring about the destruction of the heavens by fire, and the elements will melt in the heat." (2 Peter 3:10-12)</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364137212461-39</Id><Topic><Title>Paralyzed Iraq veteran plans to starve himself to death blaming Bush and Cheney</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364135737434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A sad tale, variations of which too many a veteran are dealing with...from PTSD, Gulf War Syndrome to Agent Orange and beyond... A good motive, but perhaps the wrong strategy...</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1364137212461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364137601696-40</Id><Topic><Title>BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY!</Title><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1363632899145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 14:54:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not yet. want to bet.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364137601696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364137685268-41</Id><Topic><Title>With the World teetering on the precipice of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364134195757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you could get a hobby or something. Collecting stamps, maybe?</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1364137685268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:08:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364137913396-42</Id><Topic><Title>Paralyzed Iraq veteran plans to starve himself to death blaming Bush and Cheney</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364135737434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With Bush lying us into an endless war and Obama KEEPING us there with MORE lies...what IS the right strategy ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364137913396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138001521-43</Id><Topic><Title>With the World teetering on the precipice of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364134195757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I play chess, I help Veterans, I help 90 year old parents...I blog about what I know is wrong with the world ...that fills my time ...thankyou very much</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364138001521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138150211-44</Id><Topic><Title>Paralyzed Iraq veteran plans to starve himself to death blaming Bush and Cheney</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364135737434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for With Bush lying us into an endless war and Obama KEEPING us there with MORE lies...what IS the right strategy ? . . LI ms__id16000 - self-immoliation ?</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1364138150211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138727776-45</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neo-evangelicals are right in pointing out that the Bible is not meant to be a science text. They also are correct in recognizing the limitation of human language. However, if their views were accepted, the results would be devastating. Jesus’ words and actions seem to contradict many of their claims. He said, “If I told you earthly things and you do not believe, how shall you believe if I tell you heavenly things?” (John 3:12) Jesus expected His accuracy in factually testable matters to be proof that He was telling the truth about spiritual matters that cannot be tested. Again, Jesus said to the crowd, “Which is easier, to say to the paralytic, ‘Your sins are forgiven’; or to say, ‘Arise, and take up your pallet and walk’? But in order that you may know that the Son of Man has authority on earth to forgive sins,’ He said to the paralytic, ‘I say to you, rise, take up your pallet and go home’” (Mark 2:9-11). Jesus proved that what He said about faith and the unverifiable realm was true by giving a very verifiable and physical healing. He made a point to say that what God says about this world demonstrates His truthfulness about the other world.</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1364138727776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138735545-46</Id><Topic><Title>BA will hit 90 by Friday..</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363636610950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing is playing with fires. NTSB getting hot. Thanks for the easy money.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364138735545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138884382-47</Id><Topic><Title>With the World teetering on the precipice of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364134195757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you are asking the wrong questions... how aboyt asking Gabby Giffords how she "feels" now about 'the war' against guns.bullets in the wrong hands</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364138884382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138981523-48</Id><Topic><Title>With the World teetering on the precipice of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364134195757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>World economy collapse? Sell BA.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364138981523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364139021588-49</Id><Topic><Title>With the World teetering on the precipice of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364134195757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus67517•13 minutes agoFlag 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts0 Reply . I play chess, I help Veterans, I help 90 year old parents...I blog about what I know is wrong with the world ...that fills my time ...thankyou very much . . LI ms__id31489 ___ what no eat, drink, fornicate, or march madness??? !?</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364139021588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364139681774-50</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Korean Air Plans to Add North America Capacity as A380s Arrive...... Strong sell BA......Gobbledygook</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364139681774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364140108510-51</Id><Topic><Title>5 experimental 787 aircraft flew for 2 years no battery problems</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807695147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my son, better shut up and get out, some big boy dumped 525K shares last minutes on Friday. Time to stop the Bull dung or you get burn . BA is playing with fires.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364140108510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364140472234-52</Id><Topic><Title>Paralyzed Iraq veteran plans to starve himself to death blaming Bush and Cheney</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364135737434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>self-immoliation ? Who are we to argue with a Vet who went to war ...gave his all ...and knows he has one last point to make in this insane world.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364140472234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364140594682-53</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...Yahoo! never will :-)" Typical "librul"! Someone is providing them a FREE message board service, yet the "librul" demands even more out of the giver!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1364140594682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364140812888-54</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have had the same problem in replying to certain posters only. If I get that strange list of numbers instead of a reply option, I just go to a different poster to make the entry. Using firefox.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1364140812888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364140984837-55</Id><Topic><Title>Paralyzed Iraq veteran plans to starve himself to death blaming Bush and Cheney</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364135737434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess it is sad that all the democrats supported going to war in Iraq. Speech after speech telling Bush to not wait, and go to war, and the dangers of not going to war. But it isn't unusual that someone blames Bush. Libs spent millions in a campaign influencing ignorants the need to blame Bush.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364140984837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141012408-56</Id><Topic><Title>BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY!</Title><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1363632899145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 14:54:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hang on for the big slide. Big boys is dumping. 525K last minute on Friday.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364141012408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141075630-57</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a pity that we aren't North Korea where only the Communist Party line is allowed. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364141075630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364141165008-58</Id><Title>BAdolt</Title><Msg>I would assume Yahoo! makes plenty of money off this service, so I'd use terms like "giver" advisedly. You have a strange notion of capitalism if you think there is ANY element of altruism involved.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364141165008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141248561-59</Id><Topic><Title>5 experimental 787 aircraft flew for 2 years no battery problems</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807695147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those 525k shares increased $52,500.00 in value over the last minutes on Friday.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1364141248561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:07:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364141305458-60</Id><Title>Sparty is trying out</Title><Msg>for the role of paid weeper at the veteran's funeral.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364141305458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141306510-61</Id><Topic><Title>BAdolt</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364141165008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:06:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So name either the first or last time (if ever) you clicked on and purchased something from said clicked Yahoo! ad.</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1364141306510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141341925-62</Id><Topic><Title>BA = BATTERY ASSESSMENT</Title><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1363615675873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 10:07:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hang on, get ready for the big slide. Big boys dumped 525K share last minute on Friday.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364141341925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141400687-63</Id><Topic><Title>BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY!</Title><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1363632899145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 14:54:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will see.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364141400687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364141407762-64</Id><Title>Still a dolt</Title><Msg>What does that have to do with anything? If Yahoo! doesn't profit from providint the service, Yahoo! should discontinue it.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364141407762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141744829-65</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty is trying out</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364141305458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why id you call the USS Liberty Veteans Liars ? Why do you denigrate a man who wants to blame Bush and Cheney fpr starting the War in Iraq...or Obama for continuing the Lies ? Why do you keep bragging about your own service but denigrate other more worthy men and women who served in uniform ? Why do you hate Liberty and the principles that made America great ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364141744829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364141870213-66</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gobbledy gobbledy gobbledygook where are you? Ready for the big slide next week.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364141870213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364142037070-67</Id><Topic><Title>5 experimental 787 aircraft flew for 2 years no battery problems</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807695147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait and see who will win. Ray Conner the Bull or Ray LaHood the Bear. I bet mine money on the Hood</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364142037070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364142610753-68</Id><Topic><Title>Still a dolt</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364141407762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:10:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A dolt I am...even in my Yahoo! name obviously displayed. But since they have not, I'll assume the makers are supporting the Yahoo! givers. Now why is it though, that I being a maker can reply whilst you can not? Little trimming of the fat by Yahoo! perhaps?</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1364142610753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364142757703-69</Id><Title>Gobbledy gobbledy, gobbledygook where are you? Scooby doo looking for You.</Title><Msg>Sell BA next week</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364142757703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364142791842-70</Id><Title>AirBus</Title><Msg>Boeing builds the best aircraft in the industry. When the 787 gets it right, this will be a great aircraft!</Msg><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1364142791842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364142887237-71</Id><Title>nicehereinca1, bigbirdisaneagle and hoptrannc</Title><Msg>Your pathetic "Ray Conner the Bull vs. Ray LaHood the Bear" is so weak it was worth maybe one post. To keep posting it only shows how little you have to say about the "subject." Weird that just you three bother with it. Oh, and dolt: hahahaha. That may be the first time in history a computer malfunction was blamed for right-fringe natural selection.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364142887237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364143022220-72</Id><Topic><Title>Still a dolt</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364141407762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:10:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are actually over-reaching on your name. Please change it to badoofusRepublicankookweirdo..</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1364143022220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364143136639-73</Id><Topic><Title>AirBus</Title><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1364142791842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:33:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Key word is WHEN?? 3 years delayed. Still looking for the root cause. Band aid solution. Stock is the only thing that fly. Boeing keep on saying since 2005</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364143136639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364143275030-74</Id><Topic><Title>nicehereinca1, bigbirdisaneagle and hoptrannc</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364142887237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:34:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you believed in God the father , jesus, the holy spirit. Guess who is laughing.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364143275030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364144039193-75</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Popularity Lower than George Bush in the Mid East</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1364103264071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 01:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joedokes45•2 hours 38 minutes agoFlag 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts3 Reply . Countries in the Middle East like Saudia Arabia, were very happy to see GW Bush take out Saddam. Wasn't much of a stretch for them to see Saddam taking over their oil. He already had attacked Kuwait. To think you can make friends with terrorist sponsored countries that want to kll you is as dumb... More . . LI ms__id42594 ___ So, according to one theory one covertly 'bled' the USSR out of Afghani$tan and now we just print the oily monies from Iraq</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364144039193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364144453765-76</Id><Title>nicehereinca1, bigbirdisaneagle and hoptrannc</Title><Msg>Only a fool resumes to speak for God. If he's laughing, it could be the way you post nonsense in a weak attempt to make a buck or two on your stocks.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364144453765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364144462055-77</Id><Topic><Title>nicehereinca1, bigbirdisaneagle and hoptrannc</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364142887237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:34:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for your attention Scooby doo.. I changed my bet to Ray Conner the Bull with the mighty dollar swing next week.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364144462055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364145123254-78</Id><Title>Self-immoliation is NOT in Sparty's id future</Title><Msg>but not for lack of of of self-immoliation-fuel but for he lacketh of the you-know=whaty's</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364145123254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364145166709-79</Id><Title>Bipartisan Dems Help Kill Carbon Tax</Title><Msg>Waxman and Gore go down in flames again as Dems join Repubs in voting down a carbon tax and that any attempt to reintroduce a tax would require 60 votes rather than a simple majority which in essence assures it stays dead. I support a carbon tax that returns 100% of any carbon tax DIRECTLY to the people as cash. Had they proposed for example that everyone received $3,000.00 annual check from carbon taxes for a net neutral impact on families, it might have had more of a chance to pass. Now Barry is limited to EPA and executive orders. The EPA is already under investigation for violation of using private email accounts to confer with NGOs on policy and the FOIAs and lawsuits are growing. In a related story the UK is 3 weeks away from energy shortage and they are seeing a harsh winter with increased cold deaths. Energy blackouts are anticipated and would increase cold deaths.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364145166709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:12:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364145475377-80</Id><Topic><Title>Gobbledy gobbledy, gobbledygook where are you? Scooby doo looking for You.</Title><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364142757703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scooby doo, I love you. Gobbledygook is looking for you. Shut up and get out before we get burn, BA is playing with fires.,</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364145475377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364145575568-81</Id><Topic><Title>Bipartisan Dems Help Kill Carbon Tax</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364145166709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roger that sparty, you're on record as supporting hoax based taxes to redistribute wealth i wouldn't a thunk it any other way</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1364145575568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364145598280-82</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My advice to you Scooby doo.: Sell next week Scooby doo.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364145598280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364145867413-83</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news for you Scooby doo: Korean Air Plans to Add North America Capacity as A380s Arrive. Sell BA, buy Airbus.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364145867413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364146041560-84</Id><Topic><Title>nicehereinca1, bigbirdisaneagle and hoptrannc</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364142887237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:34:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scooby doo, medias respond to your temper: Korean Air Plans to Add North America Capacity as A380s Arrive</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364146041560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364146240800-85</Id><Title>GOBBLEDYGOOK IS HERE, WHERE ARE YOU SCOOBY DOO ?</Title><Msg>Bad news Scooby doo: Japan Airlines may buy 20 Airbus A350 jets: Nikkei Sell next week , buy Airbus .</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364146240800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364146430625-86</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gobbledygook is here, where are you Scooby doo? Japan Airlines may buy 20 Airbus A350 jets,, the media is respond to you temper. Better sell BA next week, buy Airbus.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364146430625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364146612282-87</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u got to shake your hips enjoy the ride not only say love is real not fade away but play... and pray</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364146612282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364146776563-88</Id><Title>Elevator Shoes for all 787 managers!</Title><Msg>you heard it here!</Msg><Username>mike_2face</Username><Timestamp>1364146776563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364147243033-89</Id><Topic><Title>Elevator Shoes for all 787 managers!</Title><Username>mike_2face</Username><Timestamp>1364146776563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:39:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God does not make mistakes. Boeing does. BA is Inspired. IAM is going to tell you how it is going to be... love is real not fade away</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364147243033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364147296478-90</Id><Topic><Title>Bipartisan Dems Help Kill Carbon Tax</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364145166709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No wealth redistribution if 100% of money is returned to the people. Inefficient energy hogs like Al Gore would get hit because of using limos and private jets and having multiple properties that waste energy when no one is there living in them. The rich will have every opportunity to lower their energy use to the same level as you. As it stands right now you are actually subsidizing people like al Gore for their energy use. I will provide to you a real world example of why you would benefit. Let's say you live in a 2,000 sq.ft. house with a wife and one child. Prices for airline tickets, gas, etc would rise because of the tax. If you pay $4,000.00/yr. for electricity you can use your $9,000.00 rebate check to buy solar panels to bring your electricity cost down to $1,000.00/year. If you don't fly you save there too. If you do fly your rebate check offsets the added costs. Same with gas if gas is raised $1.00/gal. and you use 2,000 gallons per year you don't incur any increase in costs. If you drive a gas guzzler that gets 14 MPG and switch to a car that gets 25MPG you then pay less for gas net. This is a free market solution that empowers consumers and would help make the USA energy independent much sooner as we would make smarter energy decisions. The sooner we are free of Arab, African, Venezuelan oil the safer we are from future shortages like we had under Carter. What's wrong with that?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364147296478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364147933282-91</Id><Topic><Title>Bipartisan Dems Help Kill Carbon Tax</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364145166709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me just add that oil and gas are not going to be available forever and that while we have discovered new reserves they are ultimately a finite resource. I am all over the map politically but what is wrong with wanting to have my own energy sources rather than depending on the government or oil companies? If storage technology improves I can live off grid and be totally free from dependence on others for energy and avoid future power outages that are coming with bad policy decisions like the UK has made. Don't you want to be empowered to be free and independent?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364147933282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364148393245-92</Id><Title>LI yui_3_8_1_1_1364147891006_1064</Title><Msg>being that yahoos who let me reply to sparty, err ali, directly, i'll start new topics using the censor pseudonym regarding the communist hoax, err carbon, tax no different than the progressive income tax, which steals wealth from those who produce it, to those freeloaders, like sparty, chrissie, and maobowa, who don't</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1364148393245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364148779291-93</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>b cool</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364148779291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364149514093-94</Id><Title>Gave my 110%</Title><Msg>and my keep on chooglin' a dr. is worth what in Stratego</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364149514093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364150204603-95</Id><Title>Is God currently inspring writers...</Title><Msg>or was that door closed on... The mormons on purpose the black cat might be chinese or bietnam b-cuz it say mao over and over not diddy-mao but then, IAM not a liar...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364150204603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364150263811-96</Id><Topic><Title>Bipartisan Dems Help Kill Carbon Tax</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364145166709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some decent democrats are now turning against the corrupt progressives. Gives one confidence in ones country. But corrupt Obama? He is still trying to backdoor congress, and impliment the carbon tax via the corrupt EPA. Slime still exists in the Democrat Party.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364150263811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364150570136-97</Id><Title>Big- E words</Title><Msg>Big-E one thing WE DO NOT #$%$ EACH OTHER thye loose association of middle-school canons ...the big E ?</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364150570136</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364151413595-98</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good advice, thanks Gobbledygook.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364151413595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364151440204-99</Id><Topic><Title>What do Cessna, lithium batteries and the 787 Boeing plane share ? except for stock price ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364117576573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 05:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the 787 does not fly nor the boeing stock price ! Airbus and Cessna stock gain is much better than Boeing over the past 3 years as is the general stock market if your in a Boeing stock I am not going anyplace the only think hot about Boeing is the batteries</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364151440204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364151515336-100</Id><Title>woof the only thing hot about Boeing stock is their batteries ouch</Title><Msg>Boeing stockholders have gained 12% YTD Ouch ! , Airbus stockholders have made 35%, YTD For 3 years Boeing stock holders have made only 16%, woof and Ouch ! Airbus stockholders have made 162% Next month Airbus will start to buy back 15% of the Airbus stocks to compete with Boeing stock price manipulation. The Dow Jones Average on a ETF investment is up is up 33% for 3 years . Cessna is owned by Textron symbol TXT their investors are up by 24% YTD and for 3 years have made 44%. So for Boeing investors that is a big woof woof ,woof and ouch !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364151515336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364151776620-101</Id><Topic><Title>Gave my 110%</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364149514093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:25:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>same as a general or an infantry man haven't seen so many generals your age so will work on you instead or ships for that matter know our love is real not fade away</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364151776620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364152146090-102</Id><Topic><Title>Gave my 110%</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364149514093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:25:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If captured... what unit am I in: GFY,,, love is real not fade away all youe get is name, rank, cereal number hopefully some Quaker Oats, Rice Squares with warm milk slightly sweetened for lunch... let's means test : John McCain and I do mean, Mean Test</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364152146090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364153072040-103</Id><Title>The Raven complained so many times</Title><Msg>they finally censored this board..............Thanks Raven........you putz.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1364153072040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364153178722-104</Id><Topic><Title>LI yui_3_8_1_1_1364147891006_1064</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1364148393245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:06:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1364153178722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364153311429-105</Id><Topic><Title>Bipartisan Dems Help Kill Carbon Tax</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364145166709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the guy that said gas and oil are a finate source. The corrupt left made the claim we need green energy because there is but 20 yrs or so of oil left......when in fact there are CENTURIES of oil, and NG left. Do you think the private sector could develop an alternative that would be profitable in that time?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364153311429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364153532425-106</Id><Title>The land is very old</Title><Msg>from the prespective of a relative or a relativley new country with immense power</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364153532425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364153571552-107</Id><Topic><Title>nicehereinca1, bigbirdisaneagle and hoptrannc</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364144453765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:00:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3 names in 1 , same principle apply. Ask if Scooby doo believes in god. Probably not. A scary dog</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364153571552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364153636243-108</Id><Topic><Title>The Raven complained so many times</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1364153072040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These guys need a censor, but the shouldn't right $%#$ in place of words they dislike. That's pretty confusing.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1364153636243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364154009142-109</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scooby doo keep praying. Does not bother me. I am shorting BA. this is BA message board, Go to Yahoo, OMG! to share your dog food for thought.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364154009142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364154240046-110</Id><Topic><Title>BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY!</Title><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1363632899145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 14:54:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Korean Air Plans to Add North America Capacity as A380s Arrive........Japan Airlines may buy 20 Airbus A350 jets: Nikkei Time to sell BA....</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364154240046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364154282762-111</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is odd is YOU. If there ever was an odd reason....you should be called the voice of odd reason.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364154282762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364154543937-112</Id><Topic><Title>woof the only thing hot about Boeing stock is their batteries ouch</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364151515336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:58:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Boeing's batteries are good enough for Americans who fly they're good enough for this President!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364154543937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364154776152-113</Id><Topic><Title>The land is very old</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364153532425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sting: Under the ruins of a walled city Crumbling towers and beams of yellow light No flags of truce, no cries of pity The siege guns had been pounding all through the night It took a day to build the city We walked through its streets in the afternoon As I returned across the lands I'd known I recognized the fields where I'd once played I had to stop in my tracks for fear Of walking on the mines I'd laid And if I built this fortress around your heart Encircled you in trenches and barbed wire Then let me build a bridge For I cannot fill the chasm And let me set the battlements on fire Then I went off to fight some battle That I'd invented inside my head Away so long for years and years You probably thought or even wished that I was dead While the armies are all sleeping Beneath the tattered flag we'd made I had to stop in my track for fear Of walking on the mines I'd laid And if I built this fortress around your heart Encircled you in trenches and barbed wire Then let me build a bridge For I cannot fill the chasm And let me set the battlements on fire This prison has now become your home A sentence you seem prepared to pay It took a day to build the city We walked through its streets in the afternoon As I returned across the lands I'd known I recognized the fields where I'd once played I had to stop in my tracks for fear Of walking on the mines I'd laid And if I built this fortress around your heart Encircled you in trenches and barbed wire Then let me build a bridge For I cannot fill the chasm And let me set the battlements on fire</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364154776152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364154954363-114</Id><Topic><Title>woof the only thing hot about Boeing stock is their batteries ouch</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364151515336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:58:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>787 never make it to Airforce 1.....To Chinese #4 = bad luck, death. Apollo 13=4, 787=22=4. emergency on runway 22 ??? On Jan. 28, 2005, Boeing announced that it gave the 7E7 Dreamliner an official model designation number of 787. The airplane became known as the Boeing 787 Dreamliner. The model designation followed the company-announced orders from the People's Republic of China for 60 Dreamliners. Boeing incorporated the 8 at the time of the China order because in many Asian cultures, the number 8 represents good luck and prosperity. . Number add up to 4. not so good</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364154954363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364155375140-115</Id><Topic><Title>The Raven complained so many times</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1364153072040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven cant stand letting ideas stand on their own merit. Battling in the arean of concepts and the truth. He was crying that people were picking on him.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364155375140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364155448302-116</Id><Topic><Title>The land is very old</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364153532425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under the ruins of a walled city Crumbling towers and beams of yellow light ____ so few walled cities The UNited States of America has... crumbling walls of a ruined city, state , country Crete</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364155448302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364155455397-117</Id><Topic><Title>GOBBLEDYGOOK IS HERE, WHERE ARE YOU SCOOBY DOO ?</Title><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1364146240800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Cagook</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364155455397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364155572378-118</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The point is strong sell BA next week.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364155572378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364155632698-119</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting stuff.</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364082584859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for bringing it up . Strong sell BA next week.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364155632698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:07:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364155766773-120</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God does not reside here. She's in Yahoo!OMG. Strong sell BA next week</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364155766773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364155831731-121</Id><Topic><Title>Is God currently inspring writers...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364150204603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 14:36:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>christo jesus lit sticks of dynamite while riding a pale horse and smoking a cigar and they called me 'preacher'....</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364155831731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364155929896-122</Id><Topic><Title>Bipartisan Dems Help Kill Carbon Tax</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364145166709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 13:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unstable Economy , sell BA next week.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364155929896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:12:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364156031095-123</Id><Topic><Title>Still a dolt</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364141407762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:10:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL , try to tell Yahoo what to do, like BA try to tell NTSB what to do.... strong sell BA</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364156031095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364156234744-124</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Popularity Lower than George Bush in the Mid East</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1364103264071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 01:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell BA.........</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364156234744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:17:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364156362450-125</Id><Topic><Title>AirBus</Title><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1364142791842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:33:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When?? Next 3 years.. Next 5 years....that is the question boeing been asking since 2005</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364156362450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364157429713-126</Id><Title>Organ-grinder with a monkey called Chi-chi</Title><Msg>earn $1000.00/day me man meat</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364157429713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364157766189-127</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like most progressives, the contard, err dr in out, is a know nothing know it all, unlike most progressives he's a psychotic gay pedophile progressives, err communists, frown on religion, they don't like competing for your allegiance Alexander Tytler... "A democracy is always temporary in nature; it simply cannot exist as a permanent form of government. A democracy will continue to exist up until the time that voters discover that they can vote themselves generous gifts from the public treasury. From that moment on, the majority always votes for the candidates who promise the most benefits from the public treasury, with the result that every democracy will finally collapse due to loose fiscal policy, which is always followed by a dictatorship. The average age of the world's greatest civilizations from the beginning of history has been about 200 years. During those 200 years, these nations always progressed through the following sequence: * From bondage to spiritual faith; * From spiritual faith to great courage; * From courage to liberty; * From liberty to abundance; * From abundance to complacency; * From complacency to apathy; * From apathy to dependence; * From dependence back into bondage."</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1364157766189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364157983135-128</Id><Title>Ist, 2nd, and 4th Ammendment rights</Title><Msg>GFY you and your organ-grinding monkey named chi-chi my monkey is a cat</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364157983135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364158291677-129</Id><Topic><Title>Ist, 2nd, and 4th Ammendment rights</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364157983135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:46:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she said from a 10 pounds to an elk over 1000 lbs. the black cat with green eyes on a green lawn said wasn not sign: This Disclaimer Form with the signature of John Hancock but of course the elk was bluffing... and we would eat it...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364158291677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:51:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364159543955-130</Id><Title>So here we are...</Title><Msg>Operation An organ grinder with a monkey, photographed in 1892. The grinder would crank his organ in a public place (either a business district or in a neighborhood), moving from place to place after collecting a few coins or in order to avoid being arrested for loitering or chased by persons who would not appreciate hearing his single tune over and over again. The grinder would often[citation needed] have as a companion a White-headed Capuchin monkey to do tricks and attract attention. The monkey would collect the money from the audience and sometimes collect other shiny objects that walked across across a darkened cafeteria floor and said "would you like to dance" /?. (no, not, you horse-face, her) and she said, yes so we did as best we could it wan;t a rumba or a salsa but it cou;ld have been</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364159543955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364160025360-131</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love to dig through old posts and find your amazing calls. Did you really wait until 84.25 to cover this one?</Msg><Username>astemio65</Username><Timestamp>1364160025360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364160452369-132</Id><Topic><Title>Ist, 2nd, and 4th Ammendment rights</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364157983135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:46:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once Obama and the democrats ban the second amendment the rest of the amendments should be easy to ban. Does anyone read George Orwell anymore or is he one of the schools banned authors?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364160452369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364160620731-133</Id><Title>skjipped skool 1970</Title><Msg>high fellas ? walking into to the new multi-puurpose stadium...knowin' that anoouncer was off by at least two...in paid attendance 510 paid cusromers is off by two or more (c'mon get me is another story) what did I/we miss JNJ on a BA</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364160620731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364161384772-134</Id><Title>Saint Jesus</Title><Msg>he was born poor died rich and didn;t hurt anyone along the way -satchmo and julie brown CHRISTO</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364161384772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 17:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364162487283-135</Id><Title>magic bus</Title><Msg>it goes liker this:Operation An organ grinder with a monkey, photographed in 1892. The grinder would crank his organ in a public place (either a business district or in a neighborhood), moving from place to place after collecting a few coins or in order to avoid being arrested for loitering or chased by persons who would not appreciate hearing his single tune over and over again. The grinder would often[citation needed] have as a companion a White-headed Capuchin monkey to do tricks and attract attention. The monkey would collect the money from the audience and sometimes collect other shiny objects that attracted his attention. Operation An organ grinder with a monkey, photographed in 1892. The grinder would crank his organ in a public place (either a business district or in a neighborhood), moving from place to place after collecting a few coins or in order to avoid being arrested for loitering or chased by persons who would not appreciate hearing his single tune over and over again. The grinder would often[citation needed] have as a companion a White-headed Capuchin monkey to do tricks and attract attention. The monkey would collect the money from the audience and sometimes collect other shiny objects that attracted his attention.</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364162487283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 18:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364162501142-136</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Popularity Lower than George Bush in the Mid East</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1364103264071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 01:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Countries in the Middle East like Saudia Arabia, were very happy to see GW Bush take out Saddam" So then what you're saying is that the Muslims were very happy with Duhbya and his policies. Interesting. Was all that happiness the reason that there are many instances that Duhbya and the King Of Saudi had their pictures taken while they were kissing and nuzzling?</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1364162501142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 18:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364162716729-137</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err contard err psychotic err pedophile err TytlerspazMO err from bottomline to bumper to fascist to censored to spaz.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1364162716729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 18:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364163397239-138</Id><Topic><Title>Custerisis on translation please or how I can be a Boeing hack</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364000002319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 20:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is great sport to watch you get your panties all twisted up when we pull your chain. Some of the things you say are just outrageous. I only reply as custerisus to YOUR posts. I use a different user name to reply to the sane people. And BTW, don't you worry yourself about where I live. That changes from time to time, so I don't get bored. Actually, you do provide some entertainment for the folks on the board, so keep it up, Dell. So, why did you stop posting as Dell &amp; Fred? Yahoo get tired of you and kick you off the board, much like Boeing booted you?</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1364163397239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 18:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364163423436-139</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nahh. closed out at 77.50 i dont let little losers turn into major catastrophes. its a guy thing.</Msg><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1364163423436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 18:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364166198808-140</Id><Title>IAM is guessing on this oink</Title><Msg>a Morman a RWNJ ... tell the prost marshala provost marshall same rain</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364166198808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364167710554-141</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dr., Your post implies (via mix of scripture and your subject title) that the coming time of judgment, involving "fire" and everything being "laid bare", is somehow fulfilled by "global warming". When that time comes, it will be patently obvious that the judgment is coming form God and not man made or simple natural cycles. In fact, at one point the unrepentant folks cry out for the rocks to fall on them to hide them from the face of the One bringing on that judgement (Rev 6:16). BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1364167710554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364168151311-142</Id><Title>whitchta state</Title><Msg>gulag coast of flotriduh[] they loeck\d me inside my roomm at Harrah's just for thinkinking One trillione USD and 11/.1/2 point /...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364168151311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364168271257-143</Id><Topic><Title>whitchta state</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364168151311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Florida Gulf Coast gunna kick some booty.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364168271257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364168380092-144</Id><Title>More job cuts at Boeing</Title><Msg>Seems rushing to please Obama's rants about growing economy (BA' union supported him), like he did with GM auto sales, some shortcuts and corners cut in new 787's and it is coming abck to bite them all...</Msg><Username>investrman</Username><Timestamp>1364168380092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364168465820-145</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might mean meteorites too. More of them hitting the earth lately in larger formation and not buring up in atmosphere.</Msg><Username>investrman</Username><Timestamp>1364168465820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364168918143-146</Id><Title>It has been awhile since shot right-handed</Title><Msg>23 foot one bounce nothing but net</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364168918143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364169187524-147</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The average daily temperature where I live has been 20 degreesF below normal for over a month with March heading near historical lows so any warming from the Lord would be great. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364169187524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 19:53:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364169711986-148</Id><Topic><Title>Ist, 2nd, and 4th Ammendment rights</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364157983135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:46:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You talk to the average "liberal" (code word for believer in authoritarianism) they think this is STILL all a conspriacy theory...its HAPPENNING man.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364169711986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364169779404-149</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chemical Ali Infested again demonstrates the "preferred ignorance" that he finds so endearing. If it isn't visible a few feet from his schnozz, it doesn't exist. QED.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1364169779404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364169844878-150</Id><Title>Somebody was sayin' somethin' about American's</Title><Msg>in english, belgique, dutch, german, french, spanish, greek, itallian] GFY!!!</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364169844878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364170911027-151</Id><Title>Given three more wishes</Title><Msg>the last two wishes were wasted on engineers and the liikje during the battle of the bulge I wish to have three more wishes... Soschi 2014 no toes no no noses or possibly a few let US know how ] that goes</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364170911027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364171073067-152</Id><Title>The Linguistics of the Second Amendment...and why Liberal authoritarians get it so wrong !</Title><Msg>When I used to teach composition, it was common for students to say, “I know what I wanted to say, but I just didn’t know how to say it.” I always told them, “What you know is reflected in your words. If it’s not in the words, you don’t know it.” That was true thirty-five years ago and it’s true today. And there is a corollary to that maxim: people assume that what you say is true. It may not be, but the opening assumption is that your words reflect the truth. Otherwise, there would be little point in talking. ads not by this site These maxims – that words reflect what you know and that they reflect the truth – can be used as a weapon. For example, people who oppose private gun ownership often say that the Second Amendment protects hunting. Obama says that he doesn’t want to take anyone’s hunting rifle and has his picture taken firing a long-barreled shotgun. Anti-gun senators always introduce their remarks with fond memories of their hunting rifles. Their purpose is to convince us they are in favor of the Second Amendment, as they have re-defined it. But the Second Amendment is not about hunting. It’s about protecting citizens from an overreaching government. If that problem didn’t exist, there would have been no Second Amendment for the Framers didn’t need the Constitution to tell them they could go hunting. They needed the Constitution because they feared another King George. When the conversation is confined to what guns are appropriate for, hunting, or even when it is expanded to include self-defense (as in Heller), it becomes presumptively true (words reflect what is known and they are presumptively true) that the Second Amendment is only about self-defense and hunting. And once the issue is framed this way, the only guns citizens will be allowed to own will be for those purposes. But our Second Amendment rights, just like those of the Framers, concern our right to resist a tyrannical government, and for that, we need military weapons</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364171073067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171181510-153</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scooby doo, this is BA message board. This is your Gobbledygook friend. Short BA</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364171181510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171220747-154</Id><Topic><Title>The Linguistics of the Second Amendment...and why Liberal authoritarians get it so wrong !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364171073067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:24:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>continued....Nonetheless, our opponents have been able to cast the discussion of the Second Amendment as being about hunting. They have been able to do this because even though fear of tyranny has been part of our heritage since the beginning, public attention has never been directed to the purposes of the Second Amendment, and it has never been taught in the schools. None of us grew up aware of the possibility that our own government could one day be the enemy. That part of our heritage became apparent only with the election of President Obama, when people saw, for the first time, that one man might actually destroy the government and the society in which we live. Then, for the first time, the idea of an overreaching government hell-bent on wrecking our traditions, our way of life, our belief systems, our laws, and even the make-up of the population became a reality. So when we discuss the Second Amendment and the right of citizens to own weapons, we must do it in the context of the primary reason we need weapons at all: protection against tyranny from within. If we conduct the discussion on our opponents’ terms, if we allow them to define the need for weapons as self-defense and hunting, we will have lost the battle.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364171220747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171288795-155</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When it's hot or stormy people like Jameshate251 say they can see global warming out their window. It's snowing outside my window and 22 degrees below normal. Global warming sure is tricky.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364171288795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171324224-156</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get out of here BA PR. God does not reside here. She's in Yahoo!OMG. Strong sell BA next week</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364171324224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171454978-157</Id><Topic><Title>AirBus</Title><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1364142791842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:33:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy next week then</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364171454978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171644524-158</Id><Topic><Title>BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY!</Title><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1363632899145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 14:54:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ready for next week dive?</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364171644524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171810460-159</Id><Topic><Title>BA = BATTERY ASSESSMENT</Title><Username>nicehereinca1</Username><Timestamp>1363615675873</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 10:07:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like with all the troubles BA run into and stock price taking off, make any sense? What goes up must come down.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364171810460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171924458-160</Id><Topic><Title>BA will hit 90 by Friday..</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363636610950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA will crash by Friday. 70 coming</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364171924458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364171972751-161</Id><Topic><Title>The Linguistics of the Second Amendment...and why Liberal authoritarians get it so wrong !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364171073067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:24:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you cut and paste other people's writing, you should be careful to edit out little clues like "ads not by this site."</Msg><Username>dkmax</Username><Timestamp>1364171972751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:39:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364172124663-162</Id><Title>Barry's records</Title><Msg>to Occidental College have been released to the public. It appears that Barry Soetoro was, in fact, borned in Kenya. Impeachment of the fraud president is now likely to continue through congress. I see some frightened democrats backing away from their continued support of the president. With the 2014 elections around the corner and some democrats, in the hot seat in their districts from unpopular legislation being implemented by Washington, may choose to abandon support for their president for fear of losing their reelection bids.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364172124663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364172186270-163</Id><Topic><Title>The party of the, "chronically needy" and the entitled illegals is in control.</Title><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1364126993032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 08:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world is in turmoil. Sell ,sell , sell, BA.....</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364172186270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364172318365-164</Id><Topic><Title>God warned boeing twice with fires, The next will burn !</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1363614481033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 09:48:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy BA next week, easy money.....</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364172318365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:45:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364172440909-165</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Boeing Lithium Ion Batteries</Title><Username>morons_finder</Username><Timestamp>1364027118475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 04:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't matter what, BA still responsible . Sell BA next week .. strong sell</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364172440909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364172654475-166</Id><Topic><Title>THE NTSB DOESN"T UNFDERSTAND..........</Title><Username>honest_john101</Username><Timestamp>1363986350746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 17:05:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quit your job , short BA you'll make much more</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364172654475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364173343481-167</Id><Topic><Title>87??</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363670793057</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 01:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Head &amp; shoulder forming in hourly chart. 525K share dumped by institution last minute on Friday. Strong sell next week.</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364173343481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 21:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364174320238-168</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Climate change isn't anything new. Those of us that study history and the Paleoclimate record know this. “God Almighty has a quarrel lately with all Mankind,” lamented the Welsh historian James Howell in 1647, “for within these 12 years there have been the strangest Revolutions and horridest things happened, not only in Europe but all the world over.” The world, he thought, was “off the hinges”. He was not alone. As civil strife raged in the British Isles, rebellion tore holes in the empires of the Ming and the Ottomans, and central Europe bled in the Thirty Years’ War, other commentators sank into despair. Every day, recorded the Oxford scholar Robert ­Burton in 1638, brought news of “war, plagues, fires, inundations, thefts, murders, massacres, meteors, comets, spectrums, prodigies, apparitions; of towns taken, cities besieged in France, ­Germany, Turky [sic], Persia, Poland etc”. Four years later, a Spanish tract suggested a terrifying but increasingly popular explanation: “This seems to be one of the epochs in which every nation is turned upside down, leading some great minds to suspect that we are now approaching the end of the world.”</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364174320238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 21:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364177802190-169</Id><Topic><Title>What do Cessna, lithium batteries and the 787 Boeing plane share ? except for stock price ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364117576573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 05:32:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump this for the rich and powerful oz he goes by custerious and wstleffanms and father Z so great a personality he should bail out Boeing with his personal friend Paul Allen his friend pay up the 33 billion in the hole go custerious long walk off Short pier at Paul Allen's house "• Reply to Custerisis on translation please or how I can be a Boeing hack •Mar 22, 2013 8:53 PM custerisus said, It is great sport to watch you get your panties all twisted up when we pull your chain. Some of the things you say are just outrageous. I only reply as custerisus to YOUR posts. I use a different user name to reply to the sane people. And BTW, don't you worry yourself about where I live. That changes from time to time, so I don't get bored. Actually, you do provide some entertainment for the folks on the board, so keep it up, Dell. So, why did you stop posting as Dell &amp; Fred? Yahoo get tired of you and kick you off the board, much like Boeing booted you? Less and as youor avatar custerious here you are the rich and famous wstllfanms , when your not hob knobbing with Paul Allen _"whsteffanms on his posts and MSFT, eh! 18-Jun-11 01:42 pm whsteffanms... I was wondering your IP address shows as Everett and you have 4528 update(6039)posts, with almost all of them containing slams and HAR HAR HAR and nothing of any value to anyone, how is it that you get along so well with Paul Allen? eh! Re: Microsoft Shows First Look at Windows 8 Interface VIDEO Whsteffanms said” dell george my address may be Everett, but my mansion is actually located over on Widbey Island( sure it is) and I get back and forth with my yacht( the full size scale model?)- I tie up next to Paul Allen a lot( a lot like never !) down in Elliott bay and confer( wow) with him quite a lot-- how do you like that eh ( just like all your other emails,, har, har , har ) Rating : (No ratings) Rate it: Whsteffanms we are all impressed with you really we are, are , are no translation needed</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364177802190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364177844106-170</Id><Topic><Title>Layoffs at SC plnt? How many, howlong?</Title><Username>bobncarol1</Username><Timestamp>1362510888473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:14:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soncer what the Union &amp; the State of Washington think of that idea?</Msg><Username>loftndude2000</Username><Timestamp>1364177844106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364177995952-171</Id><Topic><Title>why do Boeing financial investors hate the numbers 12 and 16?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364024337211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 03:38:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>run that by Paul Allen, wstllefanms , I mean custerious maybe translation please first ! Say hi to your mom at the estate you have in Everett Washington at the low rent apartment, you are a good boy , your mom thinks anyway translation please !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364177995952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364178202762-172</Id><Topic><Title>787 future is in South Carolina!</Title><Username>morons_finder</Username><Timestamp>1364063735420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 14:35:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obsolete in Time?? I tthink it has already started becoming weak.</Msg><Username>loftndude2000</Username><Timestamp>1364178202762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364178320234-173</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ron anderson 727 you sound just like another user, exactly , you must have exactly disease, your face look exactly like your #$%$ , and in the mirror you look like spartacus99991 and unspart76 and unispart76 and you resemble r2----- d2-72 how many user id's do you need to attempt to trash me and be a Boeing hack ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364178320234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364178379711-174</Id><Title>SELL BA MONDAY</Title><Msg>"Even assuming battery issue is resolved and Boeing is able to hit its 787 delivery guidance at 60+, we still see 787 as a ~$6B cash drag in 2013 with ~$7B inventory build more than offsetting ~$1B advance draw," UBS analyst David Strauss wrote in a note to clients.</Msg><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1364178379711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364178420328-175</Id><Topic><Title>Problem with Boeing Lithium Ion Batteries</Title><Username>morons_finder</Username><Timestamp>1364027118475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 04:25:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>incompetent BA executives and outsourcing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364178420328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364179180964-176</Id><Topic><Title>The party of the, "chronically needy" and the entitled illegals is in control.</Title><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1364126993032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 08:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senate passes bill, after strong opposition from republicans, to provide 11 million illegal aliens currently living in America with healthcare under Obamacare. AND YOU STUPID DEMOCRATS ARE GOING TO HAVE TO PAY FOR IT JUST LIKE THE REPUBLICANS! Look for more tax increases because Obamacare is heavily underfunded at 1.7 trillion dollars.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364179180964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364179514498-177</Id><Title>800 thousand billioin</Title><Msg>bynthe pint spresd of course was locked up by7 leagal aliens</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364179514498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 22:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364183816465-178</Id><Topic><Title>AirBus</Title><Username>techno_geek_forever</Username><Timestamp>1364142791842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 12:33:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nicehereinca, stop, you are making the three stooges times two, angry, the 6 Boeing Hacks you know they have 6 users on the Boeing financial message board, with 15 names who just can't stand the truth, custerious, or sparti for short, spartacus99991,unposter76, wstlleffanms, uniposter76, barbing1965,and ron andersaomn 727 they are many of the same Boeing hacks and then there is foulmoutharbor the man who thinks airplane orders and deliveries late by 3 years and over cost by 33 billion is worth reporting . Remember airbus is up over 160% in stock value for 3 years and Boeing is up 16% in 3 years while the average that Boeing trades in the Dow Jones average is up 33% for year years . So those facts just anger the few Boeing hacks who can't stand the truth !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364183816465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 23:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>