<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370320056643-1</Id><Topic><Title>We know Obama ia a Marxist but is the Whole Democrat Party Becoming Communists</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370292876909</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That sure hit the nail on the head.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370320056643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 00:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370324990096-2</Id><Title>Boeing to increase use of its Flex Tracj automated riveting system from 777 to also 767 and 747-8</Title><Msg>Automated sytem of rails, orignially designed by Boeing, drills holes and places fasteners in place at same time. Crews reported a 98% quality improvement using this automated system.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370324990096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 01:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370325414842-3</Id><Topic><Title>F-15 are still selling well after 39 years in service</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370236049222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 01:07:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>F-22 is the better plane but McDonnald didn't like St Louis metal getting thrashed by Seattle composite and Lockheed wanted the F-35. You know a deal was made because not 1 Senator from either party raised much of an issue including the ones from Ca &amp; WA. Adam Smith is the ranking house armed services and he acted like obama to a scandal - I didn't know they were axing the F-22 until I read about it in the Seattle PI.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1370325414842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 01:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370325832732-4</Id><Topic><Title>F-15 are still selling well after 39 years in service</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370236049222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 01:07:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because the classified part, which supposedly will never be released, is very advanced</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370325832732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 02:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370326273277-5</Id><Topic><Title>F-15 are still selling well after 39 years in service</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370236049222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 01:07:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would they be embarrassed by terminating their foolishness? You think they'll be less embarrassed by keeping it going?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370326273277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 02:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370326411881-6</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republicans obviously wanted Obama in the WH. If they wanted to win, they wouldn't have run Thurston Howell III.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370326411881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 02:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370327311368-7</Id><Topic><Title>new plane</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370281615491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:46:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saw pictures of the plane on the site and like the fact that it is not too big. Looks large enough to carry alot of payload and small enough to not be so visable.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370327311368</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 02:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370328241249-8</Id><Title>I feel Boeing Phantom Ray will soon be active</Title><Msg>Flies 614 mph, 50 ft wingspan, 36 ft long----not for survellance. Get into the worst environment, looks like a small B-2 wing, drop your ordinance and get out. No need to risk life. Small, fast, and agile enough I bet to elude</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370328241249</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 02:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370328369558-9</Id><Topic><Title>whats better ACAD up 212% YTD or Boeing up 33% ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370312807992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>notice the disinformation by spartacus9991 , the time I choose is not what I said . Spatacus9991 knows that the time frame of 14 weeks is from the first time I told spartqcus99991 to look into a buy of ACAD and he is using disinformation , rather poorly but that is his intent. He knows I told him about ACAD 14 week ago Now the ACAD YTd is not my time frame other than to point out that ACAD has beat Boeing for the year. So the point of that is to show you if your wanting to make money in the stock market stay away from Boeing Instead move to the best performing stocks. Next rotate with the stock market. Spartiacus9991 is probably a paid Boeing shill or a fool , both are bad for any investor . He ahs help or different avatar names joedokes,25, foulmoutharbor, wstleffanms, somethg or other 50 censored 50 if I recall, they are all Boeing advertisement and disinformation specialists that work for Boeing or are too stupid to get into great stocks .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370328369558</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 02:46:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370344691687-10</Id><Topic><Title>We know Obama ia a Marxist but is the Whole Democrat Party Becoming Communists</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370292876909</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beginning with " They're just the poor dumb lemming...", replace "weed" with "crystal meth" and you've got a perfect description of the Tea Potty.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1370344691687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 07:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370346066930-11</Id><Topic><Title>Darrell Issa (Congressman and Punk Thug)</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1370303962470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:59:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post, thanks. I love the original headline on the editorial: "The GOP is too juvenile to govern" How true, sadly.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1370346066930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 07:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370348960429-12</Id><Topic><Title>Darrell Issa (Congressman and Punk Thug)</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1370303962470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:59:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>play acting to a commie means folks got murdered, and folks were targeted. "When you do the crime, you have to do the time".....Johnny Cockroach.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370348960429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 08:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370350613527-13</Id><Topic><Title>We know Obama ia a Marxist but is the Whole Democrat Party Becoming Communists</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370292876909</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:54:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"don't even know who the vice president is or where Europe is on the map" You should not be bad mouthing Sarah Palin like that.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1370350613527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 08:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370352633955-14</Id><Title>Male Democrats and their Feminism</Title><Msg>The government is a substitute care taker......in their minds it protects them from the horrors of independence and personal responsibility.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370352633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370353007779-15</Id><Topic><Title>Male Democrats and their Feminism</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370352633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Valueless folks that can't take responsibility for their terrible decisions. They can't be trusted to make decent decisions. The sad thing is the liberal elites know they are the uninformed with few social skills, and appeal to them as if they were stupid. Most educated 5th graders would reject the falsehoods that Obama presents to them.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370353007779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370353876916-16</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A medley of Sparty's greatest hit. Like John Candy in Splash, if something works for him, he stays with it.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370353876916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370354308834-17</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for posting that. (I'd still like to know how you get to post links. You must be an elitist. :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370354308834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:58:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370355887528-18</Id><Title>Transparency: Obama's Top Brass Use Private Email to Avoid Turning Over Information to the Public</Title><Msg>FLASHBACK: "Let me say it as simply as I can: Transparency and the rule of law will be the touchstones of this presidency." We've known for months now that former EPA Head Lisa Jackson used multiple non-governmental email accounts when doing government business. Late last year, the EPA's critics — including Republicans in Congress — accused former EPA Administrator Lisa Jackson of using an email account under the name "Richard Windsor" to sidestep disclosure rules. The EPA said emails Jackson sent using her Windsor alias were turned over under open records requests. The agency's inspector general is investigating the use of such accounts, after being asked to do so by Congress. An EPA spokeswoman described Jackson's alternate email address as "an everyday, working email account of the administrator to communicate with staff and other government officials." It was later determined that Jackson also used the email address to correspond sometimes with environmentalists outside government and at least in some cases did not correct a misperception among outsiders they were corresponding with a government employee named Richard Windsor. The same goes for former Department of Justice Assistant Attorney General for the Civil Rights Division Tom Perez, who President Obama has nominated for Labor Secretary. Perez has used a non-government email account more than 1,200 times since 2009 for official DOJ business. His personal emails were subpoenaed by the House Oversight Committee months ago and Perez has refused to comply. Labor Secretary nominee Tom Perez used his private email account to leak information about official business while he was assistant attorney general for the Justice Department’s Civil Rights Division, the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform said in a Wednesday letter to Perez. Oversight Chairman Darrell Issa (R., Calif.) said it appears Perez used his personal email account almost 1,200 times since 2009 to conduct official department business, including communicating with organizations such as Planned Parenthood, the New York Times, and Talking Points Memo. Now, the Associated Press is out with a blockbuster report showing many of President Obama's political appointees use personal email to avoid the Freedom of Information Act and other legal and transparency requirements on a regular basis. Some of President Barack Obama's political appointees, including the secretary for Health and Human Services, are using secret government email accounts they say are necessary to prevent their inboxes from being overwhelmed with unwanted messages, according to a review by The Associated Press. The scope of using the secret accounts across government remains a mystery: Most U.S. agencies have failed to turn over lists of political appointees' email addresses, which the AP sought under the Freedom of Information Act more than three months ago. The Labor Department initially asked the AP to pay more than $1 million for its email addresses. The secret email accounts complicate an agency's legal responsibilities to find and turn over emails in response to congressional or internal investigations, civil lawsuits or public records requests because employees assigned to compile such responses would necessarily need to know about the accounts to search them. Secret accounts also drive perceptions that government officials are trying to hide actions or decisions. FLASHBACK: January 21, 2009 when Obama claims a new era of transparency is here. The way to make government responsible is to hold it accountable. And the way to make government accountable is make it transparent so that the American people can know exactly what decisions are being made, how they're being made, and whether their interests are being well served. The directives I am giving my administration today on how to interpret the Freedom of Information Act will do just that. For a long time now, there's been too much secrecy in this city. The old rules said that if there was a defensible argument for not disclosing something to the American people, then it should not be disclosed. That era is now over. Starting today, every agency and department should know that this administration stands on the side not of those who seek to withhold information but those who seek to make it known. To be sure, issues like personal privacy and national security must be treated with the care they demand. But the mere fact that you have the legal power to keep something secret does not mean you should always use it. The Freedom of Information Act is perhaps the most powerful instrument we have for making our government honest and transparent, and of holding it accountable. And I expect members of my administration not simply to live up to the letter but also the spirit of this law. I will also hold myself as President to a new standard of openness. Going forward, anytime the American people want to know something that I or a former President wants to withhold, we will have to consult with the Attorney General and the White House Counsel, whose business it is to ensure compliance with the rule of law. Information will not be withheld just because I say so. It will be withheld because a separate authority believes my request is well grounded in the Constitution. Let me say it as simply as I can: Transparency and the rule of law will be the touchstones of this presidency.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370355887528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370356394650-19</Id><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Msg>I can't think of anything that can't be done without one.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370356926219-20</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need the federal government so we can jail anarchists like you x6xxx and prosecute you for sedition</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370356926219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370357091742-21</Id><Topic><Title>Darrell Issa (Congressman and Punk Thug)</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1370303962470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:59:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans have lost all credibility !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370357091742</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370357365945-22</Id><Title>Arms Treaty Doesn’t Violate Second Amendment !</Title><Msg>Texas Attorney General Greg Abbott made clear on Fox News on Wednesday that he is firmly opposed to a new United Nations arms treaty — even while admitting that it doesn’t infringe on the Second Amendment. The United Nations yesterday finally passed the Arms Trade Treaty (ATT), laying out new regulations of the $70 billion trade of arms between countries. In doing so, the U.N. has once more drawn the ire of conservatives, including those who believe that the treaty could infringe on Americans’ Second Amendment rights. Abbott sent a stern letter to President Obama, urging him not to sign the treaty, claiming it “does more than trample Second Amendment rights.” Echoing that letter, Abbott admitted on Fox today that nothing in it as written has the ability to violate the Second Amendment</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370357365945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370357444015-23</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not an anarchists nor a person so intellectually void that he has to substitute fantasies and lies for logic like zosima does.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370357444015</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370357744034-24</Id><Topic><Title>Arms Treaty Doesn’t Violate Second Amendment !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370357365945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Globlaists are getting more and more bold....Obama signed it anyway...reminds you of Barry saying we can go to War when NATO says so (instead of when Congress declares war) ...</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370357744034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370358078632-25</Id><Title>Obama Nominates three new Activists to DC Circuit</Title><Msg>to go along with all the others appointed to positions of power/authority i'm sure a reflection of our dishonest, incompetent, and destructive president, sad so many were fooled to GIVE him a position of power/authority the legacy/damage will last long after he's left office</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370358078632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370358148420-26</Id><Topic><Title>Arms Treaty Doesn’t Violate Second Amendment !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370357365945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus is playing with his stikdik</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370358148420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370358279097-27</Id><Topic><Title>Transparency: Obama's Top Brass Use Private Email to Avoid Turning Over Information to the Public</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370355887528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are a #$%$, then E-mail is not a very good way to communicate with your fellow #$%$s. I think most #$%$s finaly get this now. The IRS met with the White House about 160 times, because they didn't want phone records or E-mails leaving a trail. They get it! Still there is much room for improvement.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370358279097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370358369324-28</Id><Topic><Title>Arms Treaty Doesn’t Violate Second Amendment !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370357365945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The good news is that I can still use drones to kill people.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370358369324</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370358428761-29</Id><Topic><Title>Arms Treaty Doesn’t Violate Second Amendment !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370357365945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus changes costumes</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370358428761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370358695875-30</Id><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Msg>Right-wing media are continuing to claim Attorney General Eric Holder lied under oath because of a search warrant request that included Fox News reporter James Rosen, a myopic smear conservative legal experts are warning is baseless. Picking up where Fox News and Washington Post blogger Jennifer Rubin left off, The Wall Street Journal is repeating Republican politicians' attack that Holder perjured himself in a May 15 statement before Congress Republican Congressman Peter King of New York joined fellow Republicans like RNC chair Reince Priebus in calling for Holder’s resignation. “If I were Eric Holder, I would resign,” he said Monday. “I don’t see how he remains in office, though, very much longer, since he’s lost so much credibility with Congress and the American people.”</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370358989772-31</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima is so utterly ignorant that is you say you don't like yellow cars he will conclude you don't like cars at all. Don't let his name calling bother you......it's all he has.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370358989772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370359202267-32</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sick.....he did lie. Justice for a black man is different for every body else. That why there are so many dead beat black men in our society and in our prisons. They ttelll thier families I love you Ill take care of you, then run off with another woman. It happens every day and for so long that now they expect Handouts. Now we got this #$%$, smoking weed lover running this country breaking every law in the land</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370359202267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370359595723-33</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a dead beat white guy who outnumber dead beat black guys.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370359595723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370360492891-34</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Providing details and facts would allow people to decide for themselves if Holder lied under oath. Wouldn't that be a better way of addressing the issue?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370360492891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370360938941-35</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Create laws, provide education for the populace (all the populace), National Defense , Judiciary, Destroy immoral injustice ( like Slavery) that states feel are religious rights, religious freedom, general oversight on local demagoguery. Just to name a few. Also to protect us from fools like you.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1370360938941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:48:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370361172940-36</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= I can't think of anything that can't be done without one.= Now is that intellectual poverty, or what? Let me edit your sentence for you, so that it makes sense in the context: "I can't think." I do believe that gets at the root of your problem.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1370361172940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370361379481-37</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GRIDLOCK="White Male Southern Sepremacy" . The Federal government would do fine without these people.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1370361379481</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370361478244-38</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About the only reason in today's world for the USA to need a federal bureaucracy is a common currency but even that is questionable with the ability of being able to rapidly calculate exchange rates. Anything the fed does can now be done more efficiently by the individual state governments. .</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370361478244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370361590069-39</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're welcome, Chris. I loved the ending: "Viewed in isolation, Texas’s problems would be deadly for the law. But viewed next to California, they might mainly be a problem for the political class in Texas, which has failed to implement a clearly workable law." I think it will be very popular with the American people. Oh, and posted this through Moldavia. ;-)</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370361590069</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370361650532-40</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots... he scores!!!</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370361650532</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370362016552-41</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Call me old fashioned, but I think we need a federal government to form a more perfect Union, establish Justice, insure domestic Tranquility, provide for the common defence, promote the general Welfare, and secure the Blessings of Liberty to ourselves and our Posterity. But you wouldn't know anything about that, would you. You don't have the guts to move to a Banana Republic, so you want to put the USA into a state of corporate feudalism.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370362016552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370362045510-42</Id><Topic><Title>Male Democrats and their Feminism</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370352633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seems liberals, err progressives, i mean dumbocrats, as a rule are gender confused...the men act like women and the women wanna be men</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370362045510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:07:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370362103031-43</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To keep the hooz and his ilk feed and sheltered.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370362103031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370362359579-44</Id><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Msg>No there is no Need for a federal Government. The federal government is now so out of control it simply has become the agent of thievery, tyranny and the forced transfer of wealth from makers to takers. It is time to have 50 smaller countries competing with each other.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370362392101-45</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what people need to decide - the FOX news people ? .... and the only reason you toads are going after Holder is all politics - you care less about freedom of the press</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370362392101</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370362833497-46</Id><Topic><Title>new plane</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370281615491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:46:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what I like about FALMOUTHHARBOR Just posting FACTS about BOEING$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1370362833497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370362908471-47</Id><Title>update ACAD for the facts</Title><Msg>ACAD rose 2.00% to a new 52 week high of $14.85. During the last 52 weeks, ACAD's price has ranged from $1.30 on June 6, 2012 to today's high of $14.85. Additionally, over the last 12 months, ACAD has increased 1,014.28% while its peers in the Biotechnology industry increased 68.24%. I picked ACAD and the history for my pick on this stock is on the Boeing message board, if you follow me, or at least look into it you should make a fortune. I picked Apple below 10 and rode it to the 700 dollar and got out once Steve jobs died, I recently picked TSLA and on May 3 pointed out it was a great stock to consider, it went up 100% in just 16 days , now you have to take profits the day it short squeezed or in a day or two later if your not quick, that would have been is still 90 or 80% return in 16 days Now you can watch for a break out above the trade range or note all the positive real news not the foulmoutharbor crapola on Boeing . Instead take you limited resources and get back in to TSLA if you want. . Or you watch for a break out, its simple. Please do not buy or hold Boeing stock its a a terrible psychotic stock to own or trade you should never support executives bent on destroying a company from within. since MD took over the leadership is directly killing off Boeing with a business plan that failed against Boeing. The dumbest thing was Boeing won the world airplane wars and Phil C the CEO gave Boeing to MD before he was shown the door. It is like winning WWII, then surrendering to the German and Japanese forces that is exactly what happened.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370362908471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370362951241-48</Id><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Msg>Democrat States could legalized slavery without having to fight a war like they did in the 1860s. Red states could continue to our perform blue states economically while offering greater liberty to their citizens. People and businesses would continue to leave blue states for red states.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370363405224-49</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jonathan Turley doesn't want Holder to resign. Turley wants him fired. Holder shielded CIA torturers from prosecution, justified Obama's expansion of secret and warrantless surveillance, justified official “kill list” murder of American citizens, and personally approved the search of James Rosen’s e-mail and phone records. Turley says Holder " has supervised a comprehensive erosion of privacy rights, press freedom and due process" and charges that Democrats "would look at their shoes whenever the Obama administration was accused of constitutional abuses." Turley's column is in USAToday, called "Fire Eric Holder"</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370363405224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370363426220-50</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not working links, though. The true links could be clicked and opened from the post. Still helpful. Is this the story that says Obamacare will be a boost to small business because people who have long wanted to leave their jobs and start new business will because they will not only still be able to afford insurance but also be able to provide it for employees?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370363426220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370363556526-51</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't we take it step by step and start by abolishing the DoD? That would cut April 15 taxes by about 2/3 right there, and then we could see how it goes.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370363556526</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:32:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370364485515-52</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its true, and LWNJ are trying to weasel out of it. Holder also is still in contempt of congress over hiding materials on ' Fast and Furious'. Material that would show he was complicit in that also. you know where they were sending guns to the Mexican drug cartels so that they could use it as a push for gun control. Many who have know Holder for years claim he is a decent sort. Maybe so, but he signed of with the devil AKA BO and he has been doing his bidding.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370364485515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370364840568-53</Id><Topic><Title>Male Democrats and their Feminism</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370352633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trying to find ali infections, err sparty's, reply that shows up on topic page but nowhere else...so while i'm on topic, it's no wonder so many of our youth are confused, when daddy acts mommy and mommy thinks she's daddy</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370364840568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370364865986-54</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So your answer is to balkanize the USA. Then we would no longer have to worry about maintaining 800 military bases around the world and would no longer have the power to do evil around the world. Federal subsidies to low-performing red states would end, causing much economic suffering on the plains, in the deserts, and the mountains. Corporations would have much power relative to states. GE's annual revenues are equal to CA's budget of $150 billion. Peabody Coal has revenues of $8 billion. West Virginia has a budget of $11 billion. Wal-Mart, with revenues of $470 billion, would rule all the states.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370364865986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370364995479-55</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only reason you're NOT going after Holder is politics. Jonathan Turley slammed Bush for his crimes, and he slams Obama for his. See his op-ed "Fire Eric Holder" in USAToday.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370364995479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370365133037-56</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After the dust settles would we have a red star or a crescent moon over every government building?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370365133037</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370365307812-57</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The most obvious reason the plane did not fly over was because there was no place for it to fly to if it did fly over. The whole idea was absurd.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370365307812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370365604669-58</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're saying American citizens don't have the gumption to defend their country? If that's true, then maybe we deserve a red star or a crescent moon over every government building. Finland spends less than $4 billion a year on its military, and I don't see any red star or a crescent moon on their buildings. Dr. Robert Bowman, former director of the Star Wars program, says we could defend our borders for 20% of the cost of our current military.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370365604669</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370365687352-59</Id><Topic><Title>Male Democrats and their Feminism</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370352633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your kids get confused when you think you're daddy.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370365687352</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370365729704-60</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean would then have a government that would have a budget and end deficit spending if corporations were to take over? Heaven forbid!</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370365729704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370365772317-61</Id><Topic><Title>Male Democrats and their Feminism</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370352633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wrong again dummy</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370365772317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370366050088-62</Id><Topic><Title>Male Democrats and their Feminism</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370352633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what you think, but you have a whole lot of funny ideas.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370366050088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370366141680-63</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said after the dust settles. Plenty of us would defend the country (Red October-go Wolverines). But I won't last long with my restricted registered single shot pop gun.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370366141680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370366172875-64</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to be missing the fact that corporations benefit from deficit spending, and if all that were erased, many of them would go under. Take LMT, for instance, which gets $40 billion a year in federal contracts. Be careful what you wish for.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370366172875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370366457099-65</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a false dishotomy--supposing that the two choices are 2500 $150 million F-35s or a bunch of bubbas with pea shooters. You're not thinking this through. A volunteer citizen-based defense corps needn't necessarily mean flintlocks and six-shooters.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370366457099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370366570469-66</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell it to gun control Obama.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370366570469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370366730789-67</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And everybody can pay taxes to subsidize wall mart and oil companies. lol you want no federal government go to Somalia I hear they love your kind there.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370366730789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:25:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370367771762-68</Id><Topic><Title>Time to Abolish the Federal Government</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362951241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's not going to abolish the DoD. He's the Military-Industrial Complex's best friend!</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370367771762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370367966577-69</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks; but the dope x6xxx234 totally missed his cue: He was supposed to reply with a copy &amp; paste from Walter Williams, F. Bastiat, or that idiot bumper AKA censored50, or a mix of all three.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1370367966577</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:46:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370368484154-70</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some states would be able to engage in deficit spending and some would not. Blue states with stronger economies yes, red states with weaker economies no. Of course the free marketeers would be carpetbagging all the red states, selling off all the land, mineral rights, timber rights, and water rights to the highest bidders--probably the Chinese, Koreans, and Japanese. And then there's be a war between Arizona and Colorado about the Colorado River water. Yup, it's a real utopia you're proposing there.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370368484154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:54:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370368624746-71</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fk that - whether Holder should be fired or Not, should be based on Facts and not on rightwing garbage !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370368624746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370368737579-72</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the states can more efficiently handle the military, how are you proposing that we allocate the staffing, supply, and maintenance of 800 military bases around the world? Or do we just close them all and each state handle the defense of its own borders and that's it. Then the multinational corporations have to take on the expense of their own international security, and many of them would go out of business.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370368737579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 13:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370368849057-73</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holder is just a toady. See Jonathan Turley's essay "Fire Eric Holder". He's just a "sin eater".</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370368849057</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370369013384-74</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're saying Jonathan Turley has his facts wrong? He teaches constitutional law at The George Washington University Law School. Do you deny that Obama and Holder have "supervised a comprehensive erosion of privacy rights, press freedom and due process"?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370369013384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370370523892-75</Id><Topic><Title>update ACAD for the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370362908471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For today on TSLA until you break out draw a line under the low , notice it hit about $93.30 earlier in the day next set a buy at that level and notice it is now at $95.26 that is a 2.1% gain you can do that every day while waiting for it to take off or crapola out , draw another line at $95.60 and if it seems on volume to be crapoling out take your daily 2% that is 10% per week on this or tomorrow same thing on another stock .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370370523892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370370683608-76</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>State gov's can do everything that needs doing, as long as everything is going well. All they need is one big earthquake, wildfire, tsunami, spring flood, hurricane or tornado, or epidemic and their annual budget is shot.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370370683608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370370781474-77</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No - i was referring to GOpigs Not Jon Turley</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370370781474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370370885093-78</Id><Topic><Title>whats better ACAD up 212% YTD or Boeing up 33% ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370312807992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember spartacus9991 is involving himself in disinformation, he has told me many times he does not own Boeing stock, so why would he be here putting out disinformation because he is a Boeing paid hack or for unknown or ego reasons he does not like to be told anything of value, he wants to trade his opinion? nope very hard to explain his actions a great stock and he comes up with disinformation makes no sense</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370370885093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370370886618-79</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The News Media would co-ordinate the usual "Carpet Bombing" of the "threat's" Character.</Msg><Username>landshark49</Username><Timestamp>1370370886618</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370370951606-80</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Few red states would be able to support a viable currency.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370370951606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370371090019-81</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you have to respect that? Is going around the world committing war crimes and raping your female comrades respectable when it's under an Obama administration?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370371090019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370371701801-82</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He can call a state red or blue, and it may be based on the corporate home offices in those states, but many large corporations have branches or divisions in states of every color, so really it's only voter sentiment that determines the color of a state, which changes on occasion.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370371701801</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370372283961-83</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then the whole Bushco43 administration should have been fired along with the entire RWNJ media and every reublican fascist!!!</Msg><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1370372283961</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 14:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370372700307-84</Id><Title>How many Tuesdays UP in a row, comes to an end...</Title><Msg>to be replaced by Mondays after Friday sell-offs for profit when the fed starts thinking about raising interest rates, we only got another year or two of going UP UP and AWAY in my big beautiful balloon</Msg><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1370372700307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370373424728-85</Id><Title>Where the U.S. Economy Is Still No. 1 - despite the best efforst of the RWNJ's</Title><Msg>There’s a familiar litany of problems with the American economy: Our schools stink. Our tax system is labyrinthine and wasteful. College grads can’t find decent jobs. And too many of our politicians are mouthy hypocrites who get nothing done. But America still excels at a few things, which are evident in the details of the “better life index” released recently by the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development. In the OECD’s 2013 rankings, Switzerland came in first in overall life satisfaction, followed by the Scandinavian countries that frequently top such surveys. Australia ranked highest when all 11 categories were weighted equally, prompting some media outlets to call the land down under the world’s “happiest” country. By that standard, the United States ranked sixth. But declinists shouldn’t say “I told you so” just yet, because the U.S. is still No. 1 in two important categories—income and housing. On income, the U.S. has the highest average level of household wealth, at $116,000 per household. Americans also have the highest level of personal earnings, at $54,450 per capita, and the most disposable income, at $38,000 per capita. Ordinary folks who feel like this must describe some other country might be right, in a way. Though incomes are high in America, so is income inequality, which means the wealthy claim a disproportionate amount of all income, compared with other nations. By one OECD measure, in fact, the United States has the worst income inequality of 27 nations measured. So the wealthy in America really do inhabit a Luxembourg-like land of plenty that’s foreign to the majority of their countryfolk. Housing in the U.S. is more egalitarian, even if it seems like the rent is too damn high. Housing affordability ranks eighth out of 36 nations, according to the OECD, while the quality of housing—measured by the portion that have basic facilities such as indoor plumbing—is tied for No. 1 (along with Sweden, Spain and the Netherlands). Americans also enjoy more spacious living quarters than people in most other places. The typical American household has 2.3 rooms per person, bested only by Canadian households, with 2.6 rooms per person. That may not seem lavish, until you visit a home in Korea or Japan or even some European countries, where there’s not nearly as much open space. The U.S., of course, has generally been losing ground in various types of rankings that compare quality of life among countries. In the World Economic Forum’s global competitiveness survey, for instance, the U.S. has fallen from first to seventh since 2008. Another study found that even Cyprus had more appeal to foreign investors than the United States, before a financial crisis there nearly wrecked the entire economy. But there are usually a few discrete factors pushing this country down in global rankings, rather than wholesale decline of the entire nation. The most prominent is an exorbitant and ineffective health-care system that costs far more than in any other country on Earth. Health-care spending in the U.S. is 2.5 times the average for other developed countries, yet life expectancy is still well below average. In the WEF’s latest study, the United States ranked 54th in the trustworthiness of its politicians and 76th in the efficient spending of government resources; if America was once the paragon of democracy, it is no more. And in the OECD survey, the U.S. homicide rate ranked a pitiful 32nd out of 36 nations, ahead of only Estonia, Russia, Brazil and Mexico. To broaden it out, we remain a place with a vibrant economy and a lot of opportunity. But pathways to success may be narrowing, the wall between haves and have-nots may be getting higher, and the safety net for those who stumble may be fraying. You can still build a better life in America, it’s just not as easy as it used to be.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1370373424728</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370374258112-86</Id><Title>#$%$</Title><Msg>The lesson Republicans should have taken from Monday’s IRS hearings is “be careful what you wish for.” One of the recommendations based on the audit is “to conduct a review to assess how the IRS monitors I.R.C. sections 501(c)(4)(6) organizations to ensure that political campaign intervention does not constitute their primary activity.” On top of that, the audit revealed that there were many groups whose political intervention in campaigns should have flagged them for a review. The Honorable J. Russell George, Treasury Inspector General for Tax Administration, testified Monday in a House Appropriations Subcommittee on Financial Services and General Government hearing on the IRS “scandal”. George based his testimony on an audit in which they found a few things that don’t bode well for conservatives’ “social welfare groups”, since they outspent liberals 34-1 via nonprofits on political issues. Namely, the IRS needs to investigate more of these groups that are “intervening” in political campaigns, not less. The audit “determined that the majority of the 296 potential political cases we reviewed included indications of significant political campaign intervention.” This means that the majority reviewed were engaging in activities that warranted a review under the law. George explained that of the 296 cases singled out for review, the majority had indications of significant political campaign intervention. 91 cases did not (31%). Of those 91, only 17 involved Tea Party, Patriots, or 9/12 groups. The rest were “targeted” but were not Tea Party/Patriot/9/12 groups. “In addition, while we determined that the majority of the 296 potential political cases we reviewed included indications of significant political campaign intervention, 91 cases (31 percent) did not. Of the 91 cases, 17 involved Tea Party, Patriots, or 9/12 organizations. The IRS disagreed with this finding that the cases did not include indications of significant political campaign intervention.” The IRS did not document why they thought these 91 signaled political intervention, which is one thing the auditors recommend that they fix. But also, they found that more groups should have been investigated for their political intervention, “We determined that the Determinations Unit specialists did not identify all applications with indications of significant political campaign intervention. As a result, these cases were not referred to the team of specialists for further review.” They estimate that 175 were not sent for review but should have been, “We estimate that more than 175 organizations with indications of significant political campaign intervention were not referred to the team of specialists for further review.” Furthermore, nearly three-quarters of the groups “targeted” for inspection were not identified as opponents of the White House, so that blows the idea of being targeted for being a political enemy out of the water. It was also pointed out that 3,357 applications were made in 2012 compared with 1,735 in 2010, before Citizens United. George mentioned that inappropriate criteria were used by agents in Ohio, due to a lack of oversight, which was attributable to human challenges (read: lack of funding, and thank a Republican). The recommendations make the gist of the issue clear. This is not a political scandal, this is a government agency that is understaffed and underfunded, tasked with dealing with a huge influx of “social welfare” groups seeking tax exempt status post Citizens United. These groups were often intervening in political campaigns. The IRS workers were unclear as to how much political work these groups could be doing and still qualify as non profits. That’s the “scandal”. They were, perhaps, not trained properly or overseen enough as they dipped into unchartered waters post Citizens United. One of the recommendations is that in the future, they are going to make sure that political activity does not constitute the primary activity of these organizations. This is most assuredly not what Republicans had in mind when they started this witch hunt. George testified, “Furthermore, we plan to conduct a review to assess how the IRS monitors I.R.C. sections 501(c)(4)(6) organizations to ensure that political campaign intervention does not constitute their primary activity.” This means that they will want to review more, not less, of these organizations.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370374258112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370375317365-87</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370374258112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The silence from the so-called Tea-baggers, Libertarians, and strict-Constitutionalists especially on the RIGHT concerning illegal searches and seizures from those 'suspected' of 'serious crimes' is deafening... perhaps they are in bed with Big Brother</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370375317365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370376364212-88</Id><Title>Hi, Iam the new project manager for Yahooty Finance messagebords</Title><Msg>Hi, I am the Project Manager for the new Yahoo Message Boards. I just wanted to let you all know that we will be adding even more new features to the stunning new boards next week: 1) Starting next Monday, all new posts will automatically be translated into Norwegian. Our Yahoo Finance development team decided that users would want this, and since we do not speak directly to users before updating our site, we will assume this is a highly desired feature. The brilliant Stanford Ph.D.'s we hired to update the site thought it would be cool! Due to disk storage issues, we regret that we will no longer be able to offer your posts in English. Please learn Norwegian, and let us know how it goes on our Feedback form! We read every form you send us! 2) As you know, we recently stopped listing stock board posts chronologically, and went to a thread-based system. We feel that stock investors do not need to clearly see the latest posts during the trading day, and our Ph.D. geniuses from Stanford think you would prefer to dig through threads to find old posts on your stocks. More importantly, later this month, we will be removing the dates and times from all posts, and then in September we plan to mix them all up randomly. We hope that you are not inconvenienced by reading 8 year old posts when making investment decisions. Please use the helpful Feedback form to let us know what you think. We read every one! 3) As you may know, in the Beta we switched from a simple and effective system of "recommending" posts with a click, to a more complex one in which you rate posts with stars. Of course, you can only see the number of stars for the first post in a thread, but we feel this is better even if no one ever uses it. Our Ph.D. developers informed us that "complex" equals "better". So next month, we will replace the star system with a new even more complex one, in which you will manually calculate the cube root of how much you like the post on a scale of 3. Thanks/takk Pronunciation guide for Norwegian words and Norwegian phrases: •A as in father •E as in bed •I as in beat •U as in food •Æ as in mad •Ø as in hurt •Å as in ball •Most consonants are pronounced similar to English, with these exceptions: •J is pronounced like the "y" in yes •R is a little more "rolled" than the English R •Special Norwegian pronunciations: •KJ, KI and KY make a soft k-sound without actually blocking the throat, so that the air makes a sound as it squeezes out •SJ, SKY, SKJ and SKI as in shop Yes = Ja No = Nei Thank you = Takk Thank you very much = Tusen takk You're welcome = Vær så god Please = Vær så snill Excuse me = Unnskyld meg Hello = Hallo Goodbye = Ha det I do not understand = Jeg forstår ikke How do you say this in Norwegian? = Hvordan sier man dette på norsk? Where is ...? = Hvor er ...? How much is the fare? = Hvor mye koster billetten? One ticket to ..., please. = En billett til ..., takk. Train = Tog Bus = Buss Norwegian Subway, Underground = T-bane Airport = Flyplass Train station = Jernbanestasjon Bus station = Busstasjon Are there any vacancies for tonight? = Er det noe ledig for i natt? No vacancies = Alt opptatt. How much does this cost? = Hvor mye koster dette? What is this? = Hva er dette? I'll buy it. = Jeg kjøper det. I would like to buy ... = Jeg vil gjerne ha ... Do you have ... = Har du ... Do you accept credit cards? = Tar dere kredittkort? Norwegian Tourist Information = Turistinformasjon Museum = Museum Bank = Bank Norwegian police station = Politistasjon Hospital = Sykehus Store, Shop = Butikk Restaurant = Restaurant Church = Kirke Restrooms = Toalett</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370376364212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370376442477-89</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370374258112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminds me of that list of Freedoms lost under Obama I was asking for a few weeks ago, Got one response. they said they lost the freedom to not purchase health insurance . LMAO of course whats better than a silent Republican? maybe a couple cold beers is all I can think of.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370376442477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370376480606-90</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then there is no need for you to cross 'state lines' in any endeavor nor to escape prosecution, is there...dufass</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1370376480606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370376608456-91</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, Iam the new project manager for Yahooty Finance messagebords</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370376364212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:06:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>morsom!!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370376608456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370377010342-92</Id><Topic><Title>How many Tuesdays UP in a row, comes to an end...</Title><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1370372700307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A good reason not be a short term day to day trader. The Markets are schizo and act as a casino for many a day trader. Longer term Boeing will go up. Fundamentals are getting better by the day. Look for a dividend increase, more good news from Paris Air Show and growing earnings. Most analysts are now forecasting $120 per share. Short of a World Wide catastrophic economic event there should little in the way of this happening (IMHO)!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1370377010342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:16:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370377057419-93</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>albucucu, copy and paste the link into your browser and the article will appear. I just read it, and it's a great article.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1370377057419</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370377187845-94</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would have defeated Hitler? Sarah Palin leading the Alaska Brigade?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1370377187845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370377223394-95</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, Iam the new project manager for Yahooty Finance messagebords</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370376364212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:06:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>takks alot takks a morsom ta knbowsa one wats upuder</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370377223394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370377296057-96</Id><Topic><Title>whats better ACAD up 212% YTD or Boeing up 33% ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370312807992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Son. we know that you can't help the fact that you are gay and you were terminated by Boeing, but your Mom wants you to stop taking her panties.</Msg><Username>dellgeorgesr</Username><Timestamp>1370377296057</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370377582941-97</Id><Topic><Title>How many Tuesdays UP in a row, comes to an end...</Title><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1370372700307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope BA nevers goes from $120 to $26 again, that hurt a lot of inwestors under the Bushco/RWNJ regime should TX crude fall from over $90/bbl to $9/bbl, it would not bother me a bit...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370377582941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370378964927-98</Id><Topic><Title>whats better ACAD up 212% YTD or Boeing up 33% ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370312807992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dogleg right in the shallow of a deep creekbed 13th hole LAGC beyond the curve nothing invested, steal their golf ball off tyhe fairway and later sell it back to them for</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370378964927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 16:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370379848589-99</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would have defeated Hitler?......you ever hear the term allied forces??? instant_karma48 , you make Sarah Paling look like a genius that would make Einstein look like a imbecile like you.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370379848589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370380639970-100</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets's get the heat on sarah pee, und der madchelle bachmann have only have leftover undies froman eva braun need to make peas with one of the nicest woman in the world jean Stapleton/Edith bunker can outsing them two</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370380639970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370380874135-101</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370374258112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 15:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...whats better than a silent Republican? free beer... (for the horses) SCTV...The Great White North if find a dead mouse in long-neck bottle of beer, the state run Canadian stores give you a case... and, the silence</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370380874135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370381159422-102</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Believe me when I say to you I hope the Russians love their children too" Sting</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370381159422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370381355947-103</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>D-E-L-U-S-I-O-N-O-L TRY IT EWE MIGHT LIKE IT</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370381355947</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370381425567-104</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHAT LINK WOULD YOU LIKE TO POST. I CAN HELP...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370381425567</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370381470649-105</Id><Topic><Title>Male Democrats and their Feminism</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370352633955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored50 - for you there are only ali affections. ;-) My comment was removed for containing a link to a picture of a young Hillary Clinton twirling in a skirt and revealing that she possessed a manly appendage bulging in Weiner-like twitter pic fashion, underneath a pair of men's briefs. My comment was: The age old question of whether Clinton wears boxers or briefs (pun on Bill Clinton being asked about his underwear) has now been answered. I thought that you would enjoy the humor. You can do a search for 'spy magazine cover of Hillary Clinton' and the picture will show up under 'images'.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370381470649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:31:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370381539110-106</Id><Title>In summary for today</Title><Msg>the RWJ's took a setback, and global elitists merely not even an ice-chip off the iceberg which sank the Titanic</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370381539110</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370381607244-107</Id><Title>Bob Woodward’s credibility in tatters</Title><Msg>Bob Woodward’s credibility in tatters Why is the famed Watergate reporter spreading a debunked, week-old Daily Caller story on Fox News? Alex Seitz-Wald On Fox News Monday night, famed Washington Post reporter Bob Woodward and host Bill O’Reilly zeroed in on the latest twist in Washington scandalmania — why the White House is refusing to answer questions about the 157 times former IRS commission Doug Schulman allegedly visited the White House, a closeness that raises questions about presidential involvement in the agency’s controversial targeting of Tea Party tax-exempt groups. “This fiction that somehow [the IRS is] totally an independent agency is absurd,” Woodward, who broke the Watergate scandal, said. “You say they aren’t answering this question about the 157 visits by the IRS commissioner. They should.” “President Obama could easily come out through his spokesperson and say this is where Mr. Schulman was. And here are the dates. Here is who he met with,” O’Reilly said. “The fact that the President doesn’t do it, should raise the curiosity of every reporter, Mr. Woodward, every reporter. Yet, as I said, the major network news on television ignored the story last week in its totality. It’s amazing.” This forces us to ask the uncomfortable question of whether O’Reilly and Woodward have access to Google. Because if they did, they would have the answers to all of these questions, and they may even find a statement from the president’s spokesperson that he is supposedly refusing to give. “The IRS commissioner, in carrying out his duties, would of course have many reasons to have an appointment to visit the White House,” White House spokesperson Eric Schultz said. That’s a bit vaguer than what O’Reilly and Woodward are looking for, but the White House doesn’t really have to say any more, considering that all the specifics are already online, available to anyone who looks for them. The story of the 157 visits originated with the Daily Caller, based on a (sloppy) inspection of White House visitor logs. But as the Atlantic’s Garance Franke-Ruta reported, parsing those very same visitor logs a bit more closely, it turns out that while Schulman — a Bush appointee — was cleared to visit the White House 157 times, he appears to have actually visited only 11 times. The vast majority of the cleared visits were related to the implementation of Obamacare, in which the IRS plays a key role, and include regularly scheduled weekly meetings with administration officials on the ongoing work. Meanwhile, many people seem to be conflating the presidential mansion itself with other executive office buildings that are organizationally under the “Executive Office of the President ” — all colloquially referred to as “The White House.” They’re all included in the Secret Services’ visitors logs, but it turns out Schulman was rarely cleared to visit the actual White House, more often having permission to go to the Executive Office Building. Some Googling might also reveal a Politico story, which also cast doubt on the Daily Caller’s scoop, or plenty of others. You can see where Schulman went, whom he met with and when — all of these mysterious questions the White House refuses to answer — here. We expect it from O’Reilly, but it’s a bit disappointing from Woodward, who should know better. Still, he’s seemingly been making a subtle drift from impartial reporter to conservative pundit in recent years.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370381607244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370381645142-108</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, Individual State Governments Can do Everything Needed</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370362359579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're on a roll today. Great stuff! Let me know if you'd like to have your weenee mouthed, OK?</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1370381645142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370381793218-109</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go easy on the wild posts. The world already knows exactly what you think of all black people.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1370381793218</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370382066934-110</Id><Topic><Title>In summary for today</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370381539110</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>definitely cooler inside than outside</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370382066934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370382534180-111</Id><Title>What I read on this board in an Abomination</Title><Msg>Rome fell from the inside, and seeing how cracked you all are leads me to believe it isn't far off from our society of Fat bloated freaks have about busted the dams of morality. Then all you cracked nut jobs will have it your way, just like less than Great Britton is now. I read this cr*p on yahoo and it sickens me. "A former member of the elite U.S. Navy SEALs has come out to say she's now a woman". "Kristin Beck, formerly Chris, served 20 years as a SEAL and fought on some of the most dangerous battlefields in the world, but after she left the service she realized she wasn't living the life she wanted." Science understands physiologically why gay people exist, but any move to change natures right way (and who is to say what is right) would be an afront to exteriminating an entire aspect of societies sexuality. Maybe all people should be gay and this would fix the problems of over crowding, straining of natural resources, certain illinesses, within the lifespan of the newest generation born tomorrow or some day off in the future. For us Christians going to heaven and being in the hands of the lord is only a dream that can't happen fast enough. Heaven is perfect unlike the world, hence the perfection of the lord is where Christians want to be.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370382534180</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:48:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370382653682-112</Id><Topic><Title>Bob Woodward’s credibility in tatters</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370381607244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:33:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one, thanks. Just as it was before the election: the GOP doesn’t have a leg to stand on, if it doesn’t LIE.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1370382653682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370382743885-113</Id><Title>Democrat Blames Tea Party Groups for IRS Targeting, Paul Ryan Destroys</Title><Msg>Early Tuesday during a House Ways and Means Committee, Democrat Jim McDermott blamed tea party groups for IRS targeting. McDermott essentially said that because conservative groups dared to apply for tax exempt status, they deserved to be targeted. Luckily, Republican Rep. Paul Ryan was there to shut down his nonsense and received roaring applause in the hearing room for doing so. As a reminder, Obama's Organizing for Action is a tax exempt organization that runs President Obama's very political public relations projects and community organizing efforts.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370382743885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370382943494-114</Id><Topic><Title>Bob Woodward’s credibility in tatters</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370381607244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:33:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We expect it from O’Reilly, but it’s a bit disappointing from Woodward, who should know better. Still, he’s seemingly been making a subtle drift from impartial reporter to conservative pundit in recent years." as in US...The People of the United States the Founding Fathers do not like the alleged Supreme Court ruling reagarding 'buccal-swipes' for DNA, open your mouth or we'll open your other end for you.... ?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370382943494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370382994554-115</Id><Title>Obama's Trade Nominee Has $500,000 in Offshore Caymans Account...</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON — Michael Froman, a longtime White House economic aide nominated to be President Obama’s trade representative, holds close to $500,000 in the Cayman Islands and received millions of dollars to divest himself from Wall Street accounts that rely on a tax loophole the administration has sought to close.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370382994554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370383185172-116</Id><Title>We have Absolutely No Need for a Federal Government</Title><Msg>The Federal Government is a disaster case and an insult to REAL AMERICANS.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370383185172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370383768539-117</Id><Title>Abolish the IRS....it's a waste of money and not Needed</Title><Msg>.....not to mention it's abusive, corrupt and a tool for tyranny.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370383768539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370384256859-118</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick, I don't see how you can claim that he did not lie. He certainly did tell Congress that he didn't know anything about such activities (targeting the press) and in the same breath said that they would be inappropriate. Then, about a week later, it is revealed that he signed off on the order to do what he denied took place. In what version of facts and data does that not become a falsehood? I get that you think that Obama is surrounded by sharks - on Benghazi, on the IRS scandal, and on the DOJ's intimidation of the media. If Obama is a person of truth, then that truth will support him. On the other hand, if you are OK with people lying to the American public - for political reasons - because the "end justifies the means", then what makes you think that the next group of thugs that come along might choose to lie like Obama's team causing harm to you and the country? Lying is never acceptable. And conservatives and liberals should be in one accord on that principle. Accepting even a modicum of lying by the government, for whatever reason, is a slippery slope. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1370384256859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370384367074-119</Id><Title>the Founding Fathers do not like the alleged Supreme Court ruling reagarding 'buccal-swipes' for DNA,</Title><Msg>"Open your mouth or we'll open your other end for you..." "No!" just don;t sound right</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370384367074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370384550819-120</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lousy liar</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370384550819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370384698175-121</Id><Topic><Title>the Founding Fathers do not like the alleged Supreme Court ruling reagarding 'buccal-swipes' for DNA,</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370384367074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:19:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fingerprints photo ..#$%$</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370384698175</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370384787714-122</Id><Topic><Title>whats better ACAD up 212% YTD or Boeing up 33% ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370312807992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So 1 thumb up and 8 thumbs down to your comment. Looks like the board has spoken about your disinformation about me.HaHa. You're the one who likes to tally thumbs up and down to gauge the truth of a statement as if that has any meaning about truth. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370384787714</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370384866122-123</Id><Topic><Title>Liars &amp; Toadies calling for Eric Holder to Resign... !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370358695875</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eric Holder? Why that guy is a model of Saint hood. He's beyond the epidome' of homan decency. Just because he wouldn't prosecute the Black Panther's who committed crimes against the Constitution because he said they were Black, or because he withheld information on Fast &amp; Furious that would have exposed himself and BO is no sign anyone should get upset with Eric. That's his job to lie and protect himself and the President. And now its the IRS scandal he won't investigate. So what?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370384866122</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370384997263-124</Id><Title>The question libertarians just can’t answer</Title><Msg>The question libertarians just can’t answer If your approach is so great, why hasn’t any country anywhere in the world ever tried it? Why are there no libertarian countries? If libertarians are correct in claiming that they understand how best to organize a modern society, how is it that not a single country in the world in the early twenty-first century is organized along libertarian lines? It’s not as though there were a shortage of countries to experiment with libertarianism. There are 193 sovereign state members of the United Nations—195, if you count the Vatican and Palestine, which have been granted observer status by the world organization. If libertarianism was a good idea, wouldn’t at least one country have tried it? Wouldn’t there be at least one country, out of nearly two hundred, with minimal government, free trade, open borders, decriminalized drugs, no welfare state and no public education system?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370384997263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370385393075-125</Id><Topic><Title>The question libertarians just can’t answer</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370384997263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If your approach is so great, why hasn’t any country anywhere in the world ever tried it?" Is the question King George asked of the Continental Army in 1771.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370385393075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370385437816-126</Id><Topic><Title>update ACAD for the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370362908471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how did you pick SSN (everybody look it up) on March 7, 2009 when it peaked at 4.53 and is about 0.47 today for a 90 percent loss in value and you posted it would beat Boeing "going forward"? I know you would have gotten out when it dropped (or so you stated months later). You never comment about your losses but only when you hit a winner. Another example you touted then was SLW which has lost 47 percent in 2 years. Sure, sure, you got out without losing money. Hmmm....</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370385437816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370385538009-127</Id><Title>Yet Another Non-Scandal</Title><Msg>Obama’s newest non-scandal? The use of secret emails simply isn't the unprecedented abuse of power the AP might have you believe By Howard Koplowitz The revelation that top political appointees in President Obama’s administration are using “secret” government email accounts has left influential Republicans salivating at the thought that the exclusive Associated Press story constitutes another White House scandal. But is this another big controversy, or not that big a deal? Some in the GOP, including U.S. Sen. Lamar Alexander, R-Tenn., are concerned that the “secret” emails may be a violation of the public records law since as emails couldn’t be obtained in investigation because the probers wouldn’t know of their existence. While the report is certainly newsworthy, it’s not like this hasn’t happened before. As the Center for American Progress, a left-leaning think tank, pointed out, nonpublished email accounts were used by officials in George W. Bush’s administration. The center’s blog, ThinkProgress, said at least four Bush administration officials at the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency had two government email accounts, with one of those accounts being private. Among the officials who had a private email account was former EPA head Christine Todd Whitman, the former governor of New Jersey (towhit@epa.gov and Whitman.Christine@epa.gov.) The blog learned of the separate email addresses simply by contacting the EPA. “The AP story gives the impression that this is unprecedented, making no mention of the use of multiple addresses by previous administrations,” ThinkProgress noted. Obama Press Secretary Jay Carney also said the exclusive was not earth-shattering news and took issue with the AP headline for the story: “Top Obama Appointees Using Secret Email Accounts.” “There’s nothing secret,” Carey told the AP. He acknowledged that some Obama appointees had two government email addresses, but that the private accounts were used so they wouldn’t be inundated with messages from the public. The AP story indicated that an Obama cabinet member, U.S. Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius, was among the officials with a so-called secret email account. Her private address was identified by the AP as KGS2@hhs.gov. Her public account is Kathleen.Sebelius@hhs.gov. Kel McClanahan, executive director of the open government group National Security Counselors, told the news wire service that the separate email accounts can give the appearance that officials are trying to be deceitful. “What happens when that person doesn’t work there anymore? He leaves and someone makes a request [to review emails] in two years,” McClanahan said. “Who’s going to know to search the other accounts? You would hope that agencies doing this would keep a list of aliases in a desk drawer, but you know that isn’t happening.” But ThinkProgress said that’s not an issue and that Alexander’s concern that Obama officials may be breaking the public-records law has no merit. “[T]he release of [the EPA] information shows that both the public and private email addresses are public record and that any legitimate [Freedom of Information Act] request or subpoena for records would include those sent to and from both addresses,” ThinkProgress wrote.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385538009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370385696565-128</Id><Topic><Title>The question libertarians just can’t answer</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370384997263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots......he scores!</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370385696565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370385779355-129</Id><Title>Is God Really This Bored?</Title><Msg>House GOPers: God told us to stop Boehner coup A plan to oust the House speaker from his post reportedly fell apart after a night of prayer Jillian Rayfield A Washington Post report about in-fighting among House Republicans reveals a tidbit about the vote to reconfirm John Boehner as House speaker, and how a group of conservative members of the caucus abruptly abandoned a plan to try to oust the speaker because, as they tell it, God told them not to do it. Back in January, reports surfaced that a group of conservative Republicans were plotting to remove Boehner from his post over his handling of the “fiscal cliff” deal, which many Republicans opposed. Though conservatives needed 17 defectors to get rid of Boehner, in the end they were short by five. Rep. Steve Southerland, R-Fla., was one of the potential defectors, but he, like several others among his would-be co-conspirators, told the Post that God told him not to: Southerland, who has previously talked about his role only with the conservative Weekly Standard, said he read the Old Testament the night before the vote. He read the story of Saul and David, as the king of Israel tried to kill the future king. David wins and, with a chance to kill the king, decides to spare Saul. Southerland woke up convinced that Boehner should be spared. Others, who spoke on the condition of anonymity, said they, too, prayed before siding with Boehner. “He’s not a God of chaos, he’s a God of order,” Southerland said.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385779355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370385819609-130</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Non-Scandal</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385538009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:38:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on average, only five homicides per day in NYC under Bloombergs watch the last time we had that many homicides near Bisbee, AZ, it was over inTombstone @ the O.K. Corral, near tho the home of the lazy the 7th Siganl Command</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370385819609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370385861619-131</Id><Topic><Title>Yet Another Non-Scandal</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385538009</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:38:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>taqnks alot</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370385861619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370385888810-132</Id><Title>Why is the Most transparent Admininstration in History Lying so Much</Title><Msg>Lying, scapegoating and taking the 5th?</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370385888810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370386073905-133</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the Most transparent Admininstration in History Lying so Much</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370385888810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's undoubtedly because the truth won't work very well for them.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370386073905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370386120355-134</Id><Title>Do Democrat really think Killing Innocent Babies is Moral</Title><Msg>....or letting little girls die because they won't let her have a lung transplant. Anyone who wants these same immoral people in charge of their healthcare has a screw loose.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370386120355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:48:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370386266554-135</Id><Title>The farce that is Darrell Issa</Title><Msg>The only thing that makes Rep. Darrell Issa remotely qualified to chair the House Oversight Committee is his personal familiarity with the investigative process – on the receiving end. The man Republican House Speaker John Boehner put in charge of investigating government wrongdoing was himself indicted for stealing a car, accused of stealing at least one other car, arrested for carrying a concealed weapon, and twice suspected of insurance fraud – and once extensively investigated by authorities for arson, because his former business associates accused him, on the record, of burning down a building to collect the insurance payout. Democrats love to hate the silly, camera-chasing Issa, who came to power in 2011 promising to put the White House under generalized investigation. But now even some Republicans are happy to criticize Issa too. It’s easy for them to denounce his calling Jay Carney a “paid liar,” as well as his evidence-free claim that the IRS mess was directed from Washington, D.C., while they continue to participate in smearing the White House with non-scandals themselves, nonetheless. Issa’s extremist idiocy lets “reasonable” Republicans denounce him and/or his rhetoric, while they continue their own ethically, intellectually and politically blinkered crusades against President Obama. Sure, Sen. John McCain says it was wrong to call Carney a “paid liar” – but also on MSNBC’s “Morning Joe,” he compared the IRS mess to Ronald Reagan’s deadly Iran-Contra scandal. Um, no. Scandal-drunk Sen. Lindsey Graham says Issa went too far when he said the IRS agents who keyword-targeted Tea Party groups “were directly being ordered from Washington.” But he continued to hype the IRS story. “At the end of the day, the IRS scandal really is scary,” he told Fox’s Brian Kilmeade. “How would you like your own government to turn on you?” Is that really what happened, Lindsey Graham? And if so, it happened most brutally to a Democratic group, Emerge America, which had its tax-exempt status revoked.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370386266554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370386305868-136</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the Most transparent Admininstration in History Lying so Much</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370385888810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots.....he scores!</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1370386305868</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:51:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370386816299-137</Id><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Msg>Yes, we all know how blessed the American people are to be represented by two of the classiest and most intelligent people on the planet in Barack and Michelle Obama. So disregard all of the neocon posters and relax. Obama has everything under control.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1370386816299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370386913580-138</Id><Topic><Title>update ACAD for the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370362908471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>notice how spartacus9991 is once more straying from ACAD to another stock ssn that is disinformation , how is that related to ACAD for the current 14 week or YTd and what has ssn, which was a say trade a long time ago have to do today with ACAD? disinformation will earn you nothing spartacus99991</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370386913580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387013432-139</Id><Topic><Title>Bob Woodward’s credibility in tatters</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370381607244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 17:33:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hooz always worshipped Keith Olbermann, so that's his idea of a top notch credible journalist. Now hooz is left depending on some red diaper doper baby Alex Seitz-Geist who makes Genna look like a journalistic genius in comparison. Seitz-Geist trashing Woodward's credibility is like big pile of elephant dung calling a rose bush stinky. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387013432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387038672-140</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrat really think Killing Innocent Babies is Moral</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370386120355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:48:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>little girl can have your lung * must be 'perfect match' on all lung transfer parameters I get to be the surgeon, you get her lungs *hugs and kisses, hope you enjoy those cystic fibrosis lungs m\e IAM breathing better SHE IS WAITING...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370387038672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370387155193-141</Id><Title>Five IRS Controversy Falsehoods Manufactured By Right-Wing Media</Title><Msg>CLAIM: Washington Ordered Additional Scrutinizing Of Conservative Groups Fox News Anchor Bret Baier: IRS Employees Say "It Does In Fact Go Right To Washington." On Fox &amp; Friends, Special Report anchor Bret Baier pushed the claim that excerpts from congressional interviews of IRS employees that have been released so far show that the IRS tax-exempt organization division was ordered by Washington to target conservative organizations applying for tax-exempt status: BAIER: I think this is the focus, is whether it goes right to Washington. You have Darrell Issa, the chairman of the House Oversight Committee saying he's got interviews with these Cincinnati IRS agents saying, it does in fact go right to Washington, and he's going to lay that out this week. [Fox News, Fox &amp; Friends, 6/3/13, via Media Matters] REALITY: No Evidence Of Alleged Link Has Been Provided Rep. Cummings: Washington Link Claim "Reckless" And "Inconsistent With The Findings Of The Inspector General." In a statement released June 3, Rep. Elijah Cummings (D-MD), the ranking member of the House Committee on Oversight and Government Reform of which Rep. Darrel Issa (R-CA) is chairman, said that Issa has provided no evidence to back up his claim that IRS officials in Washington were complicit in the targeting. So far, no witnesses who have appeared before the Committee have identified any IRS official in Washington DC who directed employees in Cincinnati to use 'tea party' or similar terms to screen applicants for extra scrutiny. Chairman Issa's reckless statements today are inconsistent with the findings of the Inspector General, who spent more than a year conducting his investigation. Rather than lobbing unsubstantiated conclusions on national television for political reasons, we need to work in a bipartisan way to follow the facts where they lead and ensure that the IG's recommendations are fully implemented. We must have a sincere effort to uncover the truth so that we can restore the public's trust in the IRS. [Statement of Rep. Elijah Cummings, 6/2/13] Sen. Graham: "No Evidence" That Orders To Scrutinize Conservative Groups Came From the White House. A June 3 Hill article quoted Republican Senator Lindsey Graham of South Carolina as saying during an interview on Fox News Radio's Kilmeade and Friends that while he didn't believe the targeting of conservative groups by the IRS was "something thought up in the Cincinnati office" he had "no evidence" that the IRS was directed by the White House to do so. [The Hill, 6/3/13] CLAIM: Obama Didn't Hold Anyone Accountable For IRS Actions Bill O'Reilly: On IRS Targeting, President Obama "Is Not Holding Anyone Accountable. That's Absolutely True." Bill O'Reilly claimed during a segment of his show on the IRS' inappropriate targeting of conservative groups that "I think to be fair on this we have to say a few things definitely. That President Obama is not holding anyone accountable. That's absolutely true," and then suggested that the president should "be scolded for that." [Fox News, The O'Reilly Factor, 5/23/12, via Media Matters] REALITY: Administration Has Disciplined IRS Officials And Opened Criminal Investigation Obama Administration Fired Steven Miller, Acting IRS Commissioner. A May 15 Yahoo! News article reported that Treasury Secretary Jack Lew fired Steven Miller, the acting commissioner of the IRS, in response to the IRS actions, and said that anyone responsible will be held accountable: Obama said he had reviewed the Treasury Department Inspector General's report that details how the IRS targeted conservative groups for special scrutiny when they applied for tax-exempt status. "The misconduct that it uncovered is inexcusable. It's inexcusable, and Americans are right to be angry about it and I am angry about it," the president said in a brief prepared statement. "I will not tolerate this kind of behavior in any agency--but especially in the IRS, given the power that it has and the reach that it has into all of our lives." Obama said the "responsible parties" will be held accountable. Lew "took the first step by requesting--and accepting--the resignation of the acting commissioner of the IRS because given the controversy surrounding this audit, it's important to institute new leadership that can help restore confidence going forward," Obama added. [Yahoo! News, 5/15/13] Obama Administration Put Lois Lerner On Administrative Leave. A May 23 Washington Post article reported that Lois Lerner, who was in charge of the tax-exempt organizations division of the IRS while the targeting of conservative groups occurred, was placed on administrative leave in response to the IRS controversy: Lois Lerner, the director of the tax-exempt organizations division at the Internal Revenue Service, has been placed on administrative leave, sources in Congress and the administration confirm. [...] Lerner has been a federal employee for 34 years, holding positions at the Justice Department, the Federal Elections Commission and the IRS. She became director of the IRS's tax-exempt unit in 2006. [The Washington Post, Post Politics, 5/23/13] Attorney General Eric Holder Ordered A Criminal Investigation. A May 14 Bloomberg article reported that Attorney General Eric Holder ordered a criminal investigation into misconduct at the IRS following news of the agency's targeting of conservative organizations: Attorney General Eric Holder ordered a criminal investigation into the U.S. Internal Revenue Service's targeting of small-government advocacy groups for extra scrutiny. "The FBI is coordinating with the Justice Department to see if any laws were broken in connection with those matters related to the IRS," Holder said at a news conference today. [Bloomberg, 5/14/13] CLAIM: Former IRS Commissioner Douglas Shulman's Visits To White House Tie WH To IRS Targeting Fox's Doocy Exclaimed That "Coordinating" Was The Reason Shulman Visited The White House. Fox &amp; Friends co-host Steve Doocy implied that former IRS Commissioner Douglas Shulman's visits to the White House were about "coordinating" targeting of conservative organizations: BRIAN KILMEADE (co-host): In fact, there should have been a revolving door into the White House because he visited so much he actually outdistanced and out-lapped many people like Secretary of State Hillary Clinton, Timothy Geithner and even Eric Holder. This guy visited the White House 157 times, only for an Easter egg roll is the only one he could remember going there for -- what else was he doing there? DOOCY: Coordinating. [Fox News, Fox &amp; Friends, 5/30/13, via Media Matters] Doocy: "To Some Critics It Does Look As If He Kept Going To The White House To Coordinate Some Sort Of Political Opposition Against The President's Opponents." Later in the Fox &amp; Friends segment, Doocy said "some critics" are accusing the White House of coordinating the IRS' inappropriate targeting of conservative groupls applying for tax-exempt status: DOOCY: To some critics it does look as if he kept going to the White House to coordinate some sort of political opposition against the president's opponents. Is that what happened? Well if Mr. Shulman ever does answer the questions fully, maybe we'll know. [Fox News, Fox &amp; Friends, 5/30/13, via Media Matters] REALITY: Shulman Did Not Visit White House As Much As Claimed And Mostly Attended Meetings On Implementing Health Care Reform White House Visitor Logs "Only Reflect The Information The White House Chooses To Record." A May 23 Washington Post article reported that the White House logs "only show some visits" and are therefore unreliable: The Post's database of White House visitor logs doesn't tell the whole story. The logs only reflect the information the White House chooses to record. It certainly doesn't show what regular guests some Cabinet secretaries are at the campus centered around 1600 Pennsylvania Ave.--which we explained by noting that "bigwigs...most often get waved in," rather than having to get logged in like the rest of the commoners. Cabinet secretaries sometimes get the formal log-in treatment at official events at the White House--often when they are accompanied by spouses or other family members to events like state dinners or barbeques. [The Washington Post, In the Loop, 5/23/12] White House Visitor Logs Not Intended As "Comprehensive Means Of Documenting Every Visitor To The White House." A May 31 Atlantic article explains that the White House visitor logs are not meant to be a complete record of appointments, nor is it an accurate account of White House-specific guests: The real problem with combing through the White House visitor logs is that they were a system designed for Secret Service clearance and White House security, not as comprehensive means of documenting every visitor to the White House, high to low. They miss the top end and some of the social end of people visiting the White House -- people who are cleared through separate processes designed to protect presidential security other than getting swiped in at the front gate for an appointment. [...] The lay reader understands the White House to be the big white mansion with the columns and the Oval Office and the West Wing and the presidential family living in residence. The Daily Caller talked about visits to "the president's home." But the White House visitors' records cover the entire White House complex -- the big famous white building, along with the freestanding Eisenhower Executive Office Building inside the gated compound and the New Executive Office Building, which is up 17th Street and outside the White House gates. The vast majority of Shulman's scheduled meetings were to take place in the Eisenhower Executive Office Building -- 115 of them. Another three were slated for the NEOB. That leaves just 25 percent of the meetings in the White House itself, or on its South Lawn. [The Atlantic, 5/31/13] Shulman Mostly Visited With Staffers In Charge Of Implementing The Affordable Care Act. The Huffington Post reported on May 31 that the majority of Shulman's visits logged in the White House records were concerning implementation of the administration's health care law, the Affordable Care Act: But overall, the vast majority of Shulman's visits recorded in the White House visitor logs were to the Old Executive Office Building and with officials involved in implementing the new health care law -- indicating that the main conspiracy unearthed here is one to implement a law passed by Congress. [The Huffington Post, 5/31/13] CLAIM: IRS Continuing To Scrutinize And "Harass" Conservative Groups ACLJ's Jay Sekulow Complained That, Despite Investigation, IRS Was Continuing To "Harass" Conservative Groups He Represents In Court. American Center for Law and Justice's chief counsel Jay Sekulow appeared on America's Newsroom to discuss the IRS controversy. Sekulow complained that, despite the ongoing investigation, the IRS was continuing to apply heavy scrutiny to the conservative groups that he represents in court. As evidence, he cited an eight-page compliance letter that an unnamed nonprofit received which contained, according to Sekulow, "intrusive questions," that amounted "harassment." Sekulow provided no evidence that the groups he represents were targets of the same tactics. [Fox News, America's Newsroom, 5/29/13, via Media Matters] REALITY: Legal Experts Say The IRS Must Continue Assessing Whether Groups Are Eligible For Nonprofit Status Loyola Law School Professor: "The IRS Should Be More, Not Less, Inquisitive, But It Should Do So In An Even-Handed Fashion." In a May 16 Huffington Post article, editor of the Loyola University Law School's PoLawTics blog Jessica Levinson explained "the problem isn't that the IRS asked for too much information from organizations seeking favorable tax treatment, it is that they only asked for that information from conservative organizations": [O]nce an organization obtains non-profit status under section 501c4 of the IRS code, any political fundraising by that organization is essentially clothed in secrecy. This is a perilous state of affairs. When organizations "speak" to us by spending money to try to influence whom we chose to represent us in our government, then we the people have an important interest in knowing the identities, the true identities, behind those attempting to persuade us. [...] While there has been a good deal of public outcry concerning the IRS' admitted targeting of certain organizations applying for nonprofit status, the problem isn't that the IRS asked for too much information from organizations seeking favorable tax treatment, it is that they only asked for that information from conservative organizations. The IRS should be more, not less, inquisitive, but it should do so in an even-handed fashion. [The Huffington Post, 5/16/13] Loyola Law School Professor: "An Organization That Seeks An IRS Acknowledgment Of Its Exempt Status Subjects Itself To Scrutiny." In a Roll Call op-ed, Loyola Law School professor Ellen Aprill wrote: IRS employees who review applications for exemption have a duty to ask follow-up questions of applicants, including groups affiliated with the tea party. In the current controversy, IRS reviewers wrongly singled out conservative groups for unusually exacting follow-up. In a number of these cases, they also asked inappropriate questions, such as the identity of donors. Some media reports, however, imply that the IRS cannot and should not ask any questions of applicants for exemption, that any inquiry invades privacy and violates the First Amendment. That implication is wrong. An organization that seeks an IRS acknowledgment of its exempt status subjects itself to scrutiny -- scrutiny designed to ensure that the group in fact qualifies for the benefit of tax exemption. [Roll Call, 5/23/13] UNC Law Professor: "It Seems Fairly Clear That Many Of The C4s Are In Fact Breaking The Law." Thomas Kelley, University of North Carolina School of Law professor, explained that "many organizations are using c4s to engage in campaign activity while hiding their donors' identities": While on the subject of the IRS's current monitoring of c4 organizations, it should not be forgotten that it seems fairly clear that many of the c4s are in fact breaking the law, and that, after Citizens' United, many organizations are using c4s to engage in campaign activity while hiding their donors' identities. [CardHub.com, 5/22/13] Ezra Klein: "The IRS Scandal Is About Targeting Conservatives, Not Scrutinizing 501(c)(4)s." On the Washington Post's Wonkblog, Ezra Klein explained that the "scandal is about targeting conservatives, not scrutinizing 501(c)(4)s," and how "[t]he scrutiny was the part they did right": Here's what Sekulow is saying: Tea party groups received questions about their political activities that originated from a variety of different IRS offices, not just Cincinnati. That's not necessarily a problem and it's not even new information. It was proper that the tea party groups received heavy scrutiny. As the New York Times has firmly established, many of them were primarily political groups that potentially didn't qualify for 501(c)(4) status. [...] Sekulow is trying to widen the scandal by changing the premise: He's arguing that the real problem here was the actual questioning of tea party groups applying for 501(c)(4) status, and so anyone who participated in the work of trying to follow up on the applications chosen for extra scrutiny did something wrong. That gets this backwards: The problem wasn't that the IRS closely scrutinized questionable applications from tea party groups. It's that they didn't closely scrutinized the applications from other questionable groups as well. The scrutiny was the part they did right. The targeting was the part they did wrong. [The Washington Post, Wonkblog, 5/29/13] CLAIM: Excerpts Of IRS Employee Interviews Revealed Targeting Orders Came From Washington Daily Mail's David Martosko: Excerpts "Have Established That The Washington, D.C. Headquarters" Of IRS Was Targeting Conservative Groups. Daily Mail Online political editor David Martosko wrote that during an appearance by House Oversight Committee Chairman Darrell Issa on CNN, Issa showed that excerpts of congressional interviews of IRS employees "established" that Washington IRS officials were responsible for targeting conservative organizations: Interviews with IRS employees have established that the Washington, D.C. headquarters of the Internal Revenue Service was engaged in targeting tea party groups and other conservative organizations for unfair levels of scrutiny when they applied for tax-exempt status. Rep. Darrel lssa, chairman of powerful House Committee of Oversight and Government Reform, made that startling announcement on CNN Sunday morning. [Daily Mail Online, 6/2/13] Breitbart.com's Kerry Picket: Excerpts "Made It Clear" IRS Employees Were Told By Washington Supervisors To Target Conservative Groups. Breitbart.com's Kerry Picket posted the excerpts from interviews with IRS employees and wrote: House Oversight and Government Reform Committee Chairman Darrell Issa (R-CA) revealed new testimony from IRS employees on CNN's State of The Union on Sunday. According to transcribed excerpts released by the Committee, a Cincinnati IRS employee made it clear they were told by Washington, D.C. personnel to give extra scrutiny to Tea Party groups. [Breitbart.com, 6/2/13] Wall Street Journal: Congressional Republicans "Suggest Washington Officials Underplayed Their Involvement." On June 2, The Wall Street Journal cited the comments of Congressional Republicans to implicate Washington officials: Congressional Republicans separately on Sunday released excerpts from interviews by congressional investigators with two unnamed IRS employees that the lawmakers say suggest Washington officials underplayed their involvement in the Cincinnati office's extra scrutiny of conservative organizations. Both IRS employees, who work in Cincinnati, are quoted saying they were following orders that originated in Washington to target tea-party and other conservative groups. [The Wall Street Journal, 6/2/13] REALITY: Issa Admitted There Was No Proof Yet That Targeting Orders Came From Washington Issa Acknowledged One Of The Excerpts Was "Not Definitive" That Targeting Originated In Washington. During a June 2 interview on CNN's State of the Union, House Oversight Committee Chairman Darrell Issa agreed with host Candy Crowley that one of the excerpts from the interviews with IRS employees that he selectively leaked, after she read it on the air, is "totally not definitive": CROWLEY: And one of the excerpts we were given, and I want to talk about how problematic it is to get excerpts, because we know that you interviewed these people probably for hours and you get little excerpts which it's hard for us to kind of judge what's going on, but here's one of those -- just some IRS agent, again, from the Cincinnati office. The investigator said, "so is it your perspective that ultimately the responsible parties for the decisions that were reported by the IG," that is the decision that target tea party and Patriot applications, "are not in the Cincinnati office?" The employee says, "I don't know how to answer that question. I mean, from an agent standpoint, we didn't do anything wrong. We followed directions based on other people telling us what to do." Investigator, "and you ultimately followed directions from Washington, is that correct?" The employee, "if direction had come down from Washington, yes." The investigator, "but with respect to the particular scrutiny that was given to Tea Party applications, those directions emanated from Washington, is that right?" The employee answers, "I believe so." It's totally not definitive. ISSA: Well, that one isn't. CROWLEY: Right. [CNN, State of the Union, 6/2/13] Issa Said "We're Getting To Proving" Targeting Originated In Washington In Response To Whether He Will Release Full Transcripts Of Interviews. After Crowley questioned Issa on whether he will release complete transcripts, he responded by promising to do so but said that Republicans are still "getting to proving" their accusation that IRS supervisors in Washington, D.C., orchestrated the inappropriate targeting of conservative groups: CROWLEY: Why don't you put the whole thing out? Because you know our problem really is -- and you know that your critics say that Republicans and you in particular sort of cherry pick information that go to your foregone conclusion, so it worries us to put this kind of stuff out. Can you not put the whole transcript out? ISSA: The whole transcript will be put out. We understand -- these are in real time. And the administration is still -- they're paid liar, their spokesperson, picture behind, he's still making up things about what happens in calling this local rogue. There's no indication -- the reason the Lois Lerner tried to take the fifth is not because there is a rogue in Cincinnati, it's because this is a problem that was coordinated in all likelihood right out of Washington headquarters and we're getting to proving it. We have 18 more transcribed interviews to do. CROWLEY: But as yet, you don't -- you don't have that direct link. You have the front line agents going, yeah, I mean, we figured it was from Washington or I believe it was, but as of yet you don't have that definitive, yeah, this guy called me and said, people, go look for Tea Party and Patriot applications. [CNN, State of the Union, 6/2/13]</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370387155193</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387206167-142</Id><Topic><Title>whats better ACAD up 212% YTD or Boeing up 33% ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370312807992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>notice how angry all the users are that missed ACAD and TSLA such anger ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370387206167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370387303503-143</Id><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Msg>In response to a question from a fan on Monday afternoon, former MSNBC anchor Keith Olbermann suggested that Attorney General Eric Holder should have resigned or been fired from his post after the Associated Press phone records scandal broke, rather than having stayed on and effectively martyred a Fox News reporter. “[W]hat’s your opinion of Atty Gen Holder? Is media overplaying its victimization?” a fan named Dina wrote to Olbermann. His response: “He should’ve resigned or been dismissed after the AP overreach. Instead he made a Fox News figure a martyr.” _________________________________________ Obviously Olbermann is a racist teabagger. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387428824-144</Id><Topic><Title>Is God Really This Bored?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385779355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, In matters of faith of those that truly being in God and His salvation through Jesus, it becomes difficult to say to what extent a person is moved by God to do one thing or another - unless those resulting actions are contrary to God's Word. As to Southerland's interpretation of David's refusal to kill Saul as being equivalent to "ousting" Boehner, that is quite a stretch. I would counter that Jesus' admonition to "render to Caesar" means participate in our elections and political process - and do it without guile. And that means even recalling an elected official, for cause, or voting against someone. I seem to recall that you pointed out the absurdity of several of the early GOP candidates all saying that they were moved by God to run for President. How could God be so confused? And some mocked them, perhaps even God, as a result. "Running" and "winning" are two different things. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1370387428824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370387446900-145</Id><Title>New Topic - Lying about your Service Medals is now a crime in all 50 states</Title><Msg>"Er, um...yes, I said that I run a sub three-hour marathon" - the V.P candidate in 2012 lied Totally agree,,,lying about your branch oif service should aslso be a crime!</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370387446900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370387532609-146</Id><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Msg>unless they are in Benghazi- and might be bad for political and election issues... By William G. “Jerry” Boykin Published: June 4, 2013 Congress has shifted much of its focus recently to the Internal Revenue Service’s targeting of conservative groups, the Department of Justice’s subpoenaing of 20 Associated Press phone lines and the email account of a Fox News reporter. Because of this, Benghazi has received little attention in recent weeks. This is surprising since the topic was a leading story in April, when 700 retired and former special operations forces professionals signed an open letter to members of the U.S. House of Representatives calling for a bipartisan commission with subpoena power to investigate the terrorist attack in Libya last September. Considering that H.R. 36, a bill that would create such a commission, now has 154 co-sponsors, it’s a wonder how it hasn’t yet passed the House. Why haven’t we seen an inquiry convened? The signers of the “SOF 700” letter are tired of delays. The signers of this letter, circulated by the group Special Operations Speaks, will not rest until those responsible for the attack on the U.S. facilities in Benghazi are held accountable. Our passion about this issue is due to our background. As members of special operations units in the armed services, the 700 signers dedicated their careers and often risked their lives to respond when fellow Americans were threatened or when their safety was at risk. During their time serving the United States, the signers all knew that there would be many situations during which they would have inadequate intelligence, limited resources and little preparation time.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387562117-147</Id><Topic><Title>Is God Really This Bored?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385779355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pushed the "post" button too fast. First sentence over: "In matters of faith of those that truly BELIEVE in God and His salvation through Jesus.."</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1370387562117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387573684-148</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>During the Vietnam War, U.S. Air Force pilots regularly launched in CH-53 helicopters into enemy-held terrain to recover downed pilots. They were never sure what they would encounter in their efforts. In 1970, courageous members of the military launched a raid into North Vietnam to rescue Americans who were being held as prisoners of war near Hanoi. The first signature on the SOF 700 letter is that of retired Air Force Lt. Gen. Leroy Manor, that operation’s commander. President Richard Nixon knew that every American expected that the U.S. would make every effort to bring its warriors home. The intelligence Lt. Gen. Manor and his team used was so inadequate that when they arrived at the prison, the POWs were not even there. But that did not discourage them from trying. It was the right thing to do. No one focused on what was lacking, only on the moral imperative to try. In spite of his discomfort with using the military, President Jimmy Carter ordered a rescue effort for 52 Americans being held in the U.S. Embassy in Tehran, Iran, in April 1980. The mission was fraught with challenges and was very risky from the start, but the men on that mission never hesitated in their attempt to rescue those American hostages. Again, it was just the right thing to do. President George H.W. Bush directed that the first mission during Operation Just Cause in Panama in 1989 was to rescue an American citizen named Kurt Muse. Although the larger mission was to restore democracy, capture Manuel Noriega and protect Americans living in Panama, the president placed the highest value on the rescue of a man whose liberty had been taken from him and whose life was in danger. Like Nixon and Carter, Bush protected that long-standing American ethos that — simply stated — the U.S. never leaves anyone behind, and the U.S. always runs to the guns when one of our own is threatened.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387573684</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387620682-149</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Nixon and Carter, Bush protected that long-standing American ethos that — simply stated — the U.S. never leaves anyone behind, and the U.S. always runs to the guns when one of our own is threatened. That ethos was disregarded in Benghazi, and there has not yet been a full accounting as to why. The 700 signers will not rest until the details of this event have been determined. Our interest is not to bring down this administration. Nor is it to ruin then-Secretary of State Hillary Rodham Clinton’s political future. It is all about providing information to the families of the four Americans who died in Benghazi representing and protecting U.S. interests abroad. It is about sending a strong message to every American that, should they ever face danger abroad in the future, the American military will come to their aid. It’s the right thing to do. Our government must stop making excuses and simply do it. Lt. Gen. William G. “Jerry” Boykin (retired) served in the U.S. Army for 36 years as an original Delta Force member, as the commander of the Army’s Green Berets and of the Special Warfare Center and School, and as deputy undersecretary of defense for intelligence. He is the executive vice president of the Family Research Council, and he was a driving force behind the SOF 700 letter.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387620682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387706468-150</Id><Topic><Title>Is God Really This Bored?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385779355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is NO DOUBT the power of Jesus is in President Obama!! Make no mistake!!</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1370387706468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370387750151-151</Id><Title>Illinois state pension fund $100B in the red. Dem sell themselves out for the Union vote. The Liberal economy as we saw in Greece</Title><Msg>pension checks going to $0 Next soup lines in Illinois</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370387750151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370387785863-152</Id><Topic><Title>Is God Really This Bored?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385779355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz is proof that the concept of intelligent design has to be a joke.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387785863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370388002554-153</Id><Topic><Title>whats better ACAD up 212% YTD or Boeing up 33% ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370312807992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny thing about disinformation , it does not change the gain for ACAD compared to Boeing does it ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370388002554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370388201446-154</Id><Title>The Latest Controversy: Cheerios!</Title><Msg>Haters Gonna Hate: When Cheerios ran a short, sweet ad featuring a biracial couple and their adorable fuzzy-haired kid, enough idiot racists posted enough idiot racist rants online that Cheerios had to disable the comments. So there's that. But many, many others responded along the likes of: yo, cool, 2013, whatever. One biracial commentator, whose "family often had the audacity to eat breakfast even though cereal was not being specifically marketed to us," insists that yes, this is progress. "As dumb as this sounds, this (ad) at least provides idiots in the parking lot at Walmart a foundation of knowledge about interracial families."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370388201446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370388242921-155</Id><Topic><Title>Is God Really This Bored?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385779355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>homosexuality is an abomonation unto the Lord. God created woman for man. Obama is president of one fallen nation. Its simple to explain, Israel chose Barrabass to be freed while Jesus was crusified. Obama has the power of Satan not Jesus. Jesus has power over man and heaven.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370388242921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370388245870-156</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1370386816299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370388245870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370388607446-157</Id><Topic><Title>Is God Really This Bored?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385779355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Its simple to explain" Sure... after reading your post, I feel qualified to explain the origins of man, the philosophy of morality, and just who is seated at the right hand of God to the entire universe. Thanks. Tomorrow I'll take the "complete guide to rocket science".</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370388607446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370388615320-158</Id><Topic><Title>whats better ACAD up 212% YTD or Boeing up 33% ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370312807992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:26:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow all the comments and still ACAD up 212% year to date and Boeing, is down just 1.12% today while ACAD at a top still managed to crack a little higher Boeing hit a top and has been falling since then oh well learn to read a stock chart boyes or call if you like to troll me, then go ahead , I really don't care you can call me a gay fired Boeing employee its your choice ! BHT, facts rule over disinformation and my Boeing pension keeps cranking me out a check every month ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370388615320</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370388819432-159</Id><Topic><Title>update ACAD for the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370362908471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so BHT, a new high today on my stock ACAD and it still managed to make a little break out so sorry your in Boeing it fell another over 1% today and fails big compared to airbus for 5 years so why are you so mad at me now eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370388819432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370388920783-160</Id><Topic><Title>The Latest Controversy: Cheerios!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370388201446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No doubt, the non=catsup Raygun controversy candy-date flavor of the year - paul Ryan for VP any RWNJ fish</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370388920783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370389118288-161</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1370386816299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you think of Keith Olbermann saying that Eric Holder should have resigned or been fired? Many Progs suggest that only racist teabaggers want Holder fired. Is Olbermann a racist teabagger?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370389118288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370389216350-162</Id><Title>Airbus A350, Paris Airshow fly-by and for 5 years up over 145% Boeing stock for 5 years not even 30% gain</Title><Msg>Airbus has nominated the pilots and engineers who will conduct the first test flight of the new A350, signaling the countdown to the wide-body aircraft’s maiden voyage may be just a matter of days. The first flight will have a crew of six, including two test pilots and a project test-flight engineer who will sit in the cockpit, Airbus said. Three additional flight test crew members, all experimental flight test engineers, will work at dedicated stations on the plane to manage the flight’s progress. The first take-off will mark the beginning of more than nine months of testing, in which pilots put the aircraft through increasingly complex maneuvers to ensure its airworthiness and safety. The first plane doesn’t carry passengers, and is stuffed with computers and equipment to record performance data. A first flight in coming weeks would be a public-relations coup for Airbus ahead of the Paris Air Show, the year’s biggest aviation expo, which starts June 17. While the organizers haven’t confirmed the plane’s appearance at the event, Airbus may choose a so-called “fly-by” if civil aviation authorities give it clearance.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370389216350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370389574472-163</Id><Title>Randy Yates rode Ramrod when Gil Favor said so...</Title><Msg>so I had to cancel my subscription to Encore Westerns</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370389574472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370389774631-164</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1370386816299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know a lot about American journalists.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1370389774631</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370389843541-165</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My god - if you've lost Oberslobber- youve lost your power base , behind kissers, and sheep !! Is hell freezing over ?</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370389843541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370390069319-166</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the Most transparent Admininstration in History Lying so Much</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370385888810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously this Obama has hate for the Constitution, Bill of Rights, Congress and the Surpreme Court. He wants to be king. He is a thug like Assad.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370390069319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370390175457-167</Id><Topic><Title>Randy Yates rode Ramrod when Gil Favor said so...</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370389574472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Theme song from Rawhide insert RWNJ for cow/cattle Yee haw but taste like chicken</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370390175457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370390472619-168</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eric Holder should've been given a medal for his forthrighteousness and he should be considered for the nomination for president in 2016</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370390472619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370390652710-169</Id><Topic><Title>the Founding Fathers do not like the alleged Supreme Court ruling reagarding 'buccal-swipes' for DNA,</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370384367074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:19:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine the outrage of the Founding Fathers</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1370390652710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:04:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370391307577-170</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus A350, Paris Airshow fly-by and for 5 years up over 145% Boeing stock for 5 years not even 30% gain</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370389216350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope they take out big insurance policies so their families will at least have something. The odds for this crew are not good-- just look at the first flight fatal crash of the A320- considering the reckless rush AB has been in to field the A350 it could easily happen again. Of course that's AB's modus operendi- think of all those AB airplanes that have gone down for inadequate engineering and maintenance- Say Wayne you could probably get a ticket your self and try to make it to Paris on that airplane-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370391307577</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370391332987-171</Id><Topic><Title>New Topic - Lying about your Service Medals is now a crime in all 50 states</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370387446900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:10:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about the other 7 states.....is it OK to Lie in them?</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1370391332987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:15:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370391397419-172</Id><Title>12 bags of RWNJ/squirrel food</Title><Msg>only one RWNJ/squirrel/rodent wants to play</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370391397419</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370391765593-173</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1370386816299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither, of course. But what is metaphysically certain is chemical_ali_infested is a doofus.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1370391765593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370391942834-174</Id><Topic><Title>New Topic - Lying about your Service Medals is now a crime in all 50 states</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370387446900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:10:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now there are nine lies you said Jesus H. Christ I believe the H. stood for the Honorable Most Almighty Mother Of Mary Nicest Person I Ever Knew tell bulky-Blob and his ilk... like an Angel I told Althea I was feeling lost Lacking in some direction Althea told me upon scrutiny my back might need protection I told Althea that treachery was tearin me limb from limb Althea told me: now cool down boy - settle back easy Jim You may be Saturday's child all grown moving with a pinch of grace You may be a clown in the burying ground or just another pretty face You may be the fate of Ophelia sleeping and perchance to dream - honest to the point of recklessness self centered to the extreme Ain't nobody messin with you but you your friends are getting most concerned - loose with the truth maybe it's your fire but baby...don't get burned When the smoke has cleared, she said, that's what she said to me: You're gonna want a bed to lay your head and a little sympathy There are things you can replace and others you cannot The time has come to weigh those things this space is getting hot - you know this space is getting hot I told Althea I'm a roving sign - that I was born to be a bachelor - Althea told me: Ok that's fine - So now I'm out trying to catch her Can't talk to you without talking to me We're guilty of the same old thing Thinking a lot about less and less And forgetting the love we bring</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370391942834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370392417889-175</Id><Topic><Title>12 bags of RWNJ/squirrel food</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370391397419</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>share with a LWNJ chipmonk</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370392417889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370392485773-176</Id><Topic><Title>12 bags of RWNJ/squirrel food</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370391397419</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nano nano not nanoo nanoo</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370392485773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370392748827-177</Id><Topic><Title>12 bags of RWNJ/squirrel food</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370391397419</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that was faster then a blink of a RWNJ eye •a second ago from here to where...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370392748827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370393484473-178</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1370386816299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:00:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fbi cia nasa j. edgar sir paul knew them all along with watson &amp; Crick and Elvis to boot/and some Buddy Holly/Grand Funk Railroad/lil Sheeba 'now that you can do the BA let's make a chain now a chugga-chugga like a railroad train now</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370393484473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 20:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370394415715-179</Id><Topic><Title>Randy Yates rode Ramrod when Gil Favor said so...</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370389574472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dontcha mean Rowdy?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370394415715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370394574057-180</Id><Topic><Title>The land is very old</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364153532425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 15:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they only took my advice back then which would be : Mar 24, 2013 3:02 PM Who is going to build all the RWNJ walls when we hasve the best weapon-systems of Earth and run around like when we need spaceships pARTY OF oNE = ONE pARTY OF tWO = REPETATIVE ONE THREE 1O3</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370394574057</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370394576304-181</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus A350, Paris Airshow fly-by and for 5 years up over 145% Boeing stock for 5 years not even 30% gain</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370389216350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father _Zosima or as I like your other avatar name whsteffanms , did you discuss this with your close personal friend , Paul Allen, next father- whsteffanms where is my free ticket then eh ! Your so rich and famous have your mother visit me with the ticket eh ! father whstefanms, and still Airbus in spite of all your B---S---T is up 145% for 5 years while Boeing has not yet made even 30% for their shareholders . father whstleffanms let us review your all time favorite statement. "whsteffanms on his posts and MSFT, eh! 18-Jun-11 01:42 pm whsteffanms... I was wondering your IP address shows as Everett and you have 4528 update(6039)posts, with almost all of them containing slams and HAR HAR HAR and nothing of any value to anyone, how is it that you get along so well with Paul Allen? eh! Re: Microsoft Shows First Look at Windows 8 Interface VIDEO Whsteffanms said” dell george my address may be Everett, but my mansion is actually located over on Widbey Island( sure it is) and I get back and forth with my yacht( the full size scale model?)- I tie up next to Paul Allen a lot( a lot like never !) down in Elliott bay and confer( wow) with him quite a lot-- how do you like that eh ( just like all your other emails,, har, har , har ) Rating : (No ratings) Rate it: 1 star + unrated 5 stars whsteffanms... Male Everett WA ________________________________________</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370394576304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370395357548-182</Id><Topic><Title>According to the Bible - the RW evangelical is to speed Global Warming</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1364136616713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:50:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ali-infesto HAS BEEN WARNED MORE THAN ONCE or TWICE ABOUT TRYING INCITE RWNJ RIOTS AND HAS BEEN FOUND GUILTY ON ALL CHARGES after death, his children will not be worthy to be called Egyptian letalone children</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370395357548</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370396872727-183</Id><Topic><Title>update ACAD for the facts</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370362908471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 12:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now Wayne wants to be the Yahoo board monitor and say what others can post about stocks. Have you noticed that this is not the ACAD board (or APPL, or SSN, or SLW, or FFIV, or JCI, etc) all stocks Wayne (dell) posted on a BA board that would beat Boeing "going forward". Still maintain that the market "closed early" on March 28th or that the BA low was 55 during the last 5 years? That's what I call disinformation on a finance board.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370396872727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:47:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370396963450-184</Id><Title>Jewish school investigating after AirTran boots 100 #$%$ students- potential sue happy #$%$ law-yahs to be</Title><Msg>"An Orthodox Jewish high school in New York is investigating an incident where more than one hundred of its students were kicked off an early morning AirTran flight on Monday. Yeshivah of Flatbush's senior class trip was detoured after 101 students and eight chaperones were kicked off a plane bound for Atlanta." Bunch of spoiled rotten soon to be anti-gentilic lawyers to bring more misery on the gentiles. The pilot would have done us all a favor by crashing the plane deep into the ocean. "One student believes the group was targeted for its religious affiliation, suggesting that Southwest Airlines made up the story about the unruly group in order to cover up the staff’s anti-Semitic behavior." Those #$%$’s are quick with the anti-semitic card. I guarantee you this pilot and crew lose their jobs over this. A slimy New York #$%$ lawyer will be asking Southwest $Billions for this so called anti-semitic event. I’d take a plane full of respectfully brought up African Americans or Muslims over those soulless animals. Yeshivah is pronounced and used as: Yeah-shove-yah out of my way to get the 'GOLD'.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370396963450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370397099629-185</Id><Topic><Title>Randy Yates rode Ramrod when Gil Favor said so...</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370389574472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>takks fur minding me... Rowdy say if he had your power and couple billion dollars he would build a desalintion plant near* the mouth of the \Carmel River</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370397099629</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:51:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370397740317-186</Id><Topic><Title>Jewish school investigating after AirTran boots 100 #$%$ students- potential sue happy #$%$ law-yahs to be</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370396963450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone care to take a guess at how much AirTran's or Southwest are going to be sued for in total? 100 animals gets at least $100 million, $1 million per piece for those hooknose-heime. That ought to get them a full scholarship any where in the world, or at least enough to open a kosher deli, four by two La Heime!</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370397740317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370398500850-187</Id><Topic><Title>The Latest Controversy: Cheerios!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370388201446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Totally/100% Groovin' pre/pre-woodstock Yosemite Valley this time of year 1969 or the 1968 Veterans Day pefrormance of Santna/QSMS in the high school gymnasium after eight plus 2 x 5000 get Toghether by the Youngbloods and sometimes the entire Doors album the year B4 that, paint the house not black] but The Letter by The Boxtips on the A.M. dial... next rto the best job bto</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370398500850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:15:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370399861822-188</Id><Topic><Title>The Latest Controversy: Cheerios!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370388201446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or about 10 years before ever smoking a joint in the early heady days a. The S.F. Mint only processes the papers, most the FED live like pigs</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1370399861822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370400750485-189</Id><Topic><Title>Jewish school investigating after AirTran boots 100 #$%$ students- potential sue happy #$%$ law-yahs to be</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370396963450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 21:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It takes a slimy witch to post anti-semitic slurs.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370400750485</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370400915323-190</Id><Topic><Title>The Latest Controversy: Cheerios!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370388201446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>either Gold Fish or Go Fish</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1370400915323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370402243353-191</Id><Topic><Title>Is God Really This Bored?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370385779355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:42:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz or not, you are right: Intelligent design IS a joke.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370402243353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370402412375-192</Id><Topic><Title>US leaves NO one behind</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370387532609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Revisionist history. We didn't run to the guns in 1914 or 1939, and if we left no one behind in Vietnam, what do all the black flags mean? It's touchy-feely nonsense conservatives propogate to show how much more patriotic they are than the rest of us.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370402412375</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370402521633-193</Id><Topic><Title>Keith Olbermann: Eric Holder Should’ve Resigned Before Making ‘Martyr’ Of Fox News Reporter</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370387303503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 19:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's great to be a member of a party that allows difference of opinion rather than making its members sign on to the talking points du jour.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370402521633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370402669096-194</Id><Topic><Title>The farce that is Darrell Issa</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370386266554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 18:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, that and the fact that on the oversight committee, he gets to use his penchant to overlook (mostly GOP) things.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370402669096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370403254236-195</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Know why We need a Federal Government.?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1370356394650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Continental Congress couldn't even gets the states INDIVIDUALLY to pony up enough to feed the Continental Army.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403254236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370403909987-196</Id><Title>Can anyone tell me why we need states?</Title><Msg>I can't think of a thing they can do that a federal government cannot do better!! Harharharharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370403909987</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370404196797-197</Id><Topic><Title>Good news for barack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370307463637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:57:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah. That explains it. Did you see censored anywhere along your route?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1370404196797</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370404482784-198</Id><Title>x6xxx234</Title><Msg>to plug al capone full of hoes with a shot-gun up close next</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370404482784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 23:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>