<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361512987809-1</Id><Title>Airbus, made by Socialist Nations, none of there planes grounded like 787, LOL</Title><Msg>What a load that 787 is.</Msg><Username>contemplationgone</Username><Timestamp>1361512987809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 01:03:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361515585924-2</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, being 1st in the market gives you an advantage such as lower development cost and in the case of the 707, it became AF1 replacing the Connie and the KC-135 tanker.</Msg><Username>boeingman_1</Username><Timestamp>1361515585924</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 01:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361516628176-3</Id><Title>Japan identifies spate of Boeing 787 jet problems but still investigating key battery woes</Title><Msg>Japan identifies spate of Boeing 787 jet problems but still investigating key battery woes TOKYO (AP) -- Japanese investigators have identified the causes of fuel leaks and other problems with Boeing's 787 but are still investigating the more serious battery problem that forced an emergency landing in January and the worldwide grounding of the jets. An oil leak was caused by an improper paint job that led to a switch not working properly, while inadequate taping led to cracks in cockpit glass, and a faulty part led to braking problems, according to the Transport Ministry's investigation released Friday into problems that occurred with the 787 Dreamliner in January. Boeing and U.S. authorities are also investigating, but Friday's findings shed little light on the main problem. . The aircraft manufacturer said earlier this week that it intends to propose to U.S. federal regulators a temporary fix for the batteries. The official who spoke on condition of anonymity did not disclose details. A fix for the 787 batteries would require stopping an uncontrolled overheating reaction called "thermal runaway," in which the battery gets hotter and hotter, and short-circuits spread from one battery cell to another. The battery problems are not necessarily linked to their manufacturer and could come from the myriads of parts and systems connected to the battery. . . JAL and ANA have not said what they plan to do in the long term. Both companies have said they are ready to seek compensation from Boeing.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361516628176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 02:03:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361518209870-4</Id><Title>pusillanimous trolls and federal agents on the payroll.</Title><Msg>......do post on this board.....Gaslighting, bait and switch, chaos agents...sophisticated but designed to confuse and propagandise...they are starting to lose the infowar..</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361518209870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 02:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361522508026-5</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree that many Republicans lack knowledge about science but so do Democrats. For example Krugman says, "As the evidence for a warming planet becomes ever stronger — and ever scarier..." Where is Krugman getting this information? The most knowledgeable climate journalists at the times Andy Revkin, has recently done an article on the Arctic which counters Krgman's claim that evidence for warming is stronger and scarier than ever. Do a search on 'Eyes Turn to Antarctica as Study Shows Greenland’s Ice Has Endured Warmer Climates' and read for yourself the latest findings that Greenland averaged temperatures that were 14.4 degreesF warmer than today, over several thousands of years during the Eemian. I have read the actual study if you are interested in discussing the topic further. Here's Revkin's conclusion after consulting ice expert Richard Alley. "Considering what I’ve learned in the nine years since I got to visit the frigid summit and eroding edges of Greenland’s amazing ice sheet, in a final note to Alley here’s how I described my reply to the Climate Desk’s “Can We Save Greenland?” question: My answer would be that Greenland doesn’t need “saving,” Antarctica needs much more observation and analysis, and — separately — the long effort to slow greenhouse gas emissions needs to continue." So the Climate Desk and Chris Mooney are ignoring the science to make it scarier than the latest scientific research indicates and Krugman is clueless. The neuro science community at 'Science 2.0' completely shredded Chris Mooney's book as garbage and had Krugman read actual scientific opinions from actual scientists he would actually learn that scientists see little difference between Republican Brains and Democrat Brains. You can also read about the latest scientific research showing the growing evidence, again opposite of Krugman's claim that it's scarier, that climate sensitivity to CO2 exceeding 4.5 degreesC has pretty much been ruled out and that sensetivity estimates are declining and less scary rather than scarier as Krugman incorrectly states. Krugman is relying on anti-science clowns like Chris Mooney when he should be talking to science minded professors like Andy Revkin, and so should Republicans.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361522508026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 03:41:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361525133227-6</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus, made by Socialist Nations, none of there planes grounded like 787, LOL</Title><Username>contemplationgone</Username><Timestamp>1361512987809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 01:03:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, a load indeed... a loadoshit.</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1361525133227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 04:25:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361525462173-7</Id><Topic><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= He doesn't give a rats rear end about responsibility = Do YOU?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1361525462173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 04:31:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361526005288-8</Id><Topic><Title>Japanese discover new problems in 787</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361488204664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:10:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The has [sic] been problems in human lifetimes before automobiles. Famine, disease. War. Ring a little bell in that little skull?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1361526005288</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 04:40:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361530670285-9</Id><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Msg>Democrats and Republicans remain at odds on how to avoid a round of budget cuts so deep and arbitrary that to allow them now could push the economy back into recession. The cuts, known as a sequester, will kick in March 1 unless Republicans agree to President Obama’s demand to a legislative package that combines spending reductions and tax increases. As of Thursday, with the deadline a week off, Republicans seemed determined to say no to any new tax increases. “Spending is the problem,” declared the House speaker, John Boehner. “Spending must be the focus.” Reflecting the views of many of her Republican colleagues, Representative Martha Roby said Wednesday that Mr. Obama “already got his tax increase” as part of the January agreement over the “fiscal cliff” and that no further increases were necessary. Both are wrong. To reduce the deficit in a weak economy, new taxes on high-income Americans are a matter of necessity and fairness; they are also a necessary precondition to what in time will have to be tax increases on the middle class. Contrary to Mr. Boehner’s “spending problem” claim, much of the deficit in the next 10 years can be chalked up to chronic revenue shortfalls from the Bush-era tax cuts, which were only partly undone in the fiscal-cliff deal earlier this year. (Wars and a recession also contributed.) It stands to reason that a deficit caused partly by inadequate revenue must be corrected in part by new taxes. And the only way to raise taxes now without harming the recovery is to impose them on high-income filers, for whom a tax increase is unlikely to cut into spending. As it happens, those taxpayers are the same ones who benefited most from Bush-era tax breaks and who continue to pay low taxes. Even with recent increases, the new top rate of 39.6 percent is historically low; investment income is still taxed at special low rates; and the heirs of multimillion-dollar estates face lower taxes than at almost any time in modern memory. On the spending side, Republicans are resisting cuts to defense. That implies brutalizing cuts in nondefense discretionary areas, like education and environment, which are already set to fall to their lowest level as a share of the economy since the 1950s. As for entitlements, Republicans mainly want to cut those that mostly go to the middle class and the poor, while ignoring nearly $1.1 trillion in annual deductions, credits and other tax breaks that flow disproportionately to the highest income Americans and that cost more, each year, than Medicare and Medicaid combined. Clearly then, there is both ample room and justification to reduce the deficit by curbing tax breaks at the high end, as Mr. Obama has proposed and Republicans have rejected. Raising taxes at the top is neither punitive nor gratuitous. It is a needed step, both to achieve near-term budget goals and to lay the foundation for a healthy budget in the future. As the economy strengthens and the population ages, more taxes will be needed from further down the income scale, both to meet foreseeable commitments, especially health care, as well as unforeseeable developments, from wars to technological challenges. But there will never be a consensus for more taxes from the middle class without imposing higher taxes on wealthy Americans, who have enjoyed low taxes for a long time. NYT 21 Feb 3013</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361530890380-10</Id><Title>RE: Thank you Professional Bargaining Unit</Title><Msg>Members of the Professional Bargaining Unit aren't professionals. They're i - d - i - o - t -s and m - o - r - o - n - s. Consider what they just did. Despite working for a company that quarter after quarter after quarter, year after year after year has set new, all-time records for A/P orders, A/P deliveries and profit, they cut the retirement benefits of engineers hired after March 1, 2013 by 31 to 41% and put their own retirement benefits in grave danger. Boeing will now freeze our pension and it will cost most of us tens and tens and tens of thousands, if not hundreds of thousands, of dollars in retirement income during our lifetime. You call that a good deal? Really? Please explain how. The executives are immune from all of this of course and will still get a big, fat pension with yearly payouts EQUAL to their annual salary. And so America's race to the bottom continues and Boeing has now taken another step toward becoming the next Walmart. I cannot get out of this dying, washed up, has-been of a company fast enough, a sentiment that I'm hearing from more and more of my colleagues. As for Boeing giving us plenty of work on the 737MAX as a reward for throwing away our pension ... Boeing will do no such thing. Instead, it will continue to outsource more and more work to its "global supply chain", which will repeat the 787 experience again and again and again, so suck on that shareholders. As for you MB, #$%$ - k o - f - f.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1361530890380</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 06:01:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361531376061-11</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Automaton's get Zilch, Bupkus, Nada - Fools</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361500327521</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 21:32:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. Totally agree, with only one exception ... I'd describe it differently. My colleagues who voted to accept this ticking time bomb of a contract (and that is what it is, a ticking time bomb), folded like a cheap tent in a hurricane. For more, see my post titled RE: Thank you Profession Bargaining Unit</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1361531376061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 06:09:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361531428403-12</Id><Topic><Title>pusillanimous trolls and federal agents on the payroll.</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361518209870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 02:30:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many of the posters are just DFC's and useful idiots.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361531428403</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 06:10:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361532674618-13</Id><Topic><Title>pusillanimous trolls and federal agents on the payroll.</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361518209870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 02:30:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL... by contrast, you're a useLESS idiot, Anal G.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1361532674618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 06:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361535320644-14</Id><Topic><Title>Japanese discover new problems in 787</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361488204664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:10:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could be right...but...switching battery makers would not be simple. An upgrade in the entire quality program makes sense and is faster. Obvioulsy the problem lies with basic process controls and lack of understanding dendrites, electromigration and nucleation sites, hotspots and dialectric occlusions leading to runaways. Eventually it will get figured out. In the meantime do not depend on the Japanes to ever admit they screwed up. Even when it is proven they will deny it. Recent NYT piece"Dr. Brodd said that another possible cause of the battery problems was contamination from errant metallic shavings, which could have been left in one of the cells during manufacturing. Federal officials said Boeing had recently insisted that GS Yuasa, the Japanese company that makes the batteries, strengthen its quality control. "</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1361535320644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 07:15:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361535946991-15</Id><Topic><Title>Exposed: Obama’s Hysterical Reaction to “Sequestration”</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1361460112098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:21:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More than anything, these actions are clear evidence that he is incapable of leading. At some point, it does not matter who said what..."LEAD, FOLLOW OR GET OUT OF THE WAY"</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1361535946991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 07:25:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361536462425-16</Id><Title>787 is junk and will be scrapped.</Title><Msg>Better to start from scratch. The plane has too many issues and bobody will fly on it.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361536462425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 07:34:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361538172471-17</Id><Topic><Title>787 is junk and will be scrapped.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361536462425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 07:34:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bobody may not want to fly on the 787 Dreamliner but I sure would.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361538172471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:02:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361539022476-18</Id><Title>3/1 Sequestration is Coming</Title><Msg>Head for the hills!</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361539022476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:17:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361541082460-19</Id><Topic><Title>3/1 Sequestration is Coming</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361539022476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just remember what Obama said about all the jobs that would be lost. Whose jobs would be lost. All the policies that wouldn't be funded. He lied a big bunch just like his campaign strategy that he is still in striking fear with his lies. We need to cut out a lot more spending, and leaderless Obama needs to tell the folks where he would like to see cuts in spending made.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361541082460</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:51:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361541147377-20</Id><Title>This is getting serious</Title><Msg>Japan identifies some Boeing 787 problems Japan identifies spate of Boeing 787 jet problems but still investigating key battery woes TOKYO (AP) -- Japanese authorities have identified the causes of fuel leaks and other problems with Boeing's 787 but are still investigating the more serious battery problem that forced an emergency landing in January and the worldwide grounding of the jets. An oil leak was caused by an improper paint job that led to a switch not working properly, while inadequate taping led to cracks in cockpit glass, and a faulty part led to braking problems, according to the Transport Ministry's investigation released Friday into problems that occurred with the 787 Dreamliner in January. The aircraft manufacturer said earlier this week that it intends to propose to U.S. federal regulators a temporary fix for the batteries. The official who spoke on condition of anonymity did not disclose details.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361541147377</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:52:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361542132931-21</Id><Topic><Title>Japanese discover new problems in 787</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361488204664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:10:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A modern car can often go 100K with little more than tires, brakes, and is vastly more complex than the model T which claims to fame included being reliable and easy to fix due to simple design, yet there is no way it would over make it over 10K let alone 100K without far more maintenance than a modern vastly more complex car. Fact is despite getting drastically more complex, cars are more reliable than ever, and there is no reason the same can't hold true for aircraft.</Msg><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1361542132931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:08:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361542296453-22</Id><Topic><Title>This is getting serious</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361541147377</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:52:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's critical here is the following: TEMPORARY "The aircraft manufacturer said earlier this week that it intends to propose to U.S. federal regulators a temporary fix for the batteries. " Temporary until one lands in the Pacific</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361542296453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:11:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361542476670-23</Id><Title>BA Has Become a Big Parking Lot for No-Fly Planes</Title><Msg>So BUY BUY BUY BA to the MOOOOOOOOOOoooooooooooooooooooooonnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1361542476670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:14:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361542640334-24</Id><Title>Looks Like Outsourcing to Cheap Cheap Really Works...at Grounding a Fleet of Planes</Title><Msg>Save a penny to LOSE MILLION$.</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1361542640334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:17:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361542881884-25</Id><Title>Battery Testing? BA Don't Need to Pay a Stinking $10.000 for a Battery Test!</Title><Msg>Just WING IT!</Msg><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1361542881884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:21:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361543765304-26</Id><Topic><Title>Thank Goodness - Black History Month is Almost Over</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361543573769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:32:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for the history tip. There is a reason for everything. The other 11 months are for the "other" people that have no value.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543765304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:36:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361543855586-27</Id><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Msg>There will be clases on it. How to F an airplane.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361544063590-28</Id><Topic><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361462469804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:01:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your ideas about American citizens is pretty screwey considering that we killed several hundred thousand American citizens in the American civil war. In war morality takes a back seat when it comes to killing the enemy. Sometimes your compatriots are working with the enemy and then what do you do- just tell them to go ahead?? BTW which side are you on?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361544063590</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:41:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361544190497-29</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In thirty days as many as 60-70 787s will b e delivered and flying shorty- then we will have you by the a..</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361544190497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:43:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361544563892-30</Id><Topic><Title>Is Slavery Only Wrong If the Master is White and The Slave is Black?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361544283356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doubt if you can find an example in the past millennium of history. Doubtless what you are referring to is your desire to commit the crime of tax fraud. The RWNJ big lie about taxes seems to apply to you to a T So tell us- how did you get to be such a craven fraud, tax cheat and racist- is it some kind of genetic defect or did you learn it from your mother-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361544563892</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:49:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361544719790-31</Id><Topic><Title>Japanese discover new problems in 787</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361488204664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:10:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OLD News-- we all heard about the fuel leak the same week as the battery problems emerged. The japaese simply found the cause of the leak</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361544719790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:51:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361545015037-32</Id><Topic><Title>Does the Lenth of time of Involuntary Servitude Determine if it's Right or Wrong?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361544746745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:52:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The taxes you pay to do your civic requirement was voted on by you and approved when you elected those baggers to the senate and house and when you elected your president. Oh you mean your side didn't win? so you want to impose some kind of dictatorship and force the majority into slavery? why don't you just move to Somalia or Mogadishu - they don't have taxes and welfare and social security there- you would be ecstatic in that paradise of civic irresponsibility</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361545015037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:56:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361545019522-33</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will never get to fly on one. The plane is junk.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361545019522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:56:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361545126762-34</Id><Title>It will cost less to junk the 787 than to rework the enire plane</Title><Msg>Like a house hit by a tornado. Better bulldoze it and start over.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361545126762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:58:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361545136973-35</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shorty you had better cover now while you still can. In a few days the price of boeing will be in the 80s on its way to the 90s</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361545136973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:58:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361545227790-36</Id><Topic><Title>Thank Goodness - Black History Month is Almost Over</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361543573769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:32:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White liberals sincere about not being racist? lol ! That was a joke right.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361545227790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:00:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361545314316-37</Id><Topic><Title>Thank Goodness - Black History Month is Almost Over</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361543573769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:32:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we white liberals are holier than any of you ignorant #$%$ racists - you on the other hand seem to be controlled by the evil one or haven't got the brains to see that somethings wrong with you because of your seemingly inherent racism</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361545314316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:01:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361545370891-38</Id><Topic><Title>Is Slavery Only Wrong If the Master is White and The Slave is Black?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361544283356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope4...... Your're wasting your time trying to communicate with zosima.....he's obviously got a screw loose and is incapable of rational thought.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1361545370891</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:02:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361545693116-39</Id><Topic><Title>Is Slavery Only Wrong If the Master is White and The Slave is Black?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361544283356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rover I don't live in the 16th century like you and hope4- At least the liberal portion of humanity has changed with the times</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361545693116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:08:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546201739-40</Id><Topic><Title>Is Slavery Only Wrong If the Master is White and The Slave is Black?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361544283356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My ancestors were slaves of dark skinned people. In fact the root word for slave is derived from those early light skinned slaves. Ignorance abounds in this country where those ignorant of history believe that only those of African heritage had been enslaved. I'm sure the Democratic Black Caucus won't be bigots and include me if any reparations are discussed for descendants of slavery.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361546201739</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:16:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546230170-41</Id><Topic><Title>BA may break 80$</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361479621887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:47:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Monoply with huge back log...</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361546230170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:17:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546253837-42</Id><Topic><Title>Is Slavery Only Wrong If the Master is White and The Slave is Black?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361544283356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:44:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Social injustice has no expiration date fool.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361546253837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:17:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546259136-43</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, it's bad project management that caused bad engineering. Most of the original engineering was done in design offices in Moscow, Russia, and Madrid, Spain and sub-contractors in Japan. That was not an engineering decision. Just saying!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361546259136</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:17:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546333952-44</Id><Topic><Title>787 is junk and will be scrapped.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361536462425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 07:34:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes but on a grounded 787 Dreamliner!</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1361546333952</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:18:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546705871-45</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may get to eat dinner in an old shell. The plane is done.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1361546705871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:25:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546764394-46</Id><Topic><Title>787 is junk and will be scrapped.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361536462425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 07:34:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I expect you will be scrapped first!!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1361546764394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:26:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361546826338-47</Id><Title>787 = Ugo = Pinto = History</Title><Msg>The 787 will have a slow death but some will learn and others not.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1361546826338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:27:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546880335-48</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As are you!!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1361546880335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:28:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361546957145-49</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya, like you have a big stake in all of this!!!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1361546957145</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:29:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361546967181-50</Id><Title>Sequester Strategy</Title><Msg>I watched Carl Rove talking about how Republicans should handle the Sequester folly. He sounded like an idiot. No wonder the republicans get out manuveured by Obama with a goofy guy like Rove calling the shots for Republicans. The GOP really needs someone with at least normal intelligence to direct their political strategy, that would leave out #$%$ and Rove for sure. Get someone half way smart to direct the republican efforts and Obama won't look too good, because he's really very, very bad.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361546967181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:29:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361547096992-51</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This from the VP of Engineering!!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1361547096992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:31:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361547189110-52</Id><Topic><Title>When you are Forced to Work 4 Months of the Year for the Gubmit.......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361545748336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:09:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope it aint slavery- your baggers that you voted in were supposed to prevent it. So your side lost the election well- if you don't like it leave ok?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361547189110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:33:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361547377925-53</Id><Topic><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1361462469804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 11:01:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enjoy while you can because it's going to end really ugly, and that won't be fun for anyone.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361547377925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:36:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361547484292-54</Id><Topic><Title>When you are Forced to Work 4 Months of the Year for the Gubmit.......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361545748336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:09:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not really. Americans, conservatives anyway are compassionate folks and want to take care of those in need, but want to see that the bulk of the tax dollars goes directly to those that need it, not supporting crony capitalism, and supporting layers upon theirs of bureaucrats that destroy wealth creation, and the very system that provides for the health, and wealfare of all our citizens. It is waste, and corruption we pro-American conservatives don't support.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361547484292</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:38:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361547548442-55</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester Strategy</Title><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361546967181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:29:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What did he say idiot? Or are you so braindead you can't recall what he said?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361547548442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:39:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361547672301-56</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is in denial... 787 is on the way to the history books for bad engineering.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361543855586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 09:37:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember that restaurant chain Victoria Station that used to use old railroad cars? Maybe someone could use the 787's for something like that. They could serve 1960's style airline food and have first class and coach sections.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1361547672301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:41:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361547985140-57</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester Strategy</Title><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361546967181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:29:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would be a dynamic alternative?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361547985140</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361548311765-58</Id><Topic><Title>3/1 Sequestration is Coming</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361539022476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 08:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Dokes, Its March 1 when we will see the sequester go in effect. You ask whose jobs will be lost. More jobs will be lost from this than you can count. Watch and see. Then blame the Republicans.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361548311765</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:51:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361548355062-59</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester Strategy</Title><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361546967181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:29:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He sounded like an idiot because he was proposing to modify the sequester to give the Obama administration more control of where to make the cuts in the budgets. Now, why would any thinking republican want to do that? The leftys would then make sure the cuts would do maximum damage to middle americans, and the republicans would be blamed rightfully for makeing the sequester cuts worse. You have to be really brain dead to think of stupid ideas like that and then advocate it on TV. Just let the sequester come! If you want to get spending under control then this is a good start, and the democrats came up with the idea, so shove it down their throats.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361548355062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:52:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361548647747-60</Id><Title>I love when I wake up in the morning and Obama falls in the polls lol</Title><Msg>Gallup daily tracking poll had Obama peaking the weak before Christmas with a 58% job approval rating. Today it is at 50%. In contrast Chris Christie just set a new record for job approval at 74%.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361548647747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:57:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361548665925-61</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester Strategy</Title><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361546967181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:29:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PS Joe, I thought you would be watching Fox news! C'mon you need to stay informed.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361548665925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:57:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361548847618-62</Id><Title>These are Boeings solutions....to the battery problem only</Title><Msg>Just get the darn planes in the air, even if we have to use band aids temporarily. If the FAA approves these measures, below, they will be as much liable as the BA, should the planes catch fire. Among the 787 solutions the company will propose: * Redesigning lithium-ion batteries to insulate the cells and prevent them from overheating. * Putting the batteries in a case designed to keep cells that may overheat from burning components or parts of the Dreamliner outside the compartment. * Venting battery compartments so any fumes caused by batteries that overheat will flow outside the plane. * Instituting new rules requiring Dreamliner crews to closely monitor the battery and power units for potential problems.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361548847618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:00:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361548954088-63</Id><Title>If your thinking of investing, just remember this one point.......</Title><Msg>The problems witht he Dreamliner haven't heet been priced into the stock. Use extreme caution when buying.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361548954088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:02:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361549857540-64</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sheesh. Infested is writing in goonese again. No wonder we are doomed.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1361549857540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:17:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361551123574-65</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mabey you and Krugman can get a clue. April 26, 2012 Are Republicans Genetically Inferior? By Alex Berezow &amp; Hank Campbell Are Republicans genetically inferior to Democrats? That might sound like a preposterous question, but essentially that is the thesis of Chris Mooney's latest book The Republican Brain: The Science of Why They Deny Science -- and Reality. In a recent article, Mooney summarizes his case. "[I]t often seems there are so many factually wrong claims on the political right that those who make them live in a different reality." He continues, "So here's an idea: Maybe they actually do. And maybe we can look to science itself...to help understand why it is that they view the world so differently." Translation: Republicans are stupid and there has to be a biological explanation for it. If Mooney's argument sounds familiar to you, it should. It's called "eugenics," and it was based on the belief that some humans are genetically inferior. Taken to an extreme, it encouraged people to selectively breed in order to improve the gene pool and eliminate those who the elites determined were unfit. It was rightfully dismissed decades ago, but this does not stop a modern-day science writer from resuscitating it and applying it to political adversaries. He isn't the first to invoke dubious scientific reasoning to support a pet political belief. Evolutionary psychologist Satoshi Kanazawa got there first when he tried to make the case that liberals are more intelligent. Progressives applauded him for his keen scientific insight until he also tried to claim humans evolved to find African-American men attractive but African-American women ugly. Thus, while it can produce useful insights, evolutionary psychology at times is highly suspect because it can also be easily influenced by researcher bias. Mooney's book is largely built upon data that is vulnerable to manipulation. For instance, the field of neuroscience is in its infancy and is just now beginning to be understood. That doesn't prevent Mooney from using it to confidently paint a dubious narrative about "neuropolitics." Evolutionary biologist Jerry Coyne dismantled Mooney's claims, asserting that he has drawn "unwarranted conclusions" based upon flawed logic and an incomplete understanding of evolution. Also, take a look again at the book's title (The Republican Brain) and pause to consider our cultural double standard that allows a book with that title to be published. How would people respond if the word "Republican" was replaced with "African-American"? Or if the book tried to explain why women denied reality? There would be outrage and accusations of racism or sexism. Yet, it is socially acceptable to make similar denigrating remarks about Republicans. None of this is to say that there isn't a grain of truth to what Mooney asserts. Because our genes influence everything -- from brain size to gender differences -- it is probable that genetics plays some role in our thought processes and therefore political beliefs. But, the environment plays just as big, if not a bigger role. Mooney doesn't frame it that way. The introduction to his book details how misguided he believes Republicans are and then offers "science" as an explanation. Sorry, Republicans. You believe dumb things because biology made you that way. As climate policy analyst Roger Pielke, Jr. wryly commented, perhaps science will find a cure for this disease soon-to-be-named "Republicanism." Mooney is not a scientist, and hence, he can conduct scientific malpractice with impunity. As a journalist who has mastered the dark art of framing, he distorts science in order to fit a preconceived narrative that he wants to tell. You can do it too, sort of like a home science framing experiment. Here's how: Because liberals might have a larger anterior cingulate cortex -- a brain region linked to "uncertainty" -- perhaps this explains why Democrats historically run discombobulated campaigns. Is that an absurd argument? Sure. But Mooney advances those kinds of arguments about Republicans because he's a loyal combatant for Team Blue. This is not science. This is what happens when partisans hijack science. Mooney has become something of a national spokesperson for American scientists. The National Science Foundation, a recipient of your tax dollars, even had him teach a seminar to academics about how to communicate science to the public. Given his long record of political partisanship, one wonders if part of the lesson plan involved how to insult Republicans. Is a person who engages in this sort of "outreach" a good spokesperson for all scientists? Mooney claims to be a public defender of science. In reality, science may need defending from people like him.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361551123574</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:38:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361551175654-66</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361551175654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:39:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361551399839-67</Id><Topic><Title>Great Moments of Liberal Bigotry</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361547897352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A great democrat was Byrd....extolled the virtues of the Democrat Party perfectly.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361551399839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:43:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361551522624-68</Id><Topic><Title>More Great Moments of Liberal Bigotry</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361548346201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:52:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Yes, those are the get Democrat champions against bigotry.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361551522624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:45:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361551824764-69</Id><Topic><Title>Even More Great Moments of Liberal Bigotry</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361548454141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:54:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Himmmmm......makes you wonder why liberals are such bigots when it comes to race.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361551824764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:50:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361552006090-70</Id><Topic><Title>Here's Bill Clinton the Bigot</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361549106282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:05:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary is quite a bigot too. It seem she doesn't like the people that live in Israel or their relatives.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361552006090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:53:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361552386328-71</Id><Topic><Title>When you are Forced to Work 4 Months of the Year for the Gubmit.......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361545748336</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:09:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent point hope4......no matter how you clean it up and no matter how you dress it up in new phrases and definitions when you force one person to save the needs of another, it is a form of slavery. You are plundering the labor and property of someone. It different from throwing money in a pot that everyone gets to benefit from.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361552386328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:59:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361552480071-72</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it scientific to teach that something can come from nothing?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361552480071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:01:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361552972680-73</Id><Title>Whoa: Columbine Survivor Pens Powerful Letter to Obama on Gun Rights</Title><Msg>The Left routinely ascribes absolute moral authority to grieving victims in furtherance of their political agenda. Their agitprop is often manipulative and exploitive, but it works. Appeals to facts and reason aren't enough anymore; persuading the public increasingly requires emotional appeals. Even if they find it inherently unpalatable, conservatives must promote people whose personal stories offer counter-narratives to liberals' tragic parade of victimhood. Katie highlighted one such case earlier this week, and now The Blaze has another. This open letter is a must-read -- not only for the case it lays out, but because of its author's personal history (click through for the full, unedited missive): Mr. President, As a student who was shot and wounded during the Columbine massacre, I have a few thoughts on the current gun debate. In regards to your gun control initiatives: Ban on Military-Style Assault Weapons The evidence is very clear pertaining to the inadequacies of the assault weapons ban. It had little to no effect when it was in place from 1994 until 2004. It was during this time that I personally witnessed two fellow students murder twelve of my classmates and one teacher. The assault weapons ban did not deter these two murderers, nor did the other thirty-something laws that they broke. Gun ownership is at an all time high. And although tragedies like Columbine and Newtown are exploited by ideologues and special-interest lobbying groups, crime is at an all time low. The people have spoken. Gun store shelves have been emptied. Gun shows are breaking attendance records. Gun manufacturers are sold out and back ordered. Shortages on ammo and firearms are countrywide. The American people have spoken and are telling you that our Second Amendment shall not be infringed. 10-Round Limit for Magazines Virginia Tech was the site of the deadliest school shooting in U.S. history. Seung-Hui Cho used two of the smallest caliber hand guns manufactured and a handful of ten round magazines. There are no substantial facts that prove that limited magazines would make any difference at all. Second, this is just another law that endangers law-abiding citizens. I’ve heard you ask, “why does someone need 30 bullets to kill a deer?” Let me ask you this: Why would you prefer criminals to have the ability to out-gun law-abiding citizens? Under this policy, criminals will still have their 30-round magazines, but the average American will not. Whose side are you on? Lastly, when did they government get into the business of regulating “needs?” This is yet another example of government overreaching and straying from its intended purpose. Selling to Criminals Mr. President, these are your words: “And finally, Congress needs to help, rather than hinder, law enforcement as it does its job. We should get tougher on people who buy guns with the express purpose of turning around and selling them to criminals. And we should severely punish anybody who helps them do this.” Why don’t we start with Eric Holder and thoroughly investigate the Fast and Furious program? Furthermore, the vast majority of these mass murderers bought their weapons legally and jumped through all the hoops — because they were determined to murder. Adding more hoops and red tape will not stop these types of people. It doesn’t now — so what makes you think it will in the future? Criminals who cannot buy guns legally just resort to the black market. Criminals and murderers will always find a way... Mr. President, do the right thing, restore freedom, and save lives. Show the American people that you stand with them and not with thugs and criminals. Respectfully, Severely Concerned Citizen, Evan M. Todd</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361552972680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:09:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361553060310-74</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul Krugman? And you don't get the point here? Krugman is a proud socialist...not only ugly looking, but ugly to listen to. A repulsive individual that is an anti-capitalist, anti-American. The leftist know that Rubio is the threat to their power. Communist ?? ..the guy Obama appointed to a key position then had to remove him because people found out he was a communist, and is now back working for Obama...sent a memo to the DNC saying "beware of Marco Rubio, and that he is a threat to our power." Leftist interviewers set him up with a question like the age of the earth, that is a no win answer, and the leftist interviewer knows that. Rubio needs to just tell them politely to fukoff.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361553060310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:11:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361553721853-75</Id><Topic><Title>Boo Hoo: MSNBC Hosts Are “Sad” Jesse Jackson Jr. Got Caught</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361553386559</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:16:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't I tell you that liberals stand by their crooks? Jackson Jr.'s wife was caught for tax evasion as well., and could do time. Liberals can sob over her corruption as well.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361553721853</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:22:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361553800146-76</Id><Title>Obama's "Pay to Play"</Title><Msg>According to Common Cause, the President is considering a plan to hold in-person meetings four times yearly with those who raise $500,000 or more for his lobbying group, Organizing for America. It doesn't take a genius to understand that this is simply a pay-to-play plan. If you are willing to pony up half a million or more, you, too, can have a sit-down with the world's most powerful man every three months (presumably, the President will make time for you between vacations, rounds of golf, and scaring the country). Of course, this step -- if taken -- would merely formalize a comfortable little arrangement that's already in place: Among donors [to the Obama 2008 campaign effort] who gave $30,000 or less, about 20 percent visited the White House, according to a New York Times analysis that matched names in the visitor logs with donor records. But among those who donated $100,000 or more, the figure rises to about 75 percent. Approximately two-thirds of the president’s top fund-raisers in the 2008 campaign visited the White House at least once, some of them numerous times. . . . Some of the donors had no previous record of giving to the president or his party, or of making donations of such magnitude, so their gifts, sometimes given in close proximity to meetings, raise questions about whether they came with expectations of access or were expressions of gratitude. Really? They "raise questions"? I think not -- the answer is clear. CL</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361553800146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:23:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361553911879-77</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a joke. You joined the libdems because you supported their bogus theory that man has caused global warming?!! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA Nothin but the scientific facts for ol techpath. HAHAHA</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361553911879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:25:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361554848012-78</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corned _beef_dud is obviously a big supporter of eugenics that Krugman's buddy Chris Mooney is endorsing. CBDud probably thinks the world is a far better place will all the aborted Black babies that have been aborted because it will save the planet. What an idiot.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361554848012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:40:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361554988926-79</Id><Title>Remember when big planes had 4 engines?</Title><Msg>Now there are only 2....in the name of cost savings and profit. The risk is on passengers not. Tells you a lot about the airplane manufacturers and what they think of public safety. Among the many unanswered questions is how the 787 battery problems will affect Boeing's effort to win FAA permission for the planes to make flights that venture further from the nearest airport, such as those that travel over wide expanses of ocean. The FAA has tighter requirements for such flights in twin-engine planes because it wants to make sure the plane can keep flying if it loses an engine or encounters other problems far away from a safe landing.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361554988926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:43:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361555253707-80</Id><Title>Companies are dropping health coverage for spouses to cut costs</Title><Msg>Thanks a lot Obama and Democrats By denying coverage to spouses, employers not only save the annual premiums, but also the new fees that went into effect as part of the Affordable Care Act. This year, companies have to pay $1 or $2 “per life” covered on their plans, a sum that jumps to $65 in 2014. And health law guidelines proposed recently mandate coverage of employees’ dependent children (up to age 26), but husbands and wives are optional. “The question about whether it’s obligatory to cover the family of the employee is being thought through more than ever before,” says Helen Darling, president of the National Business Group on Health.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361555253707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:47:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361555519945-81</Id><Topic><Title>Companies are dropping health coverage for spouses to cut costs</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361555253707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:47:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL - your post illustrates that corporations are greedy and will screw their employees every chance they get to line their own pocket. If you belonged to a union, things like that wouldn't happen.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1361555519945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:51:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361555601851-82</Id><Topic><Title>If your thinking of investing, just remember this one point.......</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361548954088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 11:02:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In an efficient market, everything is reflected in the price.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1361555601851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:53:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361555745650-83</Id><Topic><Title>Companies are dropping health coverage for spouses to cut costs</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1361555253707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:47:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad union membership in companies keeps going down.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1361555745650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:55:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361556161993-84</Id><Title>Paul Krugman embaces Hitler and eugenics</Title><Msg>What is Krugman thinking? Is he lamenting that Hitler didn't do a better job and missed his anscestors? Krugman had to have known that Chris Mooney is the modern day peddler of eugenics. What a #$%$ moron Krugman is. Even funnier are the clowns here that march goosestep lockstep with Krugman and Mooney. Either they don't read or they embrace eugenics. Do you clowns greet each other with Heil Krugman!</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361556161993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:02:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361556495339-85</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Krugman embaces Hitler and eugenics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361556161993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:02:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I forgot to mention that Krugman's insanity can be found at corn_beef_ dude's post titled 'Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban'.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361556495339</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:08:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361557021992-86</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361556286915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:04:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You back racism and eugenics. What a fool.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361557021992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:17:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361557118203-87</Id><Title>787 will not not fly( at best) , until April, how are those deliveries working for you now ?</Title><Msg>Boeing proposing long-term fix for 787 batteries, but planes unlikely to fly before April The plan will require testing and partially recertifying the safety of the plane's batteries, said the officials, who spoke on condition of anonymity because they weren't authorized to speak publicly. The testing and recertification will take time, with engineers currently estimating completion sometime in April, they said. Boeing, the FAA and the National Transportation Safety Board still have not identified the root cause of a Jan. 7 fire Among the many unanswered questions is how the 787 battery problems will affect Boeing's effort to win FAA permission for the planes to make flights that venture further from the nearest airport, such as those that travel over wide expanses of ocean. The FAA has tighter requirements for such flights in twin-engine planes because it wants to make sure the plane can keep flying if it loses an engine or encounters other problems far away from a safe landing. Until it was grounded, the 787 could fly up to three hours away from the nearest airport</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361557118203</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:18:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361557157620-88</Id><Title>FAA Audit of 787</Title><Msg>ANA (or JAL?) found the main battery miswired recently. Hopefully the FAA will determine the cause sooner than later. Their investigation of the electrical system started about a month and a half ago. The audit progress most likely will be part of the decision process on whether the proposed battery fix being presented today will be accepted. "WASHINGTON – In light of a series of recent events, the FAA will conduct a comprehensive review of the Boeing 787 critical systems, including the design, manufacture and assembly. The purpose of the review is to validate the work conducted during the certification process and further ensure that the aircraft meets the FAA’s high level of safety. “The safety of the traveling public is our top priority,” said U.S. Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood. “This review will help us look at the root causes and do everything we can to safeguard against similar events in the future.” A team of FAA and Boeing engineers and inspectors will conduct this joint review, with an emphasis on the aircraft’s electrical power and distribution system. The review will also examine how the electrical and mechanical systems interact with each other. "</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361557157620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:19:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361557230544-89</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Liberals, about that minimum Wage.......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361557065982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:17:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I gave them a simple percentage math problem, and none of them could provide an answer. Who dresses these mental midgets in the morning?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361557230544</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:20:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361557504115-90</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Gets Economic Advice from Al Sharpton</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361556219752</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:03:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHAHA Obama is screwing the middle class. Give him time, and he will eliminate the middle class. Al Sharpton? Van Jones, the communist has been an economic advisor of BO's might as well meet with Al Sharpton. So far, so good...23,000,000 folks without a full time job, 46,000,000 on food stamps, and now the economy is turning back south again with taxes rising, and gas prices up, up and away again.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361557504115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:25:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361557997228-91</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To reduce the deficit in a weak economy, new taxes on high-income Americans are a matter of necessity and fairness; they are also a necessary precondition to what in time will have to be tax increases on the middle class.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1361557997228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:33:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361558026740-92</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stated perfectly.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1361558026740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:33:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361558372271-93</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when big planes had 4 engines?</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361554988926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:43:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was 2 reasons they had 4, 1 for big planes they did not have engines powerfull enought to fly a large plane on 1 engine, today that is not an issue, 2 engine reliablity has increased drasticly, and failures one reaching cruse level are few and far between. Highest reason for engine failure these days is bird strikes, and if you hit a big flock of birds 2 or 4 engines you are in deep trouble, but I think a bigger engine will likely hold up better than a smaller 1 for the same size bird ingested, as that is logical.</Msg><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1361558372271</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:39:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361558903999-94</Id><Topic><Title>Now That We've Established That Nobody is Listening to Conservatives....</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361558421944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:40:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heil Hoozdik! No matter how much you shake kick or goose step, you are a loser. "The theory of output as a whole, which is what The General Theory of Employment, Interest and Money purports to provide, is much more easily adapted to the conditions of a totalitarian state." John Maynard Keynes</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361558903999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361558935536-95</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when big planes had 4 engines?</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361554988926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:43:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps. But more is better in my eyes, as you at last have a backup. Very difficult to maneuver a plane to the ground with one engine. But you're missing the point...... it's all done for cost savings...at your expense. Remember a few years back, when the airlines tried to get on one pilot to fly the big birds? They said a co-pilot wasn't necessary. This goes to the same point.....cost savings at your expense. Yes, you may be right.........dead right.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361558935536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:48:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361559204945-96</Id><Title>SPEEA</Title><Msg>The techs could absolutely shut down commercial airplane production if they chose to go on strike. Let's start with the fabrication centers for for major components of the airplanes (Portland, Auburn, Frederickson). Those sites are heavily run by techs. Calibration and metrology of the various tools must be performed by individuals certified for those tasks. Those are techs. MRSA Planners (virtually all of them Techs) – When an NCR needs disposition, who writes the rework plans? Manufacturing Engineering Planners (virtually all of them Techs) – When a drawing needs to be released, who signs the M-note? When a drawing does get released, who creates the CAPP plans or the IP? Industrial Engineering (Virtually all of them Techs) – When an installation plan needs to be completed or an assembly needs to be fabricated, who schedules the job in the shop? Change Board (Virtually all of them Techs) - When a Rapid Revision or a mandatory/urgent PRR needs to be scheduled, to catch an airplane out on the field, who makes it happen? Service Bulletin Engineering (Many of them Techs) – When one of our customers has an airplane grounded or about to be grounded because of an Airworthiness Directive, who performs the mechanics of sending the Service Bulletin out to the customer? The issue isn't the number of people, it's their relative importance at key junctures of the production system. Boeing's commercial airplane production is utterly dependent upon the techs. The goal now is to survey the techs and find out what would get the group to vote yes on a contract offer....and then go to the table to try and achieve that. Ray -- Ray Goforth Executive Director SPEEA / IFPTE Local 2001</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1361559204945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:53:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361559365377-97</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1361559204945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:53:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point. A wheel is only good if all its spokes are in place.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361559365377</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361559884818-98</Id><Topic><Title>Now That We've Established That Nobody is Listening to Conservatives....</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361558421944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:40:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Keynes was not just an economist. Between 1937 and 1944 he served as the head of the Eugenics Society and once called eugenics ”the most important, significant and, I would add, genuine branch of sociology which exists.” And Keynes, we should add, understood that economics was a branch of sociology. So let’s be clear: Keynes thought eugenics was more important, more significant, and more genuine than economics." Eugenics — or the control of reproduction — is a very old idea. I t's clear now that Krugman, who you admire, embraces the concepts of aggregate and eugenics too thanks to corn_beef_dude's enlightening post on Krugman. "John Holdren, Obama's Science Czar, says: Forced abortions and mass sterilization needed to save the planet" Why would Obama be aligned with these people if he didn't have the same belief system? Why would you support this? History is littered with clowns like this many of which end up killing millions of people. Why do you support these people that are so devoid of any humanity?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361559884818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:04:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361560448798-99</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corned_beef_hooz thanks for the Krugman article it was very enlightening. It is nice to finally get information that is useful from a mindless fanatic.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361560448798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:14:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361560498519-100</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't fist bump yourself too hard there Hooz_beef. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361560498519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:14:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361560920532-101</Id><Title>Obama Care outrage...Yeah..get ready ...YEAH..Obama really does care</Title><Msg>Obama Care outrage THIS should be read by everyone, especially important to those over 75. If you are younger, then it applies to your parents. Your hospital Medicare admittance has just changed under Obama Care. You must be admitted by your primary Physician in order for Medicare to pay for it! If you are admitted by an emergency room doctor it is treated as outpatient care where hospital costs are not covered. This is only the tip of the iceberg for Obama Care. Just wait to see what happens in 2013 &amp; 2014! At age 72, today, I went to the Dr. For my monthly B12 shot that I have been getting for a number of years. The nurse came and got me, got out the needle filled and ready to go then looked at the computer and got very quiet and asked if I was prepared to pay for it. I said no that my insurance takes care of it. She said, that Medicare had turned it down and went to talk to my Dr. About it. 15 minutes later she came back and said, she was sorry but they had tried every-thing they could but Medicare is beginning to turn many things down for seniors because of the projected Obama Care coming in. She was brushing at tears and said, "Some day they too will get old", I am so very sorry!! Please for the sake of many good people, please... Pass this on. We all need to be informed. YOU ARE NOT GOING TO LIKE THIS... At age 76 when you most need it, you are not eligible for cancer treatment Page 272 What Nancy Pelosi didn't want us to know until after the healthcare bill was passed. Remember she said, "We have to pass the Bill so that we can see what's in it." Well, here it is. Obama Care Highlighted by Page Number THE CARE BILL HB 3200 JUDGE KITHIL IS THE 2ND OFFICIAL WHO HAS OUTLINED THESE PARTS OF THE CARE BILL. Judge Kithil of Marble Falls , TX - highlighted the most egregious pages of HB3200 Please read this....... Especially the reference to pages 58 &amp; 59 JUDGE KITHIL wrote: Page 50/section 152: The bill will provide insurance to all non-U.S. Residents, even if they are here illegally. Page 58 and 59: The government will have real-time access to an individual's bank account and will have the authority to make electronic fund transfers from those accounts. Page 65/section 164: The plan will be subsidized (by the government) for all union members, union retirees and for community organizations (such as the Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now - ACORN).Page 203/line 14-15: The tax imposed under this section will not be treated as a tax. (How could anybody in their right mind come up with that?) Page 241 and 253: Doctors will all be paid the same regardless of specialty, and the government will set all doctors' fees. Page 272. Section 1145: Cancer hospital will ration care according to the patient's age. Page 317 and 321: The government will impose a prohibition on hospital expansion; however, communities may petition for an exception. Page 425, line 4-12: The government mandates advance-care planning consultations. Those on Social Security will be required to attend an "end-of-life planning" seminar every five years. (Death counseling..) Page 429, line 13-25: The government will specify which doctors can write an end-of-life order. HAD ENOUGH???? Judge Kithil then goes on to identify: "Finally, it is specifically stated that this bill will not apply to members of Congress.Honorable David Kithil of Marble Falls , Texas All of the above should give you the ammo you need to oppose Obamacare. Please send this information on to all of your email contacts.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361560920532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:22:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361561148762-102</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when big planes had 4 engines?</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361554988926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:43:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a lot easer to fly a 2 engine plane on one that it is to fly a 4 engine plane with 2 out on the same wing, that is if it can even be done. Also with the computerized flight control systems I see no reason they can't automatically compensate for a failed engine so the pilot doesn't have to fight against the asymmetrical thrust. As for the single pilot Idea, that didn't fly because there was no backup, and hence the FAA shot it down. That is akin to me building a single engine 150 passenger plane using just ONE engine, no reason it couldn't work or fly, but if you are lucky the FAA might approve it for freight only use, because there is no backup. Now I like added redundancy too, but there is a point where costs to benefit go way out of proportion. If the old engines had a MTF of 10k hours, and the new ones have a MTF of 50k hours, a plane with 2 of the new engines would have a MTF of engine failure of 25k flying hours. A 4 engine plane with the old engines would have a MTF of engine failure of just 2,500 hours. On the other hand one with 2 of the older engines would have a MTF of engine failure of 5k flying hours, still a 5th of a new plane with 2 engines. Also the chance of both of the newer engines failing in flight is now astronomically low, which is why the FAA allowed switching to 2 engines on large airplanes. Yes there is a cost savings too, lower plane cost, lower maintenance cost, and lower fuel consumption, but the risk factor for this saving is now far lower than that it was for the older 4 engine planes.</Msg><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1361561148762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:25:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361561279437-103</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS You are talking about a .62% cut in spending for this year. And that is after a rise in govt spending for this year! If Obama doesn't like where the cuts are coming from, then have him roll up his sociialist sleeves, and start cutting where he wants to cut! The ball is in his big spending court.! Tax payers have had enough. Raising taxes does not increase tax revenues anyway. GW BUSH cut taxes, grew the economy, and tax revenues went through the roof. You need to take a basic Econ 101 course, then get back with me.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361561279437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:27:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361562503727-104</Id><Title>Feb. delivery status</Title><Msg>As of noon today, BA has delivered 20 planes in February. 16 737's. 1 767. 3 777's. They do have a number of planes which have taken first flights including a number of 747's. But these numbers are well below where they should be even without any 787 deliveries. It could be simply a customer delivery date request driving the number.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1361562503727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361562570958-105</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's that working out in Greece and France? Take that Pravda paper from New York, roll it up, and shove it up your #$%$ where it belongs. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361562570958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:49:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361563000633-106</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, ali, a news flash. Nobody really cares what you think. You're a wannabee who is incredibly ignorant and never posts anything of value. So keep on posting. You can't really harm anything because you're tilting at windmills.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1361563000633</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:56:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361563273991-107</Id><Title>Double talk by Boeing.....no temp. fix and NOT abandoning Lithium Batteries</Title><Msg>The following susre sounds like a temporary fix to me! Boeing 787 battery fix proposal to FAA not temporary fix: sources WASHINGTON/SEATTLE (Reuters) - Boeing Co's (BA) proposal for preventing battery problems that have grounded its entire fleet of 50 787 Dreamliners is not a temporary stop-gap measure aimed at getting the airplanes flying again, three sources familiar with the plan said. The proposal includes insulation between the cells of the battery and a stronger, stainless steel box with a venting tube to contain a fire and expel flames outside the aircraft should a battery catch fire again, the sources said. Boeing will not propose abandoning lithium-ion batteries, however, and is not working on a backup or longer-term fix, the sources said.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361563273991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:01:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361563305926-108</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when big planes had 4 engines?</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361554988926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:43:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Remember a few years back, when the airlines tried to get on one pilot to fly the big birds? They said a co-pilot wasn't necessary. wrong- it was a few decades ago re dropping the flight engineer. The first few 767 were planned for 3 in cockpit- but changed to two</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361563305926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:01:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361563353607-109</Id><Topic><Title>Now That We've Established That Nobody is Listening to Conservatives....</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361558421944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:40:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Taking back the house is a strong possibility especially with folks like aLi iNfEstEd continuously but unwittingly campaigning.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1361563353607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:02:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361563560233-110</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Krugman embaces Hitler and eugenics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361556161993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:02:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another simple falsehood by aLi. Also written in stupidese.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1361563560233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:06:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361563685950-111</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you don't care you wouldn't respond. See how you lie to yourself? You're like a moth to a candle and corned_beef_hooz is worried about Republican brains when he has the brain of potted plant. Now get back to goose stepping with Hooz. Shake, kick, goosestep cha cha cha.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361563685950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:08:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361564045569-112</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Krugman embaces Hitler and eugenics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361556161993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:02:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm spot on and the truth hurts. Did you read my comment on John Meynard Keynes being the head of the Eugenics Society between 1937 and 1944 and calling eugenics ”the most important, significant and, I would add, genuine branch of sociology which exists.” Krugman is outed Keynes is outed your outed. I can understand why you're in denial.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361564045569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:14:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361564196116-113</Id><Topic><Title>Why Taxes Have to Go Up</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1361530670285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 05:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bo created the weak economy you braindead! He spent $800,000,000 dollars of workin peoples money INCREASING the size of govt!. 25% increase in two years. Now he can reduce it by t hat much, and a whole lot more! Then he had the nerve to even admit that it was a waste, and did nothing to grow the economy.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361564196116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:16:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361564197837-114</Id><Topic><Title>Now That We've Established That Nobody is Listening to Conservatives....</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361558421944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:40:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You could take back a crack house for Obama. He would love that and You would to shrub.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361564197837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:16:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361564741067-115</Id><Topic><Title>Now That We've Established That Nobody is Listening to Conservatives....</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361558421944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:40:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man, you got that right.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1361564741067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:25:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361565080965-116</Id><Title>You aliases are like the BORG</Title><Msg>You're all the same collectivist, mindless, Obama turd polishers. I swear you guys must get tweets from the mother BORG Cube and then hit the Bong Board together with Obama propaganda. It's really quite hilarious and so much fun to read the dedicated idiocy.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361565080965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:31:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361567739026-117</Id><Title>The Genius of the Democrat Voter -- Beyond Stunning !</Title><Msg>The letter was originally published in the Carteret County News-Times on Jan. 23. Beaufort, N.C. Jan. 17, 2013 TO THE EDITOR: Republicans and “so-called” conservatives are at it again. They are claiming that the Constitution gives people the right to have guns without the permission of the government. If that were true, then how could New York and Chicago have laws against it? We Democrats are sick and tired of Republicans constantly using the Constitution to cover up their true plans, which are to make us all afraid of everyone else. Our great president came from a civilized part of the country where there is strict gun control, and he is only trying to bring the benefits of that more modern way of living to the rest of us. I don’t know the exact statistics, but I’m quite certain that Chicago is a lot safer that Morehead City, when it comes to gun violence. But do Republicans and conservatives listen to the voice of reason? No, of course not. All they want to do is whine and complain about how gun control and wealth redistribution violate the Constitution, as if the Constitution were all that great, anyway. There are a lot of things that need to be changed about the Constitution, I’d say, and President Obama needs to change it. The Republicans are just trying to stand in the way, because the president is black. They even dared to question whether he was born in this country. I think all this demonstrates that the Constitution needs to be amended when it comes to the qualifications for being president. Right now, it says that a person has to be 35 years old and be a natural born citizen. Well, that is obviously unfair because there are a great many otherwise qualified people who cannot run for president because their mothers had to have a C-section. But because the Constitution was written a hundred years ago, nobody even thought of the discrimination that would result from a doctor having to deliver a baby in this unnatural way. Now that we Democrats are in control of the government, that’s just one more thing we should change in our drive to make life fair. Please withhold my name because I don’t want to get crank calls. PROUD TO BE A DEMOCRAT</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1361567739026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:15:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361568331566-118</Id><Topic><Title>The Genius of the Democrat Voter -- Beyond Stunning !</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1361567739026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:15:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is genius compared to progressives hooz is polishin Obama turds here. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361568331566</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:25:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361568636648-119</Id><Title>Hold on for $80.00+</Title><Msg>Next week its in the cards and they should come to a conclusion with the fix because those a #$%$ elected thier by thier Cornies and and don't know jack#$%$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1361568636648</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:30:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361569308033-120</Id><Title>Ali infesto? when did you train with the Taliban??</Title><Msg>Dumb as you are I suppose you didn't even learn anything when you were over there in northern Pakistan</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361569308033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:41:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361570118493-121</Id><Topic><Title>Double talk by Boeing.....no temp. fix and NOT abandoning Lithium Batteries</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361563273991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When there is mention of insulation between the battery cells and pilot monitoring of individual cells, then they might as well just go on to the next step. Liquid cool the battery cells and have a software that takes overheating cells out of the loop. Of course, that's the Tesla method. It would be a little of an affront to buy aircraft technology from an auto maker but Tesla is a low-volume high-technology car maker and possibly similar to an aircraft maker.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1361570118493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:55:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361570138925-122</Id><Title>FAA, we won’t allow the 787 to return to commercial service</Title><Msg>Feb 22 (Reuters) - Boeing Co gave U.S. aviation regulators its plan to fix the volatile battery aboard its new 787 Dreamliner on Friday, even before investigators know what caused the batteries to overheat on two planes last month. Boeing will not propose abandoning the lithium-ion batteries, however, and is not working on a backup or longer-term fix for the problem that has grounded its entire fleet of 50 787 Dreamliners, three sources familiar with the plan said. "The safety of the flying public is our top priority and we won’t allow the 787 to return to commercial service until we’re confident that any proposed solution has addressed the battery failure risks," the FAA said in a statement Friday. So a fire contained in a box is a emergency landing requirement, may as well install a fireplace in the passenger cabin too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361570138925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:55:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361570472362-123</Id><Topic><Title>Double talk by Boeing.....no temp. fix and NOT abandoning Lithium Batteries</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361563273991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and a tesla can pull over to the curb in afire situation at 600 miles per hour and 30,000 feet you can jump from a 787 only one time or land in the water usually only one time</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361570472362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:01:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361571041385-124</Id><Title>how many revenue passengers have not been able to fly on the 787 since the grounding ?</Title><Msg>how many deliveries have been made on teh 787 sicne the grounding, will the increase in deliveries as planned to 7 and then 10 be met on time and on schedule , there is a user who likes to post rediculous delivery scedules he must be like a Boeing Board member it will fly in the board room, not int he real world</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571041385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:10:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571064185-125</Id><Topic><Title>Ali infesto? when did you train with the Taliban??</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361569308033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:41:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz and his aliases, are the goose stepping mindless fanatics that support Obama's terrorism killing innocent children in Pakistan. Are you ready to sign the petition for impeachment of Obama for war crimes or are you just another Obama lovin mindless fanatical goose stepper like Hooz and the aliases?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361571064185</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:11:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571308647-126</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA</Title><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1361559204945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:53:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that is right , like a 787 one missing technical team group not taking a take away contract can stop the whole program a simple striek wil ldemonstrate this to the Board Room boys who think the 787 will fly in the Board rooma nd they do not have to find and fix the cuase of the fire too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571308647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:15:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571448963-127</Id><Topic><Title>787 will not not fly( at best) , until April, how are those deliveries working for you now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361557118203</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:18:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the FAA has said not until the fire starter can be made safe with the 787 fly you can not fly safe with a fire on the plane</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571448963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:17:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571513742-128</Id><Topic><Title>787 = Ugo = Pinto = History</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1361546826338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 10:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>several other planes have killed the company, the 787 is in the race now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571513742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:18:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571606660-129</Id><Topic><Title>787 is junk and will be scrapped.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361536462425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 07:34:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the issues have been ongoing for 4 years now and getting worse, it is grounded for all the Boeing enthusiasts reality is a hard to understand</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571606660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571646552-130</Id><Topic><Title>how many revenue passengers have not been able to fly on the 787 since the grounding ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571041385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:10:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Figure 50 planes, 200 passengers per plane, 3 flights per day, and 35 days since gounding would be 50 x 200 x 3 x 35 = 1,050,000 revenue passengers. Probably more if you want to count the 787s not being delivered since the grounding.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1361571646552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:20:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571663407-131</Id><Topic><Title>Realistic Timeline for FAA Approval</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361478303628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:25:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best case is april</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571663407</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:21:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571714637-132</Id><Topic><Title>Stop the Fire from Spreadig is the Fix!?!?</Title><Username>beingtheonenow</Username><Timestamp>1361471220929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>parachutes for the passenger then eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571714637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:21:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571775053-133</Id><Topic><Title>a month to discover the electric lady is miswired ?hummmm</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376563426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:09:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dead right scary</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571775053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:22:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571830908-134</Id><Topic><Title>Poland's LOT suspends taking delivery of new Dreamliners</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376097250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:01:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>add united too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571830908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571869125-135</Id><Topic><Title>Stop the Fire from Spreadig is the Fix!?!?</Title><Username>beingtheonenow</Username><Timestamp>1361471220929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing is sure confident on the lithium batteries. If they do not come up with something that the FAA can approve, they are putting alot at stake "Boeing (BA) will not propose abandoning the lithium-ion batteries, however, and is not working on a backup or longer-term fix for the problem that has grounded its entire fleet of 50 787 Dreamliners, three sources familiar with the plan said."</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361571869125</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:24:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571919930-136</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Airworthiness Readiness Force will work !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361164990961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 00:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a friendly it is made by people who are following the money so yes sanity is not an issue it is greed</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571919930</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:25:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361571934006-137</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could lay out the facts but it would be a waste of my time. joedokes45 - ignore</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1361571934006</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:25:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361572302969-138</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Airworthiness Readiness Force will work !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361164990961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 00:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure- to keep it wet- route the toilet water to the box Thus we get to the old cliche - If you cant fix it P888 on it !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361572302969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:31:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361572428821-139</Id><Topic><Title>Double talk by Boeing.....no temp. fix and NOT abandoning Lithium Batteries</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361563273991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Telsa batteries don't explode and boeing batteries do! Boeing would be smart to buy lithium batteries from telsa,designed to have space between cells from the beginning!</Msg><Username>s3237fox</Username><Timestamp>1361572428821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:33:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361573140371-140</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Krugman embaces Hitler and eugenics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361556161993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:02:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stoopidese, goooonese, teabaggerese--all the same. They continue to campaign 24/7 and demonstrate the vapidity of the R party.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1361573140371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:45:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361573288266-141</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Care outrage...Yeah..get ready ...YEAH..Obama really does care</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361560920532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 14:22:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Three years after hoax status shown--a little too quick for Jack R.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1361573288266</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:48:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361573970298-142</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Airworthiness Readiness Force will work !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361164990961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 00:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The batteries will have a venting system, so that part will already be designed to keep the fumes out of the airplane</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361573970298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361574889526-143</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Krugman embaces Hitler and eugenics</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361556161993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 13:02:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a lost Communist? This is the BA board.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361574889526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 18:14:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361575663713-144</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I talk to climate scientists all the time and I would love to hear your facts and see how they stack up against the latest research. I hope you will actually provide peer reviewed papers and actual data from climate centers. Let's start with the 20N-20S HadAT data for the lower troposphere as it has just been updated to include 2012. Don't forget to adjust for Pinatubo and explain to me how CO2 grew by 33.4 PPM in the atmosphere but we have seen no increase in temperature anomalies for 17 years in light of Ben Santer's Paper indicating that 17 years of little to no warming increase in the LT is problematic. If you need me to hold your hand to help you find the papers and the data let me know but you made it seem like you were an expert.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361575663713</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 18:27:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361576108383-145</Id><Topic><Title>Realistic Timeline for FAA Approval</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361478303628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:25:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The FAA Agent that returns the B787 back to service will need big testicle fortitude. Wouldn't want to be him.</Msg><Username>try2try</Username><Timestamp>1361576108383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 18:35:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361578324110-146</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cherry picking, from the HadAT web site: It is important to note that significant uncertainty exists in radiosonde datasets reflecting the large number of choices available to researchers in their construction and the many heterogeneities in the data. To this end we strongly recommend that users consider, in addition to HadAT, the use of one or more of the following products to ensure their research results are robust. Currently, other radiosonde products of climate quality available from other centres (clicking on links takes you to external organisations) for bona fide research purposes are: Radiosonde Atmospheric Temperature Products for Assessing Climate (RATPAC) RAdiosonde OBservation COrrection using REanalyses (RAOBCORE) and Radiosonde Innovation Composite Homogenization (RICH) IUK (Iterative Universal Kriging) Radiosonde Analysis Project</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1361578324110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:12:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361578918231-147</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK that shows me you have never downloaded any real data from climate centers because they all have similar caveats. Also you missed the data from the other climate centers that was included. Multiple satellite readings and ballon readings from multiple climate centers is how they reduce error. However this IS the data that IPCC is using to determine forecasts into the year 2100 and if your saying you reject it then you reject the IPCC science . So if you reject the data are you not anti-science? Also if you reject the data please explain your version with your evidence.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361578918231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:21:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361579796255-148</Id><Title>What I learned about Obama Turd Polishers Today</Title><Msg>They make fun of Marco Rubio's scientific views using Paull Krugman who relies on Chris Mooney who believes in the junk science of eugenic. Eugenics is a popuar junk science of mass murderers like Adolph Hitler and Joseph Stalin so Krugman is in good company. I also learned that the people criticizing Marco Rubio, who doesn't seem to know #$%$ about climate science, don't know anything more about climate science than Rubio.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361579796255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:36:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361580413202-149</Id><Topic><Title>What I learned about Obama Turd Polishers Today</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361579796255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:36:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of these liberals that can't perform basic math at a 5th grade level, and who trust in the verbage spewed by Paul Krugman need to be sent to the recycle bin. If my dog looked like, and spewed the #$%$ that comes out of Paul Krugman's mouth, I'd shave his butt, and make him walk backwards.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361580413202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:46:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361580448793-150</Id><Topic><Title>What I learned about Obama Turd Polishers Today</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361579796255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:36:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you still haven't learned nobody cares.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1361580448793</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:47:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361580464347-151</Id><Topic><Title>What I learned about Obama Turd Polishers Today</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361579796255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:36:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama turd polishers who were screaming for Bush's impeachment also reinforced their hypocrisy as they stand still stand behind their mass murder and won't sign a petition to impeach president Obama the man that Cornell West called a 'war criminal'. This is hard for me to understand because I didn't want to impeach Bush and I don't want to impeach Obama either.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361580464347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:47:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361580470999-152</Id><Title>fear the rise of china</Title><Msg>largest army/airforce/navy by 2025 largest economy by 2015 plan to attack the ussr in 1978 willing to use nukes to regain taiwan want to revenge the rape of naking by japan wants to regain territory lost to russia wants to kick u.s out of asia wants to regain world power status denied by colonization</Msg><Username>garygirdhari</Username><Timestamp>1361580470999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:47:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361580690784-153</Id><Topic><Title>What I learned about Obama Turd Polishers Today</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361579796255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:36:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Karma why don't you give burger_barn a call and go smoke some crack with him. You strike meas someone who would find a soul mate in burger_barn.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361580690784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:51:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361581074076-154</Id><Title>Obama Turd Polisher Hooz Calls For Bush Impeachment</Title><Msg>A blast from the Best of Hooz circa 2007 Impeach George Bush to Stop War Lies, Deaths by sir_hoozdik_hertz • Jul 24, 2007 7:58 AM Flag Impeach George Bush to Stop War Lies, Deaths By Jimmy Breslin I am walking in Rosedale on this day early in the week while I wait for the funeral of Army soldier Le Ron Wilson, who died at age 18 in Iraq. He was 17 1/2 when he had his mother sign his enlistment papers at the Jamaica recruiting office. If she didn't, he told her, he would just wait for the months to his 18th birthday and go in anyway. He graduated from Thomas Edison High School at noon one day in May. He left right away for basic training. He came home in a box last weekend. He had a fast war. The war was there to take his life because George Bush started it with bold-faced lies. He got this lovely kid killed by lying. If Bush did this in Queens, he would be in court on Queens Boulevard on a murder charge. He did it in the White House, and it is appropriate, and mandatory for the good of the nation, that impeachment proceedings be started. You can't live with lies. You can't permit them to be passed on as if it is the thing to do. Yesterday, Bush didn't run the country for a couple of hours while he had a colonoscopy at the presidential retreat, Camp David. He came out of it all right. He should now take his good health and go home, quit a job he doesn't have a clue as to how to do. The other day, Bush said he couldn't understand why in the world would some people say that millions of Americans have no health insurance. "Why, all they have to do is go to the emergency room," he said. Said this with the smirk, the insolent smug, contemptuous way he speaks to citizens. People, particularly these politicians, these frightened beggars in suits, seem petrified about impeachment. It could wreck the country. Ridiculous. I've been around this business twice and we're all still here and no politician was even injured. Richard Nixon lied during a war and helped get some 58,500 Americans killed and many escaped by hanging onto helicopter skids. Nixon left peacefully. Mike Mansfield of Montana, the Democratic Senate majority leader, said on television that the Senate impeachment trial of Nixon would be televised and there would be no immunity. That meant Nixon would have to face the country under oath and if he lied he would go to prison. He knew he was finished as he heard this. Mansfield said no more. He got up and left. Barbara Walters, on the "Today" show, said, "He doesn't say very much, does he?" The second time the subject was Bill Clinton for illegal holding in the hallway. This time, we have dead bodies involved. Consider what is accomplished by the simple power of the word impeachment. If you read these broken-down news writers or terrified politicians claiming that an impeachment would leave the nation in pieces, don't give a moment to them. It opens with the appointing of an investigator to report to the House on evidence that calls for impeachment. He could bring witnesses forward. That would be all you'd need. Here in the impeachment proceedings against Richard Nixon came John Dean. His history shows how far down the honesty and honor of this country has gone. Dean was the White House counsel. Richard Nixon, at his worst, never told him not to appear or to remain silent in front of the Congress. Dean went on and did his best to fill prisons. After that came Alexander Butterfield, a nobody. All he had to say was that the White House had a taping system that caught all the conversations in the White House. Any of them not on tape were erased by a participant.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361581074076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:57:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361582275286-155</Id><Topic><Title>What I learned about Obama Turd Polishers Today</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361579796255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 19:36:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Super use of your time.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1361582275286</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:17:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361583371783-156</Id><Title>bagger turd polishers</Title><Msg>ali infested joedickhead etc are hell bent to polish Tbagger turds- and the minute somebody fires back at them they resort to their crybaby selves</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361583371783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:36:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361583517693-157</Id><Topic><Title>bagger turd polishers</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361583371783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:36:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad the USA doesn't practice eugenics- the gene pool in the Unite States wouldn't be so polluted what with the ali infestids running around loose</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361583517693</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:38:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361583620685-158</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Airworthiness Readiness Force will work !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361164990961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 00:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well they will have to have some sort of a check valve which only allows airflow in one direction- thru the case and out the jet pipe- exhaust Not too dificult but how will it work on the ground ? and continual airflow thru the battery can result in other problems like moisture, etc I know use excess bleed air ;PPP</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361583620685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:40:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361584125685-159</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Airworthiness Readiness Force will work !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361164990961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 00:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey - nobody gives a sh.t- so fly airbus</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361584125685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:48:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361584328172-160</Id><Topic><Title>bagger turd polishers</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361583371783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:36:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take it you are a bagger turd polisher to - am I right</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361584328172</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:52:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361587230282-161</Id><Title>The BA BATTERY flamethrower</Title><Msg>Coming to an airport near you Another source, who is also familiar with the 787 investigation but not authorized to speak publicly, said a key challenge for Boeing would be to redesign the battery box so that it could truly contain a fire if one occurred. Despite Boeing's statements about containment being the plan for a battery issue from the start, the blue box that held the current lithium-ion battery was clearly "not designed to contain a fire," said the source. Another person familiar with the engineering work said the new box would be made of stainless steel nearly half an inch thick. It would be capable of containing an explosion, and would have a tube to vent smoke and flame outside the jet. However, the source said engineers have raised questions about the safety of venting flames outside the plane, especially if it is on the ground and being fueled. The effect could be something like a flamethrower, this person said. From http://news.yahoo.com/boeing-787-battery-fix-proposal-faa-not-temporary-194512893--finance.html Ya can't make this up !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587230282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:40:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361587413762-162</Id><Topic><Title>The BA BATTERY flamethrower</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587230282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And look at this IF true - what do you think two such boxes will weigh ? Another person familiar with the engineering work said the new box would be made of stainless steel nearly half an inch thick. It would be capable of containing an explosion, and would have a tube to vent smoke and flame outside the jet. +++++ So now we look up a definition of b o m b Instead of Boob on board - wde will have a b o m b on board And if it goes off on the tarmac ?? Move on move on - nothing to see move on</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587413762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:43:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361587498556-163</Id><Title>cash</Title><Msg>How much cash is all this grounding /new batterys/non deliversy of the planes / the airlines will want to be paided for not being able to use their planes it going to add up</Msg><Username>averyed510</Username><Timestamp>1361587498556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361588199783-164</Id><Topic><Title>The BA BATTERY flamethrower</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587230282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are those big round oval things that hang off the wings?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1361588199783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:56:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361588703047-165</Id><Topic><Title>The BA BATTERY flamethrower</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587230282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they work by sucking in the air from in front- heating it- and pushing it out the back Just a more deluxe version of the new improved Boeing battery box Of course IF one uses a good nozzle and properly directs the hot air one of tow or three things happen 1) a jet effect like the big tubes 2) laminar flow reducing drag ( aka p-51 oil cooler ) and improving performance 3) you know you are near a corner office in chicago !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361588703047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:05:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361589103689-166</Id><Title>So what part of this “Quick”, “Standard”, “Compatible” fix seems like a good idea?</Title><Msg>In order to meet the “requirements”, the existing cell structure will be put in an explosion proof box. The only way that flame and fumes can leave the box is out the vent pipe. The vent pipe must be flame and fume proof and must not endanger anything that is in proximity. It must exit the plane somewhere. If you exit the plane on the side you have to deal with an unknown flow rate and pressure. You might put a standoff vent so that the flaming debris does not streak down the side of the plane if it is in flight. That would seem to be a good idea if the failure takes place on the ground because the problem will shoot away from the plane and land on something else. Oh, wait, there is a strong wind blowing directly into the side of the plane and a slow dribble of fire is cruising down the side of the beautiful plastic barrel. Maybe we should put it straight down on the bottom of the fuselage. That would allow the flaming goo to fall straight down onto the tarmac into a puddle and the flame and fumes will evenly barbeque the bottom. But the flow might be slow so that the emissions will only dribble out of the hole where they will flare up and the heat will cause them to rise up onto the fuselage without falling to the ground. All this presupposes that a “keep out zone” will be instituted for any conceivable situation. We wouldn’t want a ramp hand to be engulfed with flaming battery vomit. So now the fire seems to have stopped. It is time to go in and put in the new battery. The battery is now in an explosion proof box. But is it strong enough to resist an explosion if there is no vent? The problem comes when you have to remove the box.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361589103689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:11:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361589391845-167</Id><Topic><Title>So what part of this “Quick”, “Standard”, “Compatible” fix seems like a good idea?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361589103689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:11:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats only part of the problem The BA fix now comes to light ( pun intended ) with a SS box and exhaust tubes This fix sounds like a rube goldberg machine( apologies to rube, even his machines worked while accomplishing nothing ) In normal use during charging, batteries get warm In normal use during providing power batteries get warm So we make an virtually airtight box – with some sort of power vents to the outside and insulate the hell out of it – and ditto between cells Since there seems to be no discussion of cooling- and we have a open (?) exhaust system ?? what happens to the normal heat generated in use ? What happens when you put your pizza in an insulated box for delivery ? IT STAYS HOT ! Better yet- lets say this mess is approved – I’m sure the power point rangers have some purrty pic-tures well the plane lands . And the battery gets used for braking and running lights and fuel doors and . . . Its still hot from the beginning of the trip for starting engines- and the FAST recharge. Now it gets a bit hotter ! What next ? Train the ground crews – STAND CLEAR OF BATTERY EXHAUST TUBES So 10 minutes later- the automatic ejection system activates as the temperature reaches 500 degrees F and thermal runaway starts. Ejecting toxic gas and maybe sparks and portions of molten lithium all over the place – as on the fueling truck ! Ladies and gentleman- If you look out the windows on gate 66, you will be treated to the latest fireworks display OR Move on move on – nothing more to see here !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361589391845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:16:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361590279384-168</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you have never downloaded any real data... because they all have similar caveats" ??? Gotta love that logic. given that you acknowledge the caveats it's curious that you use cherry picking, not surprising since that is how the climate skeptic organizations supported by the oil industry and koch brothers are forced to use that approach. Yes, the HadAT data is used along with many others to form a composite view of the state of the earth and ALL of the peer reviewed publications indicate an aggregate warming. The latest, and one of the best, was published last year: Christiansen and Ljungqvist; Climate of the Past (8) : 765.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1361590279384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:31:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361590732666-169</Id><Topic><Title>So what part of this “Quick”, “Standard”, “Compatible” fix seems like a good idea?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361589103689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:11:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, at over 1000 degree's, thermal heat , that would be a well done pizza, I hope the bomb squad suit needed to remove the battery box from the plane can take the heat, and the guy can crawl around in the EE bay and lift a 70 pound batter with one hand too! BTW- and how is that guy going to flip a 70 pound battery overhead continuing pizza idea? if the 787 makes it to the ground, has the guy in the flame proof suit, figured out what to do with a non vented box, once removed from the external vents so he can carry the battery outside the plane, and will the box-battery then be a bomb at that point? The vented box has to be disconnected from the vent to remove it from the EE bay. The FAA indicated it won’t rush to get the Dreamliners back in the air despite the crisis that the grounding of the planes has brought to Boeing and its customers. “The safety of the flying public is our top priority and we won’t allow the 787 to return to commercial service until we’re confident that any proposed solution has addressed the battery failure risks,” said an FAA statement. , the 787 grounding has already lasted a day longer than the 1979 grounding of the DC-10 fleet, which was prompted by an air crash that killed 273 people. Boeing remains tight-lipped about its proposed fix, tight lipped and progress mean boeing better have some powerful lobby FBI connections , the fix is nothing but a cheap two bit failure on top of thecheap outsourced failure of a plane, more failure to come watch !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361590732666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:38:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361591165272-170</Id><Topic><Title>bagger turd polishers</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361583371783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:36:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the standard 'bagger routine. Throw bombs; no solutions; no compromise; no ideas; no constructive anything; cry. We are doomed until some Republicans tell the baggers to shove off and retake a once proud, effective party.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1361591165272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:46:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361591265443-171</Id><Topic><Title>Marco Rubio and the New American Taliban</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1353745795379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 03:29:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your observation on Mr. Dokes is correct. Preferred ignorance is a standard bagger mode. Somehow they think this is fun.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1361591265443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:47:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361591421545-172</Id><Topic><Title>Ali infesto? when did you train with the Taliban??</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361569308033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 16:41:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Taliban? Infested Ali? Naaah. Probably got kicked out for not being intelligent enough.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1361591421545</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:50:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361591446193-173</Id><Topic><Title>So what part of this “Quick”, “Standard”, “Compatible” fix seems like a good idea?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361589103689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:11:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...the fix is nothing but a cheap two bit failure on top of thecheap outsourced failure of a plane... Who came up with the with the cheap two bit failure fix?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1361591446193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:50:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361592067327-174</Id><Topic><Title>Realistic Timeline for FAA Approval</Title><Username>mikestarfish</Username><Timestamp>1361478303628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:25:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buckman2777, If your battery burns up it can have many or multiple causes and once damaged finding the fault is difficult. A defective structural part, like the defective 787 brake part is easy to find and fix, if your opinion was valid the 787 would be flying right now!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361592067327</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:01:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361592170469-175</Id><Topic><Title>So what part of this “Quick”, “Standard”, “Compatible” fix seems like a good idea?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361589103689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:11:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeveritas your right the 33 billion dollar and counting over cost on the 787 fix is still going on your right ! thanks good point !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361592170469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:02:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361592309627-176</Id><Topic><Title>Double talk by Boeing.....no temp. fix and NOT abandoning Lithium Batteries</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361563273991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 15:01:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>foxgang7878 the boeing plan is to ignore the battery fire and try to contain it, that has to end bad!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361592309627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:05:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361592459104-177</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Airworthiness Readiness Force will work !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361164990961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 00:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so the fire problem is to hide the fire in a box and install a big smoke stack so the people will not be harmed sounds like the ecology department needs to contact Boeing about pollution spills now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361592459104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:07:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361592620165-178</Id><Topic><Title>a month to discover the electric lady is miswired ?hummmm</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376563426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:09:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes they catch fire only one time in 10 million hours , oh wait , wait the MBA power point ranger made a math error, it is wrong they catch fire every 800 hours .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361592620165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:10:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361592930735-179</Id><Topic><Title>how many revenue passengers have not been able to fly on the 787 since the grounding ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361571041385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 17:10:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so how many passengers were not allowed to fly on the 787 due to grounding could I get a number in relations to how many passengers did fly on airbus planes and what is the relationship between airplane groundings of the 787 and the lack of deliveries on the Boeing bottom line any one? there is a user who just has to let us know about Boeing plane deliveries, so as long as he spends his time posting deliveries, could he post how many non deliveries of the 787 have occurred while since the 787 is grounded we need to know this information too</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361592930735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:15:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361593108662-180</Id><Topic><Title>So what part of this “Quick”, “Standard”, “Compatible” fix seems like a good idea?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361589103689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 22:11:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.Who came up with the with the cheap two bit failure fix? Hint - check the corner office in Chicago-</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361593108662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 23:18:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>