<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374033734665-1</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmermann only called 911 to report blk people as supicious</Title><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1373950325160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 00:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try some facts. The police were called over 400 times in a year to the peaceful and serene suburban mostly white Retreat at Twins Lakes</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1374033734665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374033910164-2</Id><Topic><Title>Documentarian says to Colbert: "You could be on Obamas Drone Kill list"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374021605264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:40:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another infowars cut &amp; past by spartadoofus. Sheesh.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1374033910164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:05:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374034134974-3</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmermann only called 911 to report blk people as supicious</Title><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1373950325160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 00:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He had been so looking forward to going to his junior prom, and he had already started talking about all the senior activities in high school,'' his mother, Sybrina Fulton, 46, said in a voice hollowed and somber. "He will never do any of those things.'' Martin would spend mornings at the high school — a roomy campus of cream buildings in Miami Gardens — and then go to George T. Baker Aviation School for the rest of the school day. Inspired by his uncle, Ronald Fulton, who had a brief career in aviation, Martin saw his future in planes. "He loved flying and working with his hands. Barrington Irving took him on his plane at the Opa-Locka Airport. He got a chance to sit in the cockpit and that did it for him,'' said Fulton, referring to the youngest person and first black person to pilot a plane around the world solo in 2007. "He wanted to be a pilot or work as a mechanic in aviation. He was mechanically inclined and could fix just about anything.'' Math was his favorite subject, according to one of his Carol City teachers, Ashley Gantt. She taught his sophomore year English honors class where the curriculum included works such as The Narrative of the Life of Frederick Douglas and Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Sometimes he would come to the second-period class looking exhausted. Gantt would call out his name. "I'm sorry, Ms. Gantt. I'm not asleep. I'm listening," he would reply, she said. He would often wear a hoodie at school — just like the one he was wearing the day he was killed in Sanford. Gantt said she never saw Martin behave aggressively or show disrespect. "He was just a sweet kid, she said. "He got A's and B's. If he received a C on an assignment, it was because he was just being a kid that day. He was very smart."</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1374034134974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374034808463-4</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman now free to blow those black kids away if they look suspicious</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1374032016278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup. That's eaxctly what 'Murica needs. lol It already skeres me that any of the RWNJ's posting even have access to a gun..letalone think the Z-man case allows them act as he did....</Msg><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1374034808463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:20:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374034906865-5</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sometimes skittles are just skittles.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1374034906865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374035393199-6</Id><Topic><Title>Justice For Trayvon</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1374006477166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:27:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet another right-fringer who can't read. I said the jury had rendered its verdict after the trial I felt was required, and it was time to let it go. Zipperman was found not guilty. The USA won nothing because the USA wasn't a party in the dispute (though that could change.) And you have correctly chosen your screen name -- except that possibly you have nothing to do with ba.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1374035393199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374035399698-7</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman now free to blow those black kids away if they look suspicious</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1374032016278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Z man did not blow away Trayvon because he looked suspicious. He blew him away cause Z was getting his head bashed in and he himself would have been killed....</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374035399698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374035422531-8</Id><Title>Even the Z-mans brother is a 'racist' RWNJ</Title><Msg>- Robert Zimmerman Jr., the brother of the man who shot and killed 17-year-old Trayvon Martin, apologized for his controversial and offensive tweets. In one, Zimmerman juxtaposed a photograph of Martin with one of 17-year-old De'Marquise Elkins, one of two teenagers charged with killing a baby in Georgia. Both Elkins and Martin appear to be flipping off the camera. "A picture speaks a thousand words. Any questions?" the tweet reads. In another tweet, Zimmerman writes: "Lib media shld ask if what these2 black teens did 2 a woman&amp;baby is the reason ppl think blacks mightB risky." Speaking on CNN's Piers Morgan Live on Wednesday night, he apologized for the messages, saying they weren't the "right thing to do." "I realize those were controversial and offensive and I did publicly apologize for them," he said. "I'm a human being. I'm being upfront about what I did. I made a mistake ...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1374035422531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374035530735-9</Id><Topic><Title>Former Teammate testifies in Court that the defendant in Court is NOT the Boston Bomber !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374022309944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:51:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet another case the Loon doesn't trust to the nation's justice system. He wants to be judge and jury RIGHT NOW...</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1374035530735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 00:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374037962298-10</Id><Topic><Title>Asiana grounds Boeing 777 in U.S. due to engine oil leak ReutersReuters – 18 minutes ago</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374023035028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:03:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you are saying would be more a reason to sell GE and not BA. Besides, one plane grounded with an oil leak out of 1,113 flying is no cause to sell any shares, GE or BA. The 777 has been in production since 1995. That's 18 years. You sound like another sucker who shorted the stock and got screwed when it went back up.</Msg><Username>logictheorist</Username><Timestamp>1374037962298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374038077471-11</Id><Topic><Title>Emergancy location transmiter fits with claim plane powered off.</Title><Username>send_this_pig_to_hell</Username><Timestamp>1373915726637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:15:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The plane could have been connected to ground power and still have all systems powered off.</Msg><Username>send_this_pig_to_hell</Username><Timestamp>1374038077471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374038260411-12</Id><Title>I wonder what the verdict would have been</Title><Msg>if Travon had survived his wound to tell a quite different version of the story.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038260411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374038706242-13</Id><Title>Dueling now legal in Florida</Title><Msg>after all, both of you were just standing your ground and the other guy moved for his weapon first.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038706242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374039389803-14</Id><Title>First Degree Murder Now Legal in Florida</Title><Msg>You may now follow, confront, provoke an altercation with and then draw your hidden handgun and shoot dead ANYONE who you can later feasibly claim made you fearful. Just be sure there are no other witnesses. However, this new right should not be abused. Black boys should be at least 13 years old to be legal targets. God help US all.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374039389803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374041502742-15</Id><Title>Boeing being sued over 777 SF crash, meanwhile Airbus stock up 218% over 5 years BA not so good 59%</Title><Msg>A Chicago law firm has taken steps to sue Boeing #$%$ behalf of 83 people who were aboard the Asiana Airlines flight that crash-landed in San Francisco earlier this month, alleging that a malfunction of the plane's auto throttle may have caused the crash. Ribbeck Law Chartered on Monday filed a petition for discovery, which is meant to preserve evidence, in Cook County Circuit Court in Chicago, where the aircraft manufacturer is headquartered. The firm said in a news release that additional pleadings will be filed against Asiana Airlines and several component parts manufacturers in coming days. In addition to potential problems with the Boeing 777's auto throttle, some emergency slides reportedly opened inside the plane, injuring passengers and blocking their exit, and some passengers had to be cut out of their seatbelts with a knife, the firm contends. Three people were killed when the airplane, carrying 307 passengers and crew on a flight from South Korea to San Francisco International Airport on July 6, approached the runway too low and slow. It clipped a seawall at the end of a runway, tearing off the tail and sending the plane spinning down the runway. The impact caused the plane to catch fire. "We must find the causes of the crash and demand that the problems with the airline and the aircraft are immediately resolved to avoid future tragedies," attorney Monica R. Kelly, head of Ribbeck's aviation department, said in a written statement.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374041502742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 02:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374041595348-16</Id><Topic><Title>Asiana grounds Boeing 777 in U.S. due to engine oil leak ReutersReuters – 18 minutes ago</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374023035028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:03:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fountain have you head about Airbus stock up 218% over 5 years Boeing 59% not so good !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374041595348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 02:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374041685240-17</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry but I've got to say this......</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374025681569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:48:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe buy Airbus up 218% over 5 year BA not so good or Disney betters BA over 5 years by 120%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374041685240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 02:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374041746316-18</Id><Topic><Title>"Boeing's Dreamliner Looks More and More Like a Nightmare"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374002118250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:15:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 she is a girl</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374041746316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 02:15:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374041820039-19</Id><Topic><Title>FIRE IN 787 REVEALS A MAJOR WEAKNESS-UNREPAIRABILITY OF PLANE</Title><Username>jeffreysauctions</Username><Timestamp>1373987203319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aluminum is much easier to remove and replace than carbon fiber</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374041820039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 02:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374041966530-20</Id><Topic><Title>What is better Boeing 787 one hour flight SF to LA or 30 minutes and the cost 20Billion BA 6 Billon EM!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373932438947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 19:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you email Elon Musk on that topic, that is what he wanted to hear. I like the question, good job Mr President you deserve a prize</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374041966530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 02:19:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374051204085-21</Id><Title>Airbus A350 has 678, firm orders , in 8 years Boeing has 930 firm 787 orders, let's see how long it takes for Airbus to better Boeing</Title><Msg>The A350 XWB MSN1 has performed well during the first 92 flight test hours already achieved since its maiden flight on June 14th 2013. The A350 XWB flight test campaign will total around 2,500 flight hours with a fleet of five development aircraft. During the first four weeks of the flight test campaign, ten Airbus experimental test pilots have flown MSN1 and have collectively put the aircraft through its paces to get to know its handling qualities and behaviour. This early phase of test flights has resulted in the clearance of the entire flight envelope and initial testing of all key systems. These include: engines, electrics, Ram Air Turbine (RAT), landing gear and braking, fuel and cabin pressurization as well as a preliminary assessment of the autopilot and auto-land functions. The A350 MSN1 will now undergo routine maintenance and upgrades of its flight test installation to ready it for the second phase of the flight test campaign which will start in August, while the design office will analyse the results of these initial flight tests. Entry into commercial service of the first customer aircraft is scheduled for the second half of 2014. To date, Airbus has recorded 678 firm orders for the A350 XWB from 34 customers worldwide. Both Boeing and Airbus stock is up 38% year to date but Airbus beats Boeing over five years in stock price gain 218% to 60%, Boeing delivered 15 plane in the month airbus delivered 48. Boosted by a wave of orders announced and signed at the Paris Air Show, Airbus surpassed the 5,000-aircraft backlog milestone – the first time an aircraft manufacturer has ever attained a backlog of this magnitude. Airbus’ 241 jetliners booked during the month increased its overall backlog to 5,109 aircraft, representing more than seven years of sustained production. This performance also brought total Airbus orders over the 13,000 aircraft mark, of which more than 9,600 are for the single-aisle A320 Family.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374051204085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 04:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374053164736-22</Id><Topic><Title>Dueling now legal in Florida</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038706242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:25:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahahahahaha!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1374053164736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 05:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374053196442-23</Id><Topic><Title>I wonder what the verdict would have been</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038260411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:17:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever heard the song Levon? hahahahahahaha!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1374053196442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 05:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374053252569-24</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and twinkies are just twinkies........so go feed your face already..........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1374053252569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 05:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374053327238-25</Id><Topic><Title>Justice For Trayvon</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1374006477166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:27:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The jury has spoken, deal with it.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1374053327238</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 05:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374053426553-26</Id><Topic><Title>Blacks fill our prison, cause they don't understand Justice but neither does Obama. Obama is above the law</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1374029312372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:48:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven and his aliases are so upset over this he can't sleep.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1374053426553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 05:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374053584694-27</Id><Topic><Title>15 yo white gal shot and killed by a black drive by shooter</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1373997197611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>checkn, LIE is your middle name.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1374053584694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 05:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374056945922-28</Id><Topic><Title>Former Teammate testifies in Court that the defendant in Court is NOT the Boston Bomber !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374022309944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:51:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean like when Hooz says "justice was not served in the Trayvon case" ...har har har har</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374056945922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 06:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374060228752-29</Id><Title>Hastings body cremated against his family's wish's</Title><Msg>Rolling Stone journalist Michael Hastings’ body was cremated against his family’s wishes, destroying potential evidence that could have contradicted the explanation that he died as a result of an accident, according to San Diego 6 reporter Kimberly Dvorak. Hastings was killed in the early hours of June 18 in the Hancock Park neighborhood of Los Angeles.when his Mercedes crashed into a tree at high speed and exploded into flames, sparking theories that the journalist, who was working on a major exposé of the CIA, could have been assassinated. Stating that she had spoken with several close friends of the family, including Alex Jones Show guest Staff Sergeant Joe Biggs, Dvorak said, “A close family friend did confirm that Michael’s body was sent home in an urn, meaning he was cremated and it wasn’t the request of the family….in fact the family wanted Michael’s body to go home.” Dvorak said the decision to cremate Hastings against his family’s wishes was “shocking” because it ensured that evidence of any substance (or indeed the absence of any substance) inside his body was lost. According to Hastings’ family, the journalist had not drunk alcohol for five years. Dvorak added that Hastings had spoken with an attorney before his death who has all the details about the story Hastings was working on. Hastings refrained from telling his wife about the story “because he said he wanted to protect her from knowing anything so if anything were to happen to him nothing could happen to her,” said Dvorak. Hastings wife has now hired a private investigator to look into the writer’s death, according to Dvorak. Dvorak also revealed that she had personally been threatened as a result of her efforts to investigate Hastings’ death on behalf of San Diego 6. Aside from Infowars, the news channel is the only media organization asking questions about what happened. “Despite the LAPD’s categorization of the Hasting fatal accident as a “no (evidence of) foul play,” LAPD continues to ignore FOI</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374060228752</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 07:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374062553397-30</Id><Topic><Title>Asiana grounds Boeing 777 in U.S. due to engine oil leak ReutersReuters – 18 minutes ago</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374023035028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:03:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorting is not my game. Too dangerous with continual Fed intevention. I have some puts, but that's about it.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374062553397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374063164170-31</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>business as usual yesterday...i'll update schedule soon as the occupier gets up and tells staff what he wants to do today.... Tuesday 9:45 AM The President receives the Presidential Daily Briefing 10:00 AM The Vice President swears in Ed Markey as Senator of Massachusetts 11:00 AM The President is interviewed by Spanish language news anchors participating in “Live from the White House” 12:45 PM Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jay Carney</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374063164170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374063231714-32</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Board Fascist, err Moderator</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373555074326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 11:04:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>business as usual yesterday...i'll update schedule soon as the occupier gets up and tells staff what he wants to do today.... Tuesday 9:45 AM The President receives the Presidential Daily Briefing 10:00 AM The Vice President swears in Ed Markey as Senator of Massachusetts 11:00 AM The President is interviewed by Spanish language news anchors participating in “Live from the White House” 12:45 PM Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jay Carney</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374063231714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374063356568-33</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you still think all African-Americans have watermelon every day? What year is this, anyway?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374063356568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374063442043-34</Id><Topic><Title>First Degree Murder Now Legal in Florida</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374039389803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:36:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374063442043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374063476167-35</Id><Topic><Title>Dueling now legal in Florida</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038706242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:25:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374063476167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374063786678-36</Id><Topic><Title>Dueling now legal in Florida</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038706242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:25:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best not to duel with a liberal. They can't count to three. Count to two, and turn around, and the lib will be facing you like Travon was facing Zimmerman when he turned around.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1374063786678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374063924324-37</Id><Title>Crissie/Spart the Race Pimp</Title><Msg>looks like i triggered our msg board ACORN, doing the bidding of his handlers. don't expect daily updates of white (n hispanic) folks mugged, beaten, and/or murdered.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374063924324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374064310611-38</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blacks will have watermelon, corn bread, blackeyed peas, and fried chicken as long as you libs get worked up,and make it a political issue. Mexicans eat tacos so what? I consume ignorant liberals everyday, and spit them out because they make my breath bad.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1374064310611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374064682101-39</Id><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Msg>NBC, MSNBC are going to make Zimmerman a very rich man. Soon he'll be able to hire armed body guards like all the outraged rich liberals who have armed body guards to stand their ground for them.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374064960710-40</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry but I've got to say this......</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374025681569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:48:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any comments or research by anyone.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374064960710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374065188560-41</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chrissie/spart reminds me of barack hussein, holder, jesse, n twanna sharpton...paid out the same community agitator pot</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374065188560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374065321953-42</Id><Topic><Title>Dueling now legal in Florida</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038706242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:25:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Best not to duel with a liberal" Thanks. You've finally admitted you're not smart enough.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374065321953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374065596800-43</Id><Title>Is BA halted in pre market trading?</Title><Msg>Last trade at 8:23 at 104. Nothing since. Anyone?</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374065596800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374065864296-44</Id><Title>Fed to yank punch bowl later this year. not suddenly, but slowly.</Title><Msg>The writing is on the wall. Watch out!</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374065864296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374065975266-45</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you mean he wont have to shoot his victims himself anymore?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1374065975266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374066331311-46</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chrissie/spart won't let go...he won't be happy until zimmerman is lynched for defending himself...he doesn't care about all the other's who've died because they weren't able</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374066331311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374066412834-47</Id><Topic><Title>FIRE IN 787 REVEALS A MAJOR WEAKNESS-UNREPAIRABILITY OF PLANE</Title><Username>jeffreysauctions</Username><Timestamp>1373987203319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It appears that management dispensed with the "ilities engineering disciplines", reliability, maintainability and product safety, during the design and development phase of the project.</Msg><Username>slvrbdge</Username><Timestamp>1374066412834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374066541166-48</Id><Topic><Title>Justice For Trayvon</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1374006477166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:27:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374066541166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374066962939-49</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope he get s $2 billion. There must be a lot of political pressure on the media. The media is ignoring and perverting truth to demonizing this guy (for trying to defend his neighborhood). He didn't shoot Trayvon for having skittles, he shot him because Trayvon jumped him and was pounding his head into the sidewalk. Trayvon wasn't a little child, he was faster, taller and stronger than Zimmerman. Zimmerman was carrying a gun because, as a lot of people know, sometimes when you walk in on a burglary in progress, the culprits kill you in order to get away. Zimmerman is not a racist. His community record speaks for itself.</Msg><Username>bdbaca99</Username><Timestamp>1374066962939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374067636769-50</Id><Topic><Title>Crissie/Spart the Race Pimp</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374063924324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chrissie/spart isn't the least bit interested in a our gov't out of control, a race baiting dishonest president and AG, gun running, benghazi, using gov't agencies to punish and intimidate opponents, wholly partisan commiecare, etc....much less hillary's village (not a happy place) he's focused on one case of many thousands....the knock out game is all the rage in hillary's village</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374067636769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374067718282-51</Id><Title>EA Safety Agency, we are prepared to Ground the 787 if a case is demonstrated that a unsafe condition exsists</Title><Msg>It’s too early to say if the aircraft could be grounded,” Dominique Fouda, a spokesman for the Cologne, Germany-based European Aviation Safety Agency, said in an e-mail. EASA is providing advice to the U.K. Air Accidents Investigation Branch that’s leading the probe into the July 12 incident in London. We are prepared to take action in our area of responsibility in case it is demonstrated that there is an unsafe condition, which is not the case so far,” EASA’s Fouda said. “It is too early to draw any conclusion.”</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374067718282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374067783621-52</Id><Topic><Title>More bad news for Boeing.....Law suit over Asiana crash</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1374014917406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 18:48:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are prepared to take action in our area of responsibility in case it is demonstrated that there is an unsafe condition, which is not the case so far,” EASA’s Fouda said. “It is too early to draw any conclusion.” update on the other Boeing line 787</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374067783621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374067989130-53</Id><Title>Wayne #$%$ = Disgruntled fired ex BA janitor</Title><Msg>What a clown this guy is..Burn shortie....</Msg><Username>tallicat9300</Username><Timestamp>1374067989130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374068219473-54</Id><Title>Zeta Terrorist Boss Caught</Title><Msg>US intelligence helped Mexico capture brutal Zeta Gang Boss Trevino Morales. A US drone strike killed an al qaeda leader in Yemen. These are examples that the NSA has not been hampered in going after terrorists by Snowden. What Snowden has made difficult is for the NSA to lie to Congress, to violate the US Constitution, and to hurt US allies. I would rather see Snowden come home with no reprisals.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1374068219473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374068276283-55</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus A350 has 678, firm orders , in 8 years Boeing has 930 firm 787 orders, let's see how long it takes for Airbus to better Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374051204085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 04:53:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let's involve the Boeing barkers, how long will it take for airbus to get 930 orders for the A350, more or less time than Boeing took to get their 930 orders for the 787 . Airbus won the Paris Airshow another contest eh ! ha ha So far Airbus has 678 A350 firm orders in their books</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374068276283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374068502600-56</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he might be dead before then !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374068502600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:41:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374068545138-57</Id><Title>lets have a contest, BA has 930 -787 orders Airbus has 678-A350 orders, how long will it take for Airbus to better boeing</Title><Msg>Boeing took several years to obtain 930 orders for 3 versions of the 787, Airbus already has 678 orders for their A350 in just 90 flight test hours, for their A350. How long will it take for Airbus to better the MD 787 any one want to play</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374068545138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374068666385-58</Id><Title>Airbus has 678 orders for their 350 Boeing has 930 orders for their MD 787 now how long for Airbus to better BA</Title><Msg>any takers for how long</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374068666385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374068976290-59</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"he shot him because Trayvon jumped him and was pounding his head into the sidewalk" Only according to known liar, George Zimmerman. No other facts such as blood on the sidewalk, injuries consistant with such including cognitive impairment. Zimmerman was carrying a gun because he was hyped up on Adderal for his ADHD, and zombied out by his Temazepam which he said he took that evening, making him crazy as described. Neighborhood watch does not condone the carrying of weapons. Neighborhood watch is NOT a vigilante police force. The aim of Neighborhood watch is to reduce crime, not cause it, or more gun violence. Get off the Faux News/RWNJ media talk.</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374068976290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374069187855-60</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Board Fascist, err Moderator</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373555074326</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 11:04:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the no account is up, a day dedicated to introducing his latest community activist... 10:00 AM The President and the Vice President receive the Presidential Daily Briefing 10:50 AM The President delivers a statement on the confirmation of Richard Cordray as the Director of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau 12:30 PM The President and the Vice President meet for lunch 12:45 PM Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jay Carney got answers? got budget?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374069187855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:53:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374069314513-61</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty using faithflagfamily ID is like calling commiecare affordable health care</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374069314513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374069354505-62</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing being sued over 777 SF crash, meanwhile Airbus stock up 218% over 5 years BA not so good 59%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374041502742</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 02:11:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The petition asks a judge to order Boeing to identify the designer and manufacturer of the airplane's autothrottle and its emergency evacuation slides. It also seeks information on the systems that indicate the airplane's glide slope and that warn how close it is to the ground. Kelly said the firm wants to protect the wreckage "from destructive testing" and to obtain maintenance records, internal memos and other evidence</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374069354505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374069482824-63</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He doesn't have a case against NBC, and is only a money-grubbing coward. Zimmerman is a coward for hiding from the media, not testifying on his own behalf in a self-defense case, and for not taking responsibility for being responsible for the events which directly led to the killing of a child. He is going to have to find other sources of income for his upcoming civil court and probably civil-right cases against himself.</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374069482824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 09:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374069875343-64</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>msdnc tried to lynch him, editing 911 tape using sound bytes out of context. you should apply for a job, twana sharpton needs a makeup man...the lap dogs have ruined his life, the least he can do is make em pay for it</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374069875343</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374069929760-65</Id><Title>Airbus A380 ready to own the sky , MD 747 slowing production due to lack of interest</Title><Msg>Following today’s delivery of the no. 1 aircraft, British Airways is scheduled to receive two more A380s this year – its second in September, and the third in October. The carrier is due to have all of the ordered A380 jetliners in its inventory by the end of 2016. Airbus has delivered 106 A380s so far to worldwide operators, which have logged over 109,000 revenue flights and carried approximately 40 million passengers since the aircraft entered commercial service in October 2007. On average, an A380 takes off or lands every five minutes around the world. Airbus has 262 firm orders for the A380, while Boeing has " Silk Way Airlines of Azerbaijan has ordered two 747-8 freighters, bringing Boeing’s tally of 2013 net orders for the jumbo jet to zero." per Seattle times article july 11, 2013 so the jumbo market is done Airbus now controls that section. That is why over 5 years Airbus stock is up 218% while Boeing stock holders are up 60%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374069929760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374070010500-66</Id><Title>MAJOR NEWS RELEASE ON 7-23-2013 ON (SEEK)</Title><Msg>buyouts early release((((((((((((((((((</Msg><Username>teddsmith210</Username><Timestamp>1374070010500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374070198873-67</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop taking your meds dumbfascist, they are only making you more of crazy-assed cracker than the drugged addled Z-man. What is holding America down to it's #37 ranking in world healthcare is mostly access to basic and preventative services by those least likey to be able to afford such. Society is often measured on well they treat the porrest and the elderly, not on well well or how many super-rich they create.</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374070198873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374070278529-68</Id><Title>delivery update for the month Airbus delivered 48 plane Boeing 15</Title><Msg>Airbus shareholders are up 218% over 5 years and Boeing shareholders are up 60%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374070278529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374070704489-69</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks To Obamacare, New Yorkers’ Health Insurance Premiums Will Plunge 50 Percent By Igor Volsky on Jul 17, 2013 at 8:34 am Health care premiums on the individual market will tumble by at least 50 percent as a result of the Affordable Care Act, the New York Times reported on Wednesday. The state joins Oregon, Montana, California, and Louisiana in reporting lower than expected rates in the law’s new health care marketplaces. Economists expected the law to significantly decrease premiums in the Empire State, which in 1993 prohibited insurers from denying coverage to individuals with pre-existing conditions, required carriers to charge “all consumers the exact same rate,” but did not compel young and healthy people to enroll in coverage. As a result, insurers dramatically increased prices and enrollment in the individual market “steadily diminished.” Today, just 17,000 New Yorkers “buy insurance on their own.” The health law’s requirement to purchase insurance and the managed competition structure in the new exchanges will now increase enrollment, state officials predict, as New Yorkers will see lower premiums and will be able to choose from 17 different insurance plans when enrolling in coverage in October: Beginning in October, individuals in New York City who now pay $1,000 a month or more for coverage will be able to shop for health insurance for as little as $308 monthly. With federal subsidies, the cost will be even lower. [...] State officials estimate as many as 615,000 individuals will buy health insurance on their own in the first few years the health law is in effect. In addition to lower premiums, about three-quarters of those people will be eligible for the subsidies available to lower-income individuals. [...] The plans to be offered on the exchanges all meet certain basic requirements, as laid out in the law, but are in four categories from most generous to least: platinum, gold, silver and bronze. An individual with annual income of $17,000 will pay about $55 a month for a silver plan, state regulators said. A person with a $20,000 income will pay about $85 a month for a silver plan, while someone earning $25,000 will pay about $145 a month for a silver plan. The exchanges are creating “a very different dynamic” for insurance companies, Sabrina Corlette, a professor at Georgetown University’s Center on Health Insurance Reform, told the New York Times. “[I]t’s prodding them to be more aggressive and competitive in their pricing.” The news comes as the House of Representatives prepares to vote on delaying the employer responsibility provision and the individual mandate, which is partly responsible for New York’s lower health care rates. During an appearance on CSPAN’s Washington Journal, Rep. John Fleming (R-LA) defended the votes and sought to dismiss the premium drop. “People with more health care problems by law their rates will have to come down, but somebody has to pay for that,” he said. “It will be a combination of younger, healthier people who will have to pay higher rates, and that is if they opt in, which we believe many won’t. There is $1 trillion worth of taxes.”</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070704489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:18:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374070839862-70</Id><Title>Question for the board</Title><Msg>I worked on the Military side of the company and had early experience with composite aircraft. I was wondering how the new 787 grounding system compares with the old system. Early on we had current problems due to graphite bonding issues. Just curious as how it has progressed with so much electrical usage in the 787. Seems to me we have h ad a number of electrical fires and this question popped up in my head.</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1374070839862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374070916532-71</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lmao...there is no depth to which the lap dogs won't sink</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374070916532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:21:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374070926368-72</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By your (sic) logic, the Martin family should sue Faux News. Fox News Coverage of the Trayvon Martin Case Criticized Fox Lies Again -This Time on Trayvon Martin ... News Corpse » Graphic Evidence Of The Racism Of Fox News ...</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374070926368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374070984851-73</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on what ground ahkmed, i mean spart</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374070984851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374070997790-74</Id><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Msg>That will be a rallying cry in the next two elections.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374071690770-75</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>suggest you idiots thing about it again before electing a community agitator to our highest office</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374071690770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374072273860-76</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is a "community agitator"?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374072273860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374072635651-77</Id><Title>New HUGE Consolidation Wave</Title><Msg>A huge wave of consolidation is beginning to take place in the cable TV industry with many cable TV operators the subject of M&amp;A rumors. During the last wave of cable TV industry consolidation in 2006 the operators were the initial stocks to run, but afterwards the focus shifted to cable TV tech vendors. Seachange (SEAC) was the subject of a Brean Capital analyst research note this past December that said "Because of SEAC's leading position in key areas of MSO investment, it is not likely to remain an independent company in an industry consolidation scenario." SEAC has been rallying big in recent days, now that a wave of industry consolidation is here, soaring past its 52-week high of $12.10 on Monday and setting a new 52-week high yesterday of $12.50 where it trades with an enterprise value/revenue ratio of 1.89. Back in 2006, SEAC was also the subject of takeover rumors - but in every article written about SEAC in 2006, its rival CCUR was mentioned as a potential takeover target as well. Since then, CCUR has actually surpassed SEAC to capture the #1 largest video on demand (VOD) technology market share, and CCUR also leads in other key areas like start-over/look-back, and Big Data Analytics. CCUR hasn't received any analyst research notes in recent months like SEAC, but if you look at the reasons Brean calls SEAC a takeover target - CCUR fits all of the same criteria, and CCUR is extremely undervalued vs. SEAC, with CCUR currently trading with an enterprise value/revenue ratio of only 0.71. For CCUR just to match SEAC's current enterprise value/revenue ratio of 1.89, CCUR needs to rise to $16.21. Look for CCUR to explode in the weeks ahead, and for CCUR to surpass SEAC's share price next month. CCUR's 10-K filing is due out next month and CCUR's annual non-GAAP EPS could potentially reach $0.50, exceeding SEAC's current non-GAAP EPS of $0.44. CCUR recently raised its dividend by 100%, and now pays a huge dividend yield of 6.2%, the highest in the industry!</Msg><Username>ttvhbn42</Username><Timestamp>1374072635651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:50:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374072720533-78</Id><Title>Why Does Rush Limbaugh Even Want to Say the N-Word?</Title><Msg>Many people have drawn many conclusions from the Trayvon Martin case, but Rush Limbaugh's is this: He's allowed to say the N-word, now. Bear in mind, I'm not writing about this because I think Limbaugh's comments are interesting or provocative. This post exists to make fun of a famous person being dumb. But I also wonder why Limbaugh -- and so many other of my fellow white people -- even want to say the N-word. In an interview with Piers Morgan, Martin's friend, Rachel Jeantel, said something Limbaugh took as the justification he's apparently long sought to say the word. He's found a loophole, you see: Jeantel said that while "n----er," is an offensive term, "n----a" is just a word that refers to "any male." She said even a Chinese person could be male. "So, n---a with an a on the end," Limbaugh said on his show Tuesday. "It's not racist! I could be talking about a male. A Chinese male. A guy at the laundromat." Sure, because that's where Chinese guys love hanging out, right? But let's set that one aside for a moment. It's unclear why Limbaugh thinks a teenage girl giving him permission to use the word would make her a spokeswoman for all people who might be offended by the word. It's also unclear why so many white people think it's so unfair that black people can say the N-word and they can't. So let's talk about fairness. White people have an amazing deal, by virtue of being born white. Is that fair? We've had a 400-year economic head start, police don't profile us, old ladies don't clutch their purses when we walk by because of our skin color. The supposed downside? We can't say the word. That's it. The one thing we can't do. Here's the reason you shouldn't say the N-word, ever, even if someone you see on TV seems to be reaching out to you directly to say it's okay: Because you might make someone feel bad. Or like you value them less because of their race. Their nice day might be ruined by having to wonder whether you were making a racial joke, or just referring to hypothetical Chinese guys "at the laundromat." Oh wait: In that situation, you would be racist either way. Bad example.</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374072720533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374072914186-79</Id><Topic><Title>Justice For Trayvon</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1374006477166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:27:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it taught us that it's ok to observe and report to protect your neighborhood, and it taught us that it's ok to defend yourself when your head is getting bashed in. At least for now.</Msg><Username>bdbaca99</Username><Timestamp>1374072914186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374072949260-80</Id><Title>Sum Ting Wong....Wit Deese Comershall Airpwanes...Dats Why I Keeps A Privit Jet</Title><Msg>Don't be axin me bout dis cuz I Be Chillin Wit My Be-auch</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1374072949260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374073247944-81</Id><Topic><Title>TESLA just made me over 10% today shorting and made 3.8% up from last Friday at the open yesterday traders win</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373995361476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:22:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so like I told you tsla is up over 8% today , because like with APPLE , when the stock became too large a percent of the index it traded on , the apple stock price went down briefly , while the stock percentage was reduced by the index as it over powered the other index stocks that it traded on. so the institutions that mirrored apple then had to divest their percentage shares to match the index. So now in a similar way tsla, is going through the same process, , also the new institutional buyers and funds that track the nasdaq 100, will have to buy tesla. over time they need to get in, so yesterdays rotten report on the estimated price by Goldman Sucks( very low but if you know how to read the report they actually upped their target price ) ha ha , none the less that report was a head fake move, nothing changed with tesla! it did not have a lithium ion fire like Boeing 787 or a crash caused by any problem like the 777, nothing had changed except on july 15 all the institutions that mirror the nasdaq 100 will need to buy in to tesla over time. The other thing is that on July 25 earning report for tesla will occur, and I doubt Elon Musk will miss his earrings , these are set by the company so he is no fool , he will meet and beat what he said. that is why prior to the actual date of july 15 a analyst upgraded tesla to 230 price target , so now you know it joined the nasdaq 100, . On BA , Tom O'Brien a expert stock market analyst has already said Boeing hits 107 in 2007 and the stock is dead on the vine now and while it will hit about 107 or a little higher it will now retrace over time to the 71 dollar range so far tom O/Brien has nailed it right, I now day trade TSLA, I am up almost 20 short gains yesterday and sold. d today up almost 8% and sold. got to go have some free time fun now you BA barkers have fun now and don't buy and good stocks ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374073247944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374073253434-82</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One definition could be a dumbfascist/censored50...</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374073253434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374073407059-83</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374073407059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374073662336-84</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie/Spart Community Agitator / Race Pimp</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374071838390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump for our race pimp...currently wearing his faithflagfamily costume</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374073662336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374073828080-85</Id><Title>This Bernanke is no Greenspan...</Title><Msg>Thanky God</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374073828080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374073857976-86</Id><Topic><Title>Dueling now legal in Florida</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038706242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:25:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suggest you never test your theory with me.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374073857976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374073971880-87</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sometimes a thug is a thug even if he has skittles.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1374073971880</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374074018212-88</Id><Title>83 Asiana plane crash survivors to sue Boeing</Title><Msg>CHICAGO –  A Chicago law firm says it has taken steps to sue aircraft manufacturer Boeing #$%$ behalf of 83 people who were aboard the Asiana Airlines flight that crash-landed in San Francisco earlier this month, claiming in a court filing that the crash might have been caused by a mechanical malfunction of the Boeing 777’s auto throttle. Ribbeck Law Chartered on Monday filed a petition for discovery — a move meant to preserve evidence — in Cook County Circuit Court in Chicago, where Boeing is headquartered. The law firm said in a news release that additional pleadings will be filed against Asiana Airlines and several component parts manufacturers in coming days. Ribbeck said that in addition to potential problems with the auto throttle, some emergency slides reportedly opened inside the plane, injuring passengers and blocking their exit, and some passengers had to be cut out of their seatbelts with a knife.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1374074018212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:13:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374074308829-89</Id><Topic><Title>Dueling now legal in Florida</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1374038706242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:25:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dueling with an unarmed man is legal if the unarmed man is black and smaller than you are.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1374074308829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374074382153-90</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think he'll enjoy it?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1374074382153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:19:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374074590471-91</Id><Topic><Title>This Bernanke is no Greenspan...</Title><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374073828080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 Trillion and counting, it's another one o dem wealth transfer programs, using the good faith n credit of all Americans to bailout the cronys in the financial markets, ben is pretending he can print money to finance our own debt, currently creating $3 for every $4 put on the credit card...buying high risk debt instruments at rates no one else willing. ben's finance programs comes at the expense of your money, devaluing the money in your pockets / savings. been to the grocery store lately. currently pumping eighty five billion per month, that would be 85,000 million / month.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374074590471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:23:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374074849012-92</Id><Topic><Title>This Bernanke is no Greenspan...</Title><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374073828080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody ever said it was going to be easy (or cheap) filling in the hole left by Bushco/Chieneyburton.</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374074849012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374075225424-93</Id><Title>Every time a Republican ask questions the market went down...</Title><Msg>When Democrats asked questions the market went up... Especially when the sequester issue came up and the fact that if the Congress didn't cut unemployment would be much lower and it makes the feds job that much harder....</Msg><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1374075225424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374075437988-94</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's anybody bumper is afraid of--which is most people.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1374075437988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374075442805-95</Id><Topic><Title>This Bernanke is no Greenspan...</Title><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374073828080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bushhhhhhhhhh....feel better #$%$? dumbos are currently exploiting the mess they created. dumbos had a majority in the senate during his first two years in office (remember tom tax cheat daschle maj leader) and both houses of congress during Bush's last two years in office. barack hussein first term part time senator was no 2 on the ALL TIME fannie freddie payola list. dumbos used funding for the war to extort their big gov't growth programs, they've grown the size of federal gov't by 43%, more'n 1.1 trillion, annually since 2006, no surprise our deficits have increased by like amount.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374075442805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374075631030-96</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have not encountered any 17 year old 'thugs', a lot of misguided yoots and a few 'punks' but no 'thugs'., and many, many kids being kids... I have encountered more than a few 28 year old 'thugs' and 'wannabes', and that description more aptly describes Zimmerman. The evidence shows an unopend bag of Skittles and an unopend can of Arizona brand flavored drink with no marijuana use in over 24 hours by the Trayvon kid. The evidence also shows that Zimmerman said he took his Temazepam the evening of the killing of Trayvon (purportedly to 'help' him sleep/wind down aftertaking his amphetamine based Allderal for ADHD in the morning)... UD: damn adderall hooks yer #$%$ up nice son! poppin the blue pills unleashes the thrills, energy up</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374075631030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374075725523-97</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any earthquake less than 5.0 on the Richter can also be considered a community agitator.</Msg><Username>lucid_luke</Username><Timestamp>1374075725523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374076182248-98</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the knock out game is all the rage in hillary's village, guess you haven't haven't heard about the vandalism, beatings, n mayhem since the verdict. every seen any of the youtube videos of the "knockout game", flash mob looting/vandalism. there was a guy killed in georgia not two weeks ago by four youth (armed with fists), i'm sure many unarmed/defenseless victims have been killed/murdered since..the lap dogs aren't big on covering those crimes, they don't fit the dumb narrative.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374076182248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374076319063-99</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chrissie/spart bumps chrissie/spart using his lucid_luke ID....paid to play, err agitate, like barack hussein and his injustice head</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374076319063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374076520993-100</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You won't.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1374076520993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374076892700-101</Id><Topic><Title>Sum Ting Wong....Wit Deese Comershall Airpwanes...Dats Why I Keeps A Privit Jet</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1374072949260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wut you be talkin bout , foo ?</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1374076892700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374077031629-102</Id><Topic><Title>Every time a Republican ask questions the market went down...</Title><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1374075225424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:33:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They did it again.... Seems like they are upset and don't believe their policy's hurt and they become argumentative ... What's with these guys that they can't accept they are wrong...Every one of them.... Oh Great Job you did over the years and we thank you for your service,but your wrong about the way we do things... DUH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1374077031629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374077125166-103</Id><Title>If Oblama had an airplane , it would look like an airbus</Title><Msg>Dat crackerhater be actin' a foo</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1374077125166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374077271106-104</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus A380 ready to own the sky , MD 747 slowing production due to lack of interest</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1374069929760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:05:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right....230 sold, I mean given away, in 13 years....what a joke you are</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1374077271106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374077653394-105</Id><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Msg>The not-guilty verdict for George Zimmerman in the death of Florida teen Trayvon Martin has outraged many people across the country, including "The Wire" creator David Simon. In an emotional, fiery post on his blog, The Audacity of Despair, Simon denounced the verdict, saying he was "ashamed to call himself an American." Simon knows a little something about race. He worked for 12 years as a crime reporter in Baltimore, witnessing firsthand the despair referenced in his blog title. He then channeled that knowledge to write nuanced, complex portrayals of race, drugs, poverty, violence, and corruption on series like "Homicide: Life on the Street," "The Corner," and "The Wire." [Related: Zimmerman Juror B37 Decides Not to Go For That Book Deal After All] From 2002-2005 on "The Wire," Simon and his team of writers depicted the often deadly consequences for young black men living within the broken education, political, and justice systems. The series was lauded as an American storytelling masterpiece, inspired professors to teach about it in college classes, and was recently named the No. 1 series of all time by Entertainment Weekly. Outside of his television writing, Simon often comments on social issues, and the Martin case stirred up particularly forceful feelings in him. Here's the entirety of his post: You can stand your ground if you're white, and you can use a gun to do it. But if you stand your ground with your fists and you're black, you're dead. In the state of Florida, the season on African-Americans now runs year round. Come one, come all. And bring a handgun. The legislators are fine with this blood on their hands. The governor, too. One man accosted another and when it became a fist fight, one man — and one man only — had a firearm. The rest is racial rationalization and dishonorable commentary. If I were a person of color in Florida, I would pick up a brick and start walking toward that courthouse in Sanford. Those that do not, those that hold the pain and betrayal inside and somehow manage to resist violence — these citizens are testament to a stoic tolerance that is more than the rest of us deserve. I confess, their patience and patriotism is well beyond my own. Behold, the lewd, pornographic embrace of two great American pathologies: Race and guns, both of which have conspired not only to take the life of a teenager, but to make that killing entirely permissible. I can't look an African-American parent in the eye for thinking about what they must tell their sons about what can happen to them on the streets of their country. Tonight, anyone who truly understands what justice is and what it requires of a society is ashamed to call himself an American." Strong words. But Simon didn't stop there. Remarkably, he took the time to address many of the comments following the post. A few highlights: One commenter chastised him for trying to "fan the flames and incite violence," to which Simon replied, "You've missed the thread of that passage utterly." Several others called on Simon to prove that Zimmerman's actions in shooting Martin were racist. He replied, "I don't think Mr. Zimmerman is by any necessity a racist. But his calculations and his behaviors were racially motivated." In other responses, Simon bemoaned the slippery slope effect — that the Martin case would be the first of many. "The law has changed — and the culture of legal self-defense is changing — in a revolutionary fashion. There will be more of these cases now. Not less."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374077764863-106</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The base is definitely energized.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077764863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374078088870-107</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm ashamed him , you, and Travon are Americans</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1374078088870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374078145031-108</Id><Title>Obama hoodwinked America</Title><Msg>Obamacare passed Congress, its the law, now Obama has delayed employer based mandate til 2015 over-riding Congress. This act is actually Unconstitutional. Americans thought they were getting something for nothing. Remember when Congress passed it. At no cost to Americans, that proved to be a lie as the price went o $800B to $1.7T to $1.7T + a tax. He won the election on Food Stamps, Free Healthcare of which neither is free. He brags about paying back the deficit but when economists looks at the numbers America is borrowing $4 instead of $5 of every dollar spent. Selling out the next two generations. Now Obama's DOJ is weighting in on local criminal cases for political gain. Before this guy is done there will be race riots in the streets of America. Americans get angry when they realize they've been hoodwinked. Obamacare is unraveling, he just doesn't want it to happen before the election.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1374078145031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:22:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374078165083-109</Id><Topic><Title>This Bernanke is no Greenspan...</Title><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374073828080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that why the tea-potty repubes wanna throw McConnell under the bus....</Msg><Username>republicanfascists</Username><Timestamp>1374078165083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374078240558-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hoodwinked America</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1374078145031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:22:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are Very Emotional, not RATIONAL...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374078240558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374078535357-111</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hoodwinked America</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1374078145031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:22:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have bad breath. Ought to watch and read the news instead of hanging out at the bar. Got to be sober to understand this stuff. Get yourself off drugs and booz for starters, then you might be able to understand this stuff, but I suspect the damage is done and you'll never understand this stuff. Obama likes stupid people.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1374078535357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:28:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374078734336-112</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hoodwinked America</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1374078145031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:22:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"you have bad breath. Ought to watch and read the news instead of hanging out at the bar. Got to be sober to understand this stuff. Get yourself off drugs and booz for starters, then you might be able to understand this stuff, but I suspect the damage is done and you'll never understand this stuff. Obama likes stupid people" ???? I defy ANYBODY to understand ANYTHING you write.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374078734336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374079068644-113</Id><Topic><Title>This Bernanke is no Greenspan...</Title><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374073828080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ichrissie/spart is copycat, i used to use demfascists after dem fascists disabled my long time ID bumper and then freedomorsocialism, guess dem fascists figured out i wouldn't be shut up/censored/blocked easily after disabling demfascists,1,2.3...42 as i've had my current ID for several months.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374079068644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374079158596-114</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hoodwinked America</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1374078145031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:22:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America hoodwinked itself. Wishful, magical thinking.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1374079158596</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374079247877-115</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why don't you move to a Banana Republic?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1374079247877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374079407691-116</Id><Title>Boston Bomber on the Cover Rolling Stone</Title><Msg>Rolling Stone has triggered a firestorm with its new cover featuring Boston Marathon bombings suspect Dzhokhar Tsarnaev. The August issue of the music magazine features a story and photo of Tsarnaev and is titled: "The Bomber: How a popular, promising student was failed by his family, fell into radical Islam and became a monster." The magazine says the story was drawn from interviews with Tsarnaev's friends, teachers, neighbors and law enforcement officials. According to Rolling Stone, the story, written by contributing editor Janet Reitman, delivers "a riveting and heartbreaking account of how a charming kid with a bright future became a monster."</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374079407691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374079593504-117</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is Terrified Obamacare Will Be a Success</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1373989174210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374079593504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374079946693-118</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have not encountered any 17 year old "thugs",..." Suggest you take a solo walk some evening in Chicago's south side. You know, the place where Obama was a community organizer before becoming President. It appears Obama's legacy there is now going to be his legacy for all America. BTW, how about a 14 year old thug. Google up where a 14 year old may be charged as an adult for the recent brutal kidnapping, rape and attempted murder of a 7 year old girl in Puyallup, Wa. The poor little misguided darling, as you would like for him to be, is still nothing more than a thug and a criminal with a violent past history.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1374079946693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374080260887-119</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is Terrified Obamacare Will Be a Success</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1373989174210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumbo politicians are terrified of the backlash</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374080260887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:57:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374080592156-120</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a SOLO WALK believe it was south and left in Amsterdam boy did I take a wrong turn only eyes showing no fear let's be peaceful unlike the Z-man who said he had noproblemo and not identify himself as a thug packing heat high on Adderall letalone a Neighborhood Watchperson who was told not to follow... are you following me...? what's your problem? 40 feet down the walkway/ 60 yards from home</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374080592156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374080677731-121</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pales in comparison to the wall street thugs</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374080677731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:04:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374080828113-122</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Hyped up, zombied out? He must be some kind of a super mastermind to be all that and still piece together a crime with an air tight alibi that includes accomplice's as police, neighbors, and even prosecution witnesses and even Trayvon himself to pose for the gunshot wound. As for your last three sentences, I couldn't agree more. However, it is legal for him to carry a weapon in Florida. Unfortunately he had to use it in self defense as the evidence proves.</Msg><Username>bdbaca99</Username><Timestamp>1374080828113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374080869181-123</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is Terrified Obamacare Will Be a Success</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1373989174210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go tell it on the mountain... and... and it will still fall on mostly deaf ears by the Faux News dittoheads and RWNJ media followers</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374080869181</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:07:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081053502-124</Id><Topic><Title>trayvons favorite drink</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1374029948169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when he's not creating new threads intended to create social division, chrissie/spart, community agitator, can't resist bumping his own dumb self on his own dumb pre-existing threads</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374081053502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081270523-125</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is Terrified Obamacare Will Be a Success</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1373989174210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm similarly terrified of commiecare, it's already cost me a couple grand in increased premiums, we were all notified recently we're gonna have to buck up add'l if'n we smoke.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374081270523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081295700-126</Id><Topic><Title>Former Teammate testifies in Court that the defendant in Court is NOT the Boston Bomber !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374022309944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:51:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave it to sparty to believe total nonsense.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1374081295700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081367298-127</Id><Topic><Title>Former Teammate testifies in Court that the defendant in Court is NOT the Boston Bomber !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374022309944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:51:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's the matter roksta, faithflagfamily not good enough? no need to change costumes just for us</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374081367298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081393267-128</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The evidence shows that the Z-man took his Temazepam the evening of the shooting (with it's own side-effects) supposedly to chill out his amphetamine based Allderall for ADHD earlier in the day. The evidence also highly suggests that the Z-man had grabbed the Trayvon kid by the shirt with his left had and fired point blank to the shirt and intermediated straight on into the Trayvon kids chest, not angulalry or slightly horizontally... do the math! The Z-man is a coward supported by RWNJ Faux News neanderthals</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374081393267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081414191-129</Id><Topic><Title>15 yo white gal shot and killed by a black drive by shooter</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1373997197611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he may look mixed but I will bet you his race on his BC is white. looks maybe a little Latino but that`s considered white !</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1374081414191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374081550025-130</Id><Title>Up, up and away in my beautiful BA--l-loon</Title><Msg>the 5th Dimension</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374081550025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081836725-131</Id><Topic><Title>Up, up and away in my beautiful BA--l-loon</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374081550025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:19:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>high headwind,,, easy more heat or more helium hydrogen is too flammable</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374081836725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081852243-132</Id><Topic><Title>15 yo white gal shot and killed by a black drive by shooter</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1373997197611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really - search on Molly Conley: Erick N Walker, 26, arrested over shooting. . . in UK press</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1374081852243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081858196-133</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>life according to contard, psychotic gay pedophile, and fugitive</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374081858196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374081926729-134</Id><Title>looks lke investigators don't have a clue on the fire</Title><Msg>Britain's Air Accidents Investigation Branch is planning to issue within days an interim fact-finding report on Friday's fire inside a Boeing Co. BA +0.72%787 Dreamliner operated by Ethiopian Airlines, according to a person familiar with AAIB planning. The report would state the known series of events occurring inside the top of the unoccupied jetliner when it was parked at London's Heathrow Airport. The report is UNLIKELY to draw any conclusions about what caused the fire, this person said.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1374081926729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374082244338-135</Id><Topic><Title>Former Teammate testifies in Court that the defendant in Court is NOT the Boston Bomber !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374022309944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:51:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and janeel today don't look like janeel two weeks ago fingerprints, dna, and own admissions will sink the Tsarnev along with all the other forensic evidence Senator Charles F. Meachum (Character) from Shooter (2007/I) the same guy from Deliverance Senator Charles F. Meachum: There's always a confused soul that thinks that one man can make a difference. And you have to kill him to convince him otherwise. That's the hassle with democracy. Bob Lee Swagger: I don't think you understand, these boys killed my dog. Share this Bob Lee Swagger: Welcome to Tennessee, patron state of shootin' stuff.</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374082244338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374082576002-136</Id><Topic><Title>Former Teammate testifies in Court that the defendant in Court is NOT the Boston Bomber !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374022309944</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:51:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senator Charles F. Meachum: It's not really as bad as it seems. It's all gonna be done in any case. You might as well be on the side that gets you well paid for your efforts. Nick Memphis: And what side are you on? Senator Charles F. Meachum: There are no sides. There's no Sunnis and Shiites. There's no Democrats and Republicans. There's only HAVES and HAVE-NOTS. Senator Charles F. Meachum: This is a country, where the Secretary of Defense can go on T.V., and tell the American public, oh, that "This is about freedom! It's not about oil!" And nobody questions him, cuz they don't wanna hear the answer, because it's a lie! There are only so many places at the table, Gunnie. Now, are you on the INSIDE, or are you on the OUT? Sarah Fenn: What are you going to do? Bob Lee Swagger: Exercise my right to bear arms. Bob Lee Swagger: I'm going to find them, burn their playhouse down.</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374082576002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374082735955-137</Id><Topic><Title>looks lke investigators don't have a clue on the fire</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1374081926729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...is planning to issue within days an interim fact-finding report on Friday's fire inside a Boeing..." will Tony Blair be in on The Deal or the Brown guy</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374082735955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374082816687-138</Id><Topic><Title>looks lke investigators don't have a clue on the fire</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1374081926729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody playing with matches?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1374082816687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374083227269-139</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>according to a dumbfascist/censored50 possibly 100,000 patient visits sometimes utilizing rides on BA aeroplanes based on choices made long time ago what's your story... moo-ed out of state for ...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374083227269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374083331663-140</Id><Title>Someone must have news before the market</Title><Msg>Could get interesting</Msg><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1374083331663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374083345150-141</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like a case of mistaken identity, he thought it was you contard.... “And people need to understand, he didn’t want that creepy #$%$ cracker going to his father or girlfriend’s house to go get — mind you, his little brother was there. You know — now, mind you, I told you — I told Trayvon it might have been a rapist,” Jeantel told CNN host Piers Morgan. Jeantel made clear that she was not referring to general fears of a neighborhood rapist but specifically to the sexual orientation of men who are “that kind of way.” Morgan, the low-rated British replacement for beloved talker Larry King, declined to draw her out on the point. “Definitely after I say may be a rapist, for every boy, for every man, every — who’s not that kind of way, seeing a grown man following them, would they be creep out?,” Jeantel said."</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374083345150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374083480004-142</Id><Title>The World does Not revolve around Republicans</Title><Msg>it revolves around the black man... and thou pathetic neocon creatures from a lost time want US policies that promote corruption, greed and hatism - things that help a GOP toadie to succeed !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374083480004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374083615075-143</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is Terrified Obamacare Will Be a Success</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1373989174210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...we're gonna have to buck up add'l if'n we smoke." FANTASTIC. It's about time.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1374083615075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374083675831-144</Id><Topic><Title>The World does Not revolve around Republicans</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374083480004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:51:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's all about dumbos, huh spart...you didn't need a new thread to say that bye now,,,time for some of us to go to workie</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1374083675831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374084581525-145</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need to go Forward possibly with civil-rights litigation I thinke we have a case: The Z-mans brother whot estified that the Z-man was not a racist posted racist tweets. The Z-man only reported black males as being suspicious despite over 400 police calls/responses to the mostly white Retreat at Twin Lakes , and the Zpman called them derogatory names. while being under the effects of some heavily abused psycho-tropic medications. The Z-man is lucky to be alive, let him show his coward face.... lol</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374084581525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374084706136-146</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is Terrified Obamacare Will Be a Success</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1373989174210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Go Tell It on the Mountain" is an African-American spiritual song, compiled by John Wesley Work, Jr., dating back to at least 1865, that has been sung and recorded by many gospel and secular performers. It is considered a Christmas carol because its original lyric celebrates the Nativity of Jesus: "Go tell it on the mountain, over the hills and everywhere; go tell it on the mountain, that Jesus Christ is born." Over the hills and everywhere Go, tell it on the mountain, That Jesus Christ is born. While shepherds kept their watching o’er silent flocks by night, Behold, throughout the heavens There shone a holy light Refrain The shepherds feared and trembled, When lo! above the earth, Rang out the angels chorus That hailed our Savior's birth. Refrain Down in a lowly manger The humble Christ was born And God sent us salvation That blessed Christmas morn. Refrain</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374084706136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374084857192-147</Id><Topic><Title>The World does Not revolve around Republicans</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374083480004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:51:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buhbye and if you over cook my out of state burger we'll just smoke your butt in the parking lot and call it the ok corral kapische</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374084857192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374085502022-148</Id><Title>The Deal</Title><Msg>possibly the KEYSTONE in Berkeley 1974 by the TJGB me moving, over 16 tons per day summetime job union job 3x minimum wage on way to 5%'er before blow'd UP</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374085502022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374085578962-149</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimmerman has inflicted bodily harm (death) and will pay for "wrongful death" in a civil trial to the fullest.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1374085578962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374085639510-150</Id><Topic><Title>The Deal</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374085502022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:25:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those were the days, the gigs, the venues... I was there often myself.</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1374085639510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374085640684-151</Id><Topic><Title>looks lke investigators don't have a clue on the fire</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1374081926729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you still have one... I used to light them on my front teeth, zipper, rwnj pinheads...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374085640684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374086549512-152</Id><Title>Trayvon, George and the Perfect Crime: Reflections on the Zimmerman Trial</Title><Msg>By Bill Blum When we think of real-life “perfect crimes,” we usually turn our attention to coldblooded, carefully planned slayings like the presumed contract killing of Teamster boss Jimmy Hoffa, or moldy old homicides like the 1947 Black Dahlia mutilation in Los Angeles, or the 1996 Las Vegas drive-by carried out on rapper Tupac Shakur. Whether executed by firearm (Shakur), cutting instrument (Dahlia) or sealed in tons of cement (as lore has it in Hoffa’s case), such crimes achieved their perverse perfection because they remain unsolved whodunits with no identifiable suspects. In the minds of millions of Americans, the slaying of 17-year-old African-American Trayvon Martin is also a perfect crime, but for entirely different reasons. Martin’s death is no whodunit. We know that George Zimmerman, a man of mixed white and Hispanic heritage, killed Martin, and we know when and how he did the deed—by firing a bullet at close range to Martin’s heart during the course of an altercation that Zimmerman had set in motion on the evening of Feb. 26, 2012, as he followed Martin while the Florida teen walked to his father’s home, carrying a bag of Skittles and a can of iced tea and wearing a hoodie to shield himself from the rain. We also know more generally that nationwide, a mere 5 percent of murder trials end in acquittals. Winning a murder prosecution may be hard work, but it isn’t like winning the lottery. How, then, for anyone except those who believe he committed no crime, did Zimmerman and his lawyers secure a not-guilty verdict on both second-degree murder and manslaughter charges? Although it’s tempting to answer that racism alone explains the trial’s outcome, digging a little deeper reveals an even more disturbing three-dimensional picture: Advertisement 1. This Is Florida: Forget the bright lights and cosmopolitan glamor of Miami or the open-mindedness and laid-back lifestyles of Key West. Florida as a whole is still the Deep South, and like other Southern venues it has a well-oiled and efficient criminal justice system geared toward convicting African-Americans accused of crimes, not to seeing them as victims. The statistics tell a chilling tale: According to the Census Bureau, African-Americans comprise 16.6 percent of Florida’s population, but the state’s Department of Corrections notes that they account for 31.5 percent of its inmates. As reported by the New York-based Brennan Center for Justice, blacks in Florida are arrested at a rate 2.9 times greater than other racial groups, and are 35 percent more likely to be convicted of a felony or misdemeanor than whites who have similar socioeconomic status, live in areas with similar crime rates and have similar criminal records. Juvenile offenders, regardless of race, receive especially tough treatment in Florida, which charges children criminally as adults and sentences them to adult prisons and jails far more frequently than any other state in the country. 2. A Botched Prosecution Narrative: None of the statistics, of course, prove that the prosecutors assigned to the Zimmerman trial were biased against Martin either because of his race or youth, or that they didn’t put forward spirited efforts. What the figures do reflect, however, is a legal culture and context in which the prosecution team seemed uncertain, out of place and out of sync almost from the opening statements. As any experienced lawyer will tell you, framing the terms of a trial’s narrative—establishing a “theory of the case,” some practitioners call it—is the key to victory. Here, the prosecution’s goal should have been to secure the moral high ground by keeping the narrative simple, arguing that this was a case of unprovoked racial profiling that resulted in death solely because Zimmerman was carrying a concealed weapon and decided against the admonition of a police dispatcher to pursue Martin, initiate a confrontation and take the law into his own hands. The goal of the defense was the exact opposite—to deny the role of race and raise reasonable doubt by complicating the trial, turning the narrative into a contest over such details as which side’s witnesses more credibly identified the voice heard screaming for help on the 911 tape of a neighbor’s phone call that was played in court (a determination that trial Judge Debra Nelson had ruled was so speculative it was beyond the scope of expert testimony), who was on top at what point in the fracas and whether the inconsistencies in Zimmerman’s public pretrial statements were material or minor. Restricted by Nelson as to what they could say to the jury, the prosecutors made no mention of race in the trial except for a brief reference to profiling during opening statements. Instead of driving home its own theory, at nearly every critical turn the prosecution bought into the defense narrative, allowing Zimmerman’s attorneys, aided by Florida’s “stand-your-ground” self-defense law, to portray their client as the victim and to cast him—instead of Martin—as worthy of sympathy before a jury that included no African-Americans. Any question as to which side’s narrative prevailed has been definitively laid to rest by the woman identified as Juror B37, who in a post-trial interview with CNN’s Anderson Cooper disclosed not only that she believed Zimmerman’s “heart was in the right place,” but that she also had “no doubt” that it was Zimmerman’s voice on the tape, or that Zimmerman feared for his life when he fired the fatal shot. 3. This Is America: It would be easy but ultimately wrong to see the trial as the product solely of Southern or Florida justice, or as the result of a pair of prosecutors getting outfoxed by savvy defense lawyers. The truth is that Martin’s death and Zimmerman’s trial are uniquely American events. It isn’t only the Florida system that refuses to see the continuing imprint of race, but the nation’s legal system as a whole, reaching all the way to the Supreme Court, which only last month gutted the Voting Rights Act in an opinion (Shelby County v. Holder) that cynically suggested racial injustice in America was a thing of the distant past. It isn’t of course, not by a long shot, or—as the Zimmerman trial illustrates—by a shot to the heart.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374086549512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374086640844-153</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Zimmerman has inflicted bodily harm (death) and will pay for "wrongful death" in a civil trial to the fullest." Good post.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374086640844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374086715818-154</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumping bisbee_angler</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374086715818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374086805958-155</Id><Topic><Title>The World does Not revolve around Republicans</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374083480004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:51:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he's panhandling at the freeway exits !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374086805958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374087351028-156</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tanks a lot</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374087351028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374087704877-157</Id><Title>Republicans Healthcare Plan</Title><Msg>remove Food Stamps - starve Americas children to death - no need for healthcare !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374087704877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:01:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374088198251-158</Id><Title>Winning One for Snowden</Title><Msg>Congress members, took to task the NSA at a Congressional hearing today. Members admitted they would not know but for Snowden that the NSA was keeping phone records on all Americans. Some Congress members were so upset with the NSA they threatened to end the NSA when it comes for up renewal in 2015. Counsel for the NSA admitted the agency was seeking to expand surveillance activities on all Americans including credit card records before Snowden revelations but now Congress is catching on. He said he was willing to work with Congress and redraw the line by now considering American privacy rights concerns.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1374088198251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374088208622-159</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so the way to fix and tutor the downtrodden is to riot- trash property- play the race card where none exists in the zimmerman case, believe in the false narrative of NBC, ignore the FACT that Zimmerman was on the bottom and had no escape, ignore the facts of taking over 40 minutes to go 1/2 mile in the rain, and FACT that trevon bragged about how to ground and pound. The watts riots accomplished what ? In seattle area a black shot a white girl at random, and some have beat up a white or hispanic just to get even. Holder misstates the law, and the jurors have to remain in hiding for their own protection. Chief racist al sharpton etc pander to the tribe. +++ No greater injury can be done to any youth than to let him feel that because he belongs to this or that race he will be advanced in life regardless of his own merits or efforts. Booker T washington</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1374088208622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374089372792-160</Id><Title>In the high school newspaper - Flotsam v. Jetsam</Title><Msg>before that it was boonbacks or bricbacts without talking we each grabbed about 20 h.s newspapers and went to self-paced french IV as seniors hooking our boots on the table across from each other and perusing the read on the opposite side of the room from the 'teach' shuffling the high-school news paper pages the 'teach' came over and grabbed our h.s newspapers out of each of our hands while we were still smiling needless to say, having an extra copies of the high school newspaper we each manged to pull out another copy and pretend to read in it french in self-paced French IV putting our our boots on the table opposite each other and across the room the 'teach'... then shuffling our high-school newspapers pages .. again and going 'hrmmph' of course the 'teach' cam,e across the room and grabbed our newspapers out of our self-paced french IV hands... now laughing again, we reached under our shirt/seat and pulled out another copy of the high-school newspaper and began reading in pretend french self-paced and putting our boots on the t\ble across from each other across the room from the'teach' and laffing some more while 'hrrmphing' and now laughing out loud by then one woulda thunked 'the teach' woulda caught on instead of grabbing not only the high-school newspaper out of our hands but also by laffing and checking under my sweater/shirt needless to say only got one semester of "A" and one semeseter of (I)ncomplete in self-paced french IV by yhe end of the year</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089372792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374089394445-161</Id><Topic><Title>In the high school newspaper - Flotsam v. Jetsam</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089372792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buy the end of the year</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089394445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374089455747-162</Id><Title>Mister Magic</Title><Msg>Chasing your troubles away... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5JwPzNqUJhs</Msg><Username>fliprnoble</Username><Timestamp>1374089455747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374089940444-163</Id><Topic><Title>In the high school newspaper - Flotsam v. Jetsam</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089372792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>le petite prince le count demonte cristo le monde sacre bleu, le francaise d'enfant/wahington poopst</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089940444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374090062978-164</Id><Topic><Title>Winning One for Snowden</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1374088198251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:09:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Congress members, took to task the NSA at a Congressional hearing today" Do you know how insane that sounds??? !?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374090062978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374090543024-165</Id><Topic><Title>looks lke investigators don't have a clue on the fire</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1374081926729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON (Reuters) - ........... Honeywell said it was responding to a report in the Wall Street Journal, which it said was based on "anonymous speculation," and said the company had not been contacted by Britain's Air Accidents Investigation Branch (AAIB) or by U.S. authorities involved in the investigation. Investigators have been looking at whether a lithium manganese battery in the Honeywell emergency locator transmitter (ELT) may have caused or contributed to the fire that damaged a parked Ethiopian Airlines (ETHA.UL) jet last Friday.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1374090543024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374091083633-166</Id><Title>I swear...a wing could fall off the Dreamliner....</Title><Msg>And Boeing shares would just smile and keep on moving higher.....</Msg><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1374091083633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374091302370-167</Id><Topic><Title>In the high school newspaper - Flotsam v. Jetsam</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089372792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when I was 17... it was very good year a very good year for small town floriduh lads to wera their hoodies in the rain to 7/11 and say two miles waz up skittles and an AZ drink no ceegars n booze before being shot and kiled by the self-proclaimed high on Addreall Zimmerman racist-profiling thug</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374091302370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374093889522-168</Id><Topic><Title>I swear...a wing could fall off the Dreamliner....</Title><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1374091083633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:58:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which wing would that be.. A 787 pilot don; t nee a wing to fly</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374093889522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374094140303-169</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thnx for taking don w. shuper down wit u</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374094140303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374094409457-170</Id><Topic><Title>I swear...a wing could fall off the Dreamliner....</Title><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1374091083633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:58:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It'll get much better fuel economy with less weight and only one engine. Meanwhile, at Forbes John Gogglia questions repairability of the pressure hull.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1374094409457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374094465634-171</Id><Title>Justice official says George Zimmerman unlikely to face federal charges</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON — George Zimmerman is unlikely to face federal charges for killing black teenager Trayvon Martin because it would be difficult to prove he acted out of racial bias, Justice Department officials said Tuesday. . . . But a successful federal prosecution of Zimmerman would require clear evidence that he set out to attack the unarmed Martin because he was black. Although that is exactly what many Americans see in the fatal shooting of the 17-year-old, it can be very hard to prove in court, legal experts said. So far, prosecutors have not shown evidence that Zimmerman acted out of racial bias. "I'd be very, very surprised if we took it," said one federal civil rights prosecutor, speaking anonymously because no decision had been made. "It's a very tough, tough case to sell" because of the lack of witnesses. "The difficult element would be proving racial motivation beyond a reasonable doubt," said University of Michigan law professor Samuel Bagenstos, a former civil rights attorney in the Obama administration. "In most of these cases, you have someone who had made racial statements or you have a group who goes looking to attack a person based on their race." -LA Times-</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374094465634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374094546939-172</Id><Topic><Title>Justice official says George Zimmerman unlikely to face federal charges</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374094465634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neighborhood Watch doesn't go out of its way to attack black people? I bet that's news to most black people.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1374094546939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374094901780-173</Id><Topic><Title>In the high school newspaper - Flotsam v. Jetsam</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089372792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven. Too bad you and Levon couldn't get married, you obsessed freak.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1374094901780</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374094963730-174</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One KENT RAVEN alias bumping another KENT RAVEN alias.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1374094963730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374095044192-175</Id><Topic><Title>In the high school newspaper - Flotsam v. Jetsam</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089372792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you following david_aaames no fish</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374095044192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374095298359-176</Id><Topic><Title>Justice official says George Zimmerman unlikely to face federal charges</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374094465634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Justice Department officials said ..." More, on Faux News Channel...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374095298359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374095395765-177</Id><Title>We all need to be ashamed to have Obonzo as our president as he allowed Black genocide on his watch</Title><Msg>Obonzo and his Chicago cronies did absolutely nothing to prevent the slaughter of Black youths for years under his watch and turning Chicago into the Black youth death capital of the USA. Obonzo and his merry little band of progressive Dem race pimps couldn't use Black on Black crime for political profit so the slaughter of Black kids continued while Obonzo did zilch. Obonzo is using tragedy for political profit and is and always has been a total #$%$ on this issue as he stood by and did nothing.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374095395765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374095406203-178</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a terrified old man. Blacks who walk too slow are criminals?</Msg><Username>i_like_ike99</Username><Timestamp>1374095406203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374095487628-179</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whose alias are you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1374095487628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374095605847-180</Id><Title>BA going to the moon...</Title><Msg>I think we should and back, not only for the minerals and rights in a 'manned' lunar mission and more but to prove that we did/could we didn;t play all-in back then</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374095605847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:13:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374095634021-181</Id><Topic><Title>In the high school newspaper - Flotsam v. Jetsam</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089372792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is Raven? Who is Levon?</Msg><Username>i_like_ike99</Username><Timestamp>1374095634021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374095839964-182</Id><Topic><Title>Justice official says George Zimmerman unlikely to face federal charges</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374094465634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In "Operation Ghetto Storm," the Malcolm X Grassroots Movement (MXGM) found at least 136 unarmed African Americans were killed by police, security guards and self-appointed vigilantes in 2012. NAACP and MoveOn petition to DoJ demanding action has a million sigs, says CNN blogger Bryan Koenig.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1374095839964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374096281455-183</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The forensic expert stated the evidence supported Zimmerman's statement. I saw the that part of the trial. If Zimmerman would have grabbed the shirt, the bullet holes would not have aligned as they did. Zimmerman was not lying.</Msg><Username>bdbaca99</Username><Timestamp>1374096281455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374096385561-184</Id><Topic><Title>Justice official says George Zimmerman unlikely to face federal charges</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374094465634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another person too stupid to read the source as being the LA Times? I put the source there just for Hooz and his merry band of race pimping morons but they can't read.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374096385561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374096410800-185</Id><Topic><Title>In the high school newspaper - Flotsam v. Jetsam</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374089372792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:29:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to my scorecard the Freirs (sp), french-catholic let me play RISK in their house with the Lawrence mostly italian-catholic lads with the FM radio blasting Break On Through a couple of them boys raised rabbits...for the restaurant let me guess alone lapine astes likechicken and wafflers until... hmmm...interesting maneuver but losing Maybe we should play CLUE or Candyland thanky-god it is not 1962 and bunkers and the RWNJ's are on the lapines</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374096410800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374096734183-186</Id><Topic><Title>Justice official says George Zimmerman unlikely to face federal charges</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374094465634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>difficult you the lapine</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374096734183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374096857054-187</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some neighborhood watchman: Neighborhood Watch Manual, USAonwatch dot org Sponsored by the National Sheriff's Assn. and the DOJ's Bureau of Justice Assistance page 20 of 37 Patrol members should be trained by law enforcement. It should be emphasized to members that they do not possess police powers and they shall not carry weapons or pursue vehicles. They should also be cautioned to alert police or deputies when encountering strange activity. Members should never confront suspicious persons who could be armed and dangerous. Patrol members can be equipped for their duties. For example, flashlights or searchlights are necessary for night patrols. Perhaps Zippy was a member of a different organization.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1374096857054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374097068117-188</Id><Topic><Title>We all need to be ashamed to have Obonzo as our president as he allowed Black genocide on his watch</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374095395765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why has it been OK for Blacks to kill Black children for all those years Obonzo was in charge? Were none of those young Black youths, several were straight A students heading to college on scholarships, killed by other Blacks worthy of being like a "son" to Obonzo? I guess not.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374097068117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374097714168-189</Id><Title>BA - wi tu lo</Title><Msg>should be 110</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374097714168</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374097861785-190</Id><Title>I 'd rather have a wing than a tail</Title><Msg>yes, i would if i could unless IT was a lobster, etc.</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374097861785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374098367133-191</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post. This case will live on for several years... and elections. African-Americans know what Zimmerman meant when he said "these a$ $holes, they always get away." Trayvon was an African-American... trouble is, he hadn't committed a crime. And Zimmerman followed Martin, eventually losing sight of him.[12] The dispatcher asked Zimmerman if he was following him. When Zimmerman answered, "yeah," the dispatcher said, "We don't need you to do that." Zimmerman responded, "Okay." But he didn't. And then the media "made it about race". Yeah, right!</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374098367133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374098466824-192</Id><Topic><Title>"Let's Win One For Trayvon"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374070997790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well that certainly clears it up.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374098466824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374098608923-193</Id><Title>Coup D Etat'</Title><Msg>By the Great Paul Craig R oberts The American people have suffered a coup d’etat, but they are hesitant to acknowledge it. The regime ruling in Washington today lacks constitutional and legal legitimacy. Americans are ruled by usurpers who claim that the executive branch is above the law and that the US Constitution is a mere “scrap of paper.” An unconstitutional government is an illegitimate government. The oath of allegiance requires defense of the Constitution “against all enemies, foreign and domestic.” As the Founding Fathers made clear, the main enemy of the Constitution is the government itself. Power does not like to be bound and tied down and constantly works to free itself from constraints. The basis of the regime in Washington is nothing but usurped power. The Obama Regime, like the Bush/Cheney Regime, has no legitimacy. Americans are oppressed by an illegitimate government ruling, not by law and the Constitution, but by lies and naked force. Those in government see the US Constitution as a “chain that binds our hands.” The South African apartheid regime was more legitimate than the regime in Washington. The apartheid Israeli regime in Palestine is more legitimate. The Taliban are more legitimate. Muammar Gaddafi and Saddam Hussein were more legitimate. The only constitutional protection that the Bush/Obama regime has left standing is the Second Amendment, a meaningless amendment considering the disparity in arms between Washington and what is permitted to the citizenry. No citizen standing with a rifle can protect himself and his family from one of the Department of Homeland Security’s 2,700 tanks, or from a drone, or from a heavily armed SWAT force in body armor.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374098608923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374098682028-194</Id><Title>Le Monde (aka the world) dit</Title><Msg>le morte de l'enfat Trayvon, ce;st ne pas juste</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374098682028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374099598424-195</Id><Title>Pentagon wants more regular testing after failed missile test</Title><Msg>Boeing: You can buy better but you can't pay more.</Msg><Username>stoopid_bubba</Username><Timestamp>1374099598424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374099806497-196</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Healthcare Plan</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374087704877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:01:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it ironic that conservative Christian Republicans believe so strongly in social Darwinism?</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1374099806497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374100402982-197</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman suing NBC for $1 billion for being race pimps</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374064682101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimmerman's not greedy. I told George to sue NBC just enough to put them out of business.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1374100402982</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374100618522-198</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Healthcare Plan</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1374087704877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:01:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>succinct</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374100618522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374100768208-199</Id><Topic><Title>Justice official says George Zimmerman unlikely to face federal charges</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374094465634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watched Holder the other night doing the old soft shoe around federal charges against Georgie Boy. Fk Obama and his hand puppet Holder!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1374100768208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374101264301-200</Id><Title>Virgin Atl. delays airbus decision</Title><Msg>Virgin Atlantic Airways Ltd. has delayed buying the Airbus SAS A380 superjumbo jet as it studies whether it wants the plane and focuses on introducing its first Boeing Co. 787 Dreamliners due in September 2014. Virgin, an initial customer for the Airbus flagship plane, has ordered six and “deferred them yet again,” Virgin Atlantic Chief Executive Officer Craig Kreeger said today at the Royal Aeronautical Society in London. The double-decker jet is now due in 2018 rather than 2017, he said. The carrier, based in Crawley, England, is looking to new planes, including the 787 Dreamliner, to reduce fuel consumption as part of a turnaround effort to end two years of losses that Kreeger called “not sustainable.” Buying the A380 would add significant capacity, though. “It’s hard but not impossible to see a world where we want to take the aircraft,” Kreeger said. “It’s not a clear choice.”</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1374101264301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:47:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374101423076-201</Id><Topic><Title>I 'd rather have a wing than a tail</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374097861785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:51:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alrighty then... a story for H.S. Newspaper we bugged out in a 1966 volkswagen beatle about noon for the 1 P.M. game with no tickets to ride Willie McCovey was still playing first base. The announcer said paid attendence was 504 that day. Was anything missed that day...besides the announcer concerning paid attendance at both the ballpark and the school ?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374101423076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374101577556-202</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I double dare you to confront your own racist stance- ask your self where you got it- ask yourself what Christ would say about you-ask yourself where you would be if your family had had to endure slavery and racism for the past 500 years and if you still didn't know how to read-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1374101577556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374101715991-203</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with a country full of braindead Neanderthal RWNJs youd expect many folks to be outraged. when you are as ignorant as a doublehaul its not hard to lead you off the cliff. Jimmy Carter hasn't said a dam thing your lying sob</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1374101715991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374101788122-204</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you bet civil rights legislation and litigation. Lets start with voter SUPPRESSION!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1374101788122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374102865682-205</Id><Topic><Title>Coup D Etat'</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1374098608923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:03:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How true</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1374102865682</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374103161109-206</Id><Title>Possibly 400 waffles one weekend</Title><Msg>no overtime no any extra pay ROTC crackers - classify 1-4 using a tongue blade me and Mike-y who also worked well in prosthetics not a one three ones, don't argue lots and lots of two' and three's and zero 4's because they didn't show up same as the GWB on his physical exam in the 3rd year of his six-year commitment in TANG ? and the RWJ's elected him president along with whast's-his-face chieney No wonder Raison in the sand can you hum a few bars...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374103161109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374104078067-207</Id><Title>The GOP Has Hit Rock Bottom</Title><Msg>Liz Cheney for Senate The Republican Party needs to hit rock bottom. Vicious, cynical and talented Liz Cheney is perfect By Jon Lovett Liz Cheney, the infamous political operative and daughter of Vice President #$%$ Cheney, announced last night that she is running for Senate. After careful consideration, I believe this is welcome news for the country and today I would like to offer my endorsement. I’ve thought about this over the past several days, in anticipation of Cheney’s announcement. As the New York Times reported earlier this month, Cheney had already moved her family to Wyoming. She alerted the sitting senator, Republican Mike Enzi, that he might face a challenger. And fearing a charge of carpetbagging, she has been, according to the Times, “showing up everywhere in the state, from chicken dinners to cattle growers’ meetings.” I’ve also enjoyed that in her Twitter feed, Cheney has started referring to Wyoming as “God’s country.” As in: “Skiing on top of the world today in God’s country –WYO!” Or: “Summer road trip – we made it to God’s country!” Or in hashtag form: My bank drive through is closed because a moose is taking a nap in it. #GodsCountry! There’s nothing wrong with this. Wyoming is awesome. But, Liz, a little free advice: When you’re actually from a place, you don’t need to constantly prove it by giving it a nickname. People who live in Chicago don’t post pictures of themselves eating bready pizza with the caption “Windy City!” It should be noted that in Cheney’s announcement video, she also listed relatives who hailed from the Cowboy State, without mentioning, though I suppose implying, that one is her well-known and well-respected father. But whatever. I don’t care where she was raised and I don’t care who her father happens to be. And neither should you. Liz Cheney deserves more respect and substantive attention. She is among the most vicious, cynical and talented partisan operatives in American public life. She helped led the appalling campaign against the so-called “Ground Zero mosque.” Her political action committee baselessly accused several Justice Department lawyers of al-Qaida sympathies. Time and again, she has rooted her political attacks not in policy differences but in an easy, slimy willingness to suggest that President Obama and his administration are disloyal to this country. “Whose side are they on?” she asks. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- And, yikes, her foreign policy! It’s just this breathless, nervous, aimless belligerence. (There is plenty of good stuff here at the YouTube page of the PAC she founded with William Kristol.) For example, of modest spending cuts at the Pentagon (in part, quite sensibly, because of the end of the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan) she said: “What President Obama is doing is something that America’s enemies – the Taliban, al Qaeda – have been unable to do: which is to decimate the fighting capability of this nation.” Cute. Cheney in recent years has also come out against withdrawing troops from Iraq and Afghanistan, closing Guantánamo, reading terrorism suspects their Miranda rights, and trying terrorism cases on U.S. soil. This is a position that, oddly, became commonplace among a certain conservative set even though it is obviously weak and cowardly to suggest that terrorists are too scary to try in our courts or hold in our jails. It’s also hammer-to-the-head stupid because we have done it countless times before. Oh, and by the way, she’s also one of those fantastic people who likes to deny the existence of climate change whenever it snows. Now, it is hard to tell where Liz Cheney’s ideology ends and her cynicism begins. (She – unlike, say, Sen. James Inhofe – is certainly too smart to believe that climate change is a hoax.) But it doesn’t so much matter. The toxic brew of fervor and contempt that Liz Cheney offers is at the core of what plagues the Republican Party today. Sure, I am a Democrat, and I know this means, despite my best efforts, that I am prone to being too hard on conservatives and too easy on liberals. It also means that I tend to have greater appreciation for moderation in Republicans than in Democrats. Nonetheless, it to me seems indisputable that the Republican Party is heading toward a reckoning. This reckoning will take place when smart, reasonable, passionate, decent conservatives take their movement back from those like Liz Cheney who have encouraged the kind of radicalization that has made governing nearly impossible, who think “compromise is akin to communism,” as former Wyoming Sen. Alan Simpson said to the Times. (To that point, in Cheney’s announcement video, which was mostly aimed at President Obama, she took two veiled swipes at her primary opponent, Sen. Mike Enzi: criticizing those who “[cut] deals with the President’s liberal allies” and promising to “never compromise when our freedom is at stake.”) Now, obviously, it is important to note: If Liz Cheney were to win she would without a doubt be a shittier senator than Mike Enzi, but only because Mike Enzi is an honorable and decent man. On policy grounds, he is very conservative. Beyond a proposal to levy a sales tax on Internet purchases, it’s hard to find a conservative mark against him. For the most part, it seems Liz Cheney is really only troubled by two facts: that Mike Enzi isn’t enough of an #$%$ and Liz Cheney isn’t enough of a senator. But the fact that Mike Enzi has failed some purity test for many conservatives, for a few meager attempts at compromise and a reasonable proposal to level the playing field for brick-and-mortar companies (and, one suspects, for failing to use the kind of fire-and-brimstone rhetoric that has become common on the right), tells you all you need to know about the state of conservatism today. America needs a strong, positive, rational conservative movement that appeals to a wider range of voters; that offers market-oriented policies and shows a willingness to work with Democrats; that serves as a check against the centrist liberal philosophy that is now, like it or not, the natural home of the majority of Americans. That is the conservative counterweight that would serve America well. But it will only be possible if the Republican Party faces its demons and the shrill and strange voices that now dominate. Liz Cheney’s candidacy will help force that conversation, and it is one the country sorely needs. In the same interview with the Times, Alan Simpson, the former senator of Wyoming, said that a contest between Liz Cheney and Mike Enzi might bring about “the destruction of the Republican Party in Wyoming.” Maybe that’s right. And maybe that’s what has to happen. Perhaps the Republican Party needs to hit rock bottom and Liz Cheney is the last shot of rail tequila before the conservative movement blacks out, wakes up and heads to a meeting. One can only hope. Liz Cheney for Senate.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374104078067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:34:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374104278242-208</Id><Topic><Title>Possibly 400 waffles one weekend</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374103161109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:19:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>400 waffles sp.corporal into your Sgt. acct</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374104278242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374104397707-209</Id><Title>Bachmann’s ethics troubles escalate</Title><Msg>Bachmann’s ethics troubles escalate A House ethics panel is now reviewing allegations that Bachmann's 2012 campaign violated campaign finance laws By Jillian Rayfield A House Ethics Committee panel will review allegations that Rep. Michele Bachmann’s 2012 presidential campaign violated campaign finance and other ethics rules, escalating the congressional probe of the campaign’s dealings. The Minneapolis Star-Tribune reports that the independent Office of Congressional Ethics (OCE), which was reviewing seven cases related to Bachmann’s campaign, sent all of them to the House Ethics Committee, an indication that they had “substantial reason” to believe that ethics violations had occurred. From the Star-Tribune: -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Under rules set forth for the ethics board, there was no public disclosure Tuesday of the individual cases transmitted for further review by the House ethics committee. Instead, the report included a general summary of the board’s actions showing that it did not dismiss or terminate any cases in the past three months, the same period that Bachmann has been under investigation. William McGinley, a Washington attorney for the Bachmann campaign, disputed the suggestion that none of the allegations against her were dropped, although he didn’t say what claims the OCE might have referred for dismissal. Bachmann, who recently announced that she would not seek reelection in 2014, is facing investigations by the FBI, the FEC and an Iowa state Senate ethics committee, in addition to the OCE, over the various allegations. Her campaign is accused of stealing an email list from a campaign volunteer, making improper payments to the Iowa chairman of her campaign and using campaign staffers to promote Bachmann’s book, among other things.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374104397707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374104588245-210</Id><Title>Thought Of The Day</Title><Msg>Shouldn't I have heard at least one right-winger today say, "if only Trayvon had been carrying a gun. He'd be alive today"?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374104588245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374105615288-211</Id><Topic><Title>I 'd rather have a wing than a tail</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374097861785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:51:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>payed attention who we got sorta... blam blam blam blam and blam if someone beat my head onto the concrete one time the foresenic evidence would not lie</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374105615288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374105724471-212</Id><Title>Niece: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Would Not Wear A Hoodie</Title><Msg>Niece of the slain civil rights leader says we need to stop dividing ourselves by race. Kit Daniels July 17, 2013 Dr. Alveda King, niece of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., rejected the now-viral image showing the late civil rights leader wearing a hoodie just like the one Travyon Martin wore the night of his death. MLK Hoodie – April 4th, 1968 by Nikkolas Smith courtesy of Deviant Art “Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. would very likely not wear a hoodie,” she said. “I can assure you he would not wear sagging pants.” Dr. King made this statement on the Andrea Tantaros Radio Show on Tuesday after being asked what she thought of the image entitled MLK Hoodie – April 4th, 1968. “I can almost promise you Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. would not wear a hoodie,” she further emphasized later in the interview. Dr. King also said that people need to think with grace rather than emotions in reference to the image and the overall backlash to the George Zimmerman verdict. “There was a reasonable doubt in that case,” she said. “So the case went the ways of the laws of this land, but now we need to go further and look at the human heart.” Dr. King also called out the mongers in the media and elsewhere who are trying to spin the verdict into racial tensions between Caucasians and African-Americans. “As far as trying to fit the Caucasians against African-Americans, Mr. Zimmerman is a Hispanic,” she said. “Although we are one blood, one human family, one human race, there’s a lot of deception and emotion in these things that are being spurred.” “Mr. Zimmerman is not a Caucasian. He’s not.” Even when her uncle was assassinated in 1968, Dr. King said that it wasn’t fair to blame it on Caucasians. Right before her father left home in order to retrieve the body of the slain civil rights leader, she said</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1374105724471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374105980497-213</Id><Title>Open Lincoln in New Window</Title><Msg>No I do like the CEO of yahooty here or there possibly there</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374105980497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374106090376-214</Id><Topic><Title>Thought Of The Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374104588245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've got to have something between your ears to have a thought. Something to think about when you come up with some grey matter. Zimmerman had a legal to carry gun having a clean record, and able to get one. Martin was a delinquent that was caught with stolen property, and marijuana possession. The punk could have never got a licence to carry.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1374106090376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374106294716-215</Id><Topic><Title>'The Wire' Creator David Simon on Trayvon Martin Case: 'Ashamed' to Be an American</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374077653394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... Former president Jimmy Carter said the jury in the George Zimmerman trial "made the right decision" and agrees with President Obama that Americans should respect its judgment. Zimmerman, a neighborhood watch volunteer, was acquitted last Saturday in the shooting death of Florida teenager Trayvon Martin. Carter, the nation's 39th president, made his comments about the high-profile case in an interview Tuesday with WXIA in Atlanta. STORY: 'Justice for Trayvon' rallies planned "I think the jury made the right decision based on the evidence presented because the prosecution inadvertently set the standard so high that the jury had to be convinced that it was a deliberate act by Zimmerman and that he was not at all defending himself," Carter said...</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1374106294716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374106591406-216</Id><Title>The price for a CEO remains the same = 0*</Title><Msg>for the CEO of YHOO pay me</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374106591406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374106723611-217</Id><Topic><Title>The price for a CEO remains the same = 0*</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374106591406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stinky bauch</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374106723611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374107018734-218</Id><Topic><Title>Thought Of The Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374104588245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He had no criminal record.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374107018734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374107075202-219</Id><Topic><Title>The price for a CEO remains the same = 0*</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374106591406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IAM over it now. Fire on a BA plane. Those bass-turds.</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374107075202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374107698676-220</Id><Topic><Title>The price for a CEO remains the same = 0*</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374106591406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nanosecond</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374107698676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:34:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374108192469-221</Id><Topic><Title>I 'd rather have a wing than a tail</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374097861785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:51:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>right hip</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374108192469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374108623434-222</Id><Topic><Title>Open Lincoln in New Window</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374105980497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nor Thrice...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374108623434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374108944651-223</Id><Title>Stinky Bauch CEO*</Title><Msg>for the fun of IT and use IT generously</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374108944651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374110130112-224</Id><Title>More Consequences from Obamacare</Title><Msg>New York state residents will be able to get health insurance next year on the Obamacare exchange for half the average price available in the state today. The cost of a "silver" plan -- which covers at least 70% of medical costs, on average -- will drop to as little as $359 a month for a single adult Manhattan resident, for instance, according to a rate sheet released Wednesday by state officials. Currently, the cheapest plan a city resident can buy on the individual market is $1,001.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1374110130112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374110351598-225</Id><Title>The line is too long....</Title><Msg>apparently I was putting too much of the best BBQ in between two buns this side of the Pecos my first 2 rodeos</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374110351598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374110742680-226</Id><Topic><Title>The line is too long....</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374110351598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that is so wrong you are such a liar let me ] light your fire</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374110742680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374111211219-227</Id><Title>Easy</Title><Msg>to sell hate.... the bisbee angler</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374111211219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374111472830-228</Id><Topic><Title>More Consequences from Obamacare</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1374110130112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:15:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one likes ObamaCare. The ones that do have been exempted. Now three progressive unions just indicated they must speak out against it. Another libtard policy failure in a long list of failures. This one is going gunnysack before it even gets fully implemented.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1374111472830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:37:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374111818123-229</Id><Title>The Russians must have snow in their ears...</Title><Msg>or else We ain't playin' Soschi that is the facts lit my fire</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374111818123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374111886553-230</Id><Topic><Title>The Russians must have snow in their ears...</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374111818123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:43:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the time-space machine is real</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374111886553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374112040690-231</Id><Topic><Title>The Russians must have snow in their ears...</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374111818123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:43:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CAN we discuss this..,..</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374112040690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374112473029-232</Id><Topic><Title>Winning One for Snowden</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1374088198251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:09:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about, Congressional committee members voiced extreme displeasure with the NSA for going beyond its stated missions and purposely keeping Congress in the dark regarding NSA activities.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1374112473029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374112776842-233</Id><Topic><Title>The Russians must have snow in their ears...</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374111818123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:43:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the rooskies call thatisschnee; let me chck my time charts concerning the snow charts ifor Soischi]and can we havew another 12,000 pie charts</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374112776842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374113008059-234</Id><Topic><Title>The Russians must have snow in their ears...</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374111818123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:43:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tips for what to do, how to do it, how to not splooge all over too quick are appreciated!!</Msg><Username>husseindamuud</Username><Timestamp>1374113008059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374113621393-235</Id><Topic><Title>Winning One for Snowden</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1374088198251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:09:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would you critique a post by Phantom that Demands the NSA stop spying on us ? War you Anti American ? Why would you call someone insane when you are insane for not defending freedom like a red blodded American ? Go away commie</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1374113621393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374113948327-236</Id><Topic><Title>The line is too long....</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374110351598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>truth</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374113948327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374114155232-237</Id><Topic><Title>The line is too long....</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374110351598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judge Roy Bean was the judge west of the Pecos. Now there was a judge that knew how to handle radical liberals.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1374114155232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374114875369-238</Id><Title>I'm ashamed that Hooz is an American</Title><Msg>What a limp wristed crybaby race pimp. ROTFLMAO</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374114875369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374114893109-239</Id><Topic><Title>The Russians must have snow in their ears...</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374111818123</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:43:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but you don't understand packed snow in their ears all of them must have light my fire go.... soschi</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374114893109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374114991960-240</Id><Topic><Title>Thought Of The Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1374104588245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't been around in a while so I thought I would check in. Looks like hoozdik is still at it. Why is it hooz that 50+ people were gunned down in Chicago during this trial but all you libs want to talk about is Travon Martin? I bet you can't name 3 of those 54 people who were gunned down. Their deaths didn't fit your left wing agenda.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1374114991960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374115201748-241</Id><Topic><Title>The line is too long....</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374110351598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ibex says russians spell soschi as soshi</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374115201748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374115655351-242</Id><Title>lLike who would invite me to Soshi 2014</Title><Msg>the bombs will be in the teapot shaped thingys called puks or curls oh well until we meet again not a one will invite me</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374115655351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374115662378-243</Id><Topic><Title>I'm ashamed that Hooz is an American</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1374114875369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's an embarrassment. I would say he cant possibly believe what he posts though. It HAS to be an elaborate scam since no one can POSSIBLY believe what he posts and still call themselves Americans</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1374115662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374117090597-244</Id><Topic><Title>The line is too long....</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374110351598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If had to guess the french(?) gal who said she dragged the mattress onto the balconey to make love last night because it was so hot/awesome who taught two weeks of German A.M. Guten morgen Guten tag Guten nacht Guten abend I believed her She picked me...well there you go again the Col and the LTC will have to wait their turn</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374117090597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374117864611-245</Id><Title>AMD, GOOG, MSFT, SWY, AND VZ</Title><Msg>WHAT;S FOUR WINNERS IN A ROW</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374117864611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374118037184-246</Id><Topic><Title>AMD, GOOG, MSFT, SWY, AND VZ</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374117864611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:24:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be unholy. Take a bath</Msg><Username>faithflagfamily</Username><Timestamp>1374118037184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374118635064-247</Id><Topic><Title>lLike who would invite me to Soshi 2014</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374115655351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:47:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like they say the 12,000</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374118635064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374119280389-248</Id><Title>Pink Floyd - Heart Beat, Pig Meat (Zabriskie Point)</Title><Msg>type message</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1374119280389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>