<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365483107367-1</Id><Title>Airbus invests 13 billion per year in American companies and uses American workers, now another 1000</Title><Msg>Airbus had led Boeing for 11 years , now with the new plant being built with american workers and utilizing american assemblers Aribus will now begin production of their 787 beater, Airbus has made their shareholders over 100% return for 5 years while Boeing has offloaded engineering and work to sub par contractors and the failed lemon 787 , a decertified flying firetrap with a containment vessel , 30 billion over cost and 3 years late is the result. The USA needs to outsource just one more department the Boeing Executives need to be replaced by French managment</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365483107367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 00:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365499540824-2</Id><Topic><Title>CommieCare "Navigators"</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365021934620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:45:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's just a DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365499540824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 05:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365499731004-3</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the names of my aliases?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365465918538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 20:05:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Projecting" is his most common defense mechanism..................notice his constant use of the word "loon" to describe anyone who either doesn't believe his fairy tales or tries to disclose the truth.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365499731004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 05:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365499789705-4</Id><Topic><Title>CommieCare "Navigators"</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365021934620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 16:45:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't Col Mustard suspend as kissing here many moons ago? You DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365499789705</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 05:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365499860428-5</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the names of my aliases?</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365465918538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 20:05:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one funny DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365499860428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 05:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365503964758-6</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I so wish President Obama had lived up to the award he was given. Instead he has chosen to continue and expand the horrors being perpetrated by our country. War is not ever the answer." Carol G., Goshen, IN "Droning people to death is not peace." William S., New York, NY "Not being George W. Bush was never sufficient ground for this award, and Mr. Obama's enthusiastic support for the extension of empire, fossil fuels, raw military power, and other violence against the earth and its people is further evidence of its unwisdom." Scott W., Durham, NC</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365503964758</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 06:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365505110177-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven is orly taint and hooz</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365395848946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 00:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obvious ? To be sure...but what is pitifully sad is how a poor wretch like the Raven spends his whole wasted life on this board trying to justify himself to others by continuously signing in under different IDs in order to try and impress others........</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365505110177</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 06:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365505218084-8</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One must walk the walk of peace, not just talk the talk of peace in order to earn the Peace Prize." Paul M., Los Angeles, CA "Drone Bombs create more terrorists than they kill." Jay J., Roachdale, IN "A war criminal is not worthy of the Nobel Peace Prize." Lars P., Afton, WI "Our President had an unprecedented opportunity to effect a turn-around in foreign policy after the illegal and failed wars of his predecessor. He was hired to do so; but he has squandered the opportunity and has in fact increased U.S. aggression. He does not deserve to be known as a Nobel Peace Prize recipient." Lynn J., Roslyn, PA</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365505218084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 07:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365505461812-9</Id><Title>General Boykin and 700 Special Ops officers DEMAND Benghazi Congressional Investigation</Title><Msg>Seven hundred retired Military Special Operations professionals from the organization “Special Operations Speaks” sent a letter to the House of Representatives urging members to support H.Res 36, which will create a House Select Committee to investigate last September’s deadly terrorist attack in Benghazi, Libya. “It appears that many of the facts and details surrounding the terrorist attack which resulted in four American deaths and an undetermined number of American casualties have not yet been ascertained by previous hearings and inquiries,” the letter states. It continues further, “Additional information is now slowly surfacing in the media, which makes a comprehensive bipartisan inquiry an imperative. Many questions have not been answered thus far.” The letter puts forth over twenty unanswered questions the select committee should address. Congressman Frank Wolf, a sub-committee chairman on the House Appropriations Committee, issued a resolution for a House Select Committee to investigate issues surrounding the Benghazi Attack last November in the 112th Congress. He re-issued his resolution for the select committee when the 113th Congress began. The resolution currently has over 60 co–sponsors. Only Speaker John Boehner (R–OH) can appoint a Select Committee and Boehner appears to mainly rely on the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence to investigate the Benghazi attack. However, any information that may be garnered from that committee will, as always, remain classified. “As a retired Special Operations officer who spent most of my thirty-six years preparing for and executing rescue missions to save fellow Americans, I am deeply troubled by the events in Benghazi on September 11, 2012. The men and women who I served with lived by an ethos that pledged to never leave a fallen comrade and to make every effort to respond when a fellow American was threatened. I have seen men take great risks to save a fellow warrior. I have even seen men die trying to</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365505461812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 07:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365505742413-10</Id><Title>Obama is stuck with all the evidence of SSN fraud</Title><Msg>Obama is stuck with all the evidence of SSN fraud, stolen CT SSN 042-68-4425, which was assigned to Harrison Bounel, forged IDs, Indonesian citizenship. If Congress, Dep of Justice, AGs and Judges do not act immediately in prosecuting Obama, they should be prosecuted as accomplices in this RICO scheme</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365505742413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 07:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365506706016-11</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven is orly taint and hooz</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365395848946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 00:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, he does create and use aliases in order to try to impress others and it only makes him look like a useless fool.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365506706016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 07:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365507041404-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven is orly taint and hooz</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365395848946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 00:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the anatomy of a wasted life</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365507041404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 07:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365508876132-13</Id><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Msg>All those who value free speech, art, public protests, internet blogs and due process should be waging an all-out information war right now to defend the Second Amendment. Why? Because if the Second Amendment is lost due to unconstitutional legislative and executive actions pursued by the government, then there are no limits to what civil liberties and individual freedoms the government can declare null and void. All those who are arguing for infringements of Second Amendment liberties (universal registration, banning AR-15s, criminalizing high-capacity magazines, etc.) are effectively arguing to hand the federal government the precedent it needs to criminalize free speech, religion, public protests, internet blogs, Youtube videos and more. In effect, gun grabbers are arguing for the government to have the power to overturn the Bill of Rights when it is popular to do so. But such power will inevitably end up being used in circumstances never envisioned by the gun grabbers… and often in the hands of someone they hoped would never hold the office of President such as a third member of the Bush regime. The Bill of Rights isn’t optional You can’t have a half-way Bill of Rights. The Bill of Rights either means what it says and strictly limits the reach of the federal government, or it means nothing and all the individual rights and liberties enumerated in the Bill of Rights are null and void. Those include the right to exercise whatever religion you choose and not have the state mandate what church you must attend; the right to speak your mind and even criticize the government without fear of being prosecuted for your opinions; the right to due process and a trial of your peers if charged with a crime; and the right to be safe in your person and effects (your home) without being subjected to illegal searches and seizures.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365511045358-14</Id><Title>NK Warns foreigners to Leave SK</Title><Msg>Toning down the rhetoric will not stop the immature lunatic from his ambition to do nuclear harm to either SK, the US or Japan. He has declared war against the US. and SK. When one country declares war against other countries it should sound alarms, NK is preparing for a hot war with SK and the US. A short to medium range nuclear head missile launch is NK's immediate goal. The war has started. Wake up you sleepy heads!</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1365511045358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:37:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365511419808-15</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no schedule out yet for today, though weekly standard has produced a preview... 7:30PM THE PRESIDENT and THE FIRST LADY host a concert celebrating Memphis Soul music as part of their “In Performance at the White House” series; THE PRESIDENT delivers remarks yesterday's schedule spent exploiting newtown to take away our guns was released sometime AFTER noon.... 11:15 AM The President receives the Presidential Daily Briefing 12:00 PM The President meets with senior advisors 3:05 PM The President departs the White House en route Joint Base Andrews 3:20 PM The President departs Joint Base Andrews 4:30 PM The President arrives Hartford, Connecticut 5:45 PM The President delivers remarks on common-sense measures to reduce gun violence 6:45 PM The President departs Hartford, Connecticut 8:00 PM The President arrives Joint Base Andrews 8:15 PM The President arrives the White House</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365511419808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365511911066-16</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven is orly taint and hooz</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365395848946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 00:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna why are you so feminine......were you unable to grow a pair?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365511911066</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365513476443-17</Id><Title>Will Obama Engage As A Leader Or Triangulate?</Title><Msg>Repubs expressing possibility of getting something done with Dems with respect to the budget, debt and tax reforms. Sure would be nice if both parties can work out a deal.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1365513476443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365513503540-18</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey mowraun have you ever heard of the election process which is utilized in the United States?? You must be agreeing that its corrupt and due to republicans monkeying with elections and due to their gerrymandering they own the House of Representatives- these should be criminal offenses- and in all likelyhood will be remedied in the coming century. Your paranoia about 1st and 2nd amendments though can be cured with antipsychotic medication. Check with your psychiatrist</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365513503540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365513519126-19</Id><Title>Airbus to add 1000 USA workers ,stock up 112% in 5 years ,Boeing layoff 1000 and stock up 4% in 5 years</Title><Msg>Are there any more de-certified 787 flying today? Only 3 years late ,30 billion over budget and a fire starter with a continment vessle that weights twice as much as planned. The new factory for the Airbus assembly is based in the USA and will employ 1000 american workers and Airbus purchases 13 billion for the USA suppliers per year. Airbus stock is up 112% for 5 years , compared to Boeing shareholders have made 4% gain in 5 years . In three years Airbus stock is up and returned th american shareholders 147% while Boeing has returned its shareholders 22%. Soon the Airbus company will start buying back 15% of its shares like Boeing has been doing to inflate its worthless share price</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365513519126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:18:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365513673486-20</Id><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Msg>Why are they so afraid of freedom? Why do they feel they need for a nanny government to regulate every aspect of their lives?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365513779704-21</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in other words the need to be armed to the teeth in a democracy is sheer lunacy when you can change members of govt in elections and avoid dictatorial governments by voting them out or recalling them- try and concentrate on that idea</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365513779704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365513782564-22</Id><Topic><Title>please , please , please , is t here a Boeing Hack that can tell us if the decertified 787 is flying today</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365434660083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 11:24:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is the de-certified 787 test experimental flying today it is so important to the investors who have made 4% return on their investment in 5 years compared to american investors who have made 147% return on investment in Airbus in only 3 years !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365513782564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365513783660-23</Id><Title>New High$$$</Title><Msg>Go Boeing kick some!!!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365513783660</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365513901043-24</Id><Topic><Title>Red Flag alert Boeing is a laggard stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365194780135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any more decertified 787 test flying today ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365513901043</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365514046182-25</Id><Topic><Title>General Boykin and 700 Special Ops officers DEMAND Benghazi Congressional Investigation</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365505461812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 07:04:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Benghazi thing would have been long forgotten except it is being used by RWNJ's to attack the present administration and is without any other raison d'etre. In other words its a typical waste of time by the RWNJs</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365514046182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365514829952-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you need help crossing the street. When you don't have enough sense to come in out of the rain, you want govt control, and loss of freedom.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365514829952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365514975589-27</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"need help crossing the sstreet" almost sounds like the sick, aged and poor doesnt it- you know- that part of the populace which the pukes deny exists or which pukes could care less about</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365514975589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365514979086-28</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A better question is....Doesn't Obama know the powers of congress, and they are the ones that make the laws, pass the bills? Why does this mowraun circumvent congress all the time to get his socialist policies ennacted?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365514979086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365516233960-29</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What needs to be concentrated on is how the fascists in power won power, and how they plan on retaining it. The opposition had better get down and dirty like the fascists in power, and act like they are not in a democracy. What Obama will work on now knowing he can't get his democrats to pass gun control is how to circumvent congress.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365516233960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:03:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365516279228-30</Id><Title>HAS WAYNEDICK NOTICED? OH NO..HE IS WRITING A BOOK!</Title><Msg>New 52 week high in the charts and more to come...</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1365516279228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365516366182-31</Id><Topic><Title>Red Flag alert Boeing is a laggard stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365194780135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 16:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Bird is BACK IN THE AIR....the short squeeze continues. The guy that made the"back in he air" post yesterday...how prophetic was that post? I can smell shorts frying right now.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365516366182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365516592086-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosima, how come dem fascists, err YAHOOs, delete my posts when i post your aliases....they find you aliases offensive, and not you?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365516592086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365516812498-33</Id><Title>Turkish airline order</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - Turkish Airlines (THYAO.IS) has decided to buy a total of 95 narrow-body planes from Boeing (BA.N) by 2021, Turkey's flag carrier said on Tuesday, just weeks after placing a large order with European aircraft maker Airbus (EAD.PA). The fast-growing airline, which is pursuing an aggressive growth strategy as it targets a larger share of the global aviation market, announced 70 firm orders and options to buy a further 25 aircraft from Boeing between 2016-2021. The company placed an order to buy 20 B737-800, 65 B737-8 MAX and 10 B737-9 MAX aircraft, it said in a statement to the Bourse Istanbul.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365516812498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365517269245-34</Id><Topic><Title>HAS WAYNEDICK NOTICED? OH NO..HE IS WRITING A BOOK!</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1365516279228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:04:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Reuters) - French media group Lagardere (LAGA.PA) has sold its 7.4 percent stake in Airbus parent EADS (EAD.PA), kicking off a long-expected overhaul in the ownership of Europe's top aircraft maker. Lagardere raised 2.3 billion euros ($3 billion) through the sale, with EADS spending 500 million euros to buy 1.6 percent of its own shares - a buyback below some analysts' expectations. EADS shares slid more than 4 percent in early trading, then trimmed losses and were down 1.9 percent at 3:28 a.m. ET. (now down 3.4% at 10:20 am EDT). "Many investors we spoke to believed EADS would acquire 1 billion to 1.5 billion euros of the stock being placed by Lagardere," JPMorgan Cazenove analysts said in a research note. "It is unclear why EADS is not taking a bigger share of this placing but it is possible that EADS is prioritizing increasing its free float over the accretion of a buyback." EADS may also want to "retain buyback ‘firepower' to SUPPORT its SHARE PRICEover the next 18 months," the analysts added.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365517269245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365517522946-35</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very nice report !</Msg><Username>mary.grooms</Username><Timestamp>1365517522946</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365517599678-36</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus invests 13 billion per year in American companies and uses American workers, now another 1000</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365483107367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 00:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you suppose that there is a LeWayneker in France who is bad mouthing Airbus for outsoucing jobs to America? Do you suppose that there is a LeWayneker in France who is badmouthing Airbus's 380 for being billions of dollars over budget, years behind schedule and is now developing wing crack? Do you suppose that there is a LeWayneker in France who is disparaging Airbus's management over the 5+ years of delay and overcost associated with the A-400 transport. Do you suppose there is a Frenchie in France who is lamenting because he had invested in Airbus instead of Boeing which is up 187% over the past 4 years?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1365517599678</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365517678801-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(almost sounds like the sick, aged and poor doesnt it) zosima.....you should are free to help the sick, aged and poor all you want - that's freedom, ain't it great! However, if you want to help them with other people's money taken by force - that's thievery.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365517678801</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365517918167-38</Id><Title>Education for zosima</Title><Msg>"Once one accepts the principle of self-ownership, what's moral and immoral becomes self-evident. Murder is immoral because it violates private property. Rape and theft are also immoral -- they also violate private property. Here's an important question: Would rape become morally acceptable if Congress passed a law legalizing it? You say: "What's wrong with you, Williams? Rape is immoral plain and simple, no matter what Congress says or does!" If you take that position, isn't it just as immoral when Congress legalizes the taking of one person's earnings to give to another? Surely if a private person took money from one person and gave it to another, we'd deem it theft and, as such, immoral. Does the same act become moral when Congress takes people's money to give to farmers, airline companies or an impoverished family? No, it's still theft, but with an important difference: It's legal, and participants aren't jailed." -- Walter Williams</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365517918167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365518038436-39</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus invests 13 billion per year in American companies and uses American workers, now another 1000</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365483107367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 00:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waynedick (lewaynaker) is a fired employee of boeing..what u expect!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1365518038436</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365518459958-40</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus invests 13 billion per year in American companies and uses American workers, now another 1000</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365483107367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 00:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, Dell, the A320 is going to beat the 787? At least, try to get your facts right!! HarHarHar!!! BTW, they said they plan on assembling the planes in about two years. Not now!!! Try and keep up with the rest of us!!!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1365518459958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:40:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365518510598-41</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not thievery; it's something called civilization. About which you clearly have no clue. Have you ever fed your neglected mind with anything but Bastiat and Rand?</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1365518510598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365518963924-42</Id><Title>increased price target</Title><Msg>From wall street cheat sheet. By Alex Capel April 09, 2013 Boeing (NYSE:BA): According to Argus, Boeing’s 787 planes should be allowed to fly again “within weeks.” The firm thinks that Boeing will then resume delivery of the planes. The research firm has increased its price target on the stock to $96 from $88, while keeping a Buy rating on the shares.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365518963924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365519150349-43</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The opposite of civilization it when you take the property of one person by force and give it to another person - that's called thievery and thievery is not very civilized.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365519150349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365519285781-44</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its the weather underground admin/party, unbounded, community agitating, race n class baiting communism</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365519285781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365519708072-45</Id><Title>Is Taxation Justa Form of thievery?</Title><Msg>Not really - if it's used only to pay the necessary cost of operating essential government services such as Courts, defense, etc. It becomes thievery when you start taxing some individuals for the benefit and enrichment of other individuals and corporations.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365519708072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365519769519-46</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, more like a braindead liberal. But there are a lot more poor out on the streets because of you leftists, and your destructive economic policies.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365519769519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365519853279-47</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hot off the press, he's supposed to release his pretend budget tomorrow, next year he should put his underlings on work sooner or announce he will no longer bother with his constitutional duties inclusive of pretending... 10:30 am The President and the Vice President receive the Presidential Daily Briefing Oval Office Closed Press 11:30 am Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jay Carney 2:00 pm The Vice President and Attorney General Eric Holder deliver remarks at the White House to continue calling on Congress to pass common-sense measures to reduce gun violence South Court Auditorium Open Press 3:00 pm The President and the Vice Presdent meet with Secretary of Defense Hagel Oval Office Closed Press 7:30 pm The President the First Lady host a concert celebrating Memphis Soul music as part of their “In Performance at the White House” series; the President delivers remarks</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365519853279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365519986458-48</Id><Title>Swammy Predicts</Title><Msg>787 FAA approval after 24 April with restrictions. Price per share just south of 80. Restrictions lift &amp; pps resumes its march north.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1365519986458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365520163821-49</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err deleted err list err aliases err offensive err spazmo</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1365520163821</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365520517574-50</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you go girl, i mean sammy / spart / ahkmed</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365520517574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365520650086-51</Id><Topic><Title>Swammy Predicts</Title><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1365519986458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with the march north in PPS. Not sure about restrictions. Either they agree with the changes or they dont. And if they simply want to make sure, how long will they be restricted? It took a long time before the problem showed up.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365520650086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365520919401-52</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus invests 13 billion per year in American companies and uses American workers, now another 1000</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365483107367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 00:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Airbus PPS down 3% today</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365520919401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365521032420-53</Id><Title>Collectivism, Democrats and Taxation</Title><Msg>Taxes to finance certain federal activities are indeed legitimate as well as constitutional. Article I, Section 8 of the U.S. Constitution enumerates just what federal functions Congress has taxing and spending authority. Among them are national defense, Post Office and post roads, courts and a few other activities. Or, as James Madison, the father of our Constitution, explained in Federalist Paper No. 45, "The powers delegated by the proposed Constitution to the federal government are few and defined. Those which are to remain in the State governments are numerous and indefinite. The former will be exercised principally on external objects, as war, peace, negotiation, and foreign commerce; with which last the power of taxation will, for the most part, be connected." Nowhere in our Constitution is there even a hint of authority for most of what Congress taxes and spends for today. Don't be tricked by those who'd argue that Congress has such authority under the Constitution's "general welfare" clause. James Madison explained, "With respect to the two words 'general welfare', I have always regarded them as qualified by the detail of powers connected with them . . .." Thomas Jefferson said, "Congress has not unlimited powers to provide for the general welfare, but only those specifically enumerated." The "detail of powers" or those "specifically enumerated" refer to what's actually laid out in the Constitution. The Framers had the foresight to see that these powers might need modification. That's why they gave us Article V as a means to amend the Constitution. One reader criticized, "The essence of democracy is that the will of the majority conveys legitimacy to actions of the state." That's a sad commentary on both understanding and education. The Founders didn't intend for us to be a democracy but instead a republic. But more importantly, majority rule often confers an aura of legitimacy to acts that would otherwise be deemed tyranny. Let's look at it. Consider a few everyday decisions such as: whom we marry, what food we eat, where we live, and what clothes we wear. How many of us would want majority rule to determine those decisions. For example, your family would like ham for Thanksgiving dinner, and vacation in Mexico but you're prevented from doing so because the majority of Americans decided on turkey for Thanksgiving and vacations in Canada. Were decisions actually made this way, most of us would agree that we'd be living in a state of tyranny. Of course these particular decisions aren't made through a majority rule political process but they do illustrate that there's nothing sacrosanct about majority rule; it can be just another form of tyranny. It's just as tyrannical for majority rule to determine other choices such as: retirement (Social Security), prescription drugs, healthcare and other unconstitutional uses of a person's earnings. When the democratic process reigns in matters of constitutionally enumerated federal government matters, we have the liberty that the Framers envisioned - anywhere else it most likely means tyranny. Walter E. Williams</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365521032420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365521828728-54</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for sharing !</Msg><Username>lucille.coffey</Username><Timestamp>1365521828728</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365521989613-55</Id><Topic><Title>BA Insider Trading Reported !!!</Title><Username>doris.shealey</Username><Timestamp>1361811207875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 11:53:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for sharing !</Msg><Username>lucille.coffey</Username><Timestamp>1365521989613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365522205185-56</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven is orly taint and hooz</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365395848946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 00:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the picture of LIAR, loon. A big mouth with nothing much to say.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365522205185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365522432735-57</Id><Topic><Title>Swammy Predicts</Title><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1365519986458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a government agency that has taken public heat for the lack of battery testing for the original certification. The NTSB, which has no authority to block a return to flight is still making noise. I'm obviously not certain on any restrictions that may be imposed but it makes perfect sense the FAA would want a little coverage on the backside. I believe it would be a token number of flight hours at most. Who knows why those batteries cooked off. Could have been a bad lot, an unfamiliar airline mechanic making an error on installation or it could just be the inherent danger of this type of battery. If the design team had an opportunity for a do-over they may have chosen a lower risk higher weight substitute battery as this has been costly. If there is one hiccup of a battery shareholders will be pounded mercilessly.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1365522432735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365522937933-58</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven is orly taint and hooz</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365395848946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 00:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's also totally crazy.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1365522937933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365523122921-59</Id><Title>Sparty's new cause</Title><Msg>Unable to get any traction for his campaigns to get Obama's birth cert. thrown out, get Obama tried for war crimes, get Obama rejected at the polls in favor of ANY old Randinista, get Obama impeached for fraud or having a bunch of SSANs or being communist/socialist/madras-educated Muslim, or being black, ot being the puppet of space aliens trying to seize our money supply and reduce us all to soylent caramel for the uber-rich, the board's First Lunatic is now trying to get a private board that spends private money to demand the return of a award they gave Obama. And he thinks others spend too much time on this board! Laughable. Pathetic and laughable.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365523122921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365523443222-60</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>racism is your shtik hawfaeces- Obama is the wrong color- and he is about 20 times more the man and more valuable to civilization than you are- thats why you keep on weeping and wailing and gnashing your teeth about it</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365523443222</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365523445272-61</Id><Topic><Title>Collectivism, Democrats and Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365521032420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:23:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leftys love power and control. They like to tell other people what to do and think. That's just they way they roll. We can't change them! So don't vote leftys into positions of power. They don't make very good leaders, unless you believe in government control</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1365523445272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365523631250-62</Id><Topic><Title>Collectivism, Democrats and Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365521032420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:23:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>walter williams knows less about econnomics and constitutional law than my 5 year old grandson- he is paid by the Kochs and the Mellons to tout their skrewey ideas to the world --Williams is a quack!!!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365523631250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365523946589-63</Id><Topic><Title>Education for zosima</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365517918167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy you will go to any extreme to paint taxation as a sin wont you? Nevermind that it is virtually the only way to finance governmental operations. The one thing you should know is that you are a "slacker" The US had to contend with slackers during most of its wars. Slackers wouldnt pay their taxes - the traded on the black markets - they dodged the draft- they did everything possible to prove that they werent worthy Americans. They should have all been deproted. BTW walter williams knows less about econnomics and constitutional law than my 5 year old grandson- he is paid by the Kochs and the Mellons to tout their skrewey ideas to the world --Williams is a quack!!!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365523946589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365524134215-64</Id><Topic><Title>Collectivism, Democrats and Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365521032420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:23:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored are you even a US citizen- you sound like a North Korean- or a Mogadishuan</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365524134215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365524142372-65</Id><Title>The Democrat's Elitism</Title><Msg>Democrat's hate the concept of freedom in general but most vehemently the hate the idea of free markets and capitalism. They believe elitist bureaucrats can make better decisions and therefore should make decisions for individuals rather than giving individuals the freedom to make their own choices. Nowhere is the elitism more apparent than when it comes to spending the money you earn. They want to tell you how much you can work for, how much employers should pay employees, how much suppliers should charge for their goods and services, how much you can pay, what quality you should get for what you pay, how much you should contribute to charitable programs, where your children should spend their education dollars and on and on. Well, how are these elitist doing making these choices? First of all they have the country $17trillion in debt, then the have driven manufacturers to other countries and given us 14% real unemployment/underemployment. Our education ranks 17 of the industrialized countries with several 3rd world countries out preforming us. 47 million on food stamps, disability is epidemic and Obamacare is a disaster. Democrats refuse to admit the reality that socialism does not work but freedom does.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365524142372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365524344663-66</Id><Topic><Title>Education for zosima</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365517918167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"he is paid by the Kochs and the Mellons" Can you prove that or are you just resorting to the favorite liberal tactic of lying when you can't argue with the truth?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365524344663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365524469503-67</Id><Topic><Title>Collectivism, Democrats and Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365521032420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:23:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>speaking of totalitarians, doesn't obama remind you of your hero chavez, born of the same mentality as robert mubage and kim jong un</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365524469503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365524592155-68</Id><Title>expanding South Carolina site</Title><Msg>CHARLESTON, S.C. (AP) -- Boeing Co. is expanding in South Carolina and will invest another $1 billion, creating 2,000 new jobs during the next eight years, the aerospace giant announced Tuesday. Company spokeswoman Candy Eslinger said the company that operates a 787 assembly plant in North Charleston will expand its operations. The first of the new 787s made in South Carolina rolled off the assembly line about a year ago.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365524592155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365524687825-69</Id><Title>The Pukes Elitism</Title><Msg>Pukes hate the concept of freedom in general but most vehemently the hate the idea of free markets, health insurance, medical care, old age pensions and capitalism. They believe RWNJ bagger bureaucrats working for the super rich in a modern Oligarchy can make better decisions and therefore should make decisions for individuals rather than giving individuals the freedom to make their own choices. Nowhere is the this oligarchy more apparent than when it comes to spending the money you earn. They want to tell you how much you can work for, how much employers should pay employees, how much suppliers should charge for their goods and services, how much you can pay, what quality you should get for what you pay, how much you should contribute to charitable programs, where your children should spend their education dollars and on and on. Well, how are these oligarchs doing making these choices? First of all they have the country 11 trillion in debt,(Raygun, Bush I, Bush II) then they have relocated manufacturers to other countries and given us 14% real unemployment/underemployment. Our education ranks 17 of the industrialized countries with several 3rd world countries out preforming us. 47 million on food stamps, disability is epidemic and Obamacare hasent even been implemented yet. Bagger Oligarchs refuse to admit the reality that anti socialism does not work but freedom does. Less</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365524687825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365524883148-70</Id><Topic><Title>The Pukes Elitism</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365524687825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so says gay pedophile / nutsuker "bagger" zosima</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365524883148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365524922147-71</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how does a man like Obama get elected when the pukes and tbaggers have rigged the polls, gerrymandered the US House representative districts, stolen all the money there was outside of Wallstreet and thensome??? Maybe God is a Democrat after all nevermind that republicans have insisted he was a republican for the past 150 years</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365524922147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365524932916-72</Id><Title>airline upgrades</Title><Msg>B/E Aerospace, Inc. (BEAV), the world's leading manufacturer of aircraft cabin interior products and the world's leading distributor of aerospace fasteners and consumables, today announced that one of its airline customers plans to retrofit its fleet of Boeing 737 aircraft with B/E Aerospace modular lavatories. The airline also plans to retrofit its entire fleet of 737 aircraft, with B/E Aerospace Aircraft Ecosystems® vacuum toilets, and eventually to upgrade the cabins of its 737 fleet with B/E Aerospace LED lighting systems.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365524932916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525027254-73</Id><Topic><Title>expanding South Carolina site</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365524592155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This will be good news for SC until the company can extort greater tax breaks somewhere else - then SC will be left twisting in the wind.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1365525027254</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525088334-74</Id><Topic><Title>Is Taxation Justa Form of thievery?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365519708072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:01:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Oil comes to mind.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365525088334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525136414-75</Id><Topic><Title>The Pukes Elitism</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365524687825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored try to contain your anger a little better ok- oh and you really ought to go to a board where you can fit in.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365525136414</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:32:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525245890-76</Id><Topic><Title>Education for zosima</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365517918167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ever hear of Google or Bing?? look it up yourself dum bsas</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365525245890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525338761-77</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the foo sh.ts - wear it hawfaeces</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365525338761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525669194-78</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumbocrafs have used OPM to finanace/grow the enemy within for decades... credit peteetongmain... "this quote was translated into English from an article appearing in the Czech Republic as published in the Prager Zeitung of 28 April 2011. "The danger to America is not Barack Obama but a citizenry capable of entrusting an inexperienced man like him with the Presidency. It will be far easier to limit and undo the follies of an Obama presidency than to restore the necessary common sense and good judgment to a depraved electorate willing to have such a man for their president.. The problem is much deeper and far more serious than Mr. Obama, who is a mere symptom of what ails America. Blaming the prince of the fools should not blind anyone to the vast confederacy of fools that made him their prince.. The Republic can survive a Barack Obama. It is less likely to survive a multitude of Idiots such as those who made him their president.""</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365525669194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525769459-79</Id><Topic><Title>airline upgrades</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365524932916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you hear United is taking reservation for May 31st on the Dreamliner$$ story under the quote page. They know something.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365525769459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525825691-80</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no DICtator worth his salt would allow the people to keep guns, huh contard, i mean a**wipe</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365525825691</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525864494-81</Id><Topic><Title>make at bet...once Post Office cuts back deliveries on Saturday and layoffs</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365521953372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:39:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what Rock did you come out off?? They allready said Saturdays mail will continue!! Go BOEING were flying May 31st united!!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365525864494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365525887147-82</Id><Title>do whatever it takes to prevent a nuclear war!</Title><Msg>do it now.</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1365525887147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525902788-83</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said! Gun lovers, many have sexual dysfunction, it's that simple Druid</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1365525902788</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365525990826-84</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>new id ahkmed?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365525990826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365526192154-85</Id><Topic><Title>The Pukes Elitism</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365524687825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>......zosima is so devoid of any rational intellect that when defending his communistic mentality he has to resort to lying and false accusation in order to maintain some semblance of denial......no matter how obviously ridiculous it is.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365526192154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365526428791-86</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hooz why are you complaining when the droppings of those moose are far more intelligent than the guy Democrats put back in the White house.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365526428791</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365526572980-87</Id><Topic><Title>Education for zosima</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365517918167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 10:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't need to....I wasn't the one making the false and lying accusations.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365526572980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365526583131-88</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'll take sarah anyday, no contest between her n barack hussein our incompetent power hungry marxist community agitator</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365526583131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365526995803-89</Id><Title>Zosima instead of lying about the Kochs and the Mellons to make your point.....</Title><Msg>.....why not just say.....it's George Bush's fault. Yea, I know, that would be lying too.....but it would be hilarious to watch your desperation when you're you've lost all sense of logic.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365526995803</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365527196429-90</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chrissie, did you know commie care forces other people to defray the costs of sex change operations...one more reason to luv your rainbow party n maobowa claus, huh</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365527196429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365527418386-91</Id><Title>Zosima, after exhaustive Searches on Google and Bing ther was no mention.....</Title><Msg>.....of the Kochs and Mellons financially supporting Walter Williams but I did find several articles on Obama being a Marxist.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527418386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365527641490-92</Id><Title>CNN Poll: Obama Underwater on Key Issues</Title><Msg>Economy: 44% Approve, 54% Disapprove Federal Budget Deficit: 38% Approve, 58% Disapprove Taxes: 46% Approve, 52% Disapprove Illegal Immigration: 44% Approve, 50% Disapprove Gun Policy: 45% Approve, 52% Disapprove Health care policy: 44% Approve, 54% Disapprove Social Security and Medicare: 44% Approve, 52% Disapprove</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527641490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365528599814-93</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for this report</Msg><Username>willian.madrigal</Username><Timestamp>1365528599814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365528645728-94</Id><Topic><Title>airline upgrades</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365524932916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I saw that. They would not have done that without knowng something positive about a return to flight of teh 787. I suspect we will see more clues in the days ahead.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365528645728</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365528744248-95</Id><Topic><Title>Zosima, after exhaustive Searches on Google and Bing ther was no mention.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527418386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:10:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima is ignorant , uneducated and just down right stupid. No sense try to have an intelligent discussion with him....ain't gonna happen. Same goes for hoozdik.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365528744248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365529478795-96</Id><Topic><Title>airline upgrades</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365524932916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have some kind of code compliance thing of not talking about an ongoing Investigation but the news always gets leaked out somehow.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365529478795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365529592580-97</Id><Title>Obama--Who Pays Men 13% More Than Women--Proclaims 'Equal Pay Day'</Title><Msg>President Barack Obama designated April 9 as National Equal Pay Day, even though 70 percent of White House staffers in the top-salary bracket were men, and male White House staffers earn on average 13 percent more than female staffers. “To grow our middle class and spur progress in the years ahead, we need to address longstanding inequity that keeps women from earning a living equal to their efforts,” Obama said in the proclamation released Monday evening. “That is why I have made pay equity a top priority -- from signing the Lilly Ledbetter Fair Pay Act days after I took office to cracking down on equal pay law violations wherever they occur. And to back our belief in equality with the weight of law, I continue to call on the Congress to pass the Paycheck Fairness Act.” CNS News reported on March 15 that 70 percent of White House staffers earning the maximum salary of $172,200 last year were men and 30 percent were women, according to the White House numbers posted on staff compensation. Further, men on the White House staff are paid $86,260.89 on average. Women on the White House staff are paid an average of $76,162.65. So men on the White House staff are paid about 13.26 percent more than women. Put another way, women earn 88.29 percent of what men earn. This has been a pattern for Obama dating back to the days before he became president. In 2008, CNS reported that then-Sen. Obama, on average, paid women on his Senate staff only 78 percent of what he paid men--with the average man on Obama's Senate staff getting an annual salary of $57,425.00 and the average woman getting an annual salary or $44,953.21. Tuesday’s proclamation said, “When working mothers make less than their male counterparts, they have less to spend on basic necessities like child care, groceries, and rent.”</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365529592580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365529635295-98</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Poll: Obama Underwater on Key Issues</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527641490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch democrats turn against our socialist leader as they head towards re-election. Obama is so radical left he asks a lot of his collegues to commit professional suicide. Like take one for the Gipper.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365529635295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365529688667-99</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Poll: Obama Underwater on Key Issues</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527641490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a bad case of buyer's remorse setting in.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365529688667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365529817294-100</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Poll: Obama Underwater on Key Issues</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527641490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now there is a long list of big hollywood contributors, leftist kooks, telling the President, "Come ON, MR. Pres. We are some of your biggest contributors!....relax the Prison sentences for drug use, and up the rehab programs! HAHAHA They bring on the drug use, and then want the tax payer again, to foot the rehab programs.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365529817294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365531915811-101</Id><Topic><Title>Zosima, after exhaustive Searches on Google and Bing ther was no mention.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527418386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:10:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Koch and George Mason University Koch and George Mason University Funding and Connections Since 1985, George Mason University (GMU), and its associated institutes and centers, has received more funding from the Koch Family Charitable Foundations than any other organization--a total of $29,604,354. The George Mason University Foundation has received the most funding, $20,297,143, while the Institute for Humane Studies has been directly given $3,111,457, the Mercatus Center $1,442,000, and George Mason University itself has received $4,753,754. In addition to financial ties, Koch also has personnel involved with the university. Richard Fink, the vice president of Koch Industries, Inc., and the former president of the Charles G. Koch Foundation and the Claude R. Lambe Foundation, serves on the board of directors of the Mercatus Center. Fink's connection to George Mason University is strong. Besides teaching at the university from 1980-1986, Fink has also served on a number of boards at the university including the Institute for Humane Studies and the Center for the Study of Public Choice, the Board of Visitors, and the Student Affairs Committee. The Institute for Humane Studies The Institute for Humane Studies (IHS) was founded by F.A. Harper in 1961 and has been associated with George Mason University since 1985. The mission of the IHS is "to support the achievement of a free society by discovering and facilitating the development of talented, productive students, scholars and other intellectuals who share a commitment to liberty and who demonstrate the potential to change significantly the current climate of opinion to one more congenial to the principles and practices of freedom." The Institute for Humane Studies provides $600,000 in scholarships each year. According to SourceWatch, the IHS acts as "a libertarian talent scout, identifying, developing, and supporting the brightest young libertarians it can find who are intent on a lever</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365531915811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 14:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365532057060-102</Id><Topic><Title>Zosima, after exhaustive Searches on Google and Bing ther was no mention.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527418386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:10:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walter Williams works for Koch, Mellon and Olin funded organizations like George Mason U, the Cato Institute the Heritige Foundations and the "Institute for Humane Studies" which are all funded by the Kochs, Mellons, Olins and other super rich wannabe Oligarchs</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365532057060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 14:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365534939294-103</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: The guy Americans put back in the White House. And they were way more intelligent than a guy like you who eats moose droppings so much he knows how intelligent moose droppings are.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365534939294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365534994264-104</Id><Topic><Title>The Pukes Elitism</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365524687825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:24:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did you have to quit using hope4whitepeople? Did Yahoo! recognize your contributions to this board and remove you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365534994264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535100275-105</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indeed. All you have to do is read all their posts about sissies, effeminates, and so on and you quickly see how concerned they are about their manliness. They think that manliness is solely a factor of magazine capacity.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365535100275</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535269912-106</Id><Topic><Title>Zosima, after exhaustive Searches on Google and Bing ther was no mention.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365527418386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 13:10:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima.....by your' warped logic, Obama works for George Soros and Peter Lewis and every communist who has donated to "Organizing for Action."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365535269912</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535537399-107</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty's new cause</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365523122921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:58:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next they will be trying something brand new: a sane Republican candidate somewhere, sometime, somehow. Pritnear a novel concept for spartalOOn and company.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1365535537399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535695040-108</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>commie care n censored n bumper n fascist n welfare bum n maobowa claus n spazmo</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1365535695040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535784421-109</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty's new cause</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365523122921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:58:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that's the scary part . A fascist in power that has defied our system, and no traction on any of his blatant violations has gained traction...flatout scary. Let's hope justice prevails here soon.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365535784421</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535823421-110</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sarahmo barracudamo err spazmo err half-term governormo err spazmo err censoredbumperfascistmo likes sarah's rackmo err spaz err Marxistmo err spazMOmoMOmo err islaMOspaz mo</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1365535823421</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:30:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535923631-111</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DICmo err I mean censored err I mean contard err I mean spaz err I mean censoredmo err I mean bumper err I mean spaz</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1365535923631</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365535925818-112</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty's new cause</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365523122921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:58:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You defile our system, jokey dokey. You and all the other right-fringers who get tired of griping about tiny and inconsequential missteps and so start to fabricate bigger ones.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365535925818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365536040994-113</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahkmed err I mean dumbocrafs err I mean OPM err err I mean spartaloon err err I mean peteetongmain err translation err err I mean err err err err err momomomomoMOmo err I mean spazMO</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1365536040994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:34:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365536530410-114</Id><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Msg>In testimony before the Oregon legislature, a survivor of the communist revolution shared his harrowing story. Manuel Martinez, who claims to have lived through the communist uprising in Cuba, told the legislators about the atrocities that can take place once freedom is lost. He chastised those who seek to impose new restrictions on gun ownership:</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365536638226-115</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get allot of Twitter foolwers.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365536638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365536746622-116</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty's new cause</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365523122921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:58:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sure have your panties in a wad defending Obama and his Marxism.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536746622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:45:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365537082014-117</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty's new cause</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365523122921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 11:58:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't defend, and have no need to defend Obama from wild-eyed accusations for which you have no proof and cannot even provide a specific example. It's just the same as how I am not in the business of explaining your nightmares to you and assuring you that you have no reason to be afraid.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365537082014</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365537304698-118</Id><Title>Despite Sequestration the Obamas Continue Lavish Parties at Tax Payer’s Expense</Title><Msg>Sequester? What sequester? The White House is still closed to the public and little school children on spring break but it'll be open tonight as President Obama hosts a slew of celebrities for yet another lavish party. Tonight’s special White House “celebration” of Memphis soul music marks the tenth time President and Mrs. Obama have been treated to an exclusive East Room “command performance” of American music featuring major stars, past and present. While the performances are televised and celebrate the nation’s culture, some may wonder whether during an era of soaring deficits it is wise to stage what are also in effect private parties for the first couple. And with this evening’s event, the performances are officially part of the “sequester-free zone” at the White House. As is well known, the daily White House tours did not make the cut. And yes, this is happening on your dime.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365537304698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365537468047-119</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not many people in the US are proposing giving up the right to own firearms. On the other hand, how many children must we sacrifice in order to maintain our right to fire an assault weapon? And on the third hand, what positive action has been taken to reduce the likelihood of mass shootings in the future? Have the strongest supporters of gun ownership made a positive suggestion other than arming school employees: a suggestion most people do not consider to be positive?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365537468047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365537598389-120</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumper-brains, ya nailed it! You have SUCH a way with words! :)))</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1365537598389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365537662378-121</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't Democrats Want to Give Freedom a chance?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365513673486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When are you ever going to OD on that trickle-down Kool-Aid?</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1365537662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365538109099-122</Id><Title>BOE5 787 flying today</Title><Msg>It flew over land down to San Francisco abd back up the coast. In the air now (flightradar24).</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365538109099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365538135749-123</Id><Title>Obama and Marxism - Is Obama one?</Title><Msg>It’s not entirely accurate to call Barack Hussein Obama a Marxist. More precisely, he is a Leninist, as Michael Savage explains: “Lenin thought that a nation could only grow more prosperous when a nation is controlled by a vanguard and elite — a people who know better than you what to do with your property. The Leninist elite would lead people to a world free of pain and poverty. There would be no more haves and have-nots or private property. Just boundless prosperity. All a nation had to do was transfer its entire wealth to Lenin’s vanguard.” This is why the correct term for the political philosophy embodied by Obama is not communism but oligarchical collectivism, which encompasses communism as it is actually practiced, as well as fascism and progressivism. Under pure Marxism, the Moonbat Messiah wouldn’t be hosting extravagant birthday bashes. As Obama’s Leninist strain of oligarchical collectivism tightens its grip around America’s throat, “America’s rich will be poorer, America’s poor will be poorer, America’s middle class will be wiped out,” Savage said. “But America’s government will be more powerful than ever, as will the elected officials and their corrupt bureaucrats.” Obama can’t take wealth from the rich at gunpoint, as Lenin did in Russia, Savage said, “so he has to use taxation and regulation.” This will only work until it sinks in that by “the rich” they mean us, and we start putting up resistance. Then our soft tyranny will either be overthrown, or will become a hard one like the Soviet Union.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365538135749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365538509258-124</Id><Title>boeing sub Spectrolab milestone</Title><Msg>SYLMAR, Calif., April 9, 2013 -- A Spectrolab solar cell recently set a world record by converting more energy from the sun into electricity than any other ground-based solar cell without solar concentration. The Boeing [NYSE: BA] subsidiary's achievement in ground-based solar cell efficiency was verified by the U.S. Department of Energy's National Renewable Energy Laboratory in Golden, Colo. The cell converted 37.8 percent of solar energy using a new class of high-efficiency multi-junction solar cell, created from two or more materials and leveraging Boeing technology that makes semiconductor materials more reliable. The record was set without concentration, the common practice of having lenses or mirrors focus solar rays on the cells. "We expect this solar cell technology will have significant benefits for space, ground-based, and sensor applications," said Troy Dawson, president of Spectrolab. Spectrolab believes this solar cell technology can attain higher levels of efficiency, "possibly more than 45 percent even under low concentrations," according to Nasser Karam, the company’s vice president for advanced technology. Spectrolab, which is part of the Boeing Defense, Space &amp; Security unit, is the world's leading merchant supplier of high-efficiency multi-junction solar cells and panels for concentrated photovoltaic and spacecraft power systems. Spectrolab offers sensors and solar simulators, in addition to being the world’s leading provider of airborne searchlights.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365538509258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365538808043-125</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would you know about magazine capacity?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365538808043</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:20:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365538844617-126</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like you have your period.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365538844617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365538986364-127</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great job.</Msg><Username>paulcoleman168</Username><Timestamp>1365538986364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365539354290-128</Id><Title>Democrats in Denial</Title><Msg>No matter how many of Obama's policies resemble those advocated in Karl's Communist Manifest LWNJs like chris_genna will hide behind technicalities in order to maintain their denial. When Karl Marx advocates class warfare and Obama openly practices, they say it's not exactly the same. When Karl say wealth distribution is good and Obama practices it - again they hide behind technical differences. You can down the list of all ten major planks of the manifesto and see how close Obama's policies mirror them but liberals will still hide behind technicalities. Marxism can best be summed up by advocating "taking from each according to his abilities and giving to each according to their needs." Obama's policies can best be summed up by advocating "taking from each according to his abilities and giving to each according to their needs."</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365539354290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365539376643-129</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you mean "The right not to get shot by a law abiding citizen" The crazys will still have guns and will continue to shot people. Like in Obama's home town Chicago! Maybe you should think of this as the armed criminal protection bill. No return fire permitted.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1365539376643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365539780854-130</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats in Denial</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365539354290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Taking from each according to his abilities and giving to each according to their political affiliation. That's a little more accurate. It's just that the people affiliated with O are usually very needy or very rich.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1365539780854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:36:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365540164893-131</Id><Topic><Title>How does a man like Obama get elected</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1365524382724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 12:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"i'll take sarah anyday," Proving that you have less brains than most tables.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1365540164893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365540174112-132</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just curious albucucu,.... but why are you gun control advocates so much more concerned about children losing their lives to firearms when it is one of the very least causes of death among children ages 0 -19. Wouldn't your time and energy be better spent on Perinatal Conditions which cause 105 times as many deaths as firearms?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365540174112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365540246498-133</Id><Topic><Title>Why US Jobs Market Is Going to Get a Lot Worse</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1365419886600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 07:18:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"people educated beyond their intelligence" You just exposed yourself as a complete fool. The GOP loves you.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1365540246498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365540766929-134</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many of those may take years and millions of YOUR tax dollars. Whereas a few simple firearms restrictions -- no more depriving you of your rights than denying you the legal use of silencers -- could happen overnight. Let's deal with one cause of death we can address while the researchers tackle others. As all you fringies have pointed out, cars, hammers and sabre saws take lives too, but those all have legitimate uses. No deer takes 30 roundws to drop if you can hit the broad side of a doe.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365540766929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365540842880-135</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do not have a "right not to get shot." You only have the right to Life. If someone unjustifiable takes your life, they can be imprisoned or executed. Should be the same for those who kill unborn babies.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365540842880</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365540908298-136</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats in Denial</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365539354290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spare me the YouQuotes. You still can't provide specifics. That's lilke Spartaloon saying I have two dozen aliases but can't list any of them.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365540908298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365541101984-137</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna must not have got the memo.....the 2nd amendment doesn't say anything about hunting.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365541101984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365541137597-138</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats in Denial</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365539354290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as The Kent Raven can get his free monthly handout so he can consume massive amounts of twinkies, he is a happy "DFC" camper.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365541137597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365541178930-139</Id><Title>boe272 787 flying today</Title><Msg>Took off after BOE5 landed. In the air now..</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365541178930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:59:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365541269392-140</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that a threat? It sure sounds like it, you DFC. Maybe I will forward that one higher.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365541269392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365541313712-141</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Define DFC, because you need to.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365541313712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365541370879-142</Id><Title>Research on Childhood Causes of Death Should not be Publicly Funded</Title><Msg>It should be privately funded so we can see how many liberals are really concerned about preventing childhood deaths instead of just using them for excuses to take away the rights of law abiding citizens.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365541370879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365541515541-143</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hoozdik would make a good standard for a crazy.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365541515541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365542256977-144</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well done.</Msg><Username>andresmith537</Username><Timestamp>1365542256977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365542331148-145</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats in Denial</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365539354290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does DFC stand for Democrat for Communism?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365542331148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:18:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365542792562-146</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All you have is trash talk when people things that displease you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365542792562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365542914625-147</Id><Topic><Title>Research on Childhood Causes of Death Should not be Publicly Funded</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365541370879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:02:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Nobel Peace Prize is privately funded, yet you fringies think you should be allowed to tell them who should get the prize and who should not. Maybe it is not all fringies; maybe it's just the insane ones?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365542914625</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365542941507-148</Id><Title>Is chris_genna an Expert at Getting Shot Down?</Title><Msg>Every time he posts on this board he gets shot down.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365542941507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365543038540-149</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It stands for Distinguished Flying Cross, floyd. That's a medal I received and one YOU can't get no matter how good you are at Flight Simulator, because it doesn't take any balls to fly Flight Simulator.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365543038540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365543122794-150</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only "above and beyond" in Flight Simulator, floyd, is the wall behind your compyter monitor.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365543122794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365543165350-151</Id><Topic><Title>boe272 787 flying today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365541178930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thought the last test flight already happened. What else is going on?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365543165350</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365543177383-152</Id><Topic><Title>Research on Childhood Causes of Death Should not be Publicly Funded</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365541370879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:02:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't care who they give their jokes of awards to. If they want to give one to Obama for no accomplishment it's OK with me......they've given ones to other terrorists before.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365543177383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:32:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365543216603-153</Id><Topic><Title>Is chris_genna an Expert at Getting Shot Down?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365542941507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't just SAY, it psych. You have to get confirmation. hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365543216603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365543345198-154</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats in Denial</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365539354290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, psych. See my earlier post to the poster ALSO known as floyd; the one who thinks he adds so much to the humor here.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365543345198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365543504834-155</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually I meant to say children and anyone else who decides to stand in a group. It's just that children have been a favored target lately. And a mass shooting that took place in an elementary school in Stockton, California several years ago has been on my mind lately, as well as the fact that very little has been done over the years since to get a handle on the ease with which a nut can gun down many at once. Now today I see that a nut has used an exacto knife on 14 people at a community college in Texas. But injuring 14 with a blade is a lot better than killing 12 with a gun, don't you think?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365543504834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365543531113-156</Id><Topic><Title>Is chris_genna an Expert at Getting Shot Down?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365542941507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you genna's butt licker?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365543531113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365544050394-157</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone with a gun could have shot the guy with a knife.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365544050394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:47:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365544107138-158</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A fetus is not a citizen. But apparently we people who have been born don't have the right to not get shot, just the right to get even. But fat lot of good that does for the dead victim.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365544107138</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365544233282-159</Id><Topic><Title>Democras ignore Major Cause of Death in Children</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365540419267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:46:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats are the only ones fighting for health insurance and health care for children. Republicans would die to prevent this kind of care. How can you blame Democrats when the Pukes are the guilty ones- criminal and evil to the core willing to deny the populace of health care and wouldeven let little children die because they havent got adequate health care- all so Charly Koch can have a few more dollars to add to his 30 billion fortune- nothing could be more evil and thats you bapsychdept</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365544233282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:50:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365544317903-160</Id><Topic><Title>boe272 787 flying today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365541178930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The previous flight was for FAA cert. data with FAA on board. Not sure why both 787's were in the air today but may not be related to the battery issue. Could be the FAA wanted more data or it could be related to the changes they made in the elactronics panel unrelated to the battery issue</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365544317903</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:51:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365544647452-161</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The guy with the knife had he had a glock 17 could have shot 17 people dead and reloaded for more- thats definitly worse than wounding 17 all of whom will recover- but what do you gun nuts care your diseased minds have no apreciation of anyone else's suffering (sociopath psychopath behavior that most gun nuts display)</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365544647452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365544776309-162</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe. Or several innocent bystanders. It's possible no one in the crowd even knew who was doing the cutting until long after the fact. Point is, a gun doesn't solve everything. We in the US had an age where almost everyone was carrying a gun, but town after town put an end to it because so many people were shooting each other over so little.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365544776309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365545039883-163</Id><Topic><Title>boe272 787 flying today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365541178930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. It's nice to have a conversation about company related business once in awhile. Not to jinx things but I know the people working for FAA are highly educated and experienced in aeronautics and manufacturing processes. I would not be surprised if they recommend some changes to the proposed fix.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365545039883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365545317964-164</Id><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Msg>....they must all be bi-polar.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365545503907-165</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you working to outlaw abortions?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545503907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365546445161-166</Id><Topic><Title>Santorum Just Doesn't Get It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365546195590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:23:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can see why gay marriage is such a personal issue to you. Have you informed chris-genna what you have in mind?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365546445161</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365546471992-167</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you very much!</Msg><Username>ingramayolanda</Username><Timestamp>1365546471992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365546673331-168</Id><Topic><Title>Democras ignore Major Cause of Death in Children</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365540419267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:46:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans are willing to pay for their own children's medical care and take money out of their own pockets to help those who cannot help themselves. Democrats refuse to do this. They insist they only way they will help other people is with other people's money.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365546673331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365547031925-169</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"President Obama's actions have shown that his words were meaningless. The Nobel Peace Prize means little if it's so easily given away." Debra J., Pasadena, MD "As an Obama voter I am deeply disappointed. It was bad judgment to give it to him in the first place." Tim K., Long Prairie, MN "Drones are offensive weapons, in every sense of the word." Richard F., Portland, OR "As much of an Obama supporter I am, perhaps stripping him of this award would get his attention, nothing else seems to be getting the message across that the American People have had enough of multiple trillion dollar unnecessary wars." Vern M., Albuquerque, NM</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365547031925</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365548011667-170</Id><Topic><Title>Democras ignore Major Cause of Death in Children</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365540419267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:46:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>private charity never was able to cover even 10% of the need. You are living in cloud cookoo land as usual- you would learn a lot if you had held a big chunk of Lehman and Country Wide and lost your sas over the last 5 years. You might find that you couldnt afford a quarter million for heart bypasses or perhaps afford the care of a child who is denied insurance because of pre existing conditions. Willing to pay for their own children??? yoou mowrawn!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365548011667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:53:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365548767046-171</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still licking the boots of the pro lifers eh?? In the first place you are bellyaching to the wrong gender. Most of the posters on this board are men. Its the women who get abortions. Women have been having abortions since at least 4,000 BC and nothing any sanctimonious self aggrandizing blue nose could do would stop it. Admittedly it was dangerous without modern medical clinics and doctors. Your contention that life begins at conception is as loony as the idea that life exists before conception and that you have spilled millions of children into the camode. Modern medical practice holds that a fetus might be aborted up to the end of 24 weeks and after that it should only be done to protect the life of the mother. This scatology by the pro lifers to justify the murder of Dr Tiller or other OB GYNs who have done abortions is as evil as anything Heinrich Himmler or Doctor Morell might have dreamt up. What you need is an education- but I suspect you havent got the brains to get educated</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365548767046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365549391592-172</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once again our valueless father speaks his ilk. Our father is so low....that a diamond...in a snake's Sphincter...appears as the brightest star in the heavens above to our low life father.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365549391592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365550167904-173</Id><Topic><Title>Is chris_genna an Expert at Getting Shot Down?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365542941507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The raven is a DFC, he'll even confirm it next time he squawks ident.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365550167904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365550336259-174</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats in Denial</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365539354290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are close........the first word is dumb.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365550336259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:32:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365550380072-175</Id><Topic><Title>Right Not to Get Shot Faces Uphill Fight in Senate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365537760594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a DFC in the wire.......</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365550380072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365550902881-176</Id><Topic><Title>boe272 787 flying today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365541178930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both flights had a lot of intermediate and low level low speed testing, unusual. Might have had something to do with flaps &amp; slats but most of those problems were resolved last year. Or could have something to do with the battery venting system performance at various speeds and altitudes. Don't think they would be checking electrical panel performance with this type of flight profile.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365550902881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:41:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365551129204-177</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Women have been having abortions since at least 4,000 BC) Can you prove that or is that another one of your lies?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365551129204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:45:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365551831020-178</Id><Topic><Title>Is chris_genna an Expert at Getting Shot Down?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365542941507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 17:29:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Squawk-Ident and strangle your parrot.....We have a confirmed kill and an auger in at the Kent Bathouse ...and a follow on butt-lick-by-the#$%$-lick using Have-Quick !</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365551831020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 19:57:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365552344741-179</Id><Topic><Title>Cuban Revolution Survivor Warns of the Dangers of Losing Gun Ownership Rights</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365536530410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 15:42:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it doesn't. It DOES say something about a "WELL-REGULATED militia," but the gun nuts always leave that part off their signs and begin with "The right of the people ..."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365552344741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365552755380-180</Id><Topic><Title>boe272 787 flying today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365541178930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the 787 was grounded for any further flight tests except the battery tests, only on a limited waiver on other types of testing</Msg><Username>bdorranc1</Username><Timestamp>1365552755380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365553528334-181</Id><Title>C17</Title><Msg>Anyone have any insight into the commercial viability of the C17. I heard today through the rumor mill that there are 50+ commercial orders but the FAA was the sticking point.</Msg><Username>brasscorpion</Username><Timestamp>1365553528334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365554751689-182</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Under Obama's leadership our assassination-by-drone foreign policy has increased dramatically, which makes him a war criminal." Frank S., Bellingham, WA "As a constituent and two-time voter for Barack Obama, I am dismayed and frightened at the warmongering ways he has displayed as our leader. I urge the revocation of his undeserved Nobel prize." Samuel P., Colton, CA "What a good idea! Yes, he has the blood of many innocents on his hands." Gene A., Athens, OH "He should have never got it in the first place!" David S., Everett, WA "I voted for the president in both elections but I do not feel he ever deserved the Nobel Peace Prize! Please rescind it!" Carol H., Michigan City, IN</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365554751689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365555278233-183</Id><Title>Benghazi-Gate and the 33 survivors the Obama Administration is trying to coerce into silence</Title><Msg>We've Got Good News And Bad News… First, the good news: As Murdock reports in National Review Online, Senator Lindsey Graham "is on the warpath on this issue." And now, the bad news: Senator Lindsey Graham is the only Senator "on the warpath on this issue." The bottom line is that there is only so much that one man can do. There is so much more that CAN be done... and so much more that MUST be done... to "Ungag the Benghazi 33." And what specifically can be done? As Murdock explains: "With an apparent full-blown cover-up and perhaps dozens of public servants eager to talk, the House immediately should move to subpoena the Obama administration for the names and contact information for all 33 Benghazi survivors. It then should subpoena each of them, immunize them against prosecution, and protect them, their jobs, and their pensions and other benefits under the appropriate federal whistleblower statutes." And why must it be done? Murdock again: "If, however, Obama &amp; Company bribed, threatened, or intimidated these public servants to stay silent in order to secure Obama’s reelection, then Benghazi will prove to be a conspiracy more explosive and evil than Watergate." Six months have come and gone and still we have no answers... only stonewalling, more unanswered questions and cover-ups. Do not be deceived. To quote Murdock one more time: "Republican leadership has the power to solve this mystery and urgently must do so." We must "Ungag the Benghazi 33," and we CAN "Ungag the Benghazi 33." But that's not going to happen until patriotic Americans like you demand that it happen. Congress needs to hear from you now</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365555278233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365556200600-184</Id><Topic><Title>C17</Title><Username>brasscorpion</Username><Timestamp>1365553528334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:25:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That viability goes all the way back to the so-called MD-17, and there is ALWAYS some sticking point. I suspect the real sticking point s that no one wants to buy it. But I like to keep an open mind, so let me know if you find some backup for the 50-order business..</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365556200600</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365556244029-185</Id><Topic><Title>Why US Jobs Market Is Going to Get a Lot Worse</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1365419886600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 07:18:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoe did you get fleeced by the lowest federal income tax rates in 40 years?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365556244029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365556569845-186</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't elect the Bill of Rights out of existence Einstein</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365556569845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365556832314-187</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It is not a good example of what peace means when the Nobel Prize is awarded to the leader of a nation engaging in war as a business strategy. Make a statement, please." Chandra P., Walsenburg, CO "I, like so many others, gave this man the benefit of the doubt. It has been thrown back in our faces." Chris C., Harrogate, Great Britain "He never deserved it and he hasn't earned it. Yes, please, take it back." Jackie F., Oakland, CA "The Nobel Peace Prize should not be awarded to war mongers and war criminals. Therefore, please revoke the Peace Prize you awarded to President Obama in 2009." Fred N., Pleasanton, CA</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365556832314</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365557738387-188</Id><Topic><Title>boe272 787 flying today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365541178930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 16:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, they have been testing the electrical panels, slats, and control systems as well as the batteries. As for these tests, I'm pretty sure they were associated with the batteries, probably follow on per FAA like Fal indicated.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365557738387</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365557829640-189</Id><Topic><Title>C17</Title><Username>brasscorpion</Username><Timestamp>1365553528334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:25:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>17s are very, very pricy, not competitive with the C-130s that are available.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1365557829640</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 21:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365560713734-190</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. I would give up my guns except that I need them to keep the Obama supporters out of my house . . . . Y.T. Jumbojetski .</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1365560713734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 22:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365562155406-191</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ever hear of bing or google?? you can read all about it on the internet eh mowrawn</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365562155406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 22:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365562226857-192</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my values vs your lack of values is like the difference between night and day-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365562226857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 22:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365562965835-193</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi-Gate and the 33 survivors the Obama Administration is trying to coerce into silence</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365555278233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 20:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Murdoch....you are quoting a Murdoch source? Why not quote the The Donald and his Trumpster hairpiece offering milliions to somone, anyone, with proof of an Obama fraudulent birth certificate. maybe you haven't heard of the lady diplomat whoi was killed in the line of service in the past couple of days, or does that not qualify? Stick to what you know best, such as 9/11, the lunar landing hoax, and the NWO of which m\Murdoch must be a member...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1365562965835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365564143222-194</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joy. My Just Bike. Pop-guns lifted from grandkids do not constitute a threat to your humble abode by the non-Mitten Rawmoney supporters. Reality might, and non pro-choice people who cano cannot spell ammend-ment righst and their supporters whether it be 1st to 10thand all the others are needed to be kept away from my house. DOW reaches all-time record height. For the third or fourth time under Obama. Break On Through. -Jim</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1365564143222</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365564376542-195</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand your cognitive disonance concerning the 5th year of relative PEACE under the Obama Administration since youe are probably a right-wing chinkenhwak war-monegring oily-profiteer and a wannabe...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1365564376542</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365564903916-196</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand you cognitive disonance concerning the ending of the cold war and ray-gun the laffable friend to what's her face thathher, as it was after ray-gunl left office that the wasll fell, mostly thanks the the soviet leader and peoples,, and buschco I son of the german war-machine prifiteer, ordered us on active duty to invade panama to get pizza-face Noriega over X-mas time because pizza-face did something about something which #$%$ bushco I off... and by the time we got home home, we had to go and invade another country to get Saddam, b4 being called-off by the same bushco I and his mad dog sidekick chien-y... imagine rawmoney/ brownie or heaven forbid mccain/palin</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1365564903916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365565113151-197</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this the latest lunatic jihad of yours? Get a life, please.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1365565113151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365565212687-198</Id><Topic><Title>If Gun Rights are lost...you will soon lose Free Speech</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365508876132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 08:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As you don';t defecate or otherwise defile yourself from atop your street corner box or impede the normal flow of peestrian ot otherwise traffic.. I do not see, hear, or speak of a problem but then IAM who IAM and not a lawyer Light my Fire -Jim</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1365565212687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365565379984-199</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Giving him a Nobel Peace Prize is an affront to the deep heritage of true peacemakers who well deserved it. Obama has waged continuous war, torture and other violence since being President. Please revoke it now." Barry S., Macdoel, CA "Bush gave us 2 unfunded wars. Will Obama add a few more? Stop wars, drones and killing with other people's children." Burt S., Pompton Plains, NJ "I voted for Obama -- twice. I am very sad to sign this petition, but I believe in my heart, what he has done with drones is totally wrong!" Gloria H., Santa Rosa, CA "Obama's deeds do not match his words." Evalyn S., Walnut Creek, CA "You lost any credibility giving Obama the peace prize. Fix it." Camilo B., Long Beach, CA "Obama's harsh treatment of whistleblowers who are trying to expose the outlandish abuses of the military/corporate state disqualify him from any awards given to peacemakers." David L., Alamosa, CO</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365565379984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365566042685-200</Id><Title>If airlines are going to be good, BA is worth 120$..</Title><Msg>No seller remorse for a year.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365566042685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365566241202-201</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus invests 13 billion per year in American companies and uses American workers, now another 1000</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365483107367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 00:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>notice how the Boeing hacks use name calling and write a book instead of focus on how bad the return on investment for Boeing shareholders has been, just like the 3 year late and decertified 787 Boeing is on fire down and Airbus is doing about 96% better over 5 years for the shareholders. Airbus has been number 1 for 11 years now and yet the Boeing Hacks try to concentrate on one person and it is not he CEO if you know what I mean har har har</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365566241202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365566339649-202</Id><Topic><Title>please , please , please , is t here a Boeing Hack that can tell us if the decertified 787 is flying today</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365434660083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 11:24:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh the decertified 787 is flying now can the Boeing Hacks get a ride so they can report it second by second woo hoo 3 years late, decertifed and 33 billion over priced and it is flying woo hoo</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365566339649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365566364761-203</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I went out of my way to vote AGAINST the most evil Bushco/Chieney in 2000 forthe first time in 28 years only to return home and find my VCR recording over one of my favorite videos with the latest update from the evil JEB Buscho's Floriduhs retracting the known and the obvious real vote count, and you wanna talke about rights... believe me when I say they don't givea flying F about you or me letalone most rights b prepared but not para-noid Break On Through -Jim, it ain't crimson and clover but bosa nova no va</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1365566364761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 23:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>