<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371790788038-1</Id><Topic><Title>Washington State said goodbye to Boeing chicago and good riddance hellow contractors and Airbus</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371753608208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:40:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing personal there, boating , like riding on a Airbus plane, the ones that make holders of airbus stock 100% better off in 3 years than Boeing stock holders by 100%. . Now spartacus9991 aka uniposter you pulled a avatar name on me , such a cry baby, , spartacus9991, now getting back to you tell us more about your wife, we all are so interested and your great pension and the social security you got after MD went bankrupt and Condit purchased MD so you could say you were under the Boeing umbrella uniposter aka spartacus9991, we all care so much about your crapola spartacus9991 aka uniposter, , do you cry baby to your wife when she tells you to get off the computer, and do something around the house? Now spartacus9991 what do you spend your retirement and social security money on, do you buy real estate in California it is so important to us we really want to know all about it and be sharing with any other information you think we need to hear about we are all listening go ahead go go</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371790788038</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 00:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371791216217-2</Id><Topic><Title>CEO of boeing compares to the USA Airbus Chairman Airbus CEO brings American jobs here which is better ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371776794989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:06:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just one cry baby with thumbs down, that is uniposter aka spartacus9991 holding on with his hands over his eyes, crying all the time , maybe his wife will comfort him now, he is on social security and has a MD-BA pension and likes California real estate and we are all so interested in any other personal information of a business or financial importance in a message that he feel compelled to tell us all about.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371791216217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 01:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371791285046-3</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two things: Why is it that anyone who thinks differently than you is UnAmerican? Secondly, About the only one of who most people consider 'founding fathers' who did much actual fighting was George Washington. The rest were what would be considered now days to be bureaucrats and landed gentry, and about the only freedom they felt they were being denied was lack of representation as taxed people.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371791285046</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 01:08:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371791657764-4</Id><Topic><Title>Let's all post</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371773326340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't the immigration reform mainly to give people who were brought here as infants with no choice of their own a chance to apply for citizenship through normal procedure, rather than to automatically be deported to a country they may have lived in for days or weeks?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371791657764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 01:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371791871043-5</Id><Topic><Title>Let's all post</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371773326340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may want to look up Authorization for Use of Military Force Against Iraq Resolution of 2002 enacted October 16, 2002, Bush put Iraq up to a vote in congress and a majority of dems in the Senate voted for it. Senator Clinton Oct 10th 2002 in speech of support "In the four years since the inspectors left, intelligence reports show that Saddam Hussein has worked to rebuild his chemical and biological weapons stock, his missile delivery capability, and his nuclear program. He has also given aid, comfort, and sanctuary to terrorists, including Al Qaeda members, though there is apparently no evidence of his involvement in the terrible events of September 11, 2001. It is clear, however, that if left unchecked, Saddam Hussein will continue to increase his capacity to wage biological and chemical warfare, and will keep trying to develop nuclear weapons. Should he succeed in that endeavor, he could alter the political and security landscape of the Middle East, which as we know all too well affects American security"</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1371791871043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 01:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371792365366-6</Id><Topic><Title>CEO of boeing compares to the USA Airbus Chairman Airbus CEO brings American jobs here which is better ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371776794989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:06:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 aka uniposter, did you fly a plane in Viet Nam for the USA or did you watch McNerney play baseball for a ivy league school , while the Airbus CEO of America fought for freedom so McNerney could learn to hate unions and to send jobs from the USA to other countries. Like McNerney why do you want to , ship good jobs to other countries . If you do not support Boeing, then why are you antagonist all the time. Boeing has made it clear they want to outsource and get rid of good American jobs and make people poor in the USA. If you were a recent graduate of a engineering school, you would be considered for work in Carolina and you would not be making what the old Boeing company paid when they designed the great planes the 707,727, 737,747,767,777 with American educated colleges that we supported by American taxpayers. I like this USA Airbus CEO, and how great he is to work for Airbus and at the same time keep good jobs in the USA. Spartacus9991 tell us more about your dogging me all the time, how is that helping Boeing or creating jobs in the USA/ What is your motivation,, just hatred of the great American way of life or are you just a disruptive person with any agenda against America and the workers of the USA? spartacus9991 you are a anti American, disruptive antagonist, with nothing of value to any user on the Boeing message board I do not like you Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371792365366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 01:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371792843452-7</Id><Title>And from Europe Obama is a dud</Title><Msg>The libs love reading the enlightened news of Europe when Bush was prez , but not anymore . Head line from the UK Telegraph: Barack Obama bombs in Berlin: a weak, underwhelming address from a floundering president. And here is a paragraph from that piece: In stark contrast to that of his presidential predecessors, Barack Obama’s message on Wednesday was pure mush, another clichéd “citizens of the world” polemic with little substance. This was a speech big on platitudes and hopeless idealism, while containing much that was counter-productive for the world’s superpower. Ultimately it was little more than a laundry list of Obama’s favourite liberal pet causes, including cutting nuclear weapons, warning about climate change, putting an end to all wars, shutting Guantanamo, ending global poverty, and backing the European Project. It was a combination of staggering naiveté, the appeasement of America’s enemies and strategic adversaries, and the championing of more big government solutions.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1371792843452</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 01:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371793044404-8</Id><Topic><Title>Second United Dreamliner diverted with oil-related problem</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1371777915699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:25:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing shareholders are responsible for any contractor problem. GE is a supplier, incidentally the CEO of Boeing was the head of GE jet engines . You would think that at least, the GE engines would be good as the CEO of Boeing was the head of GE jet engines so even this area is a miss for James McNerney. the 787, is 4 years late , 30 billion over cost and grounded , with a we don't know battery box, the shared cost, aka let the supplier company do all the work and Boeing executives sit in Chicago and do nothing, this MD bankruptcy business plan , does not work just like Hart- Smith said. James McNerney move your job to China, we would get better result or at least cheap CEO cost. .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371793044404</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 01:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371795968087-9</Id><Title>Embraer Launches E2 E-Jets with 300+ Orders at Paris Air Show--Does Boeing need a more regional jet?</Title><Msg>Does Boeing need to not only go after higher seat capacity planes, and for a more regional jet in the every growing regional markets.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371795968087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 02:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371796108544-10</Id><Topic><Title>Embraer Launches E2 E-Jets with 300+ Orders at Paris Air Show--Does Boeing need a more regional jet?</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371795968087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 02:26:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bad sentence there for sure. Do they need to address both larger higher seat range and the regional market. Seems the Middle East wants a A380 stretch version for up to 600+ people---a lot of people</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371796108544</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 02:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371799440886-11</Id><Topic><Title>Washington State said goodbye to Boeing chicago and good riddance hellow contractors and Airbus</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371753608208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:40:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us again all about your boating, your hydro racing, and the lack of traffic in Spokane. Sure is a nice break on this financial board. LOL</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371799440886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371800678308-12</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dummy, US Troops (most of whom are 99% ers) die so idiots on this board like you can remain free in the 1% club. Only the wealthy have the most to lose, but they don't to pay higher taxes because others will benefit from that. So the 1% want the 99% pay for it instead.</Msg><Username>markdferraro</Username><Timestamp>1371800678308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371801006042-13</Id><Topic><Title>CEO of boeing compares to the USA Airbus Chairman Airbus CEO brings American jobs here which is better ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371776794989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:06:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm only "antagonist" against posters who don't get their facts right and try to spin their mistakes without ever admitting that they are wrong. " person with any agenda against America and the workers of the USA?" You sure do seem to read a lot into some of my posts. Joe McCarthy would be proud of you.</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371801006042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371801012955-14</Id><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Msg>Tesla Motors Inc on Thursday unveiled a system to swap battery packs in its electric cars in about 90 seconds, a service Chief Executive Elon Musk said will help overcome fears about their driving range. The automaker will roll out the battery-swapping stations later this year, beginning along the heavily-traveled route between Los Angeles and San Francisco and then in the Washington-to-Boston corridor. "There are some people, they take a lot of convincing," Musk said at an event at Tesla's Los Angeles design studio. "Hopefully this is what convinces people finally that electric cars are the future." Electric cars have been slow to catch on with consumers because of their high price, limited driving range and lack of a charging infrastructure. Tesla has been working to address some of those issues with fast-charging stations and now with the battery-swapping technology. A battery pack swap will cost between $60 and $80, about the same as filling up a 15-gallon gas tank, Musk said. Drivers who choose to swap must reclaim their original battery on their return trip or pay the difference in cost for the new pack. Musk demonstrated two Model S battery pack swaps in the time it took for a car on a screen above the stage to fill up with gas, about four minutes.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371801128609-15</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>• spartacus99991 • May 28, 2013 11:30 AM Flag • Yes, TSLA and SCTY are better stocks than BA the last month for making money for traders. Happy now?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801128609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371801157831-16</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waynedickenson961 • Apr 11, 2013 7:01 PM • 4users liked this postsusers disliked this posts5 • • IGZ • Reply so sparti you asked me to stop pointing out that your a very poor critic and I used your ignorant claim about a stock IGZ, you offered to criticize my 19 day ago 26% acad gain. ? IGZ is not a real stock you’re a fool. IGZ you thought was up 144% but it is a test symbol for working on the stock market software, not a real stock. Fool. You picked a stock you kow nothing about trading stock do you spartacus991 you’re a antagonist and have it in for me that is your only reason to be here . First of all sparti , you started the crapola years ago with me</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801157831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371801196013-17</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and the stock price and the expert opinion and Paris win for Airbus</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371774682914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:31:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the same as "dell, fred, and veronica"? LOL</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371801196013</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371801280089-18</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The history of spartacus9991 and his reason to be here as told by spartacus9991 and the posts that note after several hours spartacus9991 reason got 100% thumbs down his reason to dog wayne is just crarpola  spartacus99991 • 6 hours ago Flag waynes world comment  0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 5  Reply show his failure . 6-20-2013 Chris, I hear you. I originally took out the spartacus99991 nick back when I was toying with the "sparty" who was big into 9/11 conspiracies and I liked to point out contrary facts and articles. Since that seemed to be a lost cause, I took up "dell's",( fred's, wayne's) challenge about his 10 stocks beating BA "going forward" from March 2011. When it seemed that he might have put me on ignore and couldn't stand to see the latest weeks results of his stocks falling behind BA (he claimed many months later that he really meant some of the 10 should be shorted, HaHa), I added "neospart99" for a while and acknowledged that I was the same as 99991. Maybe I'll go back to using that one since some on this board are having trouble differentiating the IDs, although the style and subject matter should be quite obvious. Less</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801280089</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371801666691-19</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, if you don't back up your challenge for 10 stocks to beat BA "going forward" and then switch nicks to try to avoid losing the challenge, you set yourself up as a BA basher with a hidden agenda and spreader of misinformation. Remember this one? " the stock market closes early thrusday and is not open friday-osulinn get a clue waynedickenson961 by waynedickenson961 • Mar 28, 2013 5:10 AM Flag osulinn get a clue."</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371801666691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371801739990-20</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 you are a liar, you wanted to know what stock I was trading at the time and then you made them into a forever contest comparing them to nothing, just watching the stock . that is a fools game , like IGZ your other call, so ignorant you picke d a test stock , not a real stock to tell me it was up 144% compared to my ACAD now up over 1000% by the way, spartacus9991 your nothing but a person who messed with some guy on 9 11 and now is messing with me that is what you do and you just admitted it . Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801739990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371801812308-21</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=Why is it that anyone who thinks differently than you is UnAmerican?= People who claim to know the criteria for deeming someone unAmerican are almost always "unAmerican" themselves.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1371801812308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371802143472-22</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I didn't. This is what you posted From the postings of dell (wayne) on 3/7/11: "every stock I compared with Boeing will beat Boeing going forward" "so when and if you can prove me wrong go for it" " If you do not wone(sic) them ok that is your decisions what is your comeback" "I just put my reputation on the line all the stocks I compared with Boeing will beat Boeing going forward" "because tomorrow and all the following days I will be comparing BA to my stock picks already listed over the past few days"</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371802143472</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371802149086-23</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>neospart99 aka spartacus9991 here is a fact acad is up over 1000% in one year and I picked it and TSLA is up over 200% and I picked it and Airbus is better than Boeing by over 100% in 3 years and I have been pointing that out for over three years and your point is then what ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371802149086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371802940978-24</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>neospart aka spartacus9991 your a loser , I also won the contest about which company will win the Paris airshow competition, Airbus sold more planes and booked more billions of dollars than Boeing so Airbus bettered Boeing and will continue to make more money for Airbus shareholders over time than Boeing just like the last 3 years . once more other than dogging me do you have a point this is 6-21-2013 and this is a traders stock market spartacus9991, time to read up on Tom O'Brien and Boeing, he said Boeing is done now on stock price it may hit the 107 areas of 2007 but the volume is going down over time it is dead on the vine now, spartacus9991 your so self centered when I publish your sparacus9991 cu do to me on TSLA you run and hide behind your avatar name, neospart shame on you , .spartacus9991 , you lost with dogging the 911 user and now a loser with Airbus being the winner at Paris and Airbus being better than Boeing at over 100% better than Boeing for stock price gain over the three years .you lsot to me on apple and ACAD and STLS and so you made up a years ago list of my stock then into a for ever competition against nothing you offered what a fool you are spartacus9991</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371802940978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371803035025-25</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stls should be TSLA</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371803035025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371804018962-26</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>forward definition is" near" term not forever sure you lied forward is defined as near look it up your so full of crapola Spartacus 9991 wayne I have been comparing to my stocks now they are ACAD TSLA Airbus and so your a liar look at the statement and read it spartacus9991 "because tomorrow and all the following days I will be comparing BA to my stock picks... and you do not see" forever" anyplace in that statement your a liar spartacus9991, forward by definition is a near term look, so look it it up fool Wayne your just a dog and you admitted that when you could not dog the 9-11 guy you switched to me that is the only reason your here you are nothing but a antagonist not worth anything to anyone a antagonist is a . bandit*, , crip, enemy, foe, , opposer, nothing of value to anyone who wants to maximize money invested in stocks .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371804018962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371804052341-27</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Paris airshow stock price competition isn't over until the close of markets on Friday. Another lie by Wayne. So sad.</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371804052341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 04:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371805500995-28</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so spartacus9991 aka neospart, how does it feel to be outed , as nothing but a antagonist and you admitted it , you have no interest in Boeing stock , you like to argue, first is was the 9-11 poster and now you are dogging me, my stock "picks going forward" ( by definition forward is a near term) not "forever" that word was not used, spartacus9991 , your making up your own argument , my stock picks, apple then and now acad and TSLA and Airbus that I have suggested , do beat Boeing currently, and for a long time too so that is not a after the fact report they, like apple , will not be a forever stocks, nothing is a forever stock . Since I can not stop you I can show you for what you are and I will do that your a big help to me by your user comments you really don't know when to be quiet . Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371805500995</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371806070574-29</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, people that post the unAmerican #$%$ that you do, remove all doubt...........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371806070574</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371806191775-30</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry sparticus9991 you told me those were good stock picks . what happened too good to ignore ha ha Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371806191775</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371806254935-31</Id><Topic><Title>poor thought Obozocare was going to be free. ha ha its so funny. Heathcare, food stamps free that facts is a $10.50 hr job pays $144.00 a</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371761211119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:46:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you need to get your facts straight......dipstick.......</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371806254935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371806342288-32</Id><Topic><Title>Let's all post</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371773326340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why he's a DFC, card carrying DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371806342288</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:19:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371806444670-33</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Kent Raven alias fluent in DFC lingo...........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371806444670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371807471552-34</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going forward it is ACAD up 1000% for one yearso far until the FED speech, and I have been pointing it out since ACAD gained 26% mon ths ago, when you attempted to argue with me on a stock you did not know was bogus stock symbol remember spartacus9991 aka neospart99, IGZ ,your nothing but a person who is an antagonist , you admitted it you like to dog users for no good reason other than you are argumentative , a social misfit. tsla up 200 %, Airbus up 100% better than Boeing and going forward once more spart aka neospart99 you sure like your numbers, ha ha look the definition going" forward" it is " near" term , not a forever word, like apple stock is not forever so slip on back to spartacus9991, neospart99 and stop the shame on you, hiding from the facts with a avatar name, neospart99 aka spartacus9991 and some day ACAD and TSLA will no longer be in my going" forward" near term stock picks, but I will have made a lot of money on them , why because I already have. and the stock challenge is your idea like you telling me about your wife and your social security and your Md pension and how California is the place to invest in real estate, so how is your wife tonight, we all really want to know ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807471552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371807720116-35</Id><Title>spartacus9991 leaves and poof neospart99 appears avator name</Title><Msg>so Spartacus 9991 you need to hide your argument backfired on you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807720116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371808028273-36</Id><Topic><Title>CEO of boeing compares to the USA Airbus Chairman Airbus CEO brings American jobs here which is better ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371776794989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:06:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 aka neopsart99 there is only thumb down here and it is for you, how about that better try another of yore many nicks . wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371808028273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371808232186-37</Id><Topic><Title>Another 787 diverted</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371771459195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no matter how you look at it 2 in 3 days is not a good sign for a 4 year late 787</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371808232186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371808304644-38</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus betters Boeing at paris Arishow 59 billion and 466 planes to 53 billion and 382 planes Airbus stock up 100% over BA</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371773991736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:19:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so must be a good factual user comment then right !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371808304644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371809272088-39</Id><Title>Airbus bettered Boeing at the paris Airshow and Tom O'Brein called it on Boeing stock a two for one deal</Title><Msg>Tom O"Brien on Boeing stock price and the Boeing advertisement show . Tom O'Brien, is a national stock market expert , who is famous for timing the individual stock prices . Mr. O'Brien covered Boeing , and pointed out that Boeing stock price now is just about "dead on the vine" saying the volume is going down over time. Mr. O'Brien indicated the last time Boeing was a 107 dollar stock was in 2007 and it will now ring the bell at the previous high and maybe get some more but then Boeing stock price will retreat over time to the 71 dollar range .. For any user of the Boeing financial blog, as you can see there is a core of six Boeing barkers, the doggy, bow wow self proclaimed , Boeing advertisement salesmen, for Boeing who are selling Boeing stock to potential customers. These six people are loud and colorful and like a circus barker stand at the Boeing financial page all day long barking come on in and get some Boeing stocks. Showing news stories and dogging any other opinion with personal attacks For the year to date the competition between the two major competitors, Airbus stock is better .When you have the facts on your side you argue facts, , when you do not have the facts on your side, you pound the table and call names. Airbus stock has made Airbus shareholders over 100% more gain than being stock over time, 3 years. .since Airbus sold more planes and logged more billions of Dollars at paris airshow this week, this Airbus stock trend will continue. Airbus will better Boeing in stock price in gain for the Airbus shareholder going forward over time. Remember , the Boeing barkers , the doggy bow - wow is to cover their bad position on Boeing , so they pound the table and call names.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371809272088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371812236542-40</Id><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Msg>Washington’s Blog June 21, 2013 NSA whistleblower Russel Tice – a key source in the 2005 New York Times report that blew the lid off the Bush administration’s use of warrantless wiretapping – told Peter B. Collins on Boiling Frogs Post (the website of FBI whistleblower Sibel Edmonds): Tice: Okay. They went after–and I know this because I had my hands literally on the paperwork for these sort of things–they went after high-ranking military officers; they went after members of Congress, both Senate and the House, especially on the intelligence committees and on the armed services committees and some of the–and judicial. But they went after other ones, too. They went after lawyers and law firms. All kinds of–heaps of lawyers and law firms. They went after judges. One of the judges is now sitting on the Supreme Courtthat I had his wiretap information in my hand. Two are former FISA court judges. They went after State Department officials. They went after people in theexecutive service that were part of the White House–their own people. They went after antiwar groups. They went after U.S. international–U.S. companies that that do international business, you know, business around the world. They went after U.S. banking firms and financial firms that do international business. They went after NGOs that–like the Red Cross, people like that that go overseas and do humanitarian work. They went after a few antiwar civil rights groups. So, you know, don’t tell me that there’s no abuse, because I’ve had this stuff in my hand and looked at it. And in some cases, I literally was involved in the technology that was going after this stuff. And you know, when I said to [former MSNBC show host Keith] Olbermann, I said, my particular thing is high tech and you kn</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371812456076-41</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember Justice Roberts and the swing vote for Obamacare...Roberts (as a conservative) was going to vote against it...then the next day voted FOR it...Benghazi and Petraus..going to blow the lid off Obamas role in Benghazi..decided to resign instead.....insiders are now saying they were blackmailed......do the math</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812456076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 07:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371813411747-42</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shooting...scoring !!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371813411747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 07:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371813550576-43</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...and when the IRS and the NSA send your info to fusion centers and deem you a threat ...or blackmails you...or in the extremis... send you to "reeducation camps" (after shtf) will you bask in your freedom and say how "American" you feel ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371813550576</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 07:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371815532758-44</Id><Title>Common Communist Core</Title><Msg>and 46 million NEW low information immigrants should finish the job...err half the job, the easy part, demolition</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371815532758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 07:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371818527007-45</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not a Republican but everyone of the people have accomplished great yjings in their lives. Great things besides just managing to get elected. They have light years more credit and character than the Democrat dumbbells I mentioned.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371818527007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 08:42:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371819883048-46</Id><Title>waynedickless is at it Again this morning he couldn't sleep last nght!</Title><Msg>And Boeing is going UP$$$$ Best PR man their around$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371819883048</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371820105950-47</Id><Topic><Title>Common Communist Core</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371815532758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 07:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the same principle applies to imploding buildings, destruction from within, take out the foundation = Yu ri Bez men ov (YAHOOs don’t like this guy) is a former KGB agent and an expert on ideological subversion. He discusses the slow process of demoralization that transformed America from a conservative and mostly homogeneous country into a socially-marxist and egalitarian one.- 1984 From an interview close to 30 years ago… “It's a great brainwashing process which goes very slow and is divided into four basic stages. The first one being "demoralization". It takes from 15 to 20 years to demoralize a nation. Why that many years? Because this is the minimum number of years required to educate one generation of students in the country of your enemy exposed to the ideology of [their] enemy. In other words, Marxism-Leninism ideology is being pumped into the soft heads of at least three generation of American students without being challenged or counterbalanced by the basic values of Americanism; American patriotism.... The result? The result you can see ... the people who graduated in the 60's, dropouts or half-baked intellectuals, are now occupying the positions of power in the government, civil service, business, mass media, and educational systems. You are stuck with them. You can't get through to them. They are contaminated. They are programmed to think and react to certain stimuli in a certain pattern [alluding to Pavlov]. You cannot change their mind even if you expose them to authentic information. Even if you prove that white is white and black is black, you still can not change the basic perception and the logic of behavior...</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820105950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371820258518-48</Id><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Msg>....or are they just caught up in following the Saul Alinsky model to collapse the American government? Even though the Democrat Party has always beeen absorbed with one form of slavery or another with control being their ultimate objective rather than liberty, there were still a few good Democrats who were patriotic and had fealty to the ideals of liberty and individual property rights. There are really ignorant people that would have you believe the bad Democrats became Republicans in the south and good Republicans became Democrats. I'm not here to defend Republicans but that is complete nonsense because today's Democrats are still working as hard as ever to use force or threat of force to take the fruits of labor and property of people who earned it and give it to people who didn't earn it. That's the foundation of the Democrat Party. Now, they call people vulgar names and heap vile and disgusting insults on anyone who exposes them to the wrongness of their party. This is not the result of a hatred for the Republican Party for they do it to Independents and members of the Libertarian, Conservative, Constitutional and Freedom Parties as well as others. There is a good reason why the Communist Party USA now endorses the Democrat Party and its candidates in every election.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371820329598-49</Id><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Msg>won't update topic page, unless it suits his dumbo/mobro agenda</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371820546038-50</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spart, i added comments/reply to the common communist core thread, how come it doesn't show up on topic page, when i see this thread, posted subsequent, does?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820546038</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:15:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371820973831-51</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just caught up. The leaders of the party, and the pinko followers anyway. Sure wish the decent democrats would stand up and be counted. Rumor has it there are some around.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1371820973831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371821070405-52</Id><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Msg>The state is the great fictitious entity by which everyone seeks to live at the expense of everyone else. Frederic Bastiat Mir's amendment: So, let's keep the state as small as possible.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371821070405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371821501898-53</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371821070405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:24:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you got my vote mir</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371821501898</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371821624545-54</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will each have to weigh the threat of government tyranny against the threat of terrorism. I have been biased by friends who lived under communist regimes that escaped to the United States. The experiences they shared with me shape my view. I am also biased by the knowledge passed on by family members who lived under abusive governments before coming to the USA. This is not new territory for the USA as the considerations of freedom and safety were being discussed at the birth of our nation. However the world keeps changing and so do the threats. The possibility of terrorists using nuclear devices becomes more eminent each day. Reason dictates that I can't just accept my biases without weighing all current threats and growing threats. No bumper sticker expression of freedom over tyranny can be a substitute for exhaustive thought on weighing the appropriate measures for how we can maintain our freedoms and protect ourselves from terrorist threats. I admit I was angry at first when the leaked information on monitoring came out and I lashed out at Obama, but now I have to take the time to be a 'good' American and slog through all complexities to reach an unemotional and reasoned position on this matter. No doubt my kids will be doing the same now and in the future.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371821624545</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:33:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371821777125-55</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tyranny, terrorism...spart, how bout we get rid of the tyrants so we can concentrate on the terrorists</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371821777125</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371821924990-56</Id><Topic><Title>Common Communist Core</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371815532758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 07:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is the culmination of decades of taxpayer and foundation funding for groups dedicated to our destruction...from sep 08 article in american thinker... "…Their strategy to create political, financial, and social chaos that would result in revolution blended Alinsky concepts with their more aggressive efforts at bringing about a change in U.S. government. To achieve their revolutionary change, Cloward and Piven sought to use a cadre of aggressive organizers assisted by friendly news media to force a re-distribution of the nation’s wealth… No matter where the strategy is implemented, it shares the following features: 1. The offensive organizes previously unorganized groups eligible for government benefits but not currently receiving all they can. 2. The offensive seeks to identify new beneficiaries and/or create new benefits. 3. The overarching aim is always to impose new stresses on target systems, with the ultimate goal of forcing their collapse. The vast expansion of welfare in New York City that came of the NWRO’s Cloward-Piven tactics sent the city into bankruptcy in 1975. Rudy Giuliani cited Cloward and Piven by name as being responsible for "an effort at economic sabotage." The next time you drive through one of the many blighted neighborhoods in our cities, or read of the astronomical crime, drug addiction, and out-of-wedlock birth rates, or consider the failed schools, strapped police and fire resources of every major city, remember Cloward and Piven’s thrill that "...the drain on local resources persists indefinitely."… “The CRA was Carter’s answer to a grassroots activist movement started in Chicago, and forced banks to make loans to low income, high risk customers. PhD economist and former Texas Senator Phil Gramm has called it: "a vast extortion scheme against the nation’s banks." "Make the enemy live up to their (sic) own book of rules," Alinsky wrote in his 1989 book Rules for Radicals. When pressed to honor every w</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371821924990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371822074076-57</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Post.....good government is where we all chip in a bit to provide the necessary structure for a civilized society. Democrats and Republicans have taken us far beyond what's necessary. Now we have become slaves to the state being forced to work a third of our time for it. For a hundred a fifty years our country operated just fine on 5% of the GDP. We had a strong military, good roads and schools. Now it sucks up 5 times that amount and none of it is spent well, We are giving corrupt IRS agents $90 million in bonuses while putting Doctors and Nurse who take care of our wounded warriors on furlough.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371822074076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:41:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371822344757-58</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with you. Right now the american people are in a fight to retain their culture and nation. Right now we are losing. Let's hope this attack can be turned around, but it's not looking very good. If we fail, I'm sure historians will study why a successful nation like the USA collectively felt a need to destroy itself at the height of it's power. That seems a common story in world history. The destruction of the American culture will only lead to poverty and continuation and escalation of the wars. Not many will do good here, and yet our political ruling class seem facinated by the idea of undermining american values and ideals, and replacing them with values and ideals that can only lead to the failure of the nation. The american ruling class has not served the american people very well.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1371822344757</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371822604873-59</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha funny - a GOP toadie posting about decency...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371822604873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371822616809-60</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's hard to argue with leftists. They are crazy.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1371822616809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371823092043-61</Id><Title>The Tea Party Is the New Civil Rights Movement</Title><Msg>here's a good laugh ! For the last several week, Glenn Beck has been hammering away at the theme that Tea Party activists must become the new leaders of civil rights movement because they are being discriminated against, persecuted, and denied equal protection under the law by a biased and corrupt government. And he is entirely serious, claiming that even while they are becoming the victims of KKK-like intimidation, they will eventually be the force that saves this nation.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371823092043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371823276494-62</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You don't hear them discussing primarying bad Democrats.." That is funny. The GOP destroys themselves using this process, it is right out of the COMMUNIST playbook (eliminate the "un-pure" of thought or ideology). It has proven to lead to bad candidates. One must wonder how someone of your limited mental capacities still thinks of himself as smart. Delusions are a powerful tool for you.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371823276494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371823752788-63</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really.....you have the gall to compare Maxine "let's nationalize the oil industry" Waters with Michelle Bachmann, Nancy "we have to pass the bill to see what's in it" Pelosi with Sarah Palin who took on her own party over corruption, Sheila Jackson " I'm a freed slave" Lee with Herman Cain or Hank " I'm concerned Guam might capsize Johnson with Mitt Romney. Have you been dining on hallucinogenic mushrooms or is your head full of communist rocks?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371823752788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371823932061-64</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Is the New Civil Rights Movement</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371823092043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glenn Beck makes sense, you don't. The TEA Party was proven right. OWS was a disgusting display of ignorance.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371823932061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371823998347-65</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love the new GOP narrative, slavery. From the party who actively has fought against equality over the last 70 years. Yes, the democratic party's southern wing supported all the terrible things the GOP now stands for, but a Democratic president signed the Civil Rights acts fully acknowledging that his party would lose the South for at least a generation. That is called leadership and principle, something that Mir would not know or understand even if it bit him in the Butt. Most of the Southern wing of the Democratic party fled to where their bigoted views were welcome, the GOP. That says more about the TODAY's GOP than anything that happened in 1865 era.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371823998347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371824292857-66</Id><Title>The Democrats Confusion over Equality</Title><Msg>.......The push for equality of outcomes while ignoring the equality of inputs.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371824292857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371824490055-67</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumbos treat other Americans as slaves to the dumb cause, huh spart you for instance, whens the last time you had a real job?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371824490055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371824541479-68</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spot on Mir.........the usuall mental dwarfs are upset at being exposed to the truth. Wear their name calling and infantile insults as a badge of honor.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1371824541479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371825162901-69</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Is the New Civil Rights Movement</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371823092043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glenn Beck should get attacked by you leftists. He's done more to expose your pinko movement than anyone. Communist Van Jones, ACORN's corrupt underground movement were all exposed by Glenn Beck.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1371825162901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371825588522-70</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>squirting...... missing !!!!</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1371825588522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371825715019-71</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still playing with yourself, huh spart</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371825715019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371825795214-72</Id><Title>#$%$ ? Why down again after all the new orders ?</Title><Msg>Profit taking ?</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1371825795214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371826214656-73</Id><Title>Bagdad Jim, Seattle's own</Title><Msg>Unguided since Norm's departure, where he could defer to whatever Norm says. Bagdad Jim sez having mug shots of terroist is racist?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371826214656</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371826483816-74</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you blackmail-able?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371826483816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371826979133-75</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What did you have in mind? Which tyrant would you like to start with?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371826979133</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371827226691-76</Id><Title>Furlough Doctors and Nurses Caring for Wounded Warriors......</Title><Msg>.....but give IRS agents 90 Million dollars in bonuses and send the President on a very expensive African Safari. Where are the priorities of this administration?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371827226691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:07:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371827811055-77</Id><Title>Just found- United Airline maintenance technicians did not follow the manual! Additional training is needed!</Title><Msg>No big deal!</Msg><Username>venture_capitalist123</Username><Timestamp>1371827811055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371827920870-78</Id><Topic><Title>787 cost 30 billion, profit margin is 5% what is the break even point ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370672455985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 02:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really threw the Waynker into a snit when you tweaked his nose.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1371827920870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371828381025-79</Id><Topic><Title>Why Don't We Pay Congressmen The Same pay as the Military</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371828238788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:23:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And make them work as many days as military personnel. 90 yr old career guys too old to know what they are even voting for on the tax payer dime get wheel chaired in.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1371828381025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371828437932-80</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spart, i mean ali, lets start at the top and work our way down, barack first</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371828437932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371828609548-81</Id><Topic><Title>Why Don't We Pay Congressmen The Same pay as the Military</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1371828238788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:23:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have a few local politicians worth that much so I emphasize a few, on the state level even fewer, and on the national level even fewer...but most all of them think that they are worth more...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371828609548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371828989407-82</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lunch with valerie then clearing the plate for the weekend... 10:45 AM The President receives the Presidential Daily Briefing 11:30 AM The President meets with senior advisors 2:05 PM The President makes a personnel announcement</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371828989407</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371829261947-83</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency - Obviously they have. You have to just shake your head and laugh when one of their ignoramuses mentions equality: Equality to a democrat usually means you have something you worked for that I want. So the government should take it from you and give it to me. Equality to a Democrat means we must admit someone to a university, give them a promotion at work or a loan from the bank simply because of the color of their skin while more qualified people of another color are denied these things.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371829261947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371829277437-84</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently, according to your theory, Justice Roberts, a Bushco nominees is/was balckmail-able by the Obama administration but the freshman Senator Barrak Obama was not blackmail-able by the Bushco administration..which definitely abused their NSA authority</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371829277437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371829383727-85</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spart, how come you won't put my update to white house schedule on the topic page?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371829383727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371829644050-86</Id><Topic><Title>787 cost 30 billion, profit margin is 5% what is the break even point ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370672455985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 02:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing 787 did a lot better than your A400M wayndickless- don't forget that the propeller driven A400M which is airbus's answer to the Boeing C-17 is 5 years late and facing order cancellations and a user community that doesn't trust its propulsion system- cost of the A400M more than 20 billion Euros--HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR HAR HARHAR HAR AHR HAR HARHAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371829644050</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371829644928-87</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus, the latest greatest white house schedule already has two thumbs down, how come it's not worthy of your topic page?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371829644928</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371829668779-88</Id><Title>It's Hard to Justify having a Federal government.</Title><Msg>.....the one we have now has obviously gotten so big and corrupt it's totally out of control. Let's have 50 little countries with agreements with each other to facilitate trade and defense.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371829668779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371829727190-89</Id><Title>Censored50times Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Fascist</Title><Msg>about to go ballistic on a meassageboard once again ?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371829727190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:48:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371829748779-90</Id><Topic><Title>787 cost 30 billion, profit margin is 5% what is the break even point ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370672455985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 02:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forbes is a might low- but considering the 1000 orders in hand and at least another 1000 to 2000 come the 787 will make a ton of money</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371829748779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371829837491-91</Id><Topic><Title>It's Hard to Justify having a Federal government.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371829668779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mediocreclassguy are your related to spazticus, he's also fond of dumb, if not gay, IDs</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371829837491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371830113719-92</Id><Topic><Title>It's Hard to Justify having a Federal government.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371829668779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>without the Federal Government criminals like mediocretin and censored would be able to hide under the corrupt laws of their home states, run wild and strip the population of its riches for their own gain. They would do insane things like reinstitute the slave auctions in Charleston and Savannah and outlaw abortion as well as make every citizen go out and buy dozens of guns - nuff to make you puke isn't it</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371830113719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371830130529-93</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus prefers to keep the occupiers schedule a secret...</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371830130529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371830209632-94</Id><Title>The Priorities of the Obama Administration</Title><Msg>Pulling a page from Obama’s sequester playbook, the Agriculture Department threatened to cut spending on a program that assists poor women and children rather than grant money that helps market a Bloody Mary mix, for example. Agriculture Secretary Tom Vilsack warned about the dire consequences of sequester in a letter to the Senate back in February, which included cuts to the Women, Infants and Children program, raging wildfires, the elimination of rental assistance for more than 10,000 very low-income rural residents, extensive pest and disease outbreaks, and the list went on. But Sen. Tom Coburn, also known as “Dr. No,” happened to find a few other programs that should be first on the chopping block before cutting assistance to 600,000 women and children who rely on WIC for food and health care services. Via The Washington Times: Mr. Coburn offered a number of places the Agriculture Department might look at cutting before it goes into big programs such as WIC, pointing to the $45,000 grant to market the Bloody Mary mix; the Indiana Soybean Alliance’s $15,000 grant to study the feasibility of producing fish food in that state; or the $213,000 a small Virginia farm was awarded to grow more strawberries, which are turned into ice cream and jellies. Mr. Coburn also questioned the department’s decision to designate all of Martha’s Vineyard, Mass., known as a vacation spot for the wealthy, as a rural area eligible for special Agriculture Department homeowner loans. If borrowers default on their loans, taxpayers are on the hook for the mortgages. Mr. Coburn said it seemed odd that wealthy homeowners could get access to loans, but the department had warned that sequesters could cut off rental assistance to “more than 10,000 very low income rural residents, generally elderly, disabled and single female heads of households.” “Apparently, inhabitants of these affluent summer vacation getaways — and other prosperous communities across the country — are not among the 10,000 rural residents threatened with losing rental assistance by USDA as a result of sequestration,” Mr. Coburn wrote. “Before USDA evicts elderly and disabled from rural housing, the department should end its subsidies for summer island homes for the rich and famous.” So, how many people really have been dropped from the WIC program as a result of sequestration? And just how much has the USDA spent supporting alcoholic beverages over the last five years? Coburn is demanding answers to these and a number of other questions by July 22, 2013. “With sequestration being blamed for cutting services to those in need, it is time to sober up with how federal funds are being spent and focus on serving people rather than drinks,” Coburn said.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371830209632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371830261002-95</Id><Topic><Title>Censored50times Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Fascist</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371829727190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:48:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there he is again, "bisbee_angler" AKA mxte, i mean sparty, board dope peddler/fascist</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371830261002</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:57:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371830422458-96</Id><Title>$97.42</Title><Msg>took out my option expiration for a profit yeah baby</Msg><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1371830422458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371830702849-97</Id><Topic><Title>$97.42</Title><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1371830422458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>contard, err somethingbigiscomingup, psychotic gay pedophile / raving lib has got spart's back</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371830702849</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371830747381-98</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus bettered Boeing at the paris Airshow and Tom O'Brein called it on Boeing stock a two for one deal</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371809272088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once investors realize that Airbus gave away airplanes so that they could win contracts over Boeing like the Easyjet deal, they'll run away.</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1371830747381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371830854662-99</Id><Topic><Title>Censored50times Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Fascist</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371829727190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:48:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mxte/sparty sounds like good company if a dumb-fascist out-of-state burger-flipping loser is on my tail</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371830854662</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371831127693-100</Id><Topic><Title>It's Hard to Justify having a Federal government.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371829668779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosima.....that's the beauty of having 50 little countries. If you preferred Michigan and Illinois to Texas or Colorado......you could vote with your feet or you could stay right in the slums of South Chicago where you live and work to make it like a red state. That's freedom. Why do you hate freedom so much?</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371831127693</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371831132485-101</Id><Topic><Title>Censored50times Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Fascist</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371829727190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:48:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty how come you won't put the white house schedule on the topic page? no burgers today, i'm here with you ALL day, if I so choose.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371831132485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371831217436-102</Id><Topic><Title>787 cost 30 billion, profit margin is 5% what is the break even point ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370672455985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 02:20:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Management certainly thinks they will start making money at some point down the learning curve. But, it's dangerous to project past reductions in production costs with aluminum airplanes to a composite one. So far the 87 has not correlated well. Given the way it was designed it is going to be more expensive to build than an equivalent aluminum plane. The critical question is where that value will stabilize. One symptom of concern on the part of management is their attempt to squeeze the suppliers. I hope that Boeing does start making money on the 87 (and 777x) and I hope that a competitor doesn't come up with a rival plane that optimizes composites for fabrication. Hasn't happened yet but if it does Boeing will be cooked.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371831217436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371831496195-103</Id><Topic><Title>$97.42</Title><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1371830422458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the only big coming up so far is more of the same big liar from the McNenry management clan, n'est ce pas</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371831496195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:18:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371831502709-104</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seeing as he doesn't wanna put the white house schedule on the topic page, let's put sparty front and center AGAIN, the way he likes it.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371831502709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:18:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371831868314-105</Id><Topic><Title>$97.42</Title><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1371830422458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my mistake, "bisbee_angler" is contard, the psychotic gay pedophile, who's also big into IDs... our multi ID queens seem to have a lot in common, just like barack's appointments</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371831868314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832069691-106</Id><Topic><Title>$97.42</Title><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1371830422458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>got low T, eat more nuts you loser/poser teabagged dumbfascist</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371832069691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832115620-107</Id><Topic><Title>$97.42</Title><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1371830422458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, thnx BA meassgebaord censor</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371832115620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832281827-108</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Three messages, two replies. An entire thread, all from ONE poster, censored50. Raving, barely understandable paranoia, and replies to himself. All mention ""sparty," "spart," and "spazticus," as if that one poster or the other were in control of what he can or can't post. You give too much credit, censored50; you imagine too much, and need to take a break from this board before it deranges you even more than normal. Since I usually have you on my ignore list, I only noticed because of the number of posts you have posted in this mental rut. Awesome. Almost frightening. Do us all a favor. Have a good stiff drink and get a life.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371832281827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:31:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832638619-109</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like Sparty's posts, they keep the board interesting. At least he's not a DFC.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371832638619</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832682776-110</Id><Topic><Title>It's Hard to Justify having a Federal government.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371829668779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That has been tried, mediocre, 1861-1865 and it failed so miserably only a whacko would consider going back to it. In the great drive to have a DECENTRALIZED government, the Confederate States of America implemented the first "nation"-wide INCOME TAX in the "two" nations that had once been British colonies. And the CSA also implemented the first "nation"-wide DRAFT (conscription) in our history as well. Looks like they either found a decentralized federal govt. was unworkable, or else they had nothing against strong federal govt., they just didn't like the one they had.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371832682776</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832716294-111</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what does that not surprise me sparty</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371832716294</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832761065-112</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oops, meant ....WHY does that not surprise me sparty</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371832761065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832799983-113</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to an old Russin proverb: it doesn;t matter if the cow is black or white the milk come out the same unless the cow is carribean/syrian brown whence chocolate milk</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371832799983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832882153-114</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't do the math. Do the research and use logic.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832882153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832945580-115</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ ? Why down again after all the new orders ?</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1371825795214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 10:43:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market is still reeling from yesterdays drop.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371832945580</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371832947887-116</Id><Title>In Other News</Title><Msg>Another plane came limping in.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832947887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371832991485-117</Id><Topic><Title>In Other News</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832947887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>details??</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371832991485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833017769-118</Id><Topic><Title>In Other News</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832947887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no need to change IDs just for us spart</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371833017769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833101306-119</Id><Topic><Title>Soldiers Died for Freedom</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371776881654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so right, sam! Like the first senten ce that says something about "We the People of the United States, in Order to ... insure domestic Tranquility, provide for the common defence ..." Putz</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371833101306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833174237-120</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Is the New Civil Rights Movement</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371823092043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beck is a huckster and a JOKE not worth any attention at all, far less attacking.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371833174237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833498385-121</Id><Topic><Title>Washington State said goodbye to Boeing chicago and good riddance hellow contractors and Airbus</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371753608208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:40:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See? It DOES feel better, doesn't it? ;-D</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371833498385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833504485-122</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have the fund-a-mentals changed... no thnx to Boing but...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371833504485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833513447-123</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus bettered Boeing at the paris Airshow and Tom O'Brein called it on Boeing stock a two for one deal</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371809272088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And still Boeing's stock is out performing Airbus's...........for the fifth straight day.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1371833513447</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833519232-124</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Is the New Civil Rights Movement</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371823092043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>please explain chrissie ps: if not a useful idiot, YOU're most certainly a huckster</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371833519232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833629670-125</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>contard why do my posts bout your aliases keep disappearing? you working with spart, or does he have your back?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371833629670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371833798129-126</Id><Topic><Title>In Other News</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832947887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>London to Houston-landed at Newark. Oil filter light.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371833798129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:56:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371834020100-127</Id><Title>Apparently we only have until about 20 JAN 2017</Title><Msg>to fully appreciate the Obama Administration I wonder who the repugs/fascist will run against Hillary et al... perhaps Jeb Bushco (lol) heaven forbid madchelle bachmann who will turne over her overdrive to dribbling RWNJ hat speech like a quitter srah palin for more $$$, akin to the RWNJ media ho-ho's who say they are too stoopid to be president yet reap million$ from the dimwiited repubes who berate the IRS for attempting to close the lopp-holes on illicit teabbager organizations... Christie from NJ has some mob connections and likes to say leave the cannoli... etc..</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371834020100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:00:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834199307-128</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus bettered Boeing at the paris Airshow and Tom O'Brein called it on Boeing stock a two for one deal</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371809272088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>morisretired you mean like Boeing being 4 years late and 30 billion dollars overcast on the 787 sure. Next freeveritas 5 whole days forgets both stocks , if your holding them, and you should be out now , are down today and for the last 5 days both Airbus and boeing holders are down , no way to manage your money freeveritas. over the recent trend of year to date and for 3 years any Boeing shareholder has been bettered by Airbus . Airbus stock holders over 3 years are better off by over 105% than Boeing shareholders in gains Airbus shareholders for the year to date are better off by 5% than Boeing shareholders so there is no profit on the 787 and will not be any profit for years to come . The 4 year delay has allowed Airbus to build their better answer, the 350 will eat away both the 787 and the 777 margins. .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371834199307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834363973-129</Id><Topic><Title>CEO of boeing compares to the USA Airbus Chairman Airbus CEO brings American jobs here which is better ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371776794989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:06:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets hear it for Allan McArtor a American hero and a man who will bring jobs to the USA unlike the CEO of Boeing who hates unions and American workers and ships jobs outside of the USA</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371834363973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834389182-130</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you think Obama's not being blackmailed?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371834389182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834487136-131</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody's blackmailable by parties that have enough resources. All they have to do is threaten to lie. Or they can blackmail you on the basis of your friends or relatives who may have done stupid things.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371834487136</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834513787-132</Id><Topic><Title>Slaves of Corporation have Never known Freedom</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371661606435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corporations are just one avenue - Student loans are another</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371834513787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834681047-133</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty, err chrissie, picks and chooses which posts to bury, which posts to delete, and which posts will never see front topic page. sparty is a reflection of our fascist gov't, fascist schools, and fascist media</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371834681047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834723128-134</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The proof is in the pudding...he hasn't had your #$%$ canned for $1 has he... you are no Snowden...get it...Catch-22</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371834723128</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371834806126-135</Id><Title>"Which Airline Stock Can Make You Really Rich"anaylist compares BA to Airbus conclusion Airbus is the best stock</Title><Msg>" I would put my money in EADS due to its proven price appreciation over time. This holds true now more than ever, as the latest manifestation of European engineering takes flight – I expect it to take the share price up along with it to 30,000 feet."</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371834806126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834872991-136</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heaven forbid, stoopid thingys... how about all the 'smart' thingys</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371834872991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834943482-137</Id><Topic><Title>Slaves of Corporation have Never known Freedom</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371661606435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spart, why did gov't takeover school loans? it's a control thing for dumbos huh? they wanna control the decisions/power and wealth...just as their commie, i mean health, care exchanges are little more than PACs for the dumb party.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371834943482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:15:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371834970289-138</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roger that, some spartyloon REMF calloing in an airstrike via s drone...taking out the new alQ #2</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371834970289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371835055355-139</Id><Topic><Title>In Other News</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832947887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reports show that was a low engine oil flight yesterday on the Newark landing. Two days ago one was diverted to Seattle for oil filter light.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371835055355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371835121069-140</Id><Topic><Title>NSA Whistleblower: NSA Spying On – and Blackmailing – Top Government Officials</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371812236542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:57:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>contard, how come sparty keeps deleting my posts intended to familiarize others with your aliases, surely sparty doesn't find your IDs offensive?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371835121069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371835401376-141</Id><Title>Airbus CEO on the 777x and impressions about the 350 Airbus betters Boeing</Title><Msg>Leahy dismissed the 777X, which will retain the 777 metal fuselage, as “a paper airplane, a very heavy paper airplane.” “It’s not going to be competitive with an all-new ... aircraft like the (A350)-1000,” Leahy said. In Airbus’ closing news conference, he insisted that the design concept Boeing presented in Paris is unfinished and unwieldy. He derided the planned folding wingtips as “silly things.” “We doubt Boeing is going to build the airplane you see today,” he said.Airbus has certainly handled A350 development way better than it turned out for Boeing on the 787. Walter Stephan — CEO of Austrian composites structures firm FACC, which supplies major pieces to both programs — said in an interview in Paris he believes the A350 program will meet Airbus’ goals. “It’s well organized. They’ll do it. I believe what they say,” Stephan said.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371835401376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371835484010-142</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus bettered Boeing at the paris Airshow and Tom O'Brein called it on Boeing stock a two for one deal</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371809272088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On several occasions I have pointed out how you could have "traded" different stocks for a much higher rate of return than what you said you made and boasted about with your "trades". Therefore, by your definition you are a hack and don't understand trading because you could have done so much better. Do you now "get the point" on how stupid you sound when disparage a Boeing investor who is up 230% and 30% YTD.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1371835484010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371835558518-143</Id><Topic><Title>In Other News</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832947887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey your low engine oil light is on don't worry about that, it's always on...must be a short-circuit in any case if you wanna fly the plane be my guess but please do not try to taxi-over that commuter plane as it might interupt you engine oil flow in which case... BA planes needs better pilots</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371835558518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371835623801-144</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus bettered Boeing at the paris Airshow and Tom O'Brein called it on Boeing stock a two for one deal</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371809272088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and still airbus stock is outperforming Boeing stock for the 3rd straight year by over 105% better</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371835623801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371835685627-145</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus bettered Boeing at the paris Airshow and Tom O'Brein called it on Boeing stock a two for one deal</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371809272088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 06:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and still airbus stock for the year to date is better by 5% than Boeing buy and hold shareholders see how that works freeveritas</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371835685627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371836537997-146</Id><Title>Leaving Texas on the 4th day of July</Title><Msg>burns my eyes to listen burns my eyes to see the dime will fall sun so hot clouds so low</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371836537997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371836719661-147</Id><Title>I bet a billion dollars for 50K</Title><Msg>invested another for 12k and the day ain't over yet</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371836719661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371836856293-148</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 leaves and poof neospart99 appears avator name</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807720116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I explained very clearly why I have spartacus99991 and neospart99 as ids. Have you explained why you were dell.george, fred.james48, and now waynedickinson961? Or are you hiding those identities because you couldn't back up your claims from years ago?</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371836856293</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371837143022-149</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 leaves and poof neospart99 appears avator name</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807720116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus does get a lot of things right. You on the other hand..</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1371837143022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371837647012-150</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris, I just tried to read these posts. Wow, I think I'm going to nominate censored50 as a viable contender to Wayne for board most annoying person for incoherent posts.</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371837647012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371837818409-151</Id><Topic><Title>Leaving Texas on the 4th day of July</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371836537997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grateful Dead 11-24-78 Capitol Theater Passaic NJ</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371837818409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371837952814-152</Id><Title>Will increase airplane output by another 60% in next 6 months and increase dividend payment! Raise the guidance!</Title><Msg>Very good things are coming!</Msg><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1371837952814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:05:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371837997436-153</Id><Title>Beat estimate by a wide margin! It is like Netflex and Google!</Title><Msg>Great numbers are coming!</Msg><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1371837997436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371838117918-154</Id><Topic><Title>Will increase airplane output by another 60% in next 6 months and increase dividend payment! Raise the guidance!</Title><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1371837952814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:05:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mCnERNRY MENTIONED SHARE THEW PAIN SUPPLIERS WILL ALONG WITH THE GAIN AND i AGREEd FLOOD YOU BIG RIVER</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371838117918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371838303809-155</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 leaves and poof neospart99 appears avator name</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807720116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371838303809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371838536799-156</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 leaves and poof neospart99 appears avator name</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807720116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What did he shoot and what was the score....you write like someone who never knows the score.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371838536799</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371838593678-157</Id><Topic><Title>"Which Airline Stock Can Make You Really Rich"anaylist compares BA to Airbus conclusion Airbus is the best stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371834806126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>C'mon Dell, try to keep up. Last I heard, neither BA or Airbus were in the Airline biz. Friday is my usual day to look at this board and what do I see? Dell, spewing his typical bullpuckey. I think one poster had it right when he said you are in reality a hack. I prefer the term prevaricator when I think about how to describe your obviously slanted and biased half truths. Have a nice day!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1371838593678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371838758617-158</Id><Topic><Title>Leaving Texas on the 4th day of July</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371836537997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bisbee Pumas were always such wimps. Everyone used them to put another W in the column.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371838758617</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:19:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371838905041-159</Id><Topic><Title>Leaving Texas on the 4th day of July</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371836537997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PROOF ?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371838905041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371838961070-160</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats lost all Semblance of Decency</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371820258518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:10:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sure they ever had any? I'm not.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371838961070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:22:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371839180793-161</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pure......democrats think mixing communism with democracy is embracing diversity.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371839180793</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371839214048-162</Id><Topic><Title>I bet a billion dollars for 50K</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371836719661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:45:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FEED THE FISH</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1371839214048</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371839264915-163</Id><Title>Will The Banksters ever be Punished? or AKA "Did the Banksters Ruin Your Financial Health As Well"?</Title><Msg>The Last Mystery of the Financial Crisis See Yahoo finance Everything Is Rigged: The Biggest Price-Fixing Scandal Ever In incriminating e-mail after incriminating e-mail, executives and analysts from these companies are caught admitting their entire business model is crooked. "Lord help our #$%$ scam . . . this has to be the stupidest place I have worked at," writes one Standard &amp; Poor's executive. "As you know, I had difficulties explaining 'HOW' we got to those numbers since there is no science behind it," confesses a high-ranking S&amp;P analyst. "If we are just going to make it up in order to rate deals, then quants [quantitative analysts] are of precious little value," complains another senior S&amp;P man. "Let's hope we are all wealthy and retired by the time this house of card[s] falters," ruminates one more. The Scam Wall Street Learned From the Mafia Wall Street, now there's a place one can advocate no holds barred, any machine gun goes, hunt for the three "B's" of financial ruination: Bulls, Bears and Banksters.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1371839264915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371839595458-164</Id><Topic><Title>Let's all post</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371773326340</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bus didn't say he was going to use the Authorization as a license to invade. Anybody with any sense could have told him that was lunacy. Anybody with any sense would have assumed that Bush's use of military force would have been limited to airtstrikes on power lines, pipelines, and bridges.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371839595458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:33:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371839654485-165</Id><Title>99.35-0.29(0.29%)2:31 PMEDT</Title><Msg>got to have loving</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371839654485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371839672424-166</Id><Topic><Title>Slaves of Corporation have Never known Freedom</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371661606435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many countries that don't tax incomes name one you idioooot- and if you can find a couple you can be sure that the revenue is made up for with sales taxes and/or capital gains which is as painful as income taxes- pay for you are just plain st000pid</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371839672424</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840011498-167</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats gladly follow and support their Dem politicians. These are the same politicians who have given us social security, medicare, Obama care, medicade, voting rights, civil rights, union rights, education assistance and priveliges and in each case these issues were fought tooth and nail by the RWNJs and douchebaggers- the real question is how could anybody support the RWNJs and pukes</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371840011498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:40:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840016929-168</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 leaves and poof neospart99 appears avator name</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807720116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a guy who doesn't know what the goal is.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371840016929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840142406-169</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 leaves and poof neospart99 appears avator name</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807720116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>comon chrissie, sparty has hundreds of IDs active and disabled. how many have you got? are you two related?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371840142406</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840150742-170</Id><Topic><Title>Will The Banksters ever be Punished? or AKA "Did the Banksters Ruin Your Financial Health As Well"?</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1371839264915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stay alive not the revolting travolta stay alive vinne barbarinno nonsernse but stay alive and spout your kind of sense aka the last VP candy-date from the repug party hitched hios hide to mittens and said , quoting verbatim: "ran a sub 3 hour marathon" and "dont feed fish" no wonder, we aren;t winning by so much again</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371840150742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840182544-171</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Continue War on Women</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371663965242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sdmiller4747 makes another 6th grade definition error. "Why do you call yourselves Democrats when anyone with half a brain knows that they are code word for Scientists (not Socialists) and Cooperatists (not Communists)? Maybe you should have a coming out party." Most Democrats have come out and been awarded high honors throughout the history of the USA. Take Mr. Obama's or Dr. King's Nobel Peace Prize as an example. sdmiller4747, and your multiple personalities, will never win on your current limited plateform in life. Thats why the term loser was invented. To describe the likes of your kind. However, once you get your mind right and turn your heart over to Jesus, it might be possible for your kind to reform to one degree or another.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1371840182544</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840232819-172</Id><Topic><Title>It's Hard to Justify having a Federal government.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371829668779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are really ignorant about history. It has never been tried....the civil war was a war to keep it from being tried. The articles of confederation mike make more sense today than a massive federal bureaucracy that is not accountable to anyone but its self. You must be a victim of socialized government education......your ignorance is astounding.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371840232819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840238239-173</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean those are the same politicians that rob peter to buy and/or payoff paul</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371840238239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840349647-174</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 leaves and poof neospart99 appears avator name</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371807720116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 05:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't forget zipdick and fred....</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371840349647</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840440830-175</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They haven't quite given us as much as the Communist Party gave Russia, but they keep trying .......and the results will be the same.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371840440830</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371840588931-176</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK-FEB'S TITLES...</Title><Msg>Love all his id's waynedick, dellgeorge,paul, fredjames , zipdick... zipdick is the best! Very appropriate for him!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371840588931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840652256-177</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump for spazticus, multi-id circle jerk and ba board fascist</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371840652256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371840815387-178</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Continue War on Women</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371663965242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus, err pretend patriot, bumping spazticus, sparty is gender confused as many of his multiple IDs will will attest</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371840815387</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371840913023-179</Id><Title>Obama Administration's Chemical Weapons Claim Looks Dubious</Title><Msg>It turns out the Obama Administration's claim that Syrian President Bashar al-Assad used chemical weapons in the ongoing civil war rests on dubious evidence -- from the Post: Despite months of laboratory testing and scrutiny by top U.S. scientists, the Obama administration’s case for arming Syria’s rebels rests on unverifiable claims that the Syrian government used chemical weapons against its own people, according to diplomats and experts. The United States, Britain and France have supplied the United Nations with a trove of evidence, including multiple blood, tissue and soil samples, that U.S. officials say proves that Syrian troops used the nerve agent sarin on the battlefield. But the nature of the physical evidence — as well as the secrecy over how it was collected and analyzed — has opened the administration to criticism by independent experts, who say there is no reliable way to assess its authenticity. The technical data presented by the three Western powers is of limited value to U.N. inspectors trying to determine whether Syria’s combatants used chemical weapons during the country’s 25-month-old conflict. Under the United Nations’ terms of reference, only evidence personally collected by its inspectors can be used to fashion a final judgment. But no inspectors have been allowed inside Syria, so Western governments have relied on physical evidence smuggled out of the country by rebels or intelligence operatives. Precisely who acquired the evidence and what methods were used to guard against tampering may be unknowable, according to experts experienced at investigating chemical weapons claims. The more we learn, the more we see the President's intervention in the Syrian conflict for what it is: a fool's errand.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371840913023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841023164-180</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Administration's Chemical Weapons Claim Looks Dubious</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371840913023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:55:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty denies existence and/or use of chemical and biological weapons in all cases related to m uslim made disasters</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371841023164</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841042929-181</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice non sequitur. It is what you do when you get crushed by logic.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371841042929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841123278-182</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Continue their Murderous Slaughter of Innocent Babies</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1371732586965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats want to kill the innocent and nourish the guilty.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371841123278</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841561637-183</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Continue their Murderous Slaughter of Innocent Babies</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1371732586965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rebel you are a #$%$ and a liar. No Democrat or OBGYN for that matter advocates the murder of innocent babies. These professionals do contend that abortion should be legal to the 24th week of pregnancy- keep up your criminal lies and you are going to continue to get put down. I bet you are one of the evil b.....s that communicate and cavort with that murderer Scott Roeder who murdered Dr Tiller even tho he is in prison. One of these days the supreme court will grow some balls and come after you and your ilk for violation of the Roe Wade decision</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371841561637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:06:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841699893-184</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here you go spart, i mean novit.... The Shadow Party was conceived and organized principally by George Soros, Hillary Clinton and Harold McEwan Ickes… "The Shadow Party is the real power driving the Democrat machine. It is a network of radicals dedicated to transforming our constitutional republic into a socialist hive. The leader of these radicals is ... George Soros. He has essentially privatized the Democratic Party, bringing it under his personal control. The Shadow Party is the instrument through which he exerts that control. ... It works by siphoning off hundreds of millions of dollars in campaign contributions that would have gone to the Democratic Party in normal times, and putting those contributions at the personal disposal of Mr. Soros. He then uses that money to buy influence and loyalty where he sees fit. In 2003, Soros set up a network of privately-owned groups which acts as a shadow or mirror image of the Party. It performs all the functions we would normally expect the real Democratic Party to perform, such as shaping the Party platform, fielding candidates, running campaigns, and so forth. However, it performs these functions under the private supervision of Mr. Soros and his associates. The Shadow Party derives its power from its ability to raise huge sums of money. By controlling the Democrat purse strings, the Shadow Party can make or break any Democrat candidate by deciding whether or not to fund him. During the 2004 election cycle, the Shadow Party raised more than $300 million for Democrat candidates, prompting one of its operatives, MoveOn PAC director Eli Pariser, to declare, “Now it’s our party. We bought it, we own it…”"”</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371841699893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841721126-185</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparticus thinks everyone who disagrees is UnAmerican. Censored thinks anyone who isn't Censored is Sparticus.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371841721126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:08:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841763106-186</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Continue their Murderous Slaughter of Innocent Babies</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1371732586965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zapperently you are Younger than the racist Paula Deen</Msg><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1371841763106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841789064-187</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think YOU're spaziticus</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371841789064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841889363-188</Id><Topic><Title>In Other News</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832947887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were 4 excellent pilots aboard. The plane landed without incident. The passengers continued their travels aboard a 767.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371841889363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:11:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841892429-189</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Continue their Murderous Slaughter of Innocent Babies</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1371732586965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>contard is that you, or someone pretending to be you? whoever you are, i wonder, i a black man uses the n word? is he a racist?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371841892429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841912798-190</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Logic. Governments produce nothing of themselves and can only give their citizens that which they first take from them. All of the programs mentioned by the mentally challenged (that would include norivit) are simply transfers of wealth. If everyone pays their own way....why is there such a horrendous unfunded liability? Democrats keep searching for the same utopia or worker's paradise that communists have always promised but can never deliver.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371841912798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371841997765-191</Id><Title>You can short the next big thing, you just have to buy it back..</Title><Msg>dddddddddddddddddd</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1371841997765</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371841999407-192</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know you do. But, you are mistaken-n-n.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371841999407</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371842158012-193</Id><Title>The morrels of the story is...</Title><Msg>if your powder ain't dry then how can I lit a cheery bomb and flush it down the toilet at the LACC fourth holer and IT still blow the base off.... oops the grass around that hole needs more water, imho let;s go to the fitth, up and over...then the sixth....</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1371842158012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842257966-194</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again you go to the non sequitur. "The GOP destroys themselves using this process, it is right out of the COMMUNIST playbook (eliminate the "un-pure" of thought or ideology)." You can't refute that statement because it's true, so you babble about a bunch of unrelated stuff. "All of the programs mentioned by the mentally challenged (that would include norivit)" Please name a single program i mentioned, Just one. You can't because that whole statement is a fabrication. Another COMMUNIST tactic you employ. You have become what claim to hate. That blood you see on the floor is from your nose, it's been broken by the sledgehammer you took to the face.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371842257966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842395517-195</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does that have to do with anything? More of your babble that means nothing.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371842395517</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842445202-196</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK-FEB'S TITLES...</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371840588931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Domerr, You forgot the his Best One Limpdick!!!! One hell of a week$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371842445202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842471113-197</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i don't think so, i might miss every once in awhile, but i'll bet i'm right more'n 90% of the time it's kinda tough when keeping up with ID queens, i'm still not convinced sparty n chrissie aren't one in the same moore-on, contard on the other hand is a disquishable by his psychosis and sexual deviance / innuendo...beyond gay...li'l boys, genitals, bondage...</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371842471113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842498239-198</Id><Topic><Title>In Other News</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1371832947887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The plane landed without incident despite 4 'excellent' pilots aboard.... in any case... fix the light, short-circuit...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371842498239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842607840-199</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Continue their Murderous Slaughter of Innocent Babies</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1371732586965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosima......do you still believe that black people are only 3/5s human......aa you do a 24 week old baby. Should the age of a baby determine whether you can kill it or not?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371842607840</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842643511-200</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another classic from fascist/bumper/censored: "disquishable (sic) by his psychosis."</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1371842643511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842780798-201</Id><Topic><Title>stock trading BA and TSLA and how spart came to dog me</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371801012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 03:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting spin again from dell/fred/wayne. However I was posting the challenge results every week for at least 4 months and the average of your 10 touted stocks lost every week to a $100,000 investment in BA. Just the facts, you can look it up. So, are you going to tell us now when you would have exited/shorted some of those stocks and some you would have stayed in much longer. SBUX, AAPL, and NKE did very well over the last 2 years of the challenge. Most of the others, not so well. I especially liked your pick of SSN at 4.53 and today it's 0.43 for a nice 90 percent loss. That one lost over 30 percent in the first week. Nice pick!</Msg><Username>neospart99</Username><Timestamp>1371842780798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842793004-202</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK-FEB'S TITLES...</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371840588931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh man...can't stop laughing! Ba acting very well considering the week!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371842793004</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842811873-203</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Continue War on Women</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371663965242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus err spazMOpretendMO err patriot err fascist err bumper spazticus, sparty err fascist err fascistmo err islamospazMO</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1371842811873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842859396-204</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Continue War on Women</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371663965242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spart is having a spaz</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371842859396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371842897769-205</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is an unpure thought? Is believing in freedom pure and no wanting people to take away freed unpure? You make no sense.because you have no sense.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371842897769</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371843233631-206</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty Multi ID Disinformation Peddler and Board Moderator/Fascist</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371820329598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:12:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty how come you won't let me list contards IDs, as a public service to those no so familiar with our BA board dope peddlers?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371843233631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371843261430-207</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Continue War on Women</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371663965242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's get one thing straight, please. (Put on your thinking cap.) I AM THE ONE TRUE SPAZ. Not "spart" or ______. Got that?</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1371843261430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371843659081-208</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Continue War on Women</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371663965242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roger that, you are the one true spaz, you and about 200 other IDs, current and disabled</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371843659081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:40:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371843694378-209</Id><Title>let's go, let's go down to juniors farm - paul mccartney</Title><Msg>got a good reason... She's a 21st century woman android all the way got a good reason she;s a 21st centuryy android all the way - or to to the tune of Twentieh Century Fox by the Doors; she's a 21st century droid, oh yeah a 21st century android, oh yeah she's a 21st century droid, oh yeah</Msg><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1371843694378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371844008949-210</Id><Topic><Title>let's go, let's go down to juniors farm - paul mccartney</Title><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1371843694378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty still won't let me post your aliases contard, do you two work in the same jihad center, are there two stools in the BA board cube, or do you share the same one?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371844008949</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371844044469-211</Id><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Msg>Involuntary servitude = Slavery. Something Democrats have a hard time grasping.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371844083374-212</Id><Topic><Title>99.35-0.29(0.29%)2:31 PMEDT</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371839654485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:34:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Price action today is all driven by Quad options expirations. Give 100 is a key option price the close will be close to 100 either side of it. Depends on who has not closed out their positions.</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1371844083374</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371844096600-213</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK-FEB'S TITLES...</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1371840588931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayn #$%$ gave you a thumbs down!!!!! Have a Safe weekend Domerrr!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1371844096600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371844205797-214</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better watch it, you're gonna get contard all hot and bothered, sounds like rape, right up his alley</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371844205797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371844723339-215</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Logic and truth are to RWNJs what kryptonite was to Superman.....</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1371844723339</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371844859208-216</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate trickle-down econ?</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1371844859208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:00:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371844871726-217</Id><Topic><Title>99.35-0.29(0.29%)2:31 PMEDT</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371839654485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 14:34:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>close but no ceegars butt look who took out the 97 options between friends 20 JAN 17 is only a heartebaet away from joe biden et al beep beep and beep beep yeah</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371844871726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371844937234-218</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did you copy and paste that nonsense from? 100% meaningless tripe.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1371844937234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371845010109-219</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can mirde tell us what "great yjings" are?</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1371845010109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371845041730-220</Id><Title>Social Security has an Unfunded Liability of $16.4 trillion</Title><Msg>Medicare has an unfunded liability of $86.4 trillion BTW that is more money than exist in all the countries on the planet.....no wonder we need space exploration. This is what happens when politicians promise something for little to nothing. They can't possibly ask you to pay the full cost of these programs because it would expose the fact they've been lying to you all along.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371845041730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371845273364-221</Id><Title>This really makes Democrats Angry</Title><Msg>"Once one accepts the principle of self-ownership, what's moral and immoral becomes self-evident. Murder is immoral because it violates private property. Rape and theft are also immoral -- they also violate private property. Here's an important question: Would rape become morally acceptable if Congress passed a law legalizing it? You say: "What's wrong with you, Williams? Rape is immoral plain and simple, no matter what Congress says or does!" If you take that position, isn't it just as immoral when Congress legalizes the taking of one person's earnings to give to another? Surely if a private person took money from one person and gave it to another, we'd deem it theft and, as such, immoral. Does the same act become moral when Congress takes people's money to give to farmers, airline companies or an impoverished family? No, it's still theft, but with an important difference: It's legal, and participants aren't jailed." -- Walter Williams</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371845273364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371845429706-222</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slavery in the 21st century: "jobs" at WalMart.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1371845429706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:10:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371845601643-223</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cliberg is one of sparty's EU IDs, sparty hasn't worked a real job for as long as i've been coming to the BA board, close to a decade...sparty the freeloader treats the rest of us as slaves</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371845601643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371845694879-224</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can always leave your job at Walmart and go get a better one.......unless your job at Walmart is the very best job you can get.....in which case you should be thankful you have the very best job you can get..</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371845694879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:14:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371845781939-225</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me guess, in your moronic attempt to make a point you are trying to equate taxes , and what they are used for, to slavery.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371845781939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:16:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371845791997-226</Id><Topic><Title>Social Security has an Unfunded Liability of $16.4 trillion</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371845041730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don Shula from 20 CC to 19 CC to none Kindasleazyrice from 0 to two(?) Cypress and Agusta to zero, none bapsychdept from three-toed Crow to six toe, well, we won;'t say... one gets us into...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371845791997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371845938813-227</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....only what they are used for.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371845938813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371846002360-228</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually it's theft, robbing peter to buy paul, you use gov't to do your thieving in effect i am your slave, paying your bills in return for nothing</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371846002360</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371846344037-229</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you feel that way why do you live here?</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371846344037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371846344859-230</Id><Topic><Title>Social Security has an Unfunded Liability of $16.4 trillion</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371845041730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats have lied about the cost every socialist program they peddled to the country. Obama care will be the biggest boondoggle of all. All have been designed to pass the real cost on to future generations.......nice people.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846344859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371846490068-231</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then you won't mind your throat being slit and you skull focked</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371846490068</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371846494851-232</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.....so we can change it back to the way it used to be. I'm for change ;-)</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846494851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371846521849-233</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you really think that is slavery, you are an even bigger fool than you have shown so far. Definitive proof that it is not slavery, you are free to leave and go live somewhere else, a slave does not have this ability. If you were not such an idiot you would know this. You are not paying my bills, so spare me your sanctimonious BS.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371846521849</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371846717734-234</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's the difference sparty?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371846717734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371846830352-235</Id><Title>James Madison on Using Taxes for Charitable Causes</Title><Msg>• In 1794, when Congress appropriated $15,000 for relief of French refugees who fled from insurrection in San Domingo to Baltimore and Philadelphia, James Madison stood on the floor of the House to object saying, "I cannot undertake to lay my finger on that article of the Constitution which granted a right to Congress of expending, on objects of benevolence, the money of their constituents." -- James Madison, 4 Annals of congress 179 (1794)</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846830352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371846951252-236</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ps: i pay my way, YOU're the parasite remember, save "your sanctimonious BS"</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371846951252</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371847030653-237</Id><Title>maybe I'm Amazed...</Title><Msg>made the UCSD dean's list there is a pizza pie or two baking in an oven the juke box is playing Maybe I'M Amazed, I have free parking and the Michelob brew i\s goi9ng down fine outside the waves are breakinjg favorably the ocean temperture is agreeble the w2ind speed is negligilble nevr coming back</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847030653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371847336742-238</Id><Topic><Title>maybe I'm Amazed...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847030653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not quite amazed....contard has ANOTHER ID, fourmoreprog</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371847336742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371847417280-239</Id><Topic><Title>Paris Air Show- Vote on Boeing vs Airbus Stock Price</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371247771854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, now that the markets have closed on Friday, whose stock price did better during the airshow? BA 6/14 101.83 6/21 99.98 (loss of 1.82%) EADSY 6/14 57.17 6/21 54.00 (loss of 5.54%) EAD.PA 6/14 42.84 6/21 40.75 (loss of 4.87%) Looks like Boeing did better (less bad!) than Airbus for the week. BTW, I included the EAD.PA as this seems to be the accepted stock for Airbus(EADS) in Paris. Other exchanges have very little volume. Wayne seems to like the EADSY price for all his comparisons the last few months and he probably should have done a little more research (although all exchanges move about the same but at different prices).</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371847417280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371847592637-240</Id><Topic><Title>James Madison on Using Taxes for Charitable Causes</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846830352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey idiot, that was more than 200 years ago. Times have changed. Get with it.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1371847592637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371847652956-241</Id><Topic><Title>maybe I'm Amazed...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847030653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amaze me and be dead... is not a thre3at 3...2...1... for more progress</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847652956</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371847815556-242</Id><Topic><Title>maybe I'm Amazed...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847030653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's it going your way.... cenbsored50 and the RWNj';s not evein in 50 mile radiius</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847815556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371848136801-243</Id><Topic><Title>James Madison on Using Taxes for Charitable Causes</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846830352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We used to call him Jimmy, and Jimmy jr. How they be ?</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371848136801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371848497361-244</Id><Topic><Title>maybe I'm Amazed...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847030653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the waves are breaking favorably not always the case... thanky-god almighty bulku\\\y-blob and his ilk mittens rawmoney]are where they are about where I was 40 ye3ars ago</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371848497361</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371848582451-245</Id><Topic><Title>James Madison on Using Taxes for Charitable Causes</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846830352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>times change with latest greatest crony commie / collectivist, huh bebop who'da thought you'd be able to transform the civil and prosperous society born of limited gov't so quickly bebop is another ID i'm not sure about, sparty or contard, contard or sparty</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371848582451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371848706923-246</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So I take it you support cutting the military budget by 80%. Otherwise you're a hypocrite. If you want 800 military bases overseas, you can damn well write a check yourself.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371848706923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371848819586-247</Id><Title>20 JAN 17</Title><Msg>maybe I'm amazed</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371848819586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371848820739-248</Id><Topic><Title>One Must Wonder Why Democrats Still Loyaly Support Their Current Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371775039764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:37:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you think I'm either one?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371848820739</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371848844855-249</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope, you can start by cutting back gov't to pre dumb congress levels, 2006, that'll cut 1.1 trillion out of the budget right off the bat.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371848844855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371848867791-250</Id><Topic><Title>James Madison on Using Taxes for Charitable Causes</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846830352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever happened to THE LIST? Your master LIST of all the sparties and tards and spazzes -- where IS IT?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1371848867791</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:07:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371848884798-251</Id><Topic><Title>The morrels of the story is...</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1371842158012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:15:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's "morels" morran.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371848884798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371849563293-252</Id><Topic><Title>James Madison on Using Taxes for Charitable Causes</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846830352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i've tried posting contards (yours?) several times this afternoons, I guess sparty, board moderator and fascist finds the IDs offensive, i know I do</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371849563293</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371849581437-253</Id><Topic><Title>maybe I'm Amazed...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847030653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unless you cleaning squid</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371849581437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371849864983-254</Id><Topic><Title>Paris Air Show- Vote on Boeing vs Airbus Stock Price</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371247771854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure if I can consider my vote a winner or not, did the A350 do a fly by? I guess I technically lose since I did expect it to and that would have put Airbus as my choice. My vote on June 14 was. "I vote Airbus stock % increase will lead if the A350 does a fly-by(which I expect to happen) Boeing if the A350 does not do a fly-by."</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371849864983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371849943464-255</Id><Topic><Title>maybe I'm Amazed...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847030653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll be back... state fair entries well, behind the curve... maybe, I am amazed some bigger waves thjan bigger sjong ho down now Prespident Obama donna' like my better versio9n of Hail To The Chief, or does he that is what it is all about according to big-e one/nanc</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371849943464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371850119168-256</Id><Topic><Title>The morrels of the story is...</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1371842158012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:15:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If'n when they can xpalin WTC 7 let them knoe</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1371850119168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371850447090-257</Id><Topic><Title>The morrels of the story is...</Title><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1371842158012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:15:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I f anybody thinbks they can improve me spellunks it was us, the people who set set fire to thew british ship and said tax us no mo'...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371850447090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371851156711-258</Id><Topic><Title>James Madison on Using Taxes for Charitable Causes</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1371846830352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you really want to go back to 1794, remember to get your flu shot first!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371851156711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371851202742-259</Id><Topic><Title>let's go, let's go down to juniors farm - paul mccartney</Title><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1371843694378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post. There really was a junior's farm.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371851202742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371851307733-260</Id><Topic><Title>maybe I'm Amazed...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371847030653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371851307733</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371851528752-261</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus beat Boeing in the orders at the Paris Airshow and Boeing stock price</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371744155511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:02:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like I called it! With that heavy activity and no news driving it, I think the big traders were just selling and buying back cheaper, from the suckers that got scared.</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1371851528752</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371851628971-262</Id><Topic><Title>Social Security has an Unfunded Liability of $16.4 trillion</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371845041730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only because you don't pay the FICA tax on any dollar over about $114,000. We have to protect the "job creators" doncha know? Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371851628971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371851735351-263</Id><Topic><Title>This really makes Democrats Angry</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371845273364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:07:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys can only provide us with about three quotes to justify your greed. In more than 200 years of the republic, that's all. Why is that? Because most people above the IQ of moron know your justifications are puckey?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371851735351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371851753631-264</Id><Title>House of Representatives: Still terrible at everything</Title><Msg>House of Representatives: Still terrible at everything House GOP's use of cheap tricks and a backup plan called "blaming Democrats" fails to avert farm bill humiliation By Jim Newell Somehow or other, the U.S. government, for the first time in years, is close-ish to being functional. Don’t read too heavily into that word “functional.” The government is not and will not probably be moving on your pet issue any time soon, sorry. But the Senate is actually moving, on bipartisan pieces of legislation that are in the public spotlight: a farm bill, a comprehensive immigration bill. GOP senators who typically pretend to negotiate compromises and then run for the hills once they near a motion to proceed, like Lindsey Graham and Bob Corker, are suddenly seeing out those compromises. One of the two houses of Congress, in our lifetime, may well be nearing the minimum threshold for competence. Now then, what’s the problem? Oh right, it’s the House of Representatives, which is terrible at everything, and offers no indication of being any other way until at least 2023. Let’s give some credit: They’re adept at passing go-nowhere bills to repeal Obamacare or ban abortion or tattoo the words “Under God” to every baby’s forehead. Great work there from the House Republican Party. On issues that might appeal to an even slightly broader cross-section of the country, though, they’ve got nothing. You know this. You’ve seen the same routine in nearly every important vote since 2009. Remember that time the government considered arbitrarily defaulting on the public debt and destroying the global economy forever? That was a head-scratcher for the House; took some real “working out” before they concluded it would best be averted, for now. It always works out the same way, at the 11th hour. A Senate-originated compromise, after much pouting, is taken up by the House after several defeats of their own insane legislation. Maybe a tweak or two is offered. The House passes it. Conservatives serve up uncreative epithets for John Boehner for exercising the only decent option available to him. The next big piece of legislation comes up. And, at least as of yesterday’s farm bill flop, they begin this same fatal cycle of time wasting again. The House leadership seemed to think, this time around, at least, that a combination of cheap tricks and a backup plan called “blaming Democrats” would change this deeply entrenched dynamic of incompetence that surrounds everything it tries to do. The House didn’t even get to a vote on the farm bill last year, knowing it didn’t have enough votes. What could the leadership do differently this time to make sure that a bill hated by most Democrats and still too many Republicans, facing a certain Senate death and then if necessary a White House veto, could pass for no productive reason? It could … put Iowa Rep. Steve King in charge of whipping? Yes. Yes! This would change the dynamic altogether. If a nutbird like Steve King was the one pushing for this bill then surely all conservatives would fall in line. There’s little we enjoy more than watching a useless no-voting screecher in Congress suddenly realize he needs his #$%$ corn money and then desperately try to persuade his comrades for their votes. And then when it fails, he is just so disappointed in their ability to see the bigger picture. Come on, guys, it’s about the long game here: GOP leaders blamed Democrats and insisted their whip counts were accurate, even as Rep. Steve King (R-Iowa), who helped whip support for the bill, said he was surprised at the 62 GOP defections. “I was surprised by about half of them,” he said. “I thought they would have taken more of a 10,000-foot view.” Yes, show a little maturity for once, Steve King said, to other people. Then the Republican leadership blames Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi for only bringing 24 Democratic “aye” votes to the table. Jesus. We’re not sure that Nancy Pelosi got 24 votes from the Republican Party on all major bills combined in the years 2009 and 2010. Also, there’s a reason that most Democrats didn’t vote for this farm bill, and that’s because they hate it, because it assaults the social safety net. But yeah, anyway, sure, this is Nancy Pelosi’s fault, boo, she’s evil and wears a lot of makeup, boo. There’s only one way to a bill becoming a law in this government setup, which we’re stuck with for a while: The House has to work within the framework of a Senate-drafted compromise, and lean on Democratic votes. This is the only way things work right now, and no special guest whip or hollering at the mean San Francisco lady will change that. And of course yesterday’s farm bill failure has implications on comprehensive immigration reform, which will most likely soon pass through the Senate. It’s hard to come to any other conclusion than Brian Beutler’s: But more broadly, it’s tough to look at the farm bill fiasco and imagine the House passing an immigration reform bill that Dems don’t carry. If that’s the case, then the key to the whole immigration reform effort really is John Boehner accepting the internal consequences of just putting something similar to the gang of eight bill on the floor and getting out of the way. You can watch the farm bill fail and reason that Boehner might think immigration reform isn’t worth it. Or you can watch the farm bill fail and reason that he might decide to dispense with all the member management theatrics and throw in with Democrats and GOP donors. But you can’t watch the farm bill fail and see the House GOP passing a Hastert-rule compliant immigration reform bill and going into conference with the Senate. We’d say Boehner will go with option 2, bringing immigration to the floor and leaning on Democrats. There’s no mysterious character quirk specific to Boehner that always leads him to this conclusion, as conservatives seem to believe. His decisions follow a fairly simple weighing of the pros and cons, and anyone in his position would make the same ones. That’s why he still has his job: because there’s no other way to do it, and those who would hope to become speaker can see that.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371851753631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371852022847-265</Id><Title>GOP’s 7 most jaw-dropping “scientific” theories</Title><Msg>GOP’s 7 most jaw-dropping “scientific” theories Masturbating fetuses are just the start By Evan McMurry It was Texas Representative Michael Burgess’ turn on the GOP’s Bullhorn of Crazy this week. “You watch a sonogram of a 15-week baby, and they have movements that are purposeful,” Burgess said during a congressional debate on the House Republican’s absolutely pointless bill outlawing abortions past 20 weeks. “They stroke their face. If they’re a male baby, they may have their hand between their legs. I mean, they feel pleasure, why is it so hard to think that they could feel pain?” Burgess’ prenatal masturbation musing is only the tip of the melting iceberg of Republican science denial. Here are seven battier things they believe, from trees causing global warming to fetuses in your Pepsi. 1. Abortion Leads To Cancer, Birth Defects, And Everything Else Burgess’ absurdity actually masked a very serious GOP belief. The “fetus pain” theory, which holds that fetuses begin to feel pain around 20 weeks, has been the primary logic behind a slew of recent abortion bills in state legislatures. As no reputable science backs the theory up, the GOP has been forced to find anything wearing a lab coat to make stuff up. Abortions are rare after 21 weeks, and usually occur when a woman develops serious complications with her pregnancy. But some Republicans go so far as to think the health exemption is a cover for the abortion industry. “There’s no such exception as life of the mother, and as far as health of the mother, same thing,” Joe Walsh said in 2012 on his way to losing his House seat. “With advances in science and technology, health of the mother has become a tool for abortions for any time under any reason.” (Republicans have no problem invoking science when it suits their needs.) Burgess is hardly alone in digging up scientific-sounding nonsense to back up his abortion views. Rick Santorum was the most recent peddler of the long-discounted theory that abortions lead to breast cancer, while out in Virginia, which has a nasty strain of abortion-based delusion, a state delegate advanced the notion that abortions lead to handicaps. “The number of children who are born subsequent to a first abortion with handicaps have increased dramatically,” Bob Marshall said. “Why? Because when you abort the firstborn of any, nature takes its vengeance on the subsequent children.” 2. Everything They Say About Rape Burgess’ comment was notable for not featuring the word “rape,” the hook on which many right-wing legislators hang their crazy coats, to the point that Stephen Colbert has instituted a “Days Without a Rape Reference” segment. This started with Todd Akin’s famous “legitimate rape” comment last fall, though the theory is still being repeated. Akin’s comment was so bad that even lawmakers who didn’t entirely agree with it were caught in its net: Richard Mourdock blew a gimme election in Indiana when he tripped himself trying to get away from Akin’s remark. Like Burgess, Akin’s comment was important not because it was an aberration, but because it reflected a real belief on the right, one that’s beginning to infect policy. Arguing against a rape exemption in his anti-abortion bill last week, Trent Franks stated that the incidences of pregnancy from rape are “very low.” Some see daylight between Franks’ iteration of the rape/pregnancy connection and Akin’s, but it’s minor. And while Akin’s view was rooted in medieval medicine, Franks’ theory traces its lineage right back to Nazi experiments. Whether dealing with centuries-old pseudo-science or its bleak modern mutations, the GOP’s rape/pregnancy link is bad science at its most savage. 3. Climate Change Doesn’t Exist, and If It Does It’s Caused By Trees Not all Republican science denial involves evil lady parts. Their resistance to the very idea of climate change is so staunch that it bred an entire theory of GOP-specific ignorance. The least crazy of the party acknowledge climate change is occurring but refuse to link it to human behavior, instead seeing the rise in temperatures as part of a natural cycle. After all, it’s not like Hurricane Sandy was the first extreme weather event in history. “I would point out that if you’re a believer in the Bible, one would have to say the Great Flood is an example of climate change and that certainly wasn’t because mankind had overdeveloped hydrocarbon energy,” Texas congressman Joe Barton said during a House hearing on the Keystone Pipeline. (You will remember Barton from his apology to BP over the company’s oil spill.) There’s one problem with this: refusing to link global warming to human behavior greatly reduces your options for curtailing it. See Dana Rohrabacher, a far-right California congressman, who found a natural solution to a natural problem. “Is there some thought being given to subsidizing the clearing of rainforests in order for some countries to eliminate that production of greenhouse gases?” Rohrabacher asked during a House hearing on U.N. climate policies. This is for the Republicans who actually admit climate change exists. Many don’t, and they made sure we knew about it last year when they rejected an amendment that would have simply acknowledged the occurrence of global warming. The amendment didn’t garner a single GOP vote. It gets worse. In 2012, North Carolina’s legislature went the full-ostrich route. Not only did they refuse to admit that global warming was happening, they actually banned scientists from researching it, passing a bill prohibiting the measurement of sea-levels so nobody could notice they were rising. (The ocean rudely rose anyway.) 4. Breast Implants, On The Other Hand, are a Fine Use Of Science Okay, most of their science denial involves lady parts, but not all of it’s negative! Tom Coburn proves the GOP would be scientists’ best friend if those nerds would stick to expanding things men want to look at. “I thought I would just share with you what science says today about silicone breast implants,” Coburn said during a hearing on class action lawsuits, a nagging problem for plastic surgeons. “If you have them, you’re healthier than if you don’t. That is what the ultimate science shows. . . . In fact, there’s no science that shows that silicone breast implants are detrimental and, in fact, they make you healthier.” (They don’t.) 5. No Dead Fetuses In Your Soft Drinks But the GOP’s science permissiveness begins and ends with breasts; anything that might help with, say, medical research is off the table. Stem cells in particular give Republicans the bends. Where most see the frontier of medical research, Republican candidates for senate see islands of Dr. Moreaus. “American scientific companies are cross-breeding humans and animals and coming up with mice with fully functioning human brains,” Christine O’Donnell told Bill O’Reilly in 2007. Talking Points Memo guessed O’Donnell was referencing an experiment in which doctors grew human brain cells within mice—“not the same as an actual functioning human brain, but a demonstration that human brain cells can be made from stem cells”—but they didn’t sound too confident speculating on her inspiration. At least O’Donnell wasn’t actually a lawmaker. Last year, Oklahoma State Senator Ralph Shortley got wound up over a zany Internet theory claiming stem cells were being used in the production of artificial sweeteners, and proposed a bill prohibiting companies in Oklahoma from using aborted fetuses to make food. 6. Evolution Is (Still) Out To Get Jesus “I’m not a scientist, man,” Marco Rubio recently told GQ. “I can tell you what recorded history says. I can tell you what the Bible says, but I think that’s a dispute amongst theologians. Whether the Earth was created in seven days, or seven actual eras, I’m not sure we’ll ever be able to answer that.” But Rubio’s fellow Republicans think they have answered it, as evidenced by the fact that they want schools to teach that humans and dinosaurs used to read GQ together. Republican-controlled state legislatures have been busy trying to pass bills forcing public schools from elementary to college to teach that the world was created 6,000-9,000 years ago. Their cover for this is the necessity of “teaching both sides” of the debate—though only one has scientific backing—but Georgia Representative Paul Broun recently showed the right’s hand. “All that stuff I was taught about evolution and embryology and Big Bang theory, all that is lies straight from the pit of hell,” he said during his (unopposed) run for reelection last year. “And it’s lies to try to keep me and all the folks who are taught that from understanding that they need a savior.” 7. It’s Only Science If Republicans Agree With It In perhaps the most unintentionally revealing law ever written by a Republican on science, Texas Representative Lamar Smith recently proposed that all scientific knowledge get his okay first. Called the “High Quality Research Act,” Smith’s bill would require any research receiving federal funds to go through Smith’s Congressional Committee on Science, Space and Technology, all in the name of “accountability.” Accountability in this case means agreeing with Smith, a climate change denier who has no problem going after projects he, or his donors, disapprove of. If the GOP had its way, this is how all science would work: no rising sea levels to worry about, and all the breast implants Congress can afford.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852022847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371852455275-266</Id><Topic><Title>House of Representatives: Still terrible at everything</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371851753631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:55:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jIM Newell woretwe that no wonder...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371852455275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371852654674-267</Id><Topic><Title>It's Hard to Justify having a Federal government.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1371829668779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 11:47:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The war proved it wouldn't happen that way -- and a reprise would prove it again. But before the south was defeated, its decentralized govt. still took control of almost every facet of every member state's affairs. Don't pee on my shoes and tell me it's raining, putz.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371852654674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371852761478-268</Id><Title>Paula Deen Fired By The Food Network for Racism</Title><Msg>Paula Deen reportedly wanted black people to play slaves at a wedding When asked if she uses the "N-Word," the celebrity chef replied: "Yes, of course." By Prachi Gupta If a damning new report from the National Enquirer is to be believed, celebrity chef Paula Deen is a racist. Lisa Jackson, a former general manager of Deen’s Savannah, Ga., last year filed a $1.2 million lawsuit against Deen, claiming that the celebrity chef used the N-word and that Deen’s husband was physically abusive. The case is now underway, and the National Enquirer reports that during three hours of questioning last month, when Jackson’s attorney asked Deen if she’d ever used the N-word, Deen said, “Yes, of course.” “It’s just what they are — they’re jokes … most jokes are about Jewish people, rednecks, black folk … I can’t determine what offends another person,” said Deen. When asked what she thought about casting black men as slaves at a wedding, Deen said that a restaurant she went to with her husband inspired the idea: “The whole entire waiter staff was middle-aged black men, and they had on beautiful white jackets with a black bow tie.” “I mean, it was really impressive. That restaurant represented a certain era in America … after the Civil War, during the Civil War, before the Civil War … It was not only black men, it was black women … I would say they were slaves.” Maybe Paula Deen is an Accidental Racist.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852761478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371852973997-269</Id><Title>Why the GOP Can’t Learn</Title><Msg>It’s as if they didn’t learn a thing from the 2012 elections. Republicans are on the same suicide mission as before—trying to block immigration reform (if they can’t scuttle it in the Senate, they’re ready to in the House), roll back the clock on abortion rights (they’re pushing federal and state legislation to ban abortions in the first 22 weeks), and stop gay marriage wherever possible. As almost everyone knows by now, this puts them the wrong side of history. America is becoming more ethnically diverse, women are gaining economic and political power, and young people are more socially libertarian than ever before. Why can’t Republicans learn? It’s no answer to say their “base” — ever older, whiter, more rural and male — won’t budge. The Democratic Party of the 1990s simply ignored its old base and became New Democrats, spearheading a North American Free Trade Act (to the chagrin of organized labor), performance standards in classrooms (resisted by teachers’ unions) and welfare reform and crime control (upsetting traditional liberals). Advertisement The real answer is the Republican base is far more entrenched, institutionally, than was the old Democratic base. And its power is concentrated in certain states — most of the old Confederacy plus Arizona, Alaska, Indiana, and Wisconsin — which together exert more of a choke-hold on the Republican national party machinery than the old Democrats, spread widely but thinly over many states, exerted on the Democratic Party. These Republican states are more homogenous and conspicuously less like the rest of America than the urbanized regions of the country that are growing more rapidly. Senators and representatives from these states naturally reflect the dominant views of their constituents — on immigration, abortion, and gay marriage, as well as guns, marijuana, race, and dozens of other salient issues. But these views are increasingly out of step with where most of the nation is heading. This state-centered, relatively homogenous GOP structure effectively prevents the Party from changing its stripes. Despite all the post-election rhetoric about the necessity for change emanating from GOP leaders who aspire to the national stage, the national stage isn’t really what the GOP is most interested in or attuned to. It’s directed inward rather than outward, to its state constituents rather than to the nation. This structure also blocks any would-be “New Republicans” such as Chris Christie from gaining the kind of power inside the party that a New Democrat like Bill Clinton received in 1992. The only way they’d be able to attract a following inside the Party would be to commit themselves to policies they’d have to abandon immediately upon getting nominated, as Mitt Romney did with disastrous results. It’s true that by 1992 Democrats were far more desperate to win the presidency — having been in the wilderness for twelve years — than today’s GOP appears to be. Nonetheless it’s doubtful the GOP will be willing to eschew its old base even if it loses the presidency again in 2016, because without its collection of relatively homogenous states, there just isn’t much of a GOP. The greater likelihood is a steady eclipse of the Republican Party at the national level, even as it becomes more entrenched in particular states. Those states can be expected to become regressive islands of backwardness within a nation growing steadily more progressive. The GOP’s national role will be primarily negative — seeking to block, delay, and filibuster measures that will eventually become the law of the land in any event, while simultaneously preaching “states’ rights” and praying for conservative majorities on the Supreme Court.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852973997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371853446221-270</Id><Topic><Title>Paula Deen Fired By The Food Network for Racism</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852761478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:12:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she wasn; t called tro be the sixth woman on the george zimmermann is guoilty trial n wait, imoartila and non biased</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371853446221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:24:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371853567438-271</Id><Topic><Title>Why the GOP Can’t Learn</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852973997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the funniest DFC here!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371853567438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371853622943-272</Id><Topic><Title>Paula Deen Fired By The Food Network for Racism</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852761478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:12:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>please please please if not first then second degree george zimmermann plead out same as on the tape that is all the news fit to print</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371853622943</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371853630262-273</Id><Topic><Title>GOP’s 7 most jaw-dropping “scientific” theories</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852022847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you get that from your DFC manifesto?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371853630262</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371854046696-274</Id><Title>Paul McCartney is pop's coolest dad</Title><Msg>Paul McCartney is music's coolest dad, according to June's iHeartRadio survey. The ex-Beatle has five children, four with late wife Linda (he adopted her daughter Heather and the couple had Mary, Stella and James) and daughter Beatrice with second wife Heather Mills. With an eye on Father's Day, the online survey queried more than 1,000 of iHeartRadio's Active Listener population. Respondents named Blake Shelton the music star without kids who's likely to make the best father. The survey breakdown:And in keeping with June's theme, the poll focused on the wedding season and asked which pop luminary would be the last to tie the knot. Taylor Swift was the top choice.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371854046696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371854097954-275</Id><Topic><Title>GOP’s 7 most jaw-dropping “scientific” theories</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852022847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Did you get that from your DFC manifesto?" Didn't know there was one.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371854097954</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371854212419-276</Id><Topic><Title>Paul McCartney is pop's coolest dad</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371854046696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a putz.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371854212419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371854248330-277</Id><Title>Kanasa State Fair</Title><Msg>definitely she took me half the way there...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371854248330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:37:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371854362455-278</Id><Topic><Title>GOP’s 7 most jaw-dropping “scientific” theories</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852022847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DFC's all have one.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371854362455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371854413813-279</Id><Topic><Title>Kanasa State Fair</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371854248330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kind and lucky u2</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371854413813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371854722372-280</Id><Topic><Title>GOP’s 7 most jaw-dropping “scientific” theories</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852022847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"DFC's all have one." Sure. But it's nice to hear you finally admit that you don't have one.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371854722372</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371854822741-281</Id><Topic><Title>Paul McCartney is pop's coolest dad</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371854046696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course you are jokong, Stella would have nothiong to do with my sorst ]although brianne.... pure of and deed for full line age 28 IF</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371854822741</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371855144875-282</Id><Topic><Title>GOP’s 7 most jaw-dropping “scientific” theories</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852022847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing funnier than a card carrying DFC posting under numerous aliases like a little pansy.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371855144875</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371855782279-283</Id><Title>QE1 started 11/25/2008 ,&amp; still going , so how did that work for BA ,Airbus, Disney,TSLA which is better</Title><Msg>using the yahoo finance chart , enter the date that Quantitive easing started , 11-25-2008 and end today 6-21-2013 . Background, QE1 started on 11/25/2008 to stimulate the USA economy, QE2 continued starting 11/3/2014 now we have QE3 started 9/13/2012 to present.The FED chairmans spoke and suggested in the future the tapering would begin so for the past 3 days the stock market sold off. temporary , most likely . The Result of QA on interest rate's, dropped as low at 5% or lower , bonds do not make much money, only stocks.. So , in the 4 years and 7 months , how did that work for stimulating BA compared to Disney, compared to TSLA compared to Airbus (eadsy) you can enter each stock and the chart will compare to Boeing BA . Here is the answer; Airbus is better than Boeing by almost 200%, Disney ( a DJ stock ) is better than Boeing by 100%,tesla (TSLA) is better than Boeing by 450% and the nasdaq average is about equal with Boeing . Conclusion , you could have protected yourself from the riskof a single stock like Boeing by going with the nasdaq average etf and made the same gains . If you owned a single stock , , then you should have been in Airbus(EADSY) and you should move to Airbus now, they were better than Boeing at the Paris Airshow this week, so nothing to indicate any change in the status, , dividends are not significant 1.09% for Boeing and 1.03% for Airbus, or better yet go with a solid company in the DJ like , Disney (DIS) which bettered Boeing by 100% with a dividend of 1.2%, so once more at 100% increase over Boeing stock price the dividend is not significant. and tesla(TSLA) is up 450% better than Boeing so unless Boeing were to pay a 448% dividend that is not significant ha ha . 1</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371855782279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371855831805-284</Id><Topic><Title>QE1 started 11/25/2008 ,&amp; still going , so how did that work for BA ,Airbus, Disney,TSLA which is better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371855782279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2014 should be 2010,</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371855831805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371856055864-285</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus CEO on the 777x and impressions about the 350 Airbus betters Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371835401376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the new Airbus Americas CEO is a American hero he will bring good paying jobs to the USA and maybe get the 767 tanker deal from Boeing, we will see.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371856055864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371856495303-286</Id><Topic><Title>Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of Another is Involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1371844044469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I more than pay my own way, and I am not Sparty. You are too stupid to get either of those points.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1371856495303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371856523804-287</Id><Topic><Title>"Which Airline Stock Can Make You Really Rich"anaylist compares BA to Airbus conclusion Airbus is the best stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371834806126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 13:13:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry Boeing barkers, this is a direct quote from a aerospace analyst</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371856523804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:15:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371856564729-288</Id><Topic><Title>Another 787 diverted</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371771459195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any solution as yet ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371856564729</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371856664008-289</Id><Topic><Title>Second United Dreamliner diverted with oil-related problem</Title><Username>buffetmunger</Username><Timestamp>1371777915699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:25:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>has one or the other 787 problem been fixed ?2 in 3 days not good for a 4 year late to fix it right 787 plane</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371856664008</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371856849833-290</Id><Topic><Title>CEO of boeing compares to the USA Airbus Chairman Airbus CEO brings American jobs here which is better ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371776794989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 21:06:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Allan McArtor has the most impressive resume of any aerospace CEO or division chief</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371856849833</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371857390979-291</Id><Topic><Title>QE1 started 11/25/2008 ,&amp; still going , so how did that work for BA ,Airbus, Disney,TSLA which is better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371855782279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you held any stock prior to the FED speed your not a stock market trader and you just lost money . Better to get out prior to any Fed speedk wait until the news settles down then come back in at a better start price never listen to a Boeing sales associate the 6 users here that bark all day long about why Boeing is good for you to spend your money on as a investment that is not the fact. better stocks than Boeing even another company from Europe, , like Airbus is better since the QE started in the USA , in 4 years at 7 months since QE1 began to today , Airbus actually was better than Boeing by almost 200% , conclusion, so much for QE helping Boeing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371857390979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:29:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371858244935-292</Id><Topic><Title>Paul McCartney is pop's coolest dad</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371854046696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's nice to be recognized for a prestigious title such as this one.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371858244935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371859266231-293</Id><Topic><Title>Why the GOP Can’t Learn</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852973997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The GOP’s national role will be primarily negative" The new GOP is completely negative.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1371859266231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371859556819-294</Id><Title>99% of BA mangemnt say they d0n't have a problem with Chewbaca</Title><Msg>the other half of the one percent [in are missing somebodily parts sert wookie sound here]</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371859556819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371859709228-295</Id><Title>beep....</Title><Msg>3/4 ways back from Mars</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371859709228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371860484651-296</Id><Topic><Title>beep....</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371859709228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bunch of RWNJ sissies as John Wayne used\ to say, nee Marion my feet ar bigger than his boots and jona craw fords pout together honey bunches of oats and the lad please please please the crowbar from Marylyn Monroe s titt prints</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371860484651</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371861262901-297</Id><Topic><Title>beep....</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371859709228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holey bunches of oats I have a hardon the size of Wyoming and am drilling marylyn monroe please, please, please</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371861262901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371861491478-298</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Sets Future 787 Freighter to Fend Off Airbus Jets</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371731752935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:35:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"To the tune of Mr. Ed" A short is a short of course of course And no Short can tell the truth of course That is the way of a misleading short-----hey direct them to Talk To Mr. Ed</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371861491478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371861699411-299</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Sets Future 787 Freighter to Fend Off Airbus Jets</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371731752935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:35:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let Boeing build both---better chance of success. Can't put all your eggs in one basket. What if frieghter business became too saturated. Boeing needs a more diverse product line---even a regional jet and something maybe to challenge the A380 as it seems the world wants even a bigger A380 in a stretch version. IMHO</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371861699411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371861910202-300</Id><Title>When the Republican Party is Dead</Title><Msg>Which party will the neocon toadies hijack ?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371861910202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371865019145-301</Id><Title>They probably don;t like that kinda talk around here, mister...</Title><Msg>-doc holliday said</Msg><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1371865019145</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 21:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371865247584-302</Id><Topic><Title>99% of BA mangemnt say they d0n't have a problem with Chewbaca</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371859556819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chewbaca is a good wookie...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371865247584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 21:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371866673790-303</Id><Topic><Title>Paul McCartney is pop's coolest dad</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371854046696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roughly 100% of poor Pffloyddd's posts involve: 1. Somebody who earned the Distinguished Flying Cross 2. a putz Poor pfffloyddd.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1371866673790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 22:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371866748996-304</Id><Title>99.98 0.34</Title><Msg>e-don't really care what what the NSA say nor the f.b.i. letalone the cia Charts Interactive Basic Chart Basic Tech. Analysis News &amp; Info Headlines Press Releases Company Events Message Boards Market Pulse Company Profile Key Statistics SEC Filings Competitors Industry Components Analyst Coverage Analyst Opinion Analyst Estimates Research Reports Ownership Major Holders Insider Transactions Insider Roster Financials Income Statement Balance Sheet Cash Flow . . . .. The Boeing Company (BA) -NYSE riders on the storm</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371866748996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 22:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371867508953-305</Id><Title>If I move to Holland do I still get Directv</Title><Msg>de knees swallows</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371867508953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 22:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371868003689-306</Id><Topic><Title>Why the GOP Can’t Learn</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371852973997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 18:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its not they cain't learn, heck even Jesse Jackson offered to learn 'em, its they's juss don't wanna simply learn beyond 6th grade level. Of course you'd be right in say'in they is some that ain't got the pacity to learn, like Ryan and that Kentuckian, but generally I think Jesse could learn'em a thing ur two.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1371868003689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 22:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371868362152-307</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Christian Mystics have always opined that a belief in God is an "act of Faith" of course ...".! Apoparent;ly you have two many djust particles on ypour computer screen, a period, and and and an exclamation point@! The Sabbath Is Holy twice on Sunday ):0</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371868362152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 22:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371868929481-308</Id><Topic><Title>99% of BA mangemnt say they d0n't have a problem with Chewbaca</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371859556819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I Wanda what my good dental hygie39ists think40</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371868929481</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 22:42:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371869169775-309</Id><Topic><Title>99% of BA mangemnt say they d0n't have a problem with Chewbaca</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371859556819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...a good wookie insertwookie sdound heare 9intergalatic space cruiserts yesterday 9intergalactic rwnj sphincters</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371869169775</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 22:46:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371869753643-310</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus beat Boeing in the orders at the Paris Airshow and Boeing stock price</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371744155511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:02:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne my concern is the national debt, I am expecting a 10 to 15% sell off in the next month, once that is done I am back in and Airbus perhaps a better bet over the next 6 to 8 months. I wanted to stay in then money.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371869753643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 22:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371870143144-311</Id><Topic><Title>99% of BA mangemnt say they d0n't have a problem with Chewbaca</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371859556819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A very good wookie...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371870143144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 23:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371870606795-312</Id><Topic><Title>QE1 started 11/25/2008 ,&amp; still going , so how did that work for BA ,Airbus, Disney,TSLA which is better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371855782279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 19:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can't find it in the media but Obama has already conceded \Stimulus was a waste. The rest of us honestly know that Green Energy and Obama care is and will be a waste of taxpayers money. We all read 40% of the stimulus never left the Beltway.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371870606795</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 23:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371871383121-313</Id><Topic><Title>When the Republican Party is Dead</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371861910202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 20:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like they already have the Dems under control. That's why O's polices are just the same as Boy Bush.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1371871383121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 23:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371871855119-314</Id><Title>....and the wookie can fix the hyper-drive</Title><Msg>hence no wookie no harrison ford</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371871855119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 23:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371873200654-315</Id><Topic><Title>....and the wookie can fix the hyper-drive</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371871855119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 23:30:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the wookie named Chewbaca accepts the challenge in the name of good wookies everywhere in the mean time might wanna work on the 'script' a bit/story aqnd No to a Re-hash a John Williamsh shound shcore FREE WOOKIES</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1371873200654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 23:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>