<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-02"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357103350060-1</Id><Title>One can see</Title><Msg>Just by counting his posts, you can tell Sparty's in another manic phase.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357103350060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:09:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357103848931-2</Id><Title>The Fiscal Cliff Bill is Law</Title><Msg>It is a great relief that the fiscal cliff bill is at last law. Thank you Republicans and Democrats who voted for the bill and President Obama whose leadership brought this about. Those Republican members in the House who voted against the bill; that refused to compromise and were willing to put at risk our nation's economic stabliity are first class jerks.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357103848931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:17:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357104513056-3</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity lost half his TV audience after the election</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357078113848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:08:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, do a few bad weeks matter? Long term results are what matter and according to experts this was one of the best years for FOX news and they kicked everybody's tail. :-) 'FOX News is 2012's Most Watched Cable News Channel' Written By Sara Bibel December 13th, 2012 Fox News will finish 2012 as the year's most watched cable news channel. This is the 11th consecutive year that FNC has been the top cable news channel among Total Viewers and Adults 25-54. FNC was the number three basic cable channel in primetime, behind USA and ESPN in Total Viewers. In Total Day, FNC came in fourth. Overal, it was FNC's second highest rated delivery ever in Total Viewers for both Primetime and Total Day. FNC had 2012's top 11 cable news programs in Total Viewers, including The O'Reilly Factor, Hannity, Special Report With Brett Baier and On the Record with Greta Van Susteren. The channel also had the top 7 programs among Adults 25-54.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357104513056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:28:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357104922352-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Fiscal Cliff Bill is Law</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357103848931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget the 16 Dem jerks that voted against the bill.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357104922352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357105459828-5</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity lost half his TV audience after the election</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357078113848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:08:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still has higher ratings than Rachel Madcow, p.s. what ever happened to Keith Oberdork, Air Head America?</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1357105459828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:44:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357121321502-6</Id><Topic><Title>On Thursday, Feinstein will introduce her dream bill to disarm the American people</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1356971461736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 11:31:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you some sort of smarta§§ analgonqueen wannabe?</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1357121321502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 05:08:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357123532990-7</Id><Topic><Title>One can see</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357103350060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:09:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you convincing yourself that you are in a lucid dream or are you just projecting again?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357123532990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 05:45:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357126199539-8</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity lost half his TV audience after the election</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357078113848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:08:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= Fox News will finish 2012 as the year's most watched cable news channel = Sadly, this says more about the stupidity of the average American than it says about the journalistic quality of Faux Noise.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357126199539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 06:29:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357127327108-9</Id><Topic><Title>Two Quotes that should convince the ones on the Gun confiscation Fence</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357093399487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:23:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you noticed that the Kent Raven doesn't know the difference between a semi auto and an assault rifle? Why is he so concerned with your posts?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357127327108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 06:48:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357128696873-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Fiscal Cliff Bill is Law</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357103848931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got their tax increases, $4T spending package and no spending cuts. We can not keep going down this path. I am selling everything today.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1357128696873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 07:11:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357129980592-11</Id><Topic><Title>The Fiscal Cliff Bill is Law</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357103848931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This scene will be played out over and over as the can will be kicked down the road further and further ... the balloon gets bigger and bigger meaning the eventual PAIN gets bigger and bigger......when it goes....its gonnna go HUGE !</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357129980592</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 07:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357130846729-12</Id><Topic><Title>One can see</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357103350060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:09:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Martin Luther King once said: "Our lives begin to end the minute we become silent about things that matter." (PS: lest you claim this is only a stock message board, I have given an impassioned letter to every member of congress on the second amendment and its importance to this countries traditions and to the very notion of freedom itself). You either believe in the oath you took, or you're a hypocrite and stand for nothing.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357130846729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 07:47:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357132481332-13</Id><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Msg>I know how much you multi ID baggers wanted to protect the poor downtrodden millionaires from the ravages of a 4% tax increase on their multi million dollar incomes. It was unfortunate those repub puppets in congress caved. Pathetic, Eh!</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357132922446-14</Id><Topic><Title>New BA Investors Must See</Title><Username>mccormickbrady409</Username><Timestamp>1356981479787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 14:17:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you</Msg><Username>jackwhite565</Username><Timestamp>1357132922446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:22:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357134407655-15</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where would the money go dipstick? And are you so math deficit you think someone that earns $250 a year is a millionaire?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357134407655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:46:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357135899987-16</Id><Title>wow the cliff divers will take a beating today</Title><Msg>big day for me, oh well</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1357135899987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:11:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357136638226-17</Id><Title>The Folly of Sticking it to the Rich</Title><Msg>It’s obvious the rich guys like myself are the country’s most prolific wealth producers. Raising their taxes is on the same unintelligent level as raising the minimum wage. All that is accomplished when the minimum wage is raised is less opportunity for low skill people to enter the job market. If minimum wages helped poor people, why not raise it to $50 an hour. Tell Haiti they could eliminate their poverty by raising their minimum wage. Insane I know, but that’s how victims of socialized government education have bee taught to think. Now, back to the rich. Rich guys can only consume so much. Sure, they may live in fancier houses, drive expensive cars and wear nice clothes but those things are peanuts in financial terms and they all create jobs. The vast bulk of rich people’s money is employed in creating more wealth – it’s what we do best. This activity translates into more jobs, higher wages and a higher standard of living for everyone. Yet, the majority of voters have become so jealous and envious of these high achievers they want them punished for their success. Money taken from the most prolific wealth producers in the country and given to politicians to spend is insanity on steroids. Look at how the politicians are managing the national tax revenues as opposed to how the private sector manages its revenues. We should take lessons from Singapore and Taiwan. They reign at the top of the index for economic freedom, have very few rules and regulations, a high standard of living, no minimum wage and unemployment below 2%. They are not jealous of high achievers, they are inspired by them.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357136638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357136935157-18</Id><Title>BA and PSID working together</Title><Msg>BA is not just about airplanes.</Msg><Username>trader_casino</Username><Timestamp>1357136935157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:28:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357136948398-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Folly of Sticking it to the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357136638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Old axiom: You can not legislate the poor into prosperity, by legislating the wealthy out of prosperity. Can't work, but a libtard has been led to believe it can work.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357136948398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:29:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357136963264-20</Id><Title>Shorts going to get pounded</Title><Msg>Better cover at the open its only going to get worse for the shorts.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357136963264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:29:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357137052999-21</Id><Topic><Title>wow the cliff divers will take a beating today</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1357135899987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Three more cliffs we are headed off of because of the massive debt our liberal regime' has caused. Three more in the next several months.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357137052999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:30:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357137333528-22</Id><Topic><Title>wow the cliff divers will take a beating today</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1357135899987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:11:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rally Time$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1357137333528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:35:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357137380221-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Folly of Sticking it to the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357136638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What may likely happen at many companies the Bd of Directors will vote a larger compensation package for senior executives to compensate for the tax hike on the rich. The parties to pay for these salary increases are the consumers, employees, stockholders and the companies themselves.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357137380221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:36:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357137549576-24</Id><Title>Obama Claiming Victory -- As Well He Should!</Title><Msg>And well he should. He won – and he won big. He got his precious tax increase on the rich … the rich that he claims have not been paying “their fair share” for all these years. Here’s part of the statement from the White House issued last night: At this make or break moment for the middle class, the President achieved a bipartisan solution that keeps income taxes low for the middle class and grows the economy. For the first time in 20 years, Congress will have acted on a bipartisan basis to vote for significant new revenue. This means millionaires and billionaires will pay their fair share to reduce the deficit through a combination of permanent tax rate increases and reduced tax benefits. And this agreement ensures that we can continue to make investments in education, clean energy, and manufacturing that create jobs and strengthen the middle class. Oh yeah … there we go with that “millionaires and billionaires” class warfare line again. This is all so wonderful! Now the teacher’s unions will get more money, more money can be squandered on Obama’s green energy dreams like Fisker Automotive and Solyndra, and the middle class can be strengthened by raising taxes on the very people they depend on for private sector jobs. We have a spending problem, not a tax revenue problem. The Media Party has the Democrat’s back on this, and you won’t see the details of our spending problem given anywhere near the coverage that Obama gets on his “the rich need to pay their fair share” language. Details? Fine … here they are. Take a look at what has happened to government spending since Obama became our Dear Ruler: Last night’s vote will add $4 trillion to our national debt over the next four years … that’s $4 trillion JUST from last night’s vote. Obama was on track to take America to $22 trillion in national debt by the end of his term. Thanks to this deal, he’s on track to take us to about $26 trillion. That would be more than $15 trillion in new debt under President Obama (the national debt was just over $10 trillion when Obama took office). (Source) Obama has already increased our national debt by over $6 trillion, which is more than from George Washington through the first five months of George W. Bush’s presidency. At this rate, by the end of Obama’s second term, he would have spent more than all of his predecessors combined. (Source) Spending will increase 55 percent over the next decade, if President Barack Obama's budget plan goes into effect. The finding comes from the Republican-side of the Senate Budget Committee, which notes that Obama's "Proposal Would Spend $880 Billion Over Already Projected Increases." (Source) Federal welfare spending has grown by 32 percent over the past four years. Welfare spending as measured by obligations stood at $563 billion in fiscal year 2008, but reached $746 billion in fiscal year 2011, a jump of 32 percent. (Source) Federal spending on more than 80 low-income assistance programs reached $746 billion in 2011, and state spending on those programs brought the total to $1.03 trillion, according to figures from the Congressional Research Service and the Senate Budget Committee. That makes welfare the single biggest chunk of federal spending — topping Social Security and basic defense spending. (Source) Spending on food stamps cost $75 billion in 2011, or 10 percent of welfare spending. It’s nearly twice the size it was in 2008 and accounts for a staggering 20 percent of the total welfare spending increase over those four years. (Source) Now you will notice that all of this money is being spent on programs to make more and more Americans more and more dependent on government. I’m so sick of having to go over this rant time and time again, but I told you starting in 1994 that when (not if) the Democrats got control in Washington again they were going to immediately start working to make as many people dependent on government as possible. They did, and it worked. The moochers, parasites and leaches now make up the majority of American voters. Over 60% of American households have at least one member of that household receiving a check from the government every month. Just how do you think they are going to vote? For more money, of course! NBN</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357137549576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:39:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357137957065-25</Id><Title>737 max order milestone</Title><Msg>CHICAGO (AP) -- Boeing Co. said on Wednesday that it has finalized an order for 60 of its planned 737 Max planes, pushing its total for the Max to more than 1,000. The deal, which Boeing said was finalized with leasing company Aviation Capital Group in late December, would be worth $6 billion at list prices.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357137957065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:45:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357137964770-26</Id><Title>And How About A Big Lie To Top All Of This Off!</Title><Msg>Here’s another paragraph from the White House statement last night on Obama’s huge victory: “In 2011, the President cut spending.” Can you believe that? The White House is actually claiming that in 2011 Obama cut spending. This, my friends, is a lie. An intentional and provable lie. Yet Obama get’s away with it … he gets away with it because a compliant and obedient ObamaMedia lets him get away with it. Obama was on “Meet the Press” Sunday. On that show he said to David Gregory: “Well, I have to tell you, David, if you look at my track record over the last two years, I cut spending by over a trillion dollars in 2011.” Now if David Gregory was not such an obsequious Obama #$%$-licker he might have come back with this: “But wait, Mr. President. Your own White House Office of Management and Budget reports that in fiscal year 2010 our federal government spent $3.46 trillion. Yet in 2011 we spent $3.6 trillion. How can you claim that you cut spending by a trillion dollars in 2011 when, in fact, your own White House reports that spending increased by $147 billion? What’s more, our deficit increased by more than a trillion dollars from 2010 to 2011. How does that happen if you cut spending by over a trillion dollars?” Were these figures not available to David Gregory? Did NBC not have the same access to information that a lowly back-bench talk show host has? Of course this information is available to Gregory and NBC news .. but it doesn’t fit their agenda; and their agenda is undying support for Barack Obama and anything he says or tries to do in Washington. Besides … if Gregory had asked that question of Obama it would have been the last time Obama granted him an interview. Access is more important than accuracy. NEAL</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357137964770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:46:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357138327180-27</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock market up triple digits! Geez I guess those millionaires decided against packing up and moving to Switzerland like the baggers said they would if their taxes went up. Looks like they can afford additional tax increases to help pay down that national debt the politicians in their employ are so concerned about.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357138327180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:52:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357138667566-28</Id><Topic><Title>737 max order milestone</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357137957065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:45:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fal, This Company is Buying more land and will be making US longs a lot of Money for retierment$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1357138667566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:57:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357138758174-29</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts going to get pounded</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357136963264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:29:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You bet they will get BURNED but let those roaches DIE$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1357138758174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:59:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357138782938-30</Id><Topic><Title>The Folly of Sticking it to the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357136638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point Phantom....sort of. The people who will always pay most of the taxes are the people who consume most of their earnings. The mediocre class consumes 95% of the wealth they earn. The top 1% consumes less than 5% of what they earn and other 95% is deployed to create more wealth (and jobs) or it is given to philanthropic causes. At any rate, all taxes are embedded in the wealth we consume. Since the mediocre class consumes most of the wealth consumed......guess what?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357138782938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:59:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357139479491-31</Id><Title>Republicans get clobbered Again !</Title><Msg>257 to 167 - Congress approved a plan to end Washington's long drama over the “fiscal cliff” late Tuesday after House Republicans surrendered to President Obama's demand to let taxes rise on the nation's richest households.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357139479491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:11:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357139635104-32</Id><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Msg>Sweet !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357139635104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:13:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357139899553-33</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>repubs getting their #$%$ handed to them !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357139899553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:18:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357140480399-34</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing No 1 beats AIrbus</Title><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1356966255985</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 10:04:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it for the haters $$$$$</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1357140480399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:28:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357143044360-35</Id><Topic><Title>The Fiscal Cliff Bill is Law</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357103848931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Democrat party has never placed premium on jack-booted lockstep obedience to the party. Only the Repugnantcons do that. All that Democrats are required to do is vote their conscience (and to actually HAVE a conscience ;-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357143044360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:10:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357143486993-36</Id><Topic><Title>The Fiscal Cliff Bill is Law</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357103848931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get real. A libdem is a libdem for life. Facts just get in the way of a #$%$ lib. Unionism isn't jack-booted lockstep obedience? HAHA About as Nazi as it gets.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357143486993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:18:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357143797939-37</Id><Title>Fiscal cliff deal will add $4 trillion to US deficit, says CBO</Title><Msg>For you Obama supporters, this will mean Obama will go down in history as possibly the most dishonest and most irresponsible president in history. "The Congressional Budget Office has revealed that the Senate-passed legislation to avert the "fiscal cliff" will add nearly $4 trillion to federal deficits over a decade, largely because it extends low tax rates for nearly every American. The congressional scorekeeper's analysis could fuel further debate about the legislation, which could come to a vote in the US House of Representatives on Tuesday . CBO said the fiscal year 2013 deficit would be about $330bn higher than if Congress fails to act and lets $600bn in higher taxes and spending cuts take effect. "</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357143797939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:23:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357143994864-38</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal cliff deal will add $4 trillion to US deficit, says CBO</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357143797939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Reagan proved deficits don't matter", #$%$ Cheney. I presume you wanted all the Bush tax cuts to expire then, correct?</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1357143994864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:26:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357144001483-39</Id><Title>Statement by Secretary Shinseki on the Passing of Senator Daniel Inouye</Title><Msg>Statement by Secretary Shinseki on the Passing of Senator Daniel Inouye December 18, 2012 Printable Version Need Viewer Software? "Senator Daniel K. Inouye stood among the 'greatest' of our 'Greatest Generation.' Recipient of the Medal of Honor, our Nation's highest award for valor; distinguished service as a long-serving member of the U.S. Senate; and role model to generations of Americans of Asian-Pacific Islander heritage, especially those growing up in his beloved Hawai'i, Senator Inouye made public service a noble and honorable calling. Dan Inouye's courage on the battlefield and in Congress, his passion for making a difference in the lives of average Americans, and his intense modesty spoke volumes about a remarkable American, who embodied the bedrock values and quiet virtues of our Nation. On behalf of America's 22 million Veterans, I salute the memory of a brave man, a great patriot, a devoted public servant, an unwavering benefactor to Servicemembers and Veterans of every generation, and my friend and mentor. I extend my deepest personal condolences to the entire Inouye family."</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357144001483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:26:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357144033646-40</Id><Title>People Too Dumb to Spend Own Money happy.......</Title><Msg>......that politicians will be spending more of it for them.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357144033646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:27:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357144194663-41</Id><Title>Senate-Passed Deal Means Higher Tax on 77% of Households</Title><Msg>The budget deal passed by the U.S. Senate today would raise taxes on 77.1 percent of U.S. households, mostly because of the expiration of a payroll tax cut, according to preliminary estimates from the nonpartisan Tax Policy Center in Washington. More than 80 percent of households with incomes between $50,000 and $200,000 would pay higher taxes. Among the households facing higher taxes, the average increase would be $1,635, the policy center said. A 2 percent payroll tax cut, enacted during the economic slowdown, is being allowed to expire as of yesterday.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357144194663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:29:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357144348338-42</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal cliff deal will add $4 trillion to US deficit, says CBO</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357143797939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you against the repube party wanting to extend the Bush tax-cuts permanently!!!?! What a dolt the average repube is... To listen to the moaning of some Republicans in the House of Representatives, you could be forgiven for thinking that the Republicans are losing the fiscal battle in Washington. Actually, they're winning. To see this, you just need to step back and look at the tax deal and the country's fiscal trends from a broader perspective. Yesterday, the government voted to extend almost all of the Bush Tax Cuts permanently. Not temporarily, as a stimulus measure. Permanently. Ever since the Bush Tax Cuts were first enacted in 2001, one goal of the Republican party has been to "make the Bush Tax Cuts permanent." For most of the last decade, this goal has seemed like an extremist view: Making the Bush Tax Cuts permanent would drastically reduce the federal government's revenue. It would also increase inequality and balloon the national debt and deficit--so how could we possibly justify doing that? And yet now, suddenly, almost all of the Bush Tax Cuts are permanent. And the definition of "rich" in America has been significantly increased: The only Americans subject to a minor increase in income taxes will be households making more than $450,000 a year. The Republicans also got another good deal for America's investor and owner class, making the Bush dividend tax cut permanent. This saves a lot of money in tax bills for America's wealthier investors. And the tax deal even socked it to the working class. How? By not extending the payroll tax cut. This payroll tax cut added an extra $2,000 a year in the pockets of everyone who works for their money. The payroll tax hits everyone who earns wages, including the richest Americans, but it's a highly "regressive" tax: It takes a much bigger percentage of the income of those who earn less than $110,000 a year than it does from the richest Americans. So the Republicans have won a battle there, too. It's true that the Republicans have not yet won much ground on the other front that the party claims to be fighting on--namely spending cuts on programs that primarily benefit low-income and middle-income Americans (food stamps, Medicare, Medicaid, Social Security, unemployment insurance, and so forth). But the key word there is "yet." Yesterday's deal focused only on taxes. The next government fight will be about spending cuts and the debt ceiling, and the Republicans are already mobilizing to hold the country hostage and demand entitlement cuts in exchange for not forcing the U.S. to default. And it seems reasonable to assume that, no matter how crazy and irresponsible this behavior is, the Republicans will probably extort some spending-cut concessions in exchange for agreeing to allow the United States Of America to honor its commitments. And then there's the big picture, which is also important. The Republicans are winning there, too. To listen to Republicans tell it, you would think that the country's tax burden is suddenly astronomically high, that U.S. citizens are being forced to fork over more money to the government than ever before. The truth is the opposite. As Ben White of Politico observes, thanks to the Reagan revolution and the Bush Tax Cuts (almost all of which have now been permanently extended), the federal government is collecting a much lower percent of GDP as tax revenue than it has for most of the past 50 years. Specifically, as the chart below shows, the federal government is now collecting 17% of GDP as tax revenue, versus an average of about 19% in the past few decades. One of the broad strategies of those who want to reduce the size of the federal government is a plan called "Starve the beast." The goal of that plan is to continue to reduce federal government revenue to the point where the government simply has no choice but to cut spending, because deficits have just gotten too large and unsustainable to ignore. Our deficits are not yet (quite) too large and unsustainable to ignore, but if we continue on the current path for a few more years, they'll get there. So what the chart above is telling you is that the Republicans are doing an excellent job of bringing about Phase 1 of "Starving the beast." So ignore what you're hearing out of Washington. The Republicans may not have gotten everything they wanted out of the Fiscal Cliff deal, but they got almost everything. And when it comes to the broader fiscal battle, the Republicans are winning: The federal government's tax revenues are at the lowest level as a percent of GDP in the past several decades. The Republicans, in other words, are well on their way to starving the beast.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1357144348338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:32:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357144765407-43</Id><Topic><Title>Senate-Passed Deal Means Higher Tax on 77% of Households</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357144194663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:29:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really didn't think that the middle class wouldn't pay more???There is'nt a politician out there that doesn't want higher taxes...</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357144765407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:39:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357144971540-44</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal cliff deal will add $4 trillion to US deficit, says CBO</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357143797939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You trust Henry Blodget? Good for you, you binary brained #$%$ ;-) "In 2002, then New York State Attorney General Eliot Spitzer, published Merrill Lynch e-mails in which Blodget gave assessments about stocks which allegedly conflicted with what was publicly published.[4] In 2003, he was charged with civil securities fraud by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission.[5] He agreed to a permanent ban from the securities industry and paid a $2 million fine plus a $2 million disgorgement.[6]"</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357144971540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:42:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357145138085-45</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal cliff deal will add $4 trillion to US deficit, says CBO</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357143797939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I want can only be fantasy and unimportant in the face of facts and I'm sure you're not really interested in what I want.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357145138085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:45:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357145318093-46</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal cliff deal will add $4 trillion to US deficit, says CBO</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357143797939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deficits don't matter to a math deficit libdem maybe. What matters is the percentage of debt to the size of the economy, and Obama has ruined the economy. Reagan grew the economy just as GW Bush grew the economy with tax cuts, not tax increases. Tax cuts mean more tax revenue generated. Sounds foreign to an ignorant libdem, but that is a fact...proven everytime it has been tried in US history.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357145318093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357145597337-47</Id><Topic><Title>Two Quotes that should convince the ones on the Gun confiscation Fence</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357093399487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:23:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The second amendment will never be more or less important than the first or third amendments, or any other amendments. When I read a lot of what people say about the 2nd amendment, it sounds like it's the only part of our country's documentation that they've heard of or care about, like a person who knows one quote from the Bible and applies it to everything, and even then often misquotes it.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357145597337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:53:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357146164367-48</Id><Topic><Title>A350 XWB going to cause the 777 headaches</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357079909525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:38:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This A350 could be a game changer. Engineering has really advanced on it. Those long narrow wings that curve up at the tips. Its going to be high speed and efficient. Extra cabin space. Yes there will be demand for it.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357146164367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:02:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357146252972-49</Id><Topic><Title>The Folly of Sticking it to the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357136638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said mir.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357146252972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:04:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357146658194-50</Id><Topic><Title>Two Quotes that should convince the ones on the Gun confiscation Fence</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357093399487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:23:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The raven is an imbecilic hypocrite who is a Marxist at heart. He trust politicians more than he does free people.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357146658194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:10:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357146974010-51</Id><Topic><Title>People Too Dumb to Spend Own Money happy.......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357144033646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:27:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you read posts from people filled with glee that rich people got shafted, you know you're reading the post of an utterly ignorant and economic illiterate victim of socialized government education. .</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357146974010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:16:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357147102358-52</Id><Title>Obama's Psychotic Obsession With Taxing The Rich</Title><Msg>Let’s start with a few Obama moments that really open a window into this man’s feelings about wealth and taxes. I’ve covered much of it before, but I can’t assume you were listening or reading Nealz Nuze on those days … so let#$%$ some of the high points again. First … remember Joe the Plumber? Joe encountered Obama as he walked down his street during a campaign photo op in 2008. Joe asked Obama about his plans to raise taxes. What Obama did NOT say to Joe is just as important as what he DID say. He told Joe that taxes needed to be raised to spread the wealth around. Not because the government needed the money. Not because we needed to stop borrowing. Not to get some money to pay down our debt. No. The taxes needed to be raised so that wealth could be spread around. In starker terms, wealth needed to be seized from those who earned it and given to those who did not in order to make things fair. So even while campaigning for president in 2008 Obama was promoting wealth seizure and redistribution. Not taxation to fund the necessary and proper functions of government; but taxation for the sole purpose of taking money from one person and giving it to another. Then … the infamous Charlie Gibson moment. It was April 16, 2008. The occasion was a debate between Hillary Clinton and Obama. Charlie Gibson was the moderator. The issue being discussed was Obama’s insistence on raising capital gains taxes. Here’s how the exchange went: GIBSON: All right. You have, however, said you would favor an increase in the capital gains tax. As a matter of fact, you said on CNBC, and I quote, "I certainly would not go above what existed under Bill Clinton," which was 28 percent. It's now 15 percent. That's almost a doubling, if you went to 28 percent. But actually, Bill Clinton, in 1997, signed legislation that dropped the capital gains tax to 20 percent. OBAMA: Right. GIBSON: And George Bush has taken it down to 15 percent. OBAMA: Right. GIBSON: And in each instance, when the rate dropped, revenues from the tax increased; the government took in more money. And in the 1980s, when the tax was increased to 28 percent, the revenues went down. So why raise it at all, especially given the fact that 100 million people in this country own stock and would be affected? OBAMA: Well, Charlie, what I've said is that I would look at raising the capital gains tax for purposes of fairness. There goes that “fair” word again. Obama pays ardent attention to focus groups – especially focus groups made up of low-information Americans who would be convinced to vote for and support him. He knows they love the word “fair.” Why everyone wants to be fair, right? Fair is, after all, fair! So if it would be fair to raise capital gains taxes, then raising these taxes would only be the fair thing to do and fairness demands that it be done right away! If not, it won’t be fair! Recognizing that many people who heard (or read) this are exclusively government educated, let me explain what happened here. Our so-called leader, Barack Obama, told Charlie Gibson that the reason he wanted to raise capital gains taxes was NOT to get needed revenue for the federal government – revenue to spend on new programs or to pay down our debt – but because Obama believed that it just wasn’t fair that the people who earned this money on their investments got to keep so much of it. It was more important that the money be taken away from those who earned it than it was that the government actually received increased tax revenues.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357147102358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:18:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357147349194-53</Id><Topic><Title>737 max order milestone</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357137957065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:45:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw that. Thanks.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1357147349194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:22:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357147694415-54</Id><Topic><Title>The Folly of Sticking it to the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357136638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tripe. If you really were wealthy, you wouldn't refer to the working class as the mediocre class. The kinds of things you say are the platitudes that people with some money tell themselves in order to rationalize under paying others for goods and services. There is some truth in much of what you say, but it will never be heard because of the way you say it. Most of the wealthy do not create many jobs directly, but do so indirectly by lending money to others who do. Many of the wealthy generate more wealth by investing in this fashion, some of it with considerable risk. Paying a fair rate of taxes earned on that income is just as logical as a restaurant manager paying taxes on the income he earns. If the wealthy don't pay a fair rate of tax, their money doesn't circulate enough, and adds to economic stagnation.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357147694415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:28:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357147812202-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Psychotic Obsession With Taxing The Rich</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357147102358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:18:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a total diversion from the massive spending Obama has to do to support socialism. And it isn't hard for him to convince ignorant liberals that rich folks need to pay more taxes, and it is their fault for the huge debt. Ask an ignorant liberal who's to blame for the massive debt if you don't believe me.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357147812202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:30:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357148094283-56</Id><Topic><Title>The Folly of Sticking it to the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357136638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very well said.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357148094283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:34:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357148626010-57</Id><Topic><Title>The Fiscal Cliff Bill is Law</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357103848931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 00:17:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's ironic that a right-fringer would tell anyone to "get real." In the business of governance (I'm not talking about workers' rights, now, but governing) unions are lobby groups, just like the NRA. I was talking about policy-makers, law-makers. If you could bother to read a thread rather than just jerk your knee in reaction to something I post, that would be painfully obvious (if only stupidity would be painful!) Unions don't do that. They can try to sway lawmakers, but they don't make law.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357148626010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:43:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357148844253-58</Id><Topic><Title>The Folly of Sticking it to the Rich</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357136638226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 09:23:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>albucucu.....you're obviously a victim of socialized government education who has earned his economic ignorance at the feet of Marxist teachers. Money is always in circulation unless buried in the ground somewhere. The real issue is, in who's hands will it do the most good, create the most jobs and create the most wealth. In the hands of businesses, entrepreneurs or even consumers making their choices in a free market or in the hands of politicians who will spend it on getting re-elected and paying off those who helped them get elected in the last election? The question all Americans should be asking whenever politicians wan a dollar of our money is, is the private sector capable of providing the same thing for the same or less money. If the answer is yes, then let the people who want that thing, pay for it themselves.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357148844253</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:47:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357148921767-59</Id><Title>Report: 2,670 People Shot and 532 Murdered in Chicago in 2012</Title><Msg>as reported by 'Crime in Chicago' web site. Dianne Goldman Berman Feinstein rich white skinned liberal Dem living in a secure neighborhood wants to ban guns like they have in Chicago where other rich white skinned liberals have banned guns and made it so that only bad guys have guns.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357148921767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:48:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357149303261-60</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Baggers were lighting candles and praying for the repubs to vote to raise middle class taxes thereby causing markets to crash and the economy to return to the Bush depression with unemployment over 750,000/month. Actually most of the repubs heard them and did vote to screw the middle class. The pitiful handful of repubs that voted with the Democrats to only raise taxes on millionaires and billionaires are now facing a soviet style purge from the crazies.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357149303261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:55:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357149657883-61</Id><Title>Obama voted in 2005, 2006, and 2007 to reinstate pay­ as­ you ­go (PAYGO) federal budget rules.</Title><Msg>What happened to THAT Obama? Was he kidnapped and replaced by a crazy look alike?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357149657883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:00:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357150229754-62</Id><Topic><Title>Report: 2,670 People Shot and 532 Murdered in Chicago in 2012</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357148921767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:48:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Statistics are clear. gun control does not prevent crime and proably exacerbates it and makes hte criminals (who well get guns illegally anyway) think twice. In the 17 days since an elementary school in Connecticut was attacked, an all-out war on the 2nd Amendment and our right to bear arms has culminated in President Obama backing Dianne Feinstein’s assault weapons ban to be introduced this January. Two-and-a-half weeks have gone by and we have heard it all, from hypocrite celebrities who murder people with guns in movies telling us to give up our rights in reality, to Joe Biden heading a new gun violence task force while he bragged about his guns on the 2008 campaign trail. The claim being pushed from seemingly every angle is that if we all give up our guns and our rights, it will somehow make us safer. One of CNN host Piers Morgan’s favorite arguments is that the United Kingdom has less gun crime than the United States because of its strict gun control policies. While it may be true there are less gun crimes in the U.K. than in the U.S. based on the statistics they report, this position fails to paint the full picture. A 2009 Telegraph article dubbed the U.K. The “violent crime capital of Europe,” noting the country had one of the highest reported violence rates in the world, a per capita rate worse than South Africa, Australia, and yes, even America. READ MORE</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357150229754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:10:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357150334717-63</Id><Title>I apologize to Yahoo moderators who took down my earlier post</Title><Msg>pointing out that rich white Dems with armed protection want to ban guns so that no one can protect themselves and so that only criminals have guns like in Chicago.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357150334717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:12:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357150632965-64</Id><Topic><Title>Report: 2,670 People Shot and 532 Murdered in Chicago in 2012</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357148921767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 12:48:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let Piers "punching bag" Morgan live in the Englewood district in Chicago and if he's still alive after a year let's see how he feels about only criminals having guns in Chicago. ;-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357150632965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:17:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357151698413-65</Id><Topic><Title>I apologize to Yahoo moderators who took down my earlier post</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357150334717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:12:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo must have a 'tardOmeter' where stupid posts like that peg the pointer to the max thus automatically deleting the post..</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1357151698413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:34:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357151836841-66</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'you think someone that earns $250 a year is a millionaire?' I doubt that anyone that makes $250/year is paying ANY taxes. Wow, where do you guys come from?</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1357151836841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:37:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357152360280-67</Id><Topic><Title>I apologize to Yahoo moderators who took down my earlier post</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357150334717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:12:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe but I think it was the fact that I mentioned a hypocritical liberal white yenta by name that got my post snuffed.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357152360280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:46:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357152868284-68</Id><Topic><Title>John Boehner Told Harry Reid 'Go F--- Yourself' Outside the Oval Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1357152455048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:47:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a compliment to valueless Harry. What a poor excuse for a human being. Libs champion the #$%$, but no Pro-Americans</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357152868284</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:54:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357152940153-69</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought this was going to be about all your ex lovers and how you failed to satisfy them. ROTF</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357152940153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:55:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357152958872-70</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you really think that is what drove up the market? You are one dimbulb.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357152958872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:55:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357153981564-71</Id><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Msg>God to Student: "I am not allowed in Schools"</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357154112727-72</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans get clobbered Again !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357139479491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:11:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>poor things... can't win for losing !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357154112727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:15:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357154143553-73</Id><Topic><Title>I Love it when i wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357139635104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 10:13:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i love it !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357154143553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:15:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357154171487-74</Id><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Msg>I doubt I could have ever made this much money in 2 days if Obama hadn't out-maneuvered the Repubs and saddled future generations with more debt from Obamanomics. Thanks. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357154536429-75</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>purging is Awesome !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357154536429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:22:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357154868423-76</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It could have also been about Hillary C and Diane F. They are both bags and two baggers. LOL</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154868423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:27:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357154917833-77</Id><Title>The End of GOP Allegiance to Tax Pledge !</Title><Msg>A White House source told Fox News’s Ed Henry overnight that “Obama broke [the Republicans'] tax pledge,” making the Joe Biden-negotiated deal “[one] of the most consequential policy achievements of the last couple decades.” A “senior official” told BuzzFeed Monday that the deal was “a sea change,” which shows that Republicans will bend to demands for higher taxes in the future. “It will inevitably make it easier to get [Republicans] on board whenever we ask for new revenues,” the official told BuzzFeed, “because they’ve already crossed that threshold.” Similarly, a “West Wing advisor” told Politico that getting Republicans to walkaway from their tax commitment was a “big win.”</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357154917833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:28:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357155372586-78</Id><Topic><Title>John Boehner Told Harry Reid 'Go F--- Yourself' Outside the Oval Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1357152455048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:47:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boehner cried after making that remark... !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357155372586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:36:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357155645231-79</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris Christy is a leftist bloke hiding in his Omar the tent maker suit. The fat slob needs thrown out of the GOP Party. Bankrupt the country with socialist spending, and you just might not have any money to save victims of such a natural tradegy.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357155645231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:40:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357155761622-80</Id><Topic><Title>The End of GOP Allegiance to Tax Pledge !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357154917833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:28:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden? So he's the responsible one now,....the adult in the White House? Where's the Kenyan? What happened to his leadership? Didn't he finally get some for XMAS?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357155761622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:42:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156131462-81</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares about the East Coast? They keep building and rebuilding in high risk areas and Bloomberg ignores all the engineering reports that warned him to take measures to prevent disaster and protect the infrastructure. Let the Eastern states pay for their own stupidity, bad management and chronic mistakes.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357156131462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:48:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156191978-82</Id><Topic><Title>John Boehner Told Harry Reid 'Go F--- Yourself' Outside the Oval Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1357152455048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:47:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cried too. Tears of laughter! lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357156191978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156320421-83</Id><Topic><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Who or what can keep an all-powerful, all-knowing God out of schools? What is your religion, anyway?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357156320421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:52:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156418479-84</Id><Topic><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I may even put an Obama bumper sticker on my new BMW since he bought it for me with other people's money. ROTF</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357156418479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:53:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156423422-85</Id><Topic><Title>John Boehner Told Harry Reid 'Go F--- Yourself' Outside the Oval Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1357152455048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:47:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right-fringe IQ and dedication to serving the country is on full display.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357156423422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156556494-86</Id><Topic><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All money was other people's at one time or another. That's what makes an economy.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357156556494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:55:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156632080-87</Id><Topic><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another of Spartacus many problems is that hje is dyslexic. So whe he saw the sign "No dog allowed in school," he lept to the predictabvle conclusion.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357156632080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:57:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357156848710-88</Id><Title>A look at Obamas Chilling Executive Orders</Title><Msg>EXECUTIVE ORDER 10990 allows the government to take over all modes of transportation and control of highways and seaports. This is the guy preaching the disarmament of America.... Obama has signed the following Executive Orders EXECUTIVE ORDER 10995 allows the government to seize and control the communication media EXECUTIVE ORDER 10997 allows the government to take over all electrical power, gas, petroleum, fuels and minerals.EXECUTIVE ORDER 10998 allows the government to take over all food resources and farms. EXECUTIVE ORDER 11000 allows the government to mobilize civilians into work brigades under government supervision. EXECUTIVE ORDER 11001 allows the government to take over all health, education and welfare functions EXECUTIVE ORDER 11002 designates the registration of all persons. Postmaster General to operate a national registration EXECUTIVE ORDER 11003 allows the government to take over all airports and aircraft, including commercial aircraft. EXECUTIVE ORDER 11004 allows the Housing and Finance Authority to relocate communities, build new housing with public funds, designate areas to be abandoned, and establish new locations for populations. EXECUTIVE ORDER 11005 allows the government to take over railroads, inland waterways and public storage facilities.EXECUTIVE ORDER 11049 assigns emergency preparedness function to federal departments and agencies, consolidating 21 operative Executive Orders issued over a fifteen year period. EXECUTIVE ORDER 11051 specifies the responsibility of the Office of Emergency Planning and gives authorization to put all Executive Orders into effect in times of increased international tensions and economic or financial crisis. EXECUTIVE ORDER 11310 grants authority to the Department of Justice to enforce the plans set out in Executive Orders, to institute industrial support, EXECUTIVE ORDER 11921 allows the Federal Emergency Preparednes to establish judicial and legislative liaison, to control all aliens, to operate penal and correctional institutions, and to advise and assist the Presidents Agency to develop plans to establish control over the mechanisms of production and distribution, of energy sources, wages, salaries, credit and the flow of money in U.S. financial institution in any undefined national emergency. It also provides that when a state of emergency is declared by the President, Congress cannot review the action for six months. Watch Obama's actions, not his words!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357156848710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:00:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357156954899-89</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're not compassionate at all. You're just too stupid to realize how you enable/allow others to continue to be killed by putting themselves at risk by building and living near oceans. Are you stupid enough to build and live in a flood plain? It must be so, since you support the idea.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357156954899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:02:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157062525-90</Id><Topic><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty just wants to pave the way for the day a predominantly Islamic school board requires his kids to read the Quran and pray 5 times a day on a rug. He saw that on a T-shirt and now he thinks its a verse in 2 Revelation.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357157062525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:04:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157186095-91</Id><Topic><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357157186095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:06:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157407470-92</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boehner is taking the heat for the more stubborn and stingy of his party. Congress will probably cast some aid that way in the next session. A lot of that area probably won't be rebuilt, but it still has to be cleaned up and people relocated.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357157407470</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:10:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157447296-93</Id><Topic><Title>A look at Obamas Chilling Executive Orders</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357156848710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:00:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The guy is a socialist fascist...that's what they do.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357157447296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157591450-94</Id><Topic><Title>John Boehner Told Harry Reid 'Go F--- Yourself' Outside the Oval Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1357152455048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:47:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boehner forgot to add ' and the horse you rode in on " Canvas Back Reid had at least one to many blows to his head as a boxer.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357157591450</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:13:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157724954-95</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bullshat! Disasters worse than Sandy have occurred numerous times in the past and population continues to grow in these disaster prone areas. These idiots are like moths to a flame and then they want others to pay for their stupidity and faux compassion. You watch they will still provide federal insurance where private insurance won't cover people.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357157724954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:15:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357157992432-96</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By all means prop up the Midwest RED States who continually rebuild in flood planes, tornado alleys, and have built a major metropolitan area lower than the surrounding water. Good thing we never assist those people, except for every time their is a disaster. That "infesto" is taking up residence in your excuse for a brain.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1357157992432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:19:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357158724653-97</Id><Topic><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm getting money from people not yet bor though, how great is that? lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357158724653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:32:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357158729644-98</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without the east coasts tax dollars you would have to get a job.The last major storm we had was in 1991.When you don't know what your talking about please shut up. For every dollar in taxes we pay we only get back 50 cents.Without the east coast this country would shrivel up and die.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357158729644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:32:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357158897582-99</Id><Title>The NRA Wants a Police State</Title><Msg>If one follows the “logic” of the National Rifle Association’s Wayne LaPierre, the United States should become an armed camp with armored-up police carrying high-powered weapons stationed at virtually every location where children might congregate and where a crazy person might show up with a semi-automatic assault rifle. After all, why stop at protecting schools? A mentally unstable individual could just as easily walk into a shopping mall at Christmas and murder kids waiting to talk to Santa Claus or enter a theater showing a Disney film and open fire on the tiny movie-goers or stroll onto a field where children are playing soccer and empty a 100-round magazine. If we are to really protect the children as LaPierre suggests, we should have armor-encased SWAT officers at literally every event where there are kids. It clearly wouldn’t do to just have some donut-eating cops with simple sidearms. All they would do is provide initial target practice for a gunman with his Bushmaster AR-15..... ... But LaPierre’s prescription for addressing the need to protect America’s children is to further militarize American society. A country with SWAT teams deployed preemptively at every public place where a deranged gunman might murder children is a nation with all the trappings of a police state.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357158897582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357159015766-100</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christie has too much sense to be in the Republican Party. You guys are nuts - he's the only potential Presidential candidate you have that's worth anything so go ahead - kick him out.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1357159015766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:36:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357159031235-101</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No different with tornado alley and those living in flood plains which I have already mentioned and you ignored. Again let the states pay for their own disasters and they will plan better for disasters. Your an idiot most likely because you never payed for your own mistakes. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357159031235</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:37:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357159073957-102</Id><Topic><Title>John Boehner Told Harry Reid 'Go F--- Yourself' Outside the Oval Office</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1357152455048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 13:47:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's still a U.S. Senator, Don. Someone must not be too bothered by your professional appraisal :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357159073957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357159080813-103</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take it this idiot "joedokes45" is one and the same as "harrydokes44." Both are insufferable dopes.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1357159080813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:38:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357159283808-104</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was the population in 1991 #$%$ What is it now? What did the East coast do to prevent future damage from a storm like Sandy since 1991? We need the East Cosat idiocy like we need more herpes.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357159283808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:41:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357160168383-105</Id><Topic><Title>A look at Obamas Chilling Executive Orders</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357156848710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:00:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An opinion is "The Dik is a hypocrite of immense proportions"...this is an opinion shared by most on this board but still PROBABLY an opinion strongly supported by the evidence. A Fact is where you dive off a 100 story building...you are going to die. There is enough evidence that Obama is an Authoritarian Fascist to move this as close to the realm of fact as an opinion can be.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357160168383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:56:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357160288469-106</Id><Topic><Title>The NRA Wants a Police State</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357158897582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:34:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a babbling idiot. Hey did you ever respond to the post with the stats that an Armed society in almost all cases reduces violent crime ? IE: It keeps the criminals polite</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357160288469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:58:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357160691469-107</Id><Topic><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God is EVERYWHERE my obtuse friend...but HOW young minds PERCEIVE this great and all powerful being or the LACK of perception is the moral of the story...and how that LACK of percention can lead an unschooled mind into Acts of Mass Murder....though you and the DIK are in full frantic revisionist mongoose mode to make me seem other then I am. Jesus loves me this I know....for the Bible tells me so.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357160691469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:04:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357161527016-108</Id><Title>Rachel Maddow's Surge Is Fox News' Worst Ratings Nightmare -- LOL</Title><Msg>After prophesying a landslide win for Mitt Romney, Fox News has seen its ratings decline a lot more than usual since the election — and Sean Hannity's viewers in particular keep disappearing, while Rachel Maddow's continue to tune in over at rival MSNBC. The last batch of Nielsen data available before year's end shows Hannity's viewership getting chopped in half after November 6, according to the New York Daily News's Don Kaplan. Politico's Dylan Byers argues this decline simply brings Hannity back to pre-election norms. Or perhaps these vanishing viewers are just disgruntled voters who can't stomach the news cycle anymore. Kaplan, however, attributes this decline to Hannity's implied predictions: ... viewers who basked in his preelection anti-Obama rhetoric tuned him out when they were stunned to wake up on Nov. 7 and discover that the President had won a second term — a scenario that Hannity had all but promised could never happen. MSNBC's Rachel Maddow and Ed Schultz — who both, of course, did not predict a Romney victory — have retained most of their viewership in the weeks following election night, and CNN's Anderson Cooper has lost almost none. With ratings holding strong after Obama's reelection and Maddow appearing on The Colbert Report, it appears like MSNBC is making good on president Phil Griffin's plan to bolster the channel's brand awareness. But these trends may began long before Hannity and other Fox News commentators led viewers to believe Romney was a shoe-in. Media blog News Corpse notes that throughout 2012, Fox News experienced by far the slowest year-over-year growth amongst the three major cable news channels. And even though MSNBC has captured many more eyeballs within the lucrative 25-54 demographic, Fox News still retains primetime dominance in the world of 24-hour TV news. What's left for CNN next year, well, that's up to new boss Jeff Zucker to decide. (I SMILE! :)</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357161527016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:18:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357162080424-109</Id><Topic><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm getting money from people not yet bor [sic] though, how great is that? lol" I think it's cool too. The secret is, that _those_ people will also get money from those not born yet. It's the rare Ponzi scheme that works.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1357162080424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:28:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357162963762-110</Id><Topic><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND he RAISED TAXES on the MIDDLE CLASS! Remember lyin Obama saying he didn't want to raise taxes on the middle class. Well bendover Middle Class you just got reamed! 41 times more tax hikes than spending cuts!</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357162963762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:42:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357163169556-111</Id><Topic><Title>The NRA Wants a Police State</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357158897582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:34:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spaz.... everything you wished for is coming true... !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357163169556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:46:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357163423885-112</Id><Topic><Title>My Condolences to the Two Baggers</Title><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357132481332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 08:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you bagger number 1 or bagger number2?</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357163423885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:50:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357163551566-113</Id><Topic><Title>Rachel Maddow's Surge Is Fox News' Worst Ratings Nightmare -- LOL</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357161527016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:18:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The right wing propaganda apparatus is coming apart. Who will provide misinformation to the baggers now?</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1357163551566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:52:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357164063069-114</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your an idiot" Thanks. You must be a conservative.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1357164063069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:01:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357164232399-115</Id><Topic><Title>Rachel Maddow's Surge Is Fox News' Worst Ratings Nightmare -- LOL</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357161527016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:18:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rush? A handful of them will never learn.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1357164232399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:03:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357164847517-116</Id><Topic><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh...you used to sing my praises Dik...dont bother denying it...back when I was Bringing up George Bushs transgressions...some of the exact things that the Kenyan is guilty of...remember those days ? Sure ya do ole buddy</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357164847517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:14:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357165031990-117</Id><Topic><Title>Two Quotes that should convince the ones on the Gun confiscation Fence</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357093399487</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 21:23:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree....but when EVERY other amendment is being criminally violated en masse'...as we are living through right now...then the second amendment takes on more of its original meaning..that the founders envisioned...if you gt my drift.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357165031990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:17:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357165279893-118</Id><Topic><Title>Rachel Maddow's Surge Is Fox News' Worst Ratings Nightmare -- LOL</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357161527016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:18:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the market up drastically due to avoiding the cliff......where is Fox's Richard Morris when I need him.......back in 2008 even before Obama was sworn in but the market was tanking, old Mr Morris stated the decline was due to Obama. Tell old Doc - Mr Morris - why is the market in the green today? (By the way - Mr Morris knows even less about the markets than he does politics)</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357165279893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:21:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357165567788-119</Id><Topic><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's another Dark Force in the spirit world. It is the devil/liberals/progressives/Democrats/Marxists. Although in the end they get defeated, they sure mess up things until then.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357165567788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:26:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357165756820-120</Id><Topic><Title>The NRA Wants a Police State</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357158897582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:34:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We already have a police state, dipwad. Just ask Gibson guitars and people that used to sell raw milk.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357165756820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:29:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357166127383-121</Id><Title>Establishment Republicans should Just get out of the Way</Title><Msg>Since they don't have a pair and just roll over for the socialists (thieves), they need to get out of the way of the TEA Party and Libertarians. Someone needs to stand up for REAL AMERICANS. It ain't ever gonna be the Democrats.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357166127383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:35:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357166797928-122</Id><Title>Do Democrats Still Think an African American is only 3/5 of a person?</Title><Msg>....or that a live baby living in a womb is not a person at all?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357166797928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:46:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357166869798-123</Id><Topic><Title>Establishment Republicans should Just get out of the Way</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357166127383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:35:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got it exactly right. $ 4 trillion in more govt spending, and libs call that a success. Taxes raised 41-1 over spending cuts, and there were no real spending cuts. The middle Class will pay dearly for this one, and we will still be deep in debt. For a person making $50K $1,000 in taxes goes just to pay the interest on the Obama created debt. For the $100K earner, $2K for just servicing Obama's debt. Now it will get worse.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357166869798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:47:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357166993914-124</Id><Topic><Title>The NRA Wants a Police State</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357158897582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 15:34:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stickman..You have the IQ of a stump that the stick grows on.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357166993914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:49:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357167643373-125</Id><Topic><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cuts to come with a scalpel not a tree ax - like you wish especially on the old &amp; sick while sparing big fat defense industries</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357167643373</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:00:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357168019663-126</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats Still Think an African American is only 3/5 of a person?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357166797928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All but the ones who have been successful escaping the govt plantation libs wanted to put them on. They are no longer needed, and are attacked as Uncle Toms. The rest are considered stupid, and fed lies, false promises, and bused to the polls. Finding it hard to then get off the govt plantation, their poverty numbers increase, but continue to vote dumbocrat.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357168019663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:06:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357168024273-127</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats Still Think an African American is only 3/5 of a person?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357166797928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:46:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know hoozdik is stupid......but that begs the question.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168024273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:07:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357168485830-128</Id><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Msg>Does his agenda involve communism?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168485830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:14:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357168755594-129</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168485830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:14:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you really are a one trick pony</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1357168755594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:19:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357168835381-130</Id><Title>Why are Democrats so Fearful of Freedom?</Title><Msg>Is it because they know they would be losers in free society?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168835381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:20:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357169032027-131</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Democrats so Fearful of Freedom?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168835381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:20:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>define freedom</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1357169032027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357169403906-132</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168485830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:14:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just love the entertainment of people who can't answer the question vainly trying to deflect it.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357169403906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:30:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357169791885-133</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Democrats so Fearful of Freedom?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168835381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:20:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>merriam-webster's Definition of FREEDOM 1 : the quality or state of being free: as a : the absence of necessity, coercion, or constraint in choice or action b : liberation from slavery or restraint or from the power of another : independence c : the quality or state of being exempt or released usually from something onerous I would say freedom is synonymous with responsibility. One can only be free if he is responsible and one can only be responsible if he is free.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357169791885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:36:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357169801159-134</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They were always promoting freedom from government and "Power to the people"." That was the 60's liberal of Abbey Hoffman and John Lennon and Allen Ginsberg. The new millineum "liberal" (so called) ...is a control freak, big government authoritarian who believes in the dictatorship of the proletariat and the individual should be crushed. The folks running the planet spun it that way...and brainwashed dupes suck up violations of the constitution like its the TRENDY thing to do...like buying the latest Ipod.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357169801159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:36:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357170016361-135</Id><Topic><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik: "I've moved to the left. The truth is...." The Truth is...truth is NOT a Left-Right concept....thats why I know your full of dog doo doo.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357170016361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:40:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357170266425-136</Id><Topic><Title>I want to thank Obama, those under 40 and future generations for helping me get a brand new BMW</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357154171487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:16:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>might be able to get a 2nd car and this one you can slap your dog on the roof as you drive your family to the beach just like your hero did</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357170266425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:44:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357170522819-137</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your an idiot", it's "you're" in this case. "you never payed", it is "paid". When you attempt to call another an idiot, try not do do it in an idiotic fashion that highlights your own stupidity. Demand a refund from that private school, the alleged education was wasted on you.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1357170522819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:48:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357173362480-138</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not clear why Gov. Christie cannot establish priorities. The Congress and the President barely agreed upon the "cliff" legislation early yesterday. Boehner today promised Rep King to next take up the Sandy relief legislation - at the same time that Christie is going nuclear. Given that Sandy occurred two months ago, how is a few days of further delay going to significantly impact re-building homes? Christie has lost it. He needs to get his weight under control for his own health and the well-being of those around him and those that he serves. Prior to the summer of 2011 he was the "darling" of the political scene. But then he way, way blimped out over the next year. He claims it is due to asthma medicine. It is possible, asthma medications contain steroids. Cortical steroids (like Prednisone) cause very large and immediate gains in weight, as well as loss of emotional control. Still, he is the governor and he has to find a way to maintain control and stability.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1357173362480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 19:36:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357173742198-139</Id><Topic><Title>A350 XWB going to cause the 777 headaches</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357079909525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:38:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bigger threat to Boeing is its own risk adversion. Of course, the Eurozone continues to fund civilian aircraft programs regardless of WTO rulings.</Msg><Username>mental_dwarf1</Username><Timestamp>1357173742198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 19:42:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357173950122-140</Id><Title>Is there any way.....</Title><Msg>.....a liberal can justify taking what one person earns and give it to a person who didn't earn it without calling it theft or plunder? "But how is this legal plunder to be identified? Quite simply. See if the law takes from some persons what belongs to them, and gives it to other persons to whom it does not belong. See if the law benefits one citizen at the expense of another by doing what the citizen himself cannot do without committing a crime."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357173950122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 19:45:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357175545468-141</Id><Topic><Title>Student to God: "Why do you allow such Violence in Schools"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357153981564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:13:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz: "you can't SEEM...." There is somthing rotten in the state of America....SEEMS, madam! Nay, it is; I know not "seems." It is nothing to me but a fouled and pestilent congregation of vapors.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357175545468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:12:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357176388766-142</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take it you live in a state that so far doesn't see too many natural disasters.......what an American YOU are</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357176388766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:26:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357176654848-143</Id><Topic><Title>Rachel Maddow's Surge Is Fox News' Worst Ratings Nightmare -- LOL</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357161527016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:18:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You reap what you sow</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357176654848</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:30:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357176764881-144</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168485830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:14:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our illegal immigrant president did try to get known Communist,Marxist Van Jones as head of the EPA but met STIFF resistance from a Congress that were on to Jones. Fortunately for America Van Jones withdrew his name. New EPA head,Lisa Jackson, does act like she's firmly set against Carbon Based Energy. I'm not sure if she's a Communist. But I do know that she's a Socialist hell bent against Fossil Fuels! There are many of her kind in Obama's cabinent as department heads.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1357176764881</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:32:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357176966667-145</Id><Topic><Title>The End of GOP Allegiance to Tax Pledge !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357154917833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:28:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deal passed Jan 1st - technically the rates all went up before the bill was passed so........they actually reduced some taxes???!!!!</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357176966667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:36:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357176969096-146</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357176969096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:36:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357178150102-147</Id><Topic><Title>Rachel Maddow's Surge Is Fox News' Worst Ratings Nightmare -- LOL</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357161527016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:18:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mittens - I didn't really want to be the president... same as when he was given a no-fail opportunity to head bain Capital These RWNJ's only like sweetheart deals and no-fail opportunities, and milk for as long as they last... see duhbya and chieneyburton administration/cabal and then there is duhby'as baby bro...after engineering the floriduh 2000 debacle was awarded a $37,000.00/hr job as a director for Tenet healthcare...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357178150102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 20:55:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357178904229-148</Id><Title>1/2/13 787 delivery</Title><Msg>The 6th air india 787 was delivered today from Charlston</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357178904229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:08:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357179242172-149</Id><Topic><Title>1/2/13 787 delivery</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357178904229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:08:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but did they buy the extended warranty ?</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357179242172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:14:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357179532753-150</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see mostly man made disasters like 500+ deaths in 2012</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357179532753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:18:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357179774683-151</Id><Topic><Title>Rachel Maddow's Surge Is Fox News' Worst Ratings Nightmare -- LOL</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357161527016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:18:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your corn beef is made of mad cow because you waste too much time drooling in front of the boob tube . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1357179774683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357179926790-152</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Face it, President Obama is more like Teddy Roosevelt than Teddy Kennedy and that is what upsets you, on top of the color of his skin, roots, and bio compared to yours</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357179926790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:25:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357180227080-153</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROFLMAO .... is that a joke ? Look ....... OJ won for a while too.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357180227080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:30:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357180256561-154</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>C'mon, Hooz. Don't assign fault to God regarding the bad behaviors of Boehner (foul mouth lack of decorum), Christie's (completely immature tirade), and Reid's (ridiculuous "dictatorship" accusation). Even Obama was not helpful (mostly grandstanding). Fortunately, Biden and McConnell found a way to make something happen that was a useful compromise.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1357180256561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:30:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357180631320-155</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is time for the sobbing Boehner to go, as he cannot keep the rupgnacon House in order!!! Long-time Senator and current VP Biden had to hatchet out the resolve to the fiscal-cliff, part I, over New years... and even Gov. (R) Christie has lambasted the obscenity-hurling Boehner and next in-line reugnaco nfor speaker of the house is is even more divisive and less effective</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357180631320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:37:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357180655099-156</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JFK, F Scott Fitzgerald, Einstein, Faulkner, Hemingway, Keats, Da Vinci and Ben Franklin were all bad spellers. What does spelling have to do with intelligence? Nothing, and only an idiot would think it does.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357180655099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:37:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357180736917-157</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody has ever fit the description "mealy mouthed weasel", better than Hairy Weed . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1357180736917</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:38:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357180971788-158</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Execpt (R) McConnell... god, where did the repugnacons ever find that spineless, money-grubbing bath-house scrubber</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357180971788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:42:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357181370072-159</Id><Title>President Obama to sworn into office for the fifth time 21 Jan 13</Title><Msg>but only because Chief-Justice Roberts failed to administer the oath properly... four years ago</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357181370072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:49:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357181552192-160</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I have said before, they are not liberals in the classic sense . They are little pinko henny pennies who want to be called liberals, so I do, as an act of generosity, and since they want to be named liberals, I spell it with a capital letter like this: Liberal . If you see Liberal used as a proper noun, the meaning is interchangeable with 'self righteous idiot' in all cases . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1357181552192</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:52:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357181595996-161</Id><Title>The statewide snow-pack levels are at 134% this year</Title><Msg>or about 402% of last year your government dollars at work</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357181595996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:53:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357181824158-162</Id><Topic><Title>The statewide snow-pack levels are at 134% this year</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357181595996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:53:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glow ball warming . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1357181824158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:57:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357181887249-163</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are the Bill Ayers type . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1357181887249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:58:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357182603147-164</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Ali "JFK, F Scott Fitzgerald, Einstein, Faulkner, Hemingway, Keats, Da Vinci and Ben Franklin were all bad spellers." If you think you compare to Einstein or Da Vinci, you are more insane than Sparty. As usual you missed the point, all your errors were in the process of calling another an "idiot". Look in the mirror, the idiot is you.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1357182603147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357182751781-165</Id><Topic><Title>The statewide snow-pack levels are at 134% this year</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357181595996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:53:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just wait until summer. There are different theories about handling raging wildifire in draught years. I bet your assumptions are based on the don't come/don't pass line unless you flip-flop like a mittens rawmoney fish on a hook $37,000.00/hr plus per diem and expenses and you could be 'no more'... just sayin', inflation ya know...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357182751781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:12:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357182914540-166</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Christie Ruthlessly Takes Down John Boehner Over Sandy Aid</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357155442398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 14:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who would that be ?</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357182914540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:15:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357183133283-167</Id><Topic><Title>Hilary plane crash in Iran</Title><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1356971775986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 11:36:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another cockamania story from some nut locked securely in the insane asylum</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357183133283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:18:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357183293693-168</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity lost half his TV audience after the election</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357078113848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:08:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remove the presidential election coverage and Fox is in deep trouble......2013 will bear that out</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357183293693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:21:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357183530442-169</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary now has a blood clot</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356921324875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 21:35:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still think she is fabricating all this to avoid being questioned about Benghazi...........you guys don't have the birther issue anymore so now you've moved to a plane crash in Iran, etc etc</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357183530442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:25:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357183651866-170</Id><Topic><Title>The statewide snow-pack levels are at 134% this year</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357181595996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 21:53:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many states have +100% snow pack Einstein??</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357183651866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:27:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357183863643-171</Id><Topic><Title>Rachel Maddow's Surge Is Fox News' Worst Ratings Nightmare -- LOL</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357161527016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 16:18:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When can I catch Richard Morris on Fox TV It was always funny to me to watch his lying #$%$ on TV and wondering how many actually believe his BS</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357183863643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:31:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357183980355-172</Id><Topic><Title>Hilary plane crash in Iran</Title><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1356971775986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 11:36:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This story holds about the same weight for being real as "cold fusion".</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357183980355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357183988717-173</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal cliff deal will add $4 trillion to US deficit, says CBO</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357143797939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First step.......more to come soon</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357183988717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:33:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357184113598-174</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still enjoying this "gem" from jumboot: "Re: Our Disaster-N-Chief 17-Mar-11 10:32 pm A man who looks so much like a chimp should not be Prez. It's as simple as that . Y.T. Jumbojetski "</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1357184113598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:35:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357184299580-175</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary now has a blood clot</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1356921324875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 21:35:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The birther issue will NEVER go away. (I hope.) My net worth is world class thanks to birthers--er--contributors. s/ Orly</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1357184299580</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:38:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357184575694-176</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal cliff deal will add $4 trillion to US deficit, says CBO</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357143797939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 11:23:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phase I - in which Doris gets her oats Phase II, III, and IV to follow no new limit on [defense] budget not a problem... spending cuts, even Rumsfeld said they have a billion dollars in chump change to be swept off the floor of the Pentagon... for a billioin dollars to reinforce his side of the bldg which the terrorists of 9/11 circled around and did not strike according to eyewitness testimony...</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357184575694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:42:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357184751477-177</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You a Harry Belafonte black ?</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357184751477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:45:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357184772958-178</Id><Topic><Title>Question about the meaning of "liberal"</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1356806463311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-29 13:41:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't pick on THAT jumbosca*ski. He's an imitator, after all.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1357184772958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:46:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357184899820-179</Id><Title>Nikkei 22510,395.18+72.20+0.70%</Title><Msg>bukkake!</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357184899820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 22:48:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357186453489-180</Id><Title>No human has stepped foot on the moon</Title><Msg>Neil Armstrong even told us so... "One small step for man, one giant leap for mankind" For want of a preposition,,,yet we robotically put our endeavors there more fastidiously than the others... while trying to dupe the world according to Nixon 78 rpm,,,well alright,,, buddy holly fell out of the sky onto an Iowan field along with the Big Bopper, and Richie Valens over a coin toss</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357186453489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:14:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357186636814-181</Id><Topic><Title>No human has stepped foot on the moon</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357186453489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, all right, so I'm being foolish Well, all right, let people know About the dreams and wishes you wish In the night when the lights are low Well, all right, well all right We'll live and love with all our might Well, all right, well all right Our lifetime love will be all right Well, all right, so I'm going steady It's all right when people say That those foolish kids can't be ready For the love that comes their way Well, all right, well, all right We'll live and love with all our might Well, all right, well, all right Our lifetime love will be all right Well, all right, well, all right We'll live and love with all our might Well, all right, well, all right Our lifetime love will be all right</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357186636814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357186696218-182</Id><Topic><Title>No human has stepped foot on the moon</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357186453489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be something -Paul McCartnery</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357186696218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:18:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357187582232-183</Id><Topic><Title>No human has stepped foot on the moon</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357186453489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After the 1973–74 season Ray was traded to Golden State for fellow center Nate Thurmond. In 1975 the Warriors, led by Rick Barry and coached by Al Attles, won the NBA championship. Ray led the team in rebounding and anchored the defense, finishing second in minutes played per game, after Barry. The Warriors defeated Ray's former team, the Chicago Bulls, in the Western Conference finals before sweeping the Washington Bullets in the NBA Finals. [1] despite the don't trade nate pleas</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357187582232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:33:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357187729175-184</Id><Topic><Title>Why Did Obama Appoint a Known Communist to His Administration?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168485830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:14:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once Obama's term runs out the Justice Department will have to do a thorough internal investigation of evey branch of government in order to wack the rest of those Obama Communists from their positions. It's a GD VIRUS we're talking about here! We don't want NO Saul Alinsky type hangons running around loose in Washington! America can still be saved but it's going to take a lot of hard work! And if you elect me President I'll make sure Washington comes out of this crisis smelling as fragrant as your wife's underwear!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1357187729175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:35:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357188776393-185</Id><Topic><Title>No human has stepped foot on the moon</Title><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1357186453489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ray was hardly ever called for the 'new' invention of his called 'hooking' using either the foream and/or upper-body strength to repostion an opposing player into a more unfoavourable position... while rebounding, etc. The new NBA has character... what-loop hole asks the (R) McConnell</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357188776393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 23:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>