<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360213490981-1</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs think the Hollywood libs they see in the movies are the real person? Far from it. Most live under the Big Tent with all the other kooks in our society.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360213490981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 00:04:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360213722118-2</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer People Than Ever Trust Fox News</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360205005931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:43:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PBS? lol! The network that was totatlly embarrassed by the way they fired Juan Williams?...the liberal that made the mistake of saying what he thought? Very communist like. No wonder you like PBS. And the head lib at the top of PBS got canned for making the communist like decision to fire Williams. But Williams made out fine....got a big contract with fair and balanced Fox News.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360213722118</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 00:08:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360215006533-3</Id><Topic><Title>The Biggest Problem is with 787 Is....Drum roll Please</Title><Username>forland1966</Username><Timestamp>1360212738989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 23:52:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe they said there are 2 batteries, and in case you are unaware, there are hydraulics all over the plane for the non-electrical systems</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360215006533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 00:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360217272235-4</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instead of shrinking the influence of the NRA, the gun grab vastly expanded NRA membership. More than 300,000 new members have been added to the NRA’s roster in just the last few months, and the association has become more steeled in its position than ever before. The NRA has shifted even more dramatically against gun restrictions than ever before, even reversing itself on the issue of “gun free school zones” after learning that such zones don’t work. Gun Owners of America has also seen its membership numbers soar.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360217272235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 01:07:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360218073120-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ridiculous BA is not down more</Title><Username>feru012</Username><Timestamp>1360212792466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 23:53:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Proof of manipulation</Msg><Username>utawk2me</Username><Timestamp>1360218073120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 01:21:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360218255858-6</Id><Title>SPEEA strike ??</Title><Msg>YES or NO ?</Msg><Username>junksexpert</Username><Timestamp>1360218255858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 01:24:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360220214034-7</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post. All true</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360220214034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 01:56:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360220411876-8</Id><Title>7 million losing Insurance under Obamacare</Title><Msg>President Obama’s health care law will push 7 million people out of their job-based insurance coverage — nearly twice the previous estimate, according to the latest estimates from the Congressional Budget Office released Tuesday. CBO said that this year’s tax cuts have changed the incentives for businesses and made it less attractive to pay for insurance, meaning fewer will decide to do so. Instead, they’ll choose to pay a penalty to the government, totaling $13 billion in higher fees over the next decade. But the non-partisan agency also expects fewer people to have to pay individual penalties to the IRS than it earlier projects, because of a better method for calculating incomes that found more people will be exempt.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360220411876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 02:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360224098180-9</Id><Title>The 787 Sullenberger- boat new flight safety standard for the 787 fire issue !</Title><Msg>A research of a few articles about lithium batteries combined to a conclusion as follows.1 ( from a engineer who designs airplane charging systems)"An unambiguous safety standard for the use of lithium battery or charging system systems on any airplane and the potential for a fire cause may not be found anytime soon. As a person that designs and works with lithium batteries and that designs charging and protection systems for them. I have the opinion, that with the current state of the art , lithium batteries have no place in manned aircraft For safety of flight , only. when a lithium battery is designed that can build a cell that fails to a safe condition, like other technologies-but not before., then it is safe, to use on any airplane and not before that design , is the lithium battery a safe application for electrical power.". The followwing is a group of statements about the 787, Boeing management, the problem of a fire on a 787. and general aerospace expert opinions. The engineering is not the most flawed aspect concerning the Boeing 787, this battery problem is is a symptom of the route cause for the 787 delay and excessive build cost. . It is the management of Boeing, the FAA and now the NTSB that apparently cannot be counted on to make wise risk/benefit decisions. Boeing management and their flunky’s first make up their minds , then seek underlings to support that decision. Anyone that objects or raises issues is pushed to the side while the sycophants grab the spotlight, at least until a patsy is needed to take the fall for unaware management decisions The new rules allow the shipment of lithium ion batteries weighing as much as 77 pounds, but only if they are aircraft batteries. Shipments of other lithium ion batteries greater than 11 pounds are still prohibited. The exemption makes no sense; it is a follow the money rule. The 787's two batteries weigh 63 pounds each. So if the standards need to be modified to allow the 787 to fly then instead of passenger safety, the money principal is used. Lithium-ion batteries can short circuit and ignite if they are improperly packaged damaged or has manufacturing defects. Fires involving rechargeable lithium-ion batteries can reach 1,100 degrees, close to the melting point of aluminum, or any other component that makes up a airplane, including aluminum. a key material in the construction of most airplanes the idea that smoke can be vented outside a burning battery box on a flying 787 ignores the actual cause of the ensuing crash . While the smoke can be vented a lithium fire of 1000 degrees in the vented battery section of the 787 is a crash condition at a rate of 100% . if the plane cannot land on a ground based landing strip, then on an emergency basis and over the ocean. , Since the landing strip is the ocean. You need the Sullenberger landing training at a 100% success rate, for all 787 pilots and a waiting group of rescue boats, for any out of control fire. The only realistic ocean landing would be a Chesley "Sully" Sullenberger, a former US Airways pilot famed for his precision flying that enabled passengers and crew to survive an emergency landing on the Hudson River in New York, he said in an interview that he wouldn't be comfortable flying an airliner that carried lithium ion aircraft batteries in its cargo hold. The potential for self-ignition, for uncontained fires, is huge," he said. The new regulations "need to be looked at very hard in the cold light of day, particularly with what has happened with the 787 batteries." Previously, U.S. regulations prohibited the shipment of lithium ion batteries on passenger planes in packages weighing more than 11 pounds, although heavier batteries could be shipped on cargo planes. The batteries are suspected of causing or contributing to the severity of an onboard fire that led to the September 2010 crash of a United Parcel Service plane near Dubai, killing both pilots. The two pilots of another UPS plane barely managed to escape the aircraft before it was consumed by fire moments after landing in Philadelphia in 2006. The combination of Boeing management ears wide closed , enabling FAA and NTSB self audit for Boeing and follow the money plan results in failure.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360224098180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 03:01:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360224835602-10</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That gives them about the membership of the PTA</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360224835602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 03:13:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360232078881-11</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Board of Directors, the club, bad stock to own</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360041458639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 00:17:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ronnieanderson727 do I need to give you a lollipop for your attention demands today ? Your a little old to burp arent you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360232078881</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 05:14:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360232974465-12</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does anything that's American and has to do with freedom, tick you off so much? Would you have been happier as Himmler's boot shine boy?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360232974465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 05:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360233046320-13</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talking to yourself again?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360233046320</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 05:30:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360233158698-14</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that why you created multiple aliases that always seem to agree with your radical views?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360233158698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 05:32:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360235467235-15</Id><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Msg>Ballot arrived in the mail yesterday and I promptly filled it out (no on Boeing's offer and yes for strike authorization) ... There are good things in the offer, but Boeing has inserted a "poison pill" that puts everybody's retirement benefits at risk. It is a ticking time bomb. If you're lucky enough to retire before the bomb goes off, you're fine. If you're still at Boeing when it detonates however, you're likely to lose tens if not hundreds of thousands of dollars of retirement income over your lifetime. The execs are exempt from all of this of course. Boeing wants us to take a "haircut" at a time of record profits, record orders and record deliveries, at a time when the company is showering the execs with massive bonuses equal to their annual salary and other goodies. I just can't justify that. There will be many who vote for this however. I just hope the majority see through the company's strategy. Boeing is playing "long ball". Once they have the pension, they'll go after everything else with a vengeance and eventually freeze it. Please guys, don't do the stupid thing. Don't think only short-term. Don't vote yes on the contract. Don't vote to screw yourself and everybody else. Vote no and tell Boeing to get rid of the ticking time bomb.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360237812129-16</Id><Topic><Title>The 787 Sullenberger- boat new flight safety standard for the 787 fire issue !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360224098180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 03:01:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing management cant be all bad- they were smart enough to fire Dell George AKA waynedickenson before he screwed up anything. Presumably by not cleaning his urinals properly</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360237812129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:50:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360237948798-17</Id><Topic><Title>7 million losing Insurance under Obamacare</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360220411876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 02:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>37 million gaining insurance under Obamacare. RWNJs the world over are weeping and wailing and gnashing their teeth because of Obamacare</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360237948798</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:52:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360238096854-18</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Im betting you never knew any of your fathers eh??????????</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360238096854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:54:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360238283598-19</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more raging from the tin shack that is home to joedokes/hawfaeces/agolferboooger/ghorsesa...sanon all because he never held a job long enough to get soshul security or medicare and now hes a true welfare bum</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360238283598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:58:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360238667101-20</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz's bed time fairy tale "short form was a fake" --------------------------------- and THEN boys and girls ...the great Daddy had to release a LONG FORM Birth Certificiate that he PREVIOUSLY said never existed....and THEN... all the experts said THAT was a fake too...and that really made people mad.....but there was a happy ending cause a few days later the Big Papa Daddy got to kill a big bad boogy man in Pakistan and all was right with big papa daddy.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360238667101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:04:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360238681932-21</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots He Scores</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360238681932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:04:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360238765170-22</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Board of Directors, the club, bad stock to own</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360041458639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 00:17:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anything about the unions ?</Msg><Username>oroplata68</Username><Timestamp>1360238765170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:06:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360239083595-23</Id><Title>FAA grants 787 test aircraft permission to fly!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>good thing Boeing never stopped the production lines eh??!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360239083595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:11:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360239180890-24</Id><Topic><Title>FAA grants 787 test aircraft permission to fly!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360239083595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:11:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waynedickenson weeps and wails and gnashes teeth HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360239180890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:13:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360239477241-25</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven Lunatic: "membership of the PTA" ...Are you saying that membership has swelled since you and other Obama followers have joined the Propaganda Transmittal Association ?</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360239477241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:17:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360239604401-26</Id><Title>FAA declares 787 safest plane ever!!!</Title><Msg>Well, if you guys are going to lie, and claim that test flights have been granted when they haven't, why not just proclaim that there were never any fires!</Msg><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1360239604401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:20:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360239669056-27</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure if Bush was greiving rending his flesh about not going to War in Iraq...but I did notice Bush Sr and Bush Jr and #$%$ Cheney and Don Rumsfeld made lots and lots of money through the Carlysle Group, the Bin Ladin Group, Exxon Moble and Halliburton</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360239669056</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:21:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360240564494-28</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven wants to make a solemn pilgrimage to the dedication of the Ernst Roehm Bath House in Berlin.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360240564494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:36:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360241195652-29</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oppressive gommint?? The big lie of the ignorant racist redneck continues to have currency even tho everybody knows that the 2nd amendment was the means devised to arm the slave patrols of pre civil war southern states. (the slave patrols were the true precursors of the KluKuxKan) It was and continues to be the most evil law ever instigated in the USA</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360241195652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:46:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360241352672-30</Id><Topic><Title>Latest list of a Dozen Impeachable offenses commited by Barry Soetoro</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360121701854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 22:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and that just couldn't be the voters could it? not when the baggers lost HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360241352672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:49:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360242506283-31</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Wallace slams NRA’s Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360025900325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 19:58:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course the President's children require greater protection. They need protection whereever they go. But Wayne LaPierre also has a valid point that all school children should be made as safe as the President's daughters when in school. All school children deserve a safe learning environment. It was Chris Wallace way of improving his image of being a bore by throwing in a zinger.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1360242506283</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:08:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360243048485-32</Id><Topic><Title>scafflow of the Boeing message board</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360094974292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 15:09:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once the 787 gets flying again. Your argument of Boeing no longer being a great American company flys out the window.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1360243048485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:17:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360243075860-33</Id><Topic><Title>7 million losing Insurance under Obamacare</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360220411876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 02:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How rich ya figure Big Pharma and The Insurance companies will get ? Have any stats for that please ?</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360243075860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:17:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360243176673-34</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Wallace slams NRA’s Wayne LaPierre</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360025900325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 19:58:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but the R_I_G_H_T to protect them equally is the same ...natural law</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360243176673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:19:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360243196088-35</Id><Topic><Title>Dronegate exposes Obama as a hypocrite</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360206351418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>King Obama was pressured by his own party to release the memo. It looks like the MSM will be forced to make this all public and show Once again the disdain that King Obama has for the US Constitution is evident.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360243196088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360243749845-36</Id><Topic><Title>Dronegate exposes Obama as a hypocrite</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360206351418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 22:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course Obama is a hypocrite.....he's a Democrat. The first and highest qualification of being a true Democrat is hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360243749845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:29:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360244010556-37</Id><Title>Hussein "Pinocchio" Obama Using Honest Abe Lincoln's Bible Is An Insult To Lincoln</Title><Msg>The clown that would be king took an oath to uphold the US Constitution using Abe Lincoln's Bible and in reality he takes every opportunity he can to show his contempt for the US Constitution. The irony doesn't get much richer. They need to sterilize Abe's Bible.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360244010556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:33:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360244152051-38</Id><Title>NRA Far More Popular than Obama</Title><Msg>Please Mr. Obamy......please don't throw our gun rights in that briar patch.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244152051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:35:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360244492990-39</Id><Title>New Poll: Majority of Americans Want Illegal Immigrants to Head Back to Home Countries</Title><Msg>A new poll released by the Center for Immigration Studies shows the majority of likely voters simply want illegal immigrants to head back to their home countries. A new poll using neutral language — and avoiding the false choice of conditional legalization vs. mass deportations — finds that most Americans want illegal immigrants to return to their home counties, rather than be given legal status. The findings also show a very large gap in intensity, with those who want illegal immigrants to head home feeling much stronger about that option than those who would like to see illegal immigrants receive legal status. •Of likely voters, 52 percent responded that they preferred to see illegal immigrants in the United States go back to their home countries, compared to just 33 percent who would like them to be given legal status. •There is an enormous gap in intensity between the two views on immigration. Of those who want illegal immigrants to head home, 73 percent indicated that they felt “very strongly” about that view, while just 35 percent of those who want illegal immigrants to get legal status said they felt very strongly about this view.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244492990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:41:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360245337899-40</Id><Title>Hey, Remember When Obama Claimed to Support the Troops?</Title><Msg>Well he doesn't and neither does his outgoing defense secretary: Just days before he leaves office, Defense Secretary Leon Panetta is recommending military pay be limited, effectively decreasing troop salaries next year. Panetta will recommend to Congress that military salaries be limited to a 1% increase in 2014. The Pentagon has calculated that the Labor Department's 2014 Employment Cost Index is expected to be above 1% but wants to still cut back on pay because of "budget uncertainties," a department official told CNN. In 2013, a 1.7% increase was approved, based on the index, which has been the basis for military pay for the last several years. Three Pentagon officials have confirmed details of the plan to CNN. The Joint Chiefs of Staff have also agreed to Panetta's proposed pay plan. Final approval for the pay would come from Congress in the form of the 2014 budget. The recommendation is tied to the Defense Department's 2014 budget recommendation, which was expected to be sent to Congress this month, one of the officials said. But the officials acknowledge it is going to be seen as an effort to push Congress to stop the automatic budget cuts that could go into effect if no deal is reached on spending reductions. A few reminders: 1) Sequestration was Obama's idea. That's right folks, Obama phones, welfare and solar panels are way more important than our troops getting paid what they deserve. 2) Obama has already astronomically increased healthcare costs for military families thanks to ObamaCare. The Obama administration’s proposed defense budget calls for military families and retirees to pay sharply more for their healthcare, while leaving unionized civilian defense workers’ benefits untouched. The proposal is causing a major rift within the Pentagon, according to U.S. officials. Several congressional aides suggested the move is designed to increase the enrollment in Obamacare’s state-run insurance exchanges. The disparity in treatment between civilian and uniformed personnel is causing a backlash within the military that could undermine recruitment and retention. The proposed increases in health care payments by service members, which must be approved by Congress, are part of the Pentagon’s $487 billion cut in spending. It seeks to save $1.8 billion from the Tricare medical system in the fiscal 2013 budget, and $12.9 billion by 2017. Significantly, the plan calls for increases between 30 percent to 78 percent in Tricare annual premiums for the first year. After that, the plan will impose five-year increases ranging from 94 percent to 345 percent—more than 3 times current levels. According to congressional assessments, a retired Army colonel with a family currently paying $460 a year for health care will pay $2,048. 3) And then there's this: The military is poised to extend some benefits to the same-sex partners of service members, U.S. officials said Tuesday, about 16 months after the Pentagon repealed its ban on openly gay service. Defense Secretary Leon Panetta has not made a final decision on which benefits will be included, the officials said, but the Pentagon is likely to allow same-sex partners to have access to the on-base commissary and other military subsidized stores, as well as some health and welfare programs. Panetta must walk a fine, legal line. While there has been increased pressure on the Pentagon to extend some benefits to same-sex partners, defense officials must be careful not to violate the 1996 Defense of Marriage Act, or DOMA. The federal law forbids the federal government from recognizing any marriage other than those between a man and a woman. Cutting the pay of our military is the last thing we should be doing especially on top of increasing their medical care, something soldiers need more than the average citizen when coming home from deployments.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360245337899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:55:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360245749513-41</Id><Title>Hey Obama Lovers - Over 120 Innocent Children Were Killed By Obama Drones</Title><Msg>Hooz or Genna can you explain why you're OK with the mass murder of innocent children by Obama but you got all bent out of shape and cried for impeachment when Bush had 3 terrorists water boarded with a medical team present to assure safety?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360245749513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:02:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246127338-42</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Remember When Obama Claimed to Support the Troops?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360245337899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There has been some dots regarding Obama that are very easy to connect. What he says at the teleprompter is quite different than what he does in practice, and conives behind closed doors. "fool me twice, and shame on me." In the case of the un-informed liberal? They can be fooled a thousand times over.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360246127338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:08:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360246128638-43</Id><Title>Jackson Jr plea deal will include “significant jail time” for the Corrupt Democrat</Title><Msg>Isn’t this becoming a tradition in Illinois politics? A couple of the state’s recent governors went from the big mansion to the Big House, too, and so did Jesse Jackson Jr’s predecessor in his House seat, Mel Reynolds. Jackson will follow in that tradition, according to a new report from the Chicago Sun-Times’s Michael Sneed about the structure of his plea deal on corruption charges (via the Daily Caller): Sneed has learned a plea deal is now on the table between former Rep. Jesse Jackson Jr. and federal authorities probing allegations of campaign fund misuse. Sneed is told the plea deal includes Jackson serving time in federal prison. “Significant jail time is now definitely a part of the deal,” said a top Sneed source close to the probe. Yes, Sneed writes about herself in the third person. Bear with it for a bit longer, because the story gets better. The federal investigation into Jackson started off by looking at both him and his wife Sandi. Now, however, the investigation of Sandi Jackson has spun off into its own probe, and Sandi Jackson believes that Jesse sold her out, according to Sneed: “But I think [Jackson’s wife] Sandi, feels like she was thrown under the bus by her husband, ” now that a separate probe has begun on her, a second source added. Sandi Jackson claims she was stunned by campaign finance abuse disclosures against her husband, who has been treated for mental disorders and allegedly spent $40,000 on a Rolex watch purchased with campaign funds. Mrs. Jackson was a Chicago alderman until last month, and also a paid consultant to her husband’s campaign — to the tune of $5,000 a month, which only ended well after the election. According to the Sun-Times report, investigators haven’t yet decided whether to charge Sandi Jackson, but they’re taking a long look at her involvement in her husband’s alleged corruption. It’s possible that investigators opened the probe against Jackson’s wife to put more pressure on him to accept prison time as part of the deal, too. That would certainly make sense, especially after the public-relations effort put into painting Jackson as a victim of mental illness, which may still be true, of course. The machinations appear to be coming to an end soon, though, and we’ll soon find out whether Jackson threw his wife under the bus or whether he’s going to rescue her from it.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360246128638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:08:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246360808-44</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Majority of Americans Want Illegal Immigrants to Head Back to Home Countries</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244492990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:41:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's reality...Obama doesn't have to go by polls, and public opinion like most other Presidents have been forced to follow. Why? Because the mainstream media will support whatever socialist desires he wants. If the mainstream media was just slightly more honest than a Hooz, he'd cave to poll, and public opinion numbers.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360246360808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:12:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246391265-45</Id><Topic><Title>FAA declares 787 safest plane ever!!!</Title><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1360239604401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:20:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too much money is involved. Just for the money dance the bear,</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1360246391265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:13:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360246728079-46</Id><Title>Bad news from Gov. Quinn: Illinois’ pension systems are kind of a trainwreck</Title><Msg>As Republicans search for ways in which the party can more effectively make its case for free-markets and slimmer tax codes as the best and most efficient means to create the healthiest, most prosperous societies, many of the country’s 30 GOP governors are looking to turn their states into models of the ways in which conservative principles can work — a feat highlighted by the WSJ earlier this week: Kansas Gov. Sam Brownback says he wants to create a ‘red-state model’ for the national Republican Party. How? By turning Kansas into what he calls Exhibit A for how sharp cuts in taxes and government spending can generate jobs, wean residents off public aid and spur economic growth. … Coming off the largest tax cut in state history on Jan. 1, Kansas is now on the leading edge of a growing but still largely untested quest among conservative governors to create growth by dramatically revamping state tax codes. … The focus on fiscal innovations in the heartland comes as conservatives nationally seek ways to revive the GOP’s standing in the aftermath of its stinging election losses last year. Bruised by the continuing budget battles in Washington, where divided government has led to near-gridlock, top Republicans nationally are holding up Kansas and other GOP-dominated states as examples of what the party might accomplish if left to its own devices. And while many GOP governors are looking for innovative solutions to help make their states more competitive, the highly illustrative flip side of the red-blue coin is readily available from the state with the country’s worst credit rating. Reuters reports: Illinois Governor Pat Quinn, already the most unpopular governor in the nation, has his work cut out for him at his annual “state of the state” speech on Wednesday… The fiscal crisis caused by pension underfunding in Illinois is so bad that some hospitals wait a year to be paid by the state for insurance claims. At the same time, teachers in Chicago’s wealthy suburbs are retiring with six-figure salaries set by school districts on which pensions are calculated, and the state pays the bill. The benefits cannot be reduced, according to the state constitution. Illinois’ pension systems are in the worst financial shape of any state at 39 percent funded when no less than 80 percent is considered healthy. State pensions are in the hole by the staggering amount of nearly $97 billion, or $20,000 per Illinois household and nearly four times the annual state revenue. … But economic growth in President Barack Obama’s home state has lagged the nation for decades, according to a national task force on state budget problems, and its unemployment rate of 8.7 percent is the sixth highest in the nation. The state has been making half-hearted, gimmicky attempts to “balance” their budget via delaying bill payments, and any real reform to the system will require Democrats willing to take on the state’s organized labor interests — a daunting task, to say the least. Breaking up union-strangleholds have also been on Republican governors’ to-do lists of late, with right-to-work legislation recently passing through Indiana and Michigan, and Pennsylvania might even be on deck. Maybe Illinois should consider take a leaf out of their book? …I know, I know. I can dream.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360246728079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:18:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360246821471-47</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Majority of Americans Want Illegal Immigrants to Head Back to Home Countries</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244492990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:41:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only poll I trust is from Fox, what are the numbers from their poll on immigrants</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360246821471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:20:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360247046330-48</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Majority of Americans Want Illegal Immigrants to Head Back to Home Countries</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244492990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:41:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Honesty has nothing to do with Obama's strategy. If people have their ears ans eyes open, it's clear he feels it's perfectly alright to lie and say anything to get a bill passed or to get support for his Marxist ideology. The him and most other Democrat politicians the end always justifies the means.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360247046330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:24:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360247587082-49</Id><Title>Global Warming to Cause Friday Blizzard to Bury New England...</Title><Msg>"Two storms will merge quickly enough to bring colder air, heavy snow and increasing wind to New England. Some areas will be hit with an all-out blizzard and a couple of feet of snow. The worst of the storm will hit the Boston-area late Friday and Friday night and will wind down Saturday morning. However, lingering effects from blowing and drifting snow, blocked roads and other travel delays are likely to linger into much of the weekend." Sure hope all those storm victims still waiting for Obama to help them out in NY don't get cold.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360247587082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:33:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360247700635-50</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer People Than Ever Trust Fox News</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360205005931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:43:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Juan Williams was fired by NPR.......I'm glad he did get a fat contract with Fox News, he at least gives a voice on reasoning instead of a voice approaching insanity, if he wasn't there they might have Michelle Malkin in his place and then you talk about a plunge in Fox's ratings....down to the basement. She's as worthless as Palin &amp; Morris combined.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360247700635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:35:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360248968277-51</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming to Cause Friday Blizzard to Bury New England...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360247587082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:33:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Changes in the global climate will not make winter or snow go away no matter how stupid you have been led whoops I mean fed.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360248968277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:56:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249112181-52</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer People Than Ever Trust Fox News</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360205005931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:43:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least gives? Fox news openly debates the major issues, and invites lots of liberals onto the network...lots of them. The mainstream liberal media won't even bring up many of the big issues of the day because of their leftist views like yours. They censor the facts rather than debate them. When all you libtards result to character assassinating a network, or an individual rather than discussing substance that they bring up it is quite obvious you are on the side of wrong, and support fascism.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360249112181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:58:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360249467869-53</Id><Title>ba up again????</Title><Msg>What a suprise!!!!!! Cover now shorts before it costs you more.I warned you at 74....</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360249467869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:04:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360249495433-54</Id><Topic><Title>Bad news from Gov. Quinn: Illinois’ pension systems are kind of a trainwreck</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360246728079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:18:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I brought this up many, many times long ago. Union pension plans invested in what they thought were USA govt backed securities that liberals created by forcing subprime loans on the banks. These bad loans were then sold to union pension funds, and to central banks around the world as govt backed guaranteed good securities. These bundled packages of investments were called "Dirivitives" and when the loans went bad, and the govt couldn't back them the ENTIRE bundle went under because they couldn't be un-bundled if you will. The libs put the bad apple in the barrel. Now, slowly but surely these union pension funds are going under...what they call "unfunded liabilities"</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360249495433</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:04:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360249668811-55</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK WHATS UP...STOCK UP AGAIN?</Title><Msg>Waynedick...whats up...stock up again despite with all your junk! lol</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360249668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:07:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360249950758-56</Id><Title>Cable News Ratings, FOX Still #1</Title><Msg>Once you get past headlines like Fox News Sees Its Worst Ratings Since 2001, and Fox News Ratings Hit 12-Year Demo Lows In January Cable News Figures, you might be curious, like I was, to see what that’s about? Come to find out, according to Nielsen Media Research, the ratings people, January marked “11 consecutive years of FNC’s dominance as the #1-rated cable news network.” What? As a matter of fact, after the re-election of The One, I tuned out, not just to FOX, but to all of it. ‘It’ being the euphoria that the mainstream media was enjoying with the post-election burial of another Republican campaign, as well as the high of Obama’s second inauguration. It figures that the 51% wasn’t watching FOX either. They were watching everyone else. Turns out, that’s exactly what happened. A MSNBC show Rachel Maddow jumped up from 14th a year ago to 10th in prime time. Beating FOX’s Studio B and the 11 p.m. re-run of The O’Reilly Factor. Just from reading the headlines and the progressive talking heads, you can see them jumping for joy. With the help of President Obama, they’ve finally buried FOX. Well, not. JANUARY 2013 NIELSEN RATINGS (7 day week): TOTAL DAY: FNC: 1,029,000 total viewers; (209,000 in 25-54) MSNBC: 491,000 total viewers; (160,000 in 25-54) CNN: 448,000 total viewers; (135,000 in 25-54) PRIMETIME” FNC: 1,617,000 total viewers; (267,000 in 25-54) MSNBC: 790,000 total viewers; (235,000 in 25-54) CNN: 664,000 total viewers; (200,000 in 25-54) Every once and awhile, it pays to remember Hooz is full of BullSheet.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360249950758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:12:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250301737-57</Id><Topic><Title>Cable News Ratings, FOX Still #1</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360249950758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:12:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By a big margin for those that want to be informed. But have an interview with the duffus on a big city street, and many can't answer basic 3rd grade questions regarding the issues of the day, or names of prominent people in our history. And that is what the Hoozes rely on...the ignorant. Long ago, in the 60's the disruptive plans of the Progressives surfaced, One was to disrupt our educaitonal system. And for the very reason I mentioned. Create ignorant people that would vote socialist.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360250301737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:18:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360250423176-58</Id><Title>BA is going to break over $77 today! This is a non issue now! atch the run by Monday $80 is coming</Title><Msg>NON-ISSUE!</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1360250423176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:20:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250471820-59</Id><Topic><Title>Cable News Ratings, FOX Still #1</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360249950758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:12:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foxnewspeak number one? that's nuthin- Dr Goebbels radio propaganda programs were number one for at least 15 years till april 1945</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360250471820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:21:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360250715434-60</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Majority of Americans Want Illegal Immigrants to Head Back to Home Countries</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244492990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:41:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The American Indians felt the same way when the europeans came. They too had a very poor immigration policy, and worthless leaders. Didn't do them any good though. Their culture was crushed.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1360250715434</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360250870992-61</Id><Title>Biden: Government has the Right “To Determine what Type of Weapons can be Owned by the Public.”</Title><Msg>Guess the elitists in the government like Biden and Obama forget that they are supposed to be servants of the government who is "we the people." There is a little document called the constitution that restrains their ego-maniacal lust for power.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360250870992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:27:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360251000489-62</Id><Topic><Title>Bad news from Gov. Quinn: Illinois’ pension systems are kind of a trainwreck</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360246728079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:18:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Chicago Democrat Machine's Mike Madigan runs the state. Quinn is a do nothing dupe. Madigan's daughter is the Illinois AG and she protects her dad and corruption abounds. The corrupt Obama in the White House there will be no federal scrutiny so corruption will continue to abound. If you're a slum lord rich 1%er like Valerie Jarrett, the close friend and advisor of BHO, life is great because she only pays 1/4 of what everyone else is made to pay in property taxes. It's like comedy central when I listen to Obama spout off about others not paying their fair share because I know that in Chicago, for Obama and all the other rich Democrats, FAIR SHARE means the peasants are made subsidize the rich Democrats like Valerie Jarrett and Obama. It's good to be the King.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360251000489</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:30:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360251080143-63</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Rock: Obama is ‘… Dad of the Country’</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360198000933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 19:46:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does that apply to Obama's birth certificate!</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1360251080143</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:31:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360251396961-64</Id><Title>About ready to run over $77 today again!!!!!!!! $80 next week earnings and all will be well</Title><Msg>This is just silly!</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1360251396961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:36:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360251451435-65</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK WHATS UP...STOCK UP AGAIN?</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360249668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:07:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DARN WAYNEDICK...THE STOCK IS SO STRONG....$ 77 W/ 787 AROUND THE CORNER AND $ 87 W/ 787 BY YEARS END...PLUS ALL YOUR JUNK (LOL)</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360251451435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:37:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360251825709-66</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK WHATS UP...STOCK UP AGAIN?</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360249668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:07:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be careful,wayne will get his panties in a knot and TOS you....</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360251825709</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:43:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360252229429-67</Id><Title>China test flighted first domestically developed jumbo cargo jet</Title><Msg>Wow... China has now surpassed Japan in terms of technology. Even Japan couldn't build its own jet. Will this be a major threat to Boeing and Airbus. Both Airbus and China jumbo jet are state-sponsored project - socialism at its best.</Msg><Username>android_shopper</Username><Timestamp>1360252229429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:50:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360252634795-68</Id><Title>787 is in the air and heading to Everett</Title><Msg>BOE382. You can observe on flightradar24.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360252634795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360253273784-69</Id><Title>FOUND IT! LIVE ON TV! SOLVED! BOEING TO 90.00!!!</Title><Msg>Live on CNBc NTSB found the short circuit!</Msg><Username>ohthestupidity344</Username><Timestamp>1360253273784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:07:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360253327103-70</Id><Topic><Title>FOUND IT! LIVE ON TV! SOLVED! BOEING TO 90.00!!!</Title><Username>ohthestupidity344</Username><Timestamp>1360253273784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NTSB news is fabulous. Short circuit and minor re-enginnering and new wiring for dropping 4 volts out of 32!</Msg><Username>helloagain19777</Username><Timestamp>1360253327103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:08:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360253335776-71</Id><Title>nothing "solved' yet</Title><Msg>They should look at software.</Msg><Username>ka1524</Username><Timestamp>1360253335776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:08:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360253392134-72</Id><Title>Looking to buy puts</Title><Msg>failure</Msg><Username>ibuububeme</Username><Timestamp>1360253392134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:09:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360253552116-73</Id><Topic><Title>Looking to buy puts</Title><Username>ibuububeme</Username><Timestamp>1360253392134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:09:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOUR BEST BET IS TO SELL PUTS .... NOT BUY THEM!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360253552116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:12:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360253577277-74</Id><Topic><Title>787 is in the air and heading to Everett</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360252634795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Left Fort Worth at 924 AM CST. Due Everett 1048 AM PST.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360253577277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:12:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360253623975-75</Id><Title>Boeing headed to 100.00</Title><Msg>Parking lot full of jets waiting to get new battery wiring.</Msg><Username>upinouthome8594</Username><Timestamp>1360253623975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:13:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360254197218-76</Id><Title>.27 for teh $77.50 CALLS was a steal!!!!! Shoulld run over $2 when This clears up today!!!!</Title><Msg>$80 by Monday!</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1360254197218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:23:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360255269911-77</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Advancement for The Boeing Company. Read Now!</Title><Username>brian_black</Username><Timestamp>1360241622220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:53:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checking it out as we speak.</Msg><Username>davidrichard533</Username><Timestamp>1360255269911</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:41:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360256365518-78</Id><Topic><Title>UNMANNED STEALTH DRONES FLYING ALL OVER USA...</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360250781597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:26:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Black Helicopters are REAL. How do you like that.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1360256365518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:59:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360256588995-79</Id><Title>Aluminum Wiring to Blame ? Japan article on Boeing has this comment</Title><Msg>Thoughts ? Comments ? BuzzBJan. 22, 2013 - 08:07PM JST I have my eye on the aluminum wire on this plane. It is a well known fact that aluminum wire is tricky to employ especially where there are extremes in temperature and vibration. There is a reason it was outlawed in building wiring systems. Also, do we fully understand how current flows in/on aluminum wire. I've been an electrician for over 40 years. We always learned that DC travels inside the copper wire and and AC travels on the outside surface. This is known as the "skin effect". Airplanes usually employ 400 Hz AC as well as DC. 28 volts DC used to be the standard but I'm betting all these old rules have been bent and twisted for "cutting edge" advantage. So are these aluminum wire bundles a mixed bag? With DC circuits and AC circuits alongside each other? I know how inductive coupling of AC circuits works on copper lines but am not knowledgeable about how that works on aluminum. These systems were no doubt tested to great length individually without fail. But how do they all get along in a big crowd?? If it turns out to be inductive coupling then this will be a costly fix for sure</Msg><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1360256588995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:03:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360256925362-80</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leftys are never unbiased, and they never tell the truth. That's just the way they roll.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360256925362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:08:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360257337289-81</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Advancement for The Boeing Company. Read Now!</Title><Username>brian_black</Username><Timestamp>1360241622220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:53:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already subscribed as of last week.</Msg><Username>rickyanthony438</Username><Timestamp>1360257337289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:15:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360257886941-82</Id><Title>dod contract</Title><Msg>On Wednesday, the Department of Defense announced that it has awarded Boeing (NYSE: BA ) subsidiary Insitu a 25-month contract to provide intelligence, surveillance, and reconnaissance (ISR) support to the U.S. Special Operations Command (SOCOM). The contract, which calls upon Insitu to provide "Mid-Endurance Unmanned Aircraft System (MEUAS)" ISR services to SOCOM, is valued at up to $190 million over the 25-month period. It specifies, however, not the actual purchase of unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs), but rather the hiring of Insitu to provide ISR services "using contractor-owned and contractor-operated equipment."</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360257886941</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:24:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360258226143-83</Id><Title>Close over $77 tomorrow for sure. This wekend alot get answered. American industry need this!</Title><Msg>$80 by Friday next week</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1360258226143</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:30:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360258497630-84</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Obama Lovers - Over 120 Innocent Children Were Killed By Obama Drones</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360245749513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:02:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! The right-fringers seem to have whipped (?) themselves into overdrive this morning. I'm worried about them overheating their batteries.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360258497630</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360258608826-85</Id><Topic><Title>Solution to Boeing battery problem</Title><Username>oneinrev333</Username><Timestamp>1360255176196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 11:39:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are they using the most unstable lithium battery made, when there is Lithium Phosphate available with overcharge protection already incorporated in it's design. If they would have chose VLNC battery they may have saved millions and VLNC now bankrupt !!!! Sounds pretty fishy to me.</Msg><Username>capozzoli_louis</Username><Timestamp>1360258608826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:36:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360258689784-86</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More lies from our commie Hooz. The NRA has raised tons of money due to Obama's fascist desire for gun control...250,000 new members were signed up in short order after ignorant Joe was assigned the job of coming up with a plan for gun control. Classes for gaining a concealed weapons permit have gone off the charts.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360258689784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:38:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259021587-87</Id><Topic><Title>787 is in the air and heading to Everett</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360252634795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't think you can locate a plane individually on that website. Just a total look (summation) for all flight???</Msg><Username>u8everything</Username><Timestamp>1360259021587</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:43:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259163689-88</Id><Topic><Title>787 is in the air and heading to Everett</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360252634795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it has a "filter" feature. Enter "BOE" as a filter and it only shows flights with BOE prefix.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360259163689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:46:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259176960-89</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something like 64% of the Natl. Runt Assn.'s "war chest" comes not from members, but from the gun manufacturers who bought and paid for the NRA. It doesn't represent people, it's a lobby group for big business. Why else would the Natl. Runt Assn. oppose background checks when 78% of their membership supports them?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360259176960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:46:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360259182896-90</Id><Title>Will the FAA Authorize Flights while the NTSB Investigation is still open?</Title><Msg>This is a strange situation for the FAA to be in since it is only going to be an "interim factual report" in 30 days "National Transportation Safety Board head Deborah Hersman told a press conference on Thursday that the agency will issue an "interim factual report" in 30 days, but said the decision to return the 787 to flight will be made by the Federal Aviation Administration."</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360259182896</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:46:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360259226309-91</Id><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Msg>Google "Aurora theater shooting victims harassed by conspiracy theorists" Is there anything lower than these psycho POS's who call themselves "American". There is a special place in hell for them all.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259565148-92</Id><Topic><Title>Aluminum Wiring to Blame ? Japan article on Boeing has this comment</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1360256588995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:03:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The NTSB has stated that the incident in Boston was teh result of a failure in a single cell of the battery. It was operating normally at about 32 volts and suddenly dropped to 28 volts which is the voltage in each cell. What they dont know yet is why the cell shorted. I am not sure how they would be able to determine the exact cause of the short.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360259565148</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360259888043-93</Id><Topic><Title>Will the FAA Authorize Flights while the NTSB Investigation is still open?</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360259182896</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:46:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the FAA is the only gov. body that can allow/deny flights. The NTSB is only an ivestigating body. The FAA could allow flights if the batteries were changed to some other type but only after testing but the NTSB will still continue investigating the original failure.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360259888043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:58:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360260939589-94</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty and Alex Jones should be ashamed of themselves.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360260939589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:15:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360262038789-95</Id><Title>Actually worse than I thought.</Title><Msg>Two damning statements from NTSB "That's at odds with what Boeing told the Federal Aviation Administration when the agency was working to certify the innovative aircraft for flight, Hersman said. The manufacturer asserted its testing showed that any short circuiting could be contained within a single cell, preventing thermal runaway and fire, she said. Boeing's testing also showed the batteries were likely to cause smoke in only 1 in 10 million flight hours, she said. But the Boston fire was followed nine days later by a smoking battery in an All Nippon Airways plane that made an emergency landing in Japan. The 787, Boeing's newest and most technologically advanced plane, has recorded less than 100,000 flight hours, Hersman noted. " so earlier, I had posted that once they discover that root cause of the failure, they will have to examine their analysis, models and assumptions to determine what was in error, and re-do the all the analysis that used those incorrect inputs. But now, the NTSB has found two "summary conclusions" from Boeing that are flat out wrong, and the NTSB is not only questioning Boeing's analysis, but how the FAA actually certified the 787. Next I would suspect that even after they determine the root cause of the battery failure and enact a corrective solution, the FAA will be requested to a "red-team" review of the entire certification process. Since the NTSB has only offered an "interim" report in 30 days, I would now modify my estimate of when the Dreamliner will fly again, from Mid- March, till late April.</Msg><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1360262038789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:33:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360262241079-96</Id><Topic><Title>787 is in the air and heading to Everett</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360252634795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the flightradar shows BOE382 nearing Everett. Since it shows up in orange rather than yellow the data is on a 5 minute delay. You can watch the plane land at Everett by going to the paine field webcam (google it). Picture updates every 60 seconds.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360262241079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:37:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360262552274-97</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Advancement for The Boeing Company. Read Now!</Title><Username>brian_black</Username><Timestamp>1360241622220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:53:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes they do good work</Msg><Username>haywood_jesus</Username><Timestamp>1360262552274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:42:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360262998048-98</Id><Topic><Title>Substantial Advancement for The Boeing Company. Read Now!</Title><Username>brian_black</Username><Timestamp>1360241622220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 07:53:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are fantastic</Msg><Username>ivorysean279</Username><Timestamp>1360262998048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:49:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263165175-99</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>King Obama will beat everyone to hell. He is a mass murderer of innocent children and granted himself the licence to kill with impunity.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360263165175</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263262236-100</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take your meds, you are foaming at the mouth and ranting incoherent and irrational non-sense.</Msg><Username>rividiot</Username><Timestamp>1360263262236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:54:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263270124-101</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are the conspiricy theoriss? Couldn't be a conservative being called a theorist...they proudly present the facts.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360263270124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:54:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263320262-102</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are all hypocrites and cowards for protecting Obama when he has done far worse than Bush who you all complained about for years and years. You have 0 credibility and Sparty looks honorable compared to you. You're the one's without shame.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360263320262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:55:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263346171-103</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpity bump ...</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360263346171</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:55:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263446574-104</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Obama Lovers - Over 120 Innocent Children Were Killed By Obama Drones</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360245749513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:02:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Chris? You are a big supporter of Obama war atrocities now?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360263446574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 13:57:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263666132-105</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is one for you. I just got back from my local sporting goods store. I asked the clerk why the big line outside the door at midweek waiting for the store to open? She says for guns and ammo. They hope we have got in a shipment of AK 47's. And last week she said they camped outside the store overnite hoping we got a shipment in. And the 1,000 rounds of ammo for the AKs that were $349.00 a case has gone up to $379.00, BUT some of the other stores have sold those cases for over $700.00 the salesman tells me. Yeh, the NRA is really hurting.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360263666132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:01:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263752766-106</Id><Topic><Title>UNMANNED STEALTH DRONES FLYING ALL OVER USA...</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360250781597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:26:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shhhh,,don't tell the public,they may get mad at YOU.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360263752766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:02:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360263988221-107</Id><Topic><Title>UNMANNED STEALTH DRONES FLYING ALL OVER USA...</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360250781597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:26:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually they are only monitoring RWNJs- so they know where to go to take their guns away</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360263988221</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:06:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360264031729-108</Id><Title>787 lands at everett</Title><Msg>Landed about 9 minutes ago.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360264031729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:07:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360264120288-109</Id><Topic><Title>Cable News Ratings, FOX Still #1</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360249950758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:12:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to your numbers 80% of FNC viewers are NOT in the age group 25-54. So I suppose that's age 55 and above and that group is getting on down the road. Demographics aren't in favor of your beloved FNC. So celebrate now if you want but doesn't look good as time goes on.</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360264120288</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:08:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360264210075-110</Id><Topic><Title>UNMANNED STEALTH DRONES FLYING ALL OVER USA...</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360250781597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:26:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gotta be Obama's liberal friends that are criticizing his drone policy that is snuffing out the top terrorist generals. Sure wouldn't be a conservative criticizing those operations. The big worry is keeping tabs on what our fascist leader is really up to.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360264210075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:10:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360264251819-111</Id><Title>$77.70 close today!!! Over $80 by Monday as all is well!!!!! $77.50 CAlls where sooooo cheap yesterday</Title><Msg>and Today!!!!</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1360264251819</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:10:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360264581785-112</Id><Topic><Title>NRA less popular with Americans than it's ever been</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360203837341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 21:23:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I stand behind the "0" government 100% Pass a law and get rid of guns. And then don't forget to buy a whole bunch of new guns to enforce your new law. duhhhhhh!</Msg><Username>otto_pilot_blow_me</Username><Timestamp>1360264581785</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:16:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360264714975-113</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Outrageous. What motivates those idiots?</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360264714975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:18:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360265529401-114</Id><Title>Being a Viet Nam Veterian gives domer special liar rights</Title><Msg>domerrrrr45, you dishonor every service person past, present and future with your behavior ! domerrrrr45 if you are a Viet Nam veteran that does not give you any liar rights , vulgar communication rights or criminal rights sorry ! domerrrrr45 on Feb 4 you state waynedick was a fired Boeing employee, on Feb 6, Domerrrrr45 , you state to waynedick "I thought you said ( to waynedick) u didnt work for boeing, now you claim u worked for 15 years. So first you make a false claim waynedickenson was a fired Boeing employee then two days later domerrrrr45 claims he thinks waynedickenson told domerrrrr45 that waynedickenson said he never worked for Boeing, you can't have it both ways . domerrrrr45, it is simple you are unaware that your lies catch up to you domerrrrr45 stop living in denial. BTW post your source for your claim that waynedickenson claimed he did not work for Boeing, cannot do that ! domerrrrr45 you claim to be a Viet Nam veteran so that gies you the right to be a liar too and a vulgarian who is a scofflaw. You might be a Viet Nam Veteran but you sure act like a criminal . Dormerrrrr45 in two days you make two false statement in continuing Yahoo TOS violation. about waynedickenson domerrrrr45by domerrrrr45.Feb 2, 2013 9:29 PM.Permalink.Go to topic TOS TOS TOS..SCARY! • Re: WAYNEDICK....BOEING domerrrrr45by domerrrrr45.Feb 4, 2013 8:23 AM.Permalink.Go to topic • Waynedick...u r a fired employee of boeing...expected! Sentiment: Strong Buy o 2users liked this posts6users disliked this posts o • Re: Re: Re: Re: scofflaw of the Boeing message board waynedickenson961by waynedickenson961.Feb 6, 2013 2:10 PM.Permalink.Go to topic domerrrrr45 , you said i thought u didn't work for boeing,now u claim u worked for 15y... domerrrrr45 , you said i thought u didn't work for boeing,now u claim u worked for 15years w/777 which one is it? BTW...boeing is still a great american company. Not withstanding your moronic garbage. domerrrrr45 please post any statement from me that indicates I did not work for Boeing? If not why are you making up stuff o o</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360265529401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:32:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360266200399-115</Id><Title>boeing stock price compared to the Dow Jones average</Title><Msg>Boeing trades in a narrow range ,it tops in the low 80 range , for the year Boeing is up now 2.5% while the average it belongs to, the Dow Jones average is up 8,2% so too much risk to reward for any Boeing holder. Better yet the s and p average is up 12% for the year. Boeing would need to break above 85 and hold for two weeks to be a buy. Red my other user comments that has already been stated and the fact that Boeing is now in a narrow slow move up within its narrow trade range. Boeing is using the 2 billion stock buyback to pump up the stock price while the 787 is grounded, next the SPEEA strike issue will give Boeing another black eye. Better stocks to select than a 2.5% gain Boeing in a year . cc FBI team Boeing har !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360266200399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:43:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266269721-116</Id><Topic><Title>787 lands at everett</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360264031729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:07:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Were the batteries on fire or not</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360266269721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:44:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360266407143-117</Id><Title>Oh My it's 29 degrees here on Grand Cayman.....brrrrrrrr.</Title><Msg>Oh wait that's Celsius.......that would be 84 degrees Fahrenheit. I love the Canadian Healthcare system but I have a good idea I'm gonna love Obama care a whole lot more. Hahahahahah</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360266407143</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:46:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266421000-118</Id><Topic><Title>$77.70 close today!!! Over $80 by Monday as all is well!!!!! $77.50 CAlls where sooooo cheap yesterday</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1360264251819</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:10:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing is the Place to Be$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1360266421000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:47:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266477336-119</Id><Topic><Title>boeing stock price compared to the Dow Jones average</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360266200399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:43:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for any Boeing investor the next test or support resistence is $79.13 Boeing will need to break and hold above 79.13 for two weeks now to be more than a snap up price good luck.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360266477336</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:47:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266511655-120</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Riv explain how I'm being irrational. Obama is killing innocent children in Pakistan a country that we are not at war with. Genna, Hooz and other aliases here wanted Bush tried for war crimes for 3 water boardings with a medical team present to assure that terrorists wouldn't be harmed. Isn't committing war atrocities by killing innocent children worse? What's irrational is the lack of outcry by the people here that wanted Bush tried for war crimes but are silent in support of Obama's war crimes.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360266511655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:48:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360266630367-121</Id><Title>$78 today!!!!!!!! BUY the $77.50 CALLS been saying it all day .23-.80 easily or better!!!</Title><Msg>Run over $2 by Friday</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1360266630367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:50:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266688617-122</Id><Topic><Title>Global Warming to Cause Friday Blizzard to Bury New England...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360247587082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 09:33:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pay4ityourself - post your global warming comments this summer........thanks</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360266688617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:51:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360266939519-123</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Far More Popular than Obama</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244152051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:35:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are mentally stable you don't have to fret.........what's that? You say you're now feeling really distressed!!?? Guess y'all will hav to lern how to deal with the briar patch</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360266939519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:55:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267025106-124</Id><Topic><Title>Being a Viet Nam Veterian gives domer special liar rights</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360265529401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:32:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45, waiting for your comment , as a Viet Nam veteran you have claimed the right of free speech , so tell me more, we all want to hear what you have to say about waynedick, and any other topic you fought for , you have your rights !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360267025106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:57:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267574772-125</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets be clear- there IS a problem with the Pension Plan (BCERP- alternate formula and covered compensation ) However- the presentation and buc presentation and Goforth blather at about 4 minutes into his video on the site, plus the ' scrap the cap " fiasco by Matt IS 99 percent BOGUS ! Worst case if covered comp goes bonkers is about 3 to 4 months flatline of pension- NOT several years Why- cuz SPEEA refuses to get EXPERT help from the firm they have on retainer- and the STAFF involved is 75 percent or more incompetent on ERISA rules and even what Boeing published regarding MINIMUM ALTERNATE FORMULA !!! For a complete- or at least a more detailed explanation SPEEA council urges members to reject Boeing 'final' offer article in Everett Herald - blog has a 5 part comment by myself with many links to the facts and data One can also look up speea- talk and I have repeated most of MY Herald comments there AND added a link to a spreadsheet Search on the term- thread THE SPEEA INFINITE COVERED COMPENSATION FIASCO</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360267574772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:06:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267659262-126</Id><Topic><Title>The jet stream is set to gain mach 1 speed</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360267021587</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:57:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>450 per second?? you must be talking about the planet Jupiter</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360267659262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:07:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360267999854-127</Id><Topic><Title>787 lands at everett</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360264031729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:07:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No sign of smoke or fire. Flight seemed uneventful according to what I saw on flighttracker..</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360267999854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:13:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360268152999-128</Id><Title>Odd video of the 787 in Everett today...</Title><Msg>Just saw the video (CNBC) of the 787 returning to Everett in beautiful, clear blue skies. Strange part about this video is I'm here in Everett and the sky has been very dark and gloomy last night and today with no blue sky breaks? Ahhhh yes, the magic of Boeing.</Msg><Username>morin669</Username><Timestamp>1360268152999</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:15:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268391180-129</Id><Topic><Title>The jet stream is set to gain mach 1 speed</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360267021587</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:57:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No he is talking about Uranus.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360268391180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:19:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360268492252-130</Id><Title>BA battery problem</Title><Msg>Its called made in japan.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360268492252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:21:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268510875-131</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A QUICKIE LOOK can be found- cannot post links But search on the following on goo- BCERPBASICF5 SPEEABUCCLAIM BCERPCREDITEDSERVICE</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360268510875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:21:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268709820-132</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of no shame, which name does NOT belong to the following group: Newtie Gingrich Batsh*t Bachmann "Spreading" Santorum T. Willard Rmoney Robbney Hairrr Perry "Herb" Cain Caribou Barbie Palin Lyin' Ryan Jon Huntsman Tee-Paw</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1360268709820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:25:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360268907486-133</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truly, a Rogue's Gallery</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360268907486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:28:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360269038935-134</Id><Topic><Title>The jet stream is set to gain mach 1 speed</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360267021587</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:57:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not even close. Do you serve on the House Science Committee? Why are you so proud of your ignorance?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360269038935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:30:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360269107761-135</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a big isle. You keep to your side and I'll keep to mine. The surfing is better on your side of the isle anyway.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360269107761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:31:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360269192067-136</Id><Topic><Title>Odd video of the 787 in Everett today...</Title><Username>morin669</Username><Timestamp>1360268152999</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:15:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In everett, it depends on where you are standing. Mostly cloudy sky with patches of blue sky. Check paine field web cam.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360269192067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:33:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360269306027-137</Id><Topic><Title>Will BA Bounce? SEE OUR IN DEPTH BA BOUNCE REPORT</Title><Username>kyledurham521</Username><Timestamp>1360012053563</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, good report</Msg><Username>ivorycampbell321</Username><Timestamp>1360269306027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:35:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360269343523-138</Id><Title>CVU - Ready to Rally!</Title><Msg>Breakout!</Msg><Username>weinstein_s</Username><Timestamp>1360269343523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:35:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360269369978-139</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry me a river.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360269369978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:36:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360269639110-140</Id><Topic><Title>Odd video of the 787 in Everett today...</Title><Username>morin669</Username><Timestamp>1360268152999</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:15:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then it MUST be faked. Like the moon landing! Harharharharhar (Blue skies and sunny in Kent. Maybe you should call the Everett Chamber of Commerce complaint hot line.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360269639110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:40:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360270216918-141</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK....</Title><Msg>Plain and simple...u bash boeing i will bash you take it to the bank... and have you noticed the stock price $ 77+?</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360270216918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:50:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360270378692-142</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK....</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360270216918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:50:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..and stop threathening me with your tos b/s....u r getting nowhere....</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360270378692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:52:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360270441943-143</Id><Title>Expand 787 Battery Search to Chargers</Title><Msg>Hey Boeing, As a savvy EE I strongly recommend expanding the root cause search for the 787 battery problem beyond the batteries themselves. The root cause could be an unintended operating mode in charger or protection circuits. In the mid 1990s, a significant portion of the analog IC industry began experimenting with various bonus schemes to improve new-product time to market and stock performance. But analog ICs are cantankerous beasts and multiple revisions for new designs proved necessary regardless of the incentives. The net result was pressure to cheat by pushing defective products to market for bonuses. I was employed in a new-product verification role at the time and was often the last line of defense in quality regarding bugs. There was begging, scheming, falsification of test data and outright threats to my employment made to get defective products past me. And I was terminated in retaliation for standing my ground on quality. Since then, I've seen an industry-wide loss of new-product bug testing talent. And I've seen many bugs making it to market. For example, one analog IC had two battery chargers for Lithium-Ion cells. One of the chargers had a floating node that caused the charger's current to very slowly ramp from microamperes to amperes over the course of hours despite the charger being off. That IC is not in the 787 because it failed on the market due to other bugs and was obsoleted. But its a good example illustrating my advice. Floating nodes and such problems are very difficult to find in analog ICs because they exhibit themselves in an intermittent, non-deterministic way. The one I found was only caught because I was paying close attention while characterizing other attributes of the new-product. The initial symptoms were so subtle that 999/1000 engineers would have missed them and I almost did. There was only a slow monotonic increase in the values of the lowest digits of the 6 digit DMM. But I was the best of the best in my trade at that time and it was a lucky day. Best wishes in fixing the unfortunate problem in your otherwise fine new plane. Regards Ypresian</Msg><Username>ypresian</Username><Timestamp>1360270441943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:54:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360270462973-144</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A bit more on the levelling- Reducing the RATE of pension growth is a NO NO under erisa without adequate notice and a few other hoops. But SPEEA years ago agreed to the issue of pension levelling - again due to Gross Incompetence. As a result, only the BASIC benefit has increased over the years- and those who supposeldy earned enough to be above that amount- HAVE NEVER GOTTEN AN REAL INCREASE SINE THE 1990'S SINCE SPEEA agreed to the levelling - and congratulated Boeing for doing the ' right thing' hundreds of SPEEA members who have retired have been screwed out of significant pension $$ Here for example is the wonderous speea explanation in 2000-2001- forgettting that dropping the pension calculation $$ as Boeig had done from time to time was a violation of ERISA. But since SPEEA agreed to it - nothing could be done . And the beat goes on .... Retirement Saw-tooth - "Covered Compensation" &amp; "1996 Lump Sum Bonus" In the first few months of 2001, two changes will occur which may affect retirement benefits for employees retiring under theAlternate Benefit formula. These changes will not apply to the Standard benefit calculation. Each year in January, "covered compensation" in our Alternate Benefit formula is updated to reflect changes in nationwidewage data as determined by the Bureau of Labor Statistics. For the year 2001, this will affect the Alternate formula byreducing the February benefit, relative to the January benefit, by about $18.75 per month for an employee with 25 years ofcredited service. This has a "saw-tooth" effect on the Alternate Benefit, which otherwise increases steadily as credited serviceand final average earnings (FAE) increase. The second change involves the 5% lump sum bonus paid on January 26, 1996. That bonus is applied to the Alternate benefit,after final average earnings are calculated. The bonus is applied by adding one fifth of the bonus to the annual FAE (or onesixtieth of the bonus to the monthly FAE). The bonus is added onto FAE for anyone who received the bonus in the five yearspreceding their retirement date. For someone with $60,000 final average earnings, and 25 years experience, the bonus addsabout $15-20 per month to their retirement benefit, depending on their raise history, and age. With our retirement plan, someone terminates, often on the last day of some month, and begins retirement on the first day ofthe next month. For example, retirees terminating in December 2000 would begin retirement on January 1, 2001. In that case,the year 2000 covered compensation value would apply to their Alternate benefit, and the "five years preceding theirretirement" would be January 1, 1996 through December 31, 2000. Thus, January 1, 2001 retirees would enjoy the effect oflower covered compensation, and the addition to final average earnings from the 1996 bonus. Employees retiring in February2001 would see the higher covered compensation and would NOT have one fifth of the 1996 bonus added to their final averageearnings. In October 2000, we discussed these two items with Boeing Benefits representatives. We understood that a review wasunderway which might result in lower benefits when covered compensation increased. Past practice regarding lump sum payments has varied. We received a large (10%) bonus in December 1989. Five years later, retireeswould have received reduced retirement benefits for several months starting January 1995, but Boeing chose to apply theDecember 1994 benefit level, until the saw-tooth effect was overcome. After other bonuses, no adjustment was made. Binding language in the Summary Plan Document clearly states that a retiree's benefit "will not be reduced" due to increasingcovered compensation, and Federal law also discourages cut-backs in benefits already accrued. A few days after our meetings,we were notified that the review had been completed, and that Boeing had decided to pay retirees in February 2001 theJanuary or February benefit level, whichever is higher. As a result, neither the bonus effect nor the increase in covered compensation will reduce the Alternate Benefit calculation for February retirees. We'd like to thank the Company for doing theright thing in this situation.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360270462973</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:54:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360270504360-145</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK....</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360270216918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:50:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..and you are the bihggest liar..day after day..with waynedick, dellgeorge,gaylord whatever....enough of your b/s!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360270504360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:55:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360270525520-146</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK....</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360270216918</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:50:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BIHGGEST=BIGGEST</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360270525520</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:55:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360270930238-147</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW- the above extract was from the NOVEMBER 2000 Spotlite- which, with a little manipulation of the archive listings going back only to year 2001, can be found . . . . . /Archive_Spotlite/Spotlite_2000/Spotlite_nov_00.html</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360270930238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:02:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360271242430-148</Id><Topic><Title>China test flighted first domestically developed jumbo cargo jet</Title><Username>android_shopper</Username><Timestamp>1360252229429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 10:50:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take a look at some of their pictures. They're using '60s type engines (low bypass). Not going to get much performance with those.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360271242430</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:07:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360271684920-149</Id><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Msg>There's a dastardly conspiracy afoot to shut down the United States Postal Service, Lefty screamer Ed Schultz has informed his MSNBC audience. The culprits? Conservatives. Economic ignorance seems to be a magnet for liberals. It's probably time to sell the postal service to private companies who actually understand how to run a business. Trusting anything to the knuckle headed elitists currently occupying the white house is tantamount to throwing your money away.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360272036411-150</Id><Title>Wacko Liberal G.A.Y. Democrat: I Wanted to Kill as Many as Possible.......</Title><Msg>and Smear Chick-fil-A in Their Faces. Yesterday 28-year-old Floyd Lee Corkins II, the man who attempted to kill members of the conservative Family Research Council in Washington D.C. in August 2012, plead guilty to three charges including committing an act of terrorism. The question since August has been: Why did Corkins choose FRC as his target? After all, he was a gay activist who bizarrely walked into the FRC offices with a Chik-fil-A bag in one hand and a gun in the other before he opened fire, shooting a security guard who luckily survived his injuries. According to an interview with the FBI immediately after the shooting in August, which was released during the court hearing yesterday, Corkins wanted to “kill as many as possible and smear the Chick-Fil-A sandwiches in victims' faces, and kill the guard." This is what happens when you watch left-wing fake news like MSNBC.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360272036411</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:20:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360272173641-151</Id><Title>Why up 1.49% Today?</Title><Msg>The market down, Boeing up. What gives? I've glazed over the news and nothing stands out. Thanks.</Msg><Username>aznflorists</Username><Timestamp>1360272173641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:22:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360272303158-152</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The postal service is one government service specifically mention uin the U.S. Constitution. You know, the GD piece of paper conservatives read and weep tears of patriotic joy.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360272303158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:25:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360272396916-153</Id><Title>Outgoing CIA Chief: Obama Nowhere to Be Found Night of Benghazi Attack</Title><Msg>Confirmed again: Obama missed his 3 a.m. phone call on 9/11/2012. Early Thursday morning during testimony on Capitol Hill, Panetta told Senators he did not speak with President Obama or anybody in the White House the night the terrorist attack was carried out on the U.S. consulate in Benghazi, leaving four Americans dead including U.S. Ambassador Chris Stevens. "He knew generally what was deployed out there but as to specifics about time, etc., etc., he left that up to us." Confirmed again: Obama missed his 3 a.m. phone call on 9/11/2012. Early Thursday morning during testimony on Capitol Hill, Panetta told Senators he did not speak with President Obama or anybody in the White House the night the terrorist attack was carried out on the U.S. consulate in Benghazi, leaving four Americans dead including U.S. Ambassador Chris Stevens. "He knew generally what was deployed out there but as to specifics about time, etc., etc., he left that up to us." Two weeks ago when former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton testified about Benghazi, she said she was in contact with the White House about the attack throughout the night. Clinton testified she spoke to National Security Adviser Tom Donilon, then-CIA director Gen. David Petraeus, who had a compound in Benghazi, and the White House. She said U.S. officials participated in talks about what to do in a secure video conference with senior officials from the White House, the intelligence community and the Defense Department. "I spoke to President Obama later in the day," she said. As I've said since the beginning of this mess, those men were left to die that night and the President of the United States didn't bother to ask about details.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360272396916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:26:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360272486468-154</Id><Topic><Title>Being a Viet Nam Veterian gives domer special liar rights</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360265529401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:32:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45, Your actions are a disgrace to every American Veteran of all services!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360272486468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:28:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360272507875-155</Id><Topic><Title>787 lands at everett</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360264031729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:07:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were no batteries on board!</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1360272507875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:28:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360272588355-156</Id><Topic><Title>boeing stock price compared to the Dow Jones average</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360266200399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:43:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>speea next black eye for Boeing Chicago the outsource failure management team if its a787 it is not made in America !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360272588355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:29:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360272636391-157</Id><Topic><Title>Being a Viet Nam Veterian gives domer special liar rights</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360265529401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 14:32:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45, you disgrace teh uniform !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360272636391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:30:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360272700479-158</Id><Title>Wrong Battery</Title><Msg>Why are they using the most unstable lithium battery made, when there is Lithium Phosphate available with overcharge protection already incorporated in it's design. If they would have chose VLNC battery they may have saved millions and VLNC now bankrupt !!!! Sounds pretty fishy to me.</Msg><Username>capozzoli_louis</Username><Timestamp>1360272700479</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360272846169-159</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know, the "GD piece of paper" statement liberals keep using is a myth, liberals know it's a myth (or they're ignorant).......but they have to resort to myths when intellect in non-existent. I love it when the Kent Raven is reduced to using this myth as he has many times. However, you're right about the post office and constitution.......but when did Democrats ever start being concerned with what the constitution says?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360272846169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:34:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360272886746-160</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK...</Title><Msg>You said..."my actions are disgrace.....blah blah" u lie about boeing day after day -a great american company- that issues 170,000 paychecks weekly /biweekly whatever.to american workers -- and i am a disgrace for serving my country proudly during the 'nam conflict? my friend you are one low life piece of garbage. Now u can tos me one more time!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1360272886746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:34:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360273145274-161</Id><Title>Phantom Eye milestone</Title><Msg>ST. LOUIS, Feb. 7, 2013 -- Boeing's [NYSE: BA] liquid hydrogen-powered Phantom Eye unmanned aircraft system has completed taxi testing at Edwards Air Force Base in California as it progresses toward its second flight. During the testing, which occurred Feb. 6, the Phantom Eye demonstrator aircraft sitting atop its launch cart reached speeds up to 40 knots, or approximately 46 miles per hour. The Phantom Eye team has also completed software and hardware upgrades to prepare for flying at higher altitudes. "We upgraded the autonomous flight systems and have achieved all the required test points in preparation for the next flight," said Drew Mallow, Phantom Eye program manager. Additionally, the team improved the aircraft’s landing system following Phantom Eye's first flight, when the landing gear dug into the Edwards lakebed and broke.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360273145274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:39:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360273272325-162</Id><Title>What does a man with Honor act like ?</Title><Msg>Being a Viet Nam Veterian gives domer special liar rights by waynedickenson961.Feb 7, 2013 2:32 PM.Permalink . domerrrrr45, you dishonor every service person past, present and future with your behavior ! domerrrrr45 if you are a Viet Nam veteran that does not give you any liar rights , vulgar communication rights or criminal rights sorry ! domerrrrr45 on Feb 4 you state waynedick was a fired Boeing employee, on Feb 6, Domerrrrr45 , you state to waynedick "I thought you said ( to waynedick) u didnt work for boeing, now you claim u worked for 15 years. So first you make a false claim waynedickenson was a fired Boeing employee then two days later domerrrrr45 claims he thinks waynedickenson told domerrrrr45 that waynedickenson said he never worked for Boeing, you can't have it both ways . domerrrrr45, it is simple you are unaware that your lies catch up to you domerrrrr45 stop living in denial. BTW post your source for your claim that waynedickenson claimed he did not work for Boeing, cannot do that ! domerrrrr45 you claim to be a Viet Nam veteran so that gies you the right to be a liar too and a vulgarian who is a scofflaw. You might be a Viet Nam Veteran but you sure act like a criminal . Dormerrrrr45 in two days you make two false statement in continuing Yahoo TOS violation. about waynedickenson domerrrrr45by domerrrrr45.Feb 2, 2013 9:29 PM.Permalink.Go to topic TOS TOS TOS..SCARY! • Re: WAYNEDICK....BOEING domerrrrr45by domerrrrr45.Feb 4, 2013 8:23 AM.Permalink.Go to topic • Waynedick...u r a fired employee of boeing...expected! Sentiment: Strong Buy o 2users liked this posts6users disliked this posts o • Re: Re: Re: Re: scofflaw of the Boeing message board waynedickenson961by waynedickenson961.Feb 6, 2013 2:10 PM.Permalink.Go to topic domerrrrr45 , you said i thought u didn't work for boeing,now u claim u worked for 15y... domerrrrr45 , you said i thought u didn't work for boeing,now u claim u worked for 15years w/777 which one is it? BTW...boeing is still a great american company. Not withstanding your moronic garbage. domerrrrr45 please post any statement from me that indicates I did not work for Boeing? If not why are you making up stuff</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360273272325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:41:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360273333166-163</Id><Title>DHS Purchases 21.6 Million More Rounds of Ammunition</Title><Msg>The Department of Homeland Security is set to purchase a further 21.6 million rounds of ammunition to add to the 1.6 billion bullets it has already obtained over the course of the last 10 months alone, figures which have stoked concerns that the federal agency is preparing for civil unrest. A solicitation posted yesterday on the Fed Bid website details how the bullets are required for the DHS Federal Law Enforcement Training Center in Artesia, New Mexico. The solicitation asks for 10 million pistol cartridge .40 caliber 165 Grain, jacketed Hollow point bullets (100 quantities of 100,000 rounds) and 10 million 9mm 115 grain jacketed hollow point bullets (100 quantities of 100,000 rounds). The document also lists a requirement for 1.6 million pistol cartridge 9mm ball bullets (40 quantities of 40,000 rounds). An approximation of how many rounds of ammunition the DHS has now secured over the last 10 months stands at around 1.625 billion. In March 2012, ATK announced that they had agreed to provide the DHS with a maximum of 450 million bullets over four years, a story that prompted questions about why the feds were buying ammunition in such large quantities. In September last year, the federal agency purchased a further 200 million bullets. To put that in perspective, during the height of active battle operations in Iraq, US soldiers used 5.5 million rounds of ammunition a month. Extrapolating the figures, the DHS has purchased enough bullets over the last 10 months to wage a full scale war for almost 30 years. Such massive quantities of ammo purchases have stoked fears that the agency is preparing for some kind of domestic unrest. In 2011, Department of Homeland Security chief Janet Napolitano directed Immigration and Customs Enforcement to prepare for a mass influx of immigrants into the United States, calling for the plan to deal with the “shelter” and “processing” of large numbers of people. The federal agency’s primary concern is now centered around thwarting “homegrown terrorism,” but information produced and used by the DHS to train its personnel routinely equates conservative political ideology with domestic extremism.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273333166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:42:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360273440912-164</Id><Topic><Title>President should declare All African Americans are Tax Exempt !!!!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360273125063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:38:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Obama would only pay half taxes?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360273440912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:44:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360273588383-165</Id><Topic><Title>President should declare All African Americans are Tax Exempt !!!!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360273125063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:38:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh wait, his Kenyan father and ancestors were not slaves in America. Never mind.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360273588383</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:46:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360273779888-166</Id><Title>Obama:‘I Often Search Scripture to Figure Out How I Can Be a Better Man as Well as Better President'</Title><Msg>He should read the part about "thou shalt not lie"......over and over and over again.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273779888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:49:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360273942765-167</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven plagiarizes that statement too.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273942765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:52:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360274047533-168</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir, explain the retirement funding requirement for us, please.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1360274047533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:54:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360274228184-169</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate the Constitution so much?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1360274228184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:57:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360274390723-170</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Economic ignorance, a magnet for liberals. HAHA No truer words were ever spoken. What has to happen to further liberalism is for the liberal elites that want power..they have to turn basic Economic 101 commonsense understandings upside down..right is wrong, and get the masses of the uninformed to believe their economic falsehoods are true, and vote them in.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360274390723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:59:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360274509762-171</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not a myth, oh mighty yachtsman. The reporter had to repudiate it when his source at the meeting, no doubt "gotten to" by Boxarox or, scarier still, #$%$ Cheney, decided he should not have been quoted and backed out. Dealing with suddenly gutless sources is something every journalist has had to do. I once knew an engineer at Boeing I had to ask repeatedly on different stories if he was sure he wanted me to use this bit or that bit. My concern was that a higher-up would know he was the only guy who could have heard a particular utterance. However, this guy had the stones or the courage of his convictions -- and I don't think you would know about either of those.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360274509762</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:01:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360274925100-172</Id><Title>Uh Oh.....temp already dipping to 28 dgrees........</Title><Msg>....here in George Town. Oh wait a minute.....that 28 Celsius......that's 82 Degrees Fahrenheit . Let me know how the weather is up there in liberal land Boston tomorrow. Bring me another one of those rum and coconut liqueur tall ones please.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360274925100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:08:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360275053460-173</Id><Topic><Title>LMAO - MSNBC: Damn These Conservatives for Trying to "Kill the Post Office"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360271684920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or perhaps Congress simply thought "reasonable regulation" of the contitutionally protected US Postal service would be OK. Something like we want with keeping and bearing arms.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360275053460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:10:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360275105600-174</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Far More Popular than Obama</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244152051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:35:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Playwithyourself is probably already behind bars - if he isn't , he should be. People with obvious mental problems like he has should not be allowed to run around loose.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1360275105600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:11:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360275167867-175</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock a chart look</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360170682278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 12:11:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for the FBI team boeing the stock price is doing exactly what I predicted on feb 6, with 2 billion in stock buy back and to cover for the 787 black eye boeing is pumping any stockholders money by purchasing the BA stocks back, this is not making a investor any money in the long run but a good opportunity to get out or wait to the next level of resistance-support at $79.13 if Boeing were to clear that price and go to 85 and hold it would be a buy but so far both the DOW and the S and P averages are much better than Boeing for a year Dow is up over 8% sand and p is up over 11% while Boeing is up now 2.5% for a year better than flat but not as good as the Dow average ! on the 787-"WASHINGTON, Feb 7 (Reuters) - An air safety investigation of a battery fire on a Boeing Co 787 Dreamliner last month has narrowed the source to one of the battery's eight cells, though the actual cause of the fire is not yet known, the head of the National Transportation Safety Board said on Thursday. Regulators should now reconsider the assumptions used to certify the plane's lithium-ion batteries, Deborah Hersman said at a news conference in Washington, adding to the uncertainty of when the cutting-edge plane might be cleared to fly again.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360275167867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:12:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360275396039-176</Id><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Msg>From (Left-Wing) Ask Fact Check.Org Q: Did President Bush call the Constitution a #$%$ piece of paper"? A: Extremely unlikely. The Web site that reported those words has a history of quoting phony sources and retracting bogus stories. FULL QUESTION Is it true that President Bush called the Constitution a #$%$ piece of paper?" He has never denied it, and it appears that there were several witnesses. FULL ANSWER The report that Bush "screamed" those words at Republican congressional leaders in November 2005 is unsubstantiated, to put it charitably. We judge that the odds that the report is accurate hover near zero. It comes from Capitol Hill Blue, a Web site that has a history of relying on phony sources, retracting stories and apologizing to its readers. Update, Feb. 21, 2011: The author of the Capitol Hill Blue story has now withdrawn it. Doug Thompson messaged us to say: Doug Thompson: This is to let you know that the piece on Bush and the Constitution has been changed and reads: "This article was based on sources that we thought, at the time, were reliable. We have since discovered reasons to doubt their veracity. For that reason, this article has been removed from our database." I no longer stand behind that article or its conclusions and have said so in answers to several recent queries. In addition, I have asked that it be removed from a documentary film. Thompson elaborated on what led him to retract his story in an item posted on his website Jan. 1, 2011. He also noted that an earlier article, in which he had referred to Bush as a "madman," has been removed from the site entirely. The Quote The report was posted on Dec. 5, 2005. According to author, Doug Thompson, unnamed Republican leaders complained to Bush during a White House meeting about "onerous" portions of the USA Patriot Act, prompting the following: Capitol Hill Blue: “I don’t give a #$%$,” Bush retorted. “I’m the President and the Commander-in-Chief. Do it my way.” “Mr. President,” one aide in the meeting said. “There is a valid case that the provisions in this law undermine the Constitution.” “Stop throwing the Constitution in my face,” Bush screamed back. “It’s just a #$%$ piece of paper!” The Evidence There’s no record of Bush ever using these words in public and no other news organization has reported him using them privately. Thompson based his report on three sources whom he didn’t name. He gave the date of the quote as "last month," which would put it sometime in November 2005. Thompson told us he once removed the story from his Web site when others raised doubts and no other news organization came up with a similar story. But he said he later reinstated it and currently believes it to be true. "I wrote the story and I stand by it," Thompson said in a telephone interview. Thompson told us he based the story on e-mail messages from three persons he knows, all of whom claim to have been present at a White House meeting and to have heard Bush make the statement. He said he finds their account credible: "Sometimes I just have to go with my gut, and my gut tells me he did say this." The Unreliable Gut Thompson’s "gut" has proven to be a unreliable guide in the past, however. He has admitted quoting trusted sources in the past who later turned out to be frauds — twice. In 2003 Thompson confessed that he had been "conned big time" by a source who claimed to be a former CIA contract consultant named Terrance J. Wilkinson. Thompson quoted this "source" as claiming to be present at two White House meetings in which Bush ignored intelligence officials’ doubts about reports of Iraq seeking uranium. Thompson said he had been relying on the same man for two decades and had "no doubt" about his credibility, only to discover that "someone has been running a con on me for 20 some years and I fell for it like a little old lady in a pigeon drop scheme." He erased a number of stories from the site that had been based on information from "Wilkinson" and deleted anonymous quotes given to him by "Wilkinson" from other stories. Thompson said then: "It will be a long time (and perhaps never) before I trust someone else who comes forward and offers inside information. The next one who does had better be prepared to produce a birth certificate, a driver’s license and his grandmother’s maiden name." That was two years before the "piece of paper" quote attributed to three unnamed sources. But, far from demanding solid proof, Thompson continued to quote at least one more phony source until 2006, when a blogger started to question the existence of "George Harleigh." Thompson had for years quoted this supposed former Nixon and Bush appointee. But when no records of such a man could be found, Thompson admitted he had never even met him:</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360275527545-177</Id><Topic><Title>What does a man with Honor act like ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360273272325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:41:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domer use those communication skills you fought for , we all want to know more about waynedickenson, please tell us all about it</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360275527545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:18:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360275588695-178</Id><Topic><Title>DHS Purchases 21.6 Million More Rounds of Ammunition</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273333166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They should put them to good use and go after people who like to avoid taxes by stashing their money in the Cayman islands while they sit around playing with their tube steaks and little US flag pins made in China.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360275588695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:19:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360275765025-179</Id><Title>Boeing up 34% stock holders up 2.5%</Title><Msg>Boeing paid the CEO 34% more last year for meeting weak performance goals and the owners fo the company the shareholders just finally broke above flat and are up 2.5% for a year while the rest of the Dow is up over 8% and the s and p average is up over 11% not so good for the shareholders</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360275765025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:22:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360276623581-180</Id><Topic><Title>USE (((EIPC))) tech for batteries in the dreamliner</Title><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1359083656473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 22:14:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>boeing is finally taking action on batteries</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1360276623581</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:37:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360276659445-181</Id><Title>NSTB the 787 fire failure issue has a "long road ahead"</Title><Msg>Feb 7 (Reuters) - U.S. safety regulators have a "long road ahead" in their investigation of problems associated with the lithium ion batteries on Boeing Co's 787 Dreamliners. National Transportation Safety Board head Deborah Hersman said at a press conference that the agency's "interim factual report" that will be filed in 30 days will not mark the conclusion of the investigation. Hersman said the NTSB has pinpointed the origin of a battery fire on a 787 in Boston last month, but has not yet determined the cause of a short circuit in that battery. The 50 Dreamliners in service have been grounded since Jan. 16 while the NTSB, FAA and other aviation regulators around the world investigate the battery failures</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360276659445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:37:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360276689675-182</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And to go way back to 1994-1995 we have this bit of flapdoodle by SPEEA Seattle Professional Engineering Employees Association September 2, 1994 No, 1526 COMPANY ADDRESSES 1989 LUMP SUM/RETIREMENT ISSUE As reported in a prior SPEEA Newsletter (Issue #1504, March 18, 1994), the 10% lump sum payment made in December 1989 will be dropped from The a[ternate benefit retirement calculation for those retiring January 1, 1995 and later. The final average earnings (FAE) value used in the alternate benefit formula only includes lump sum payments made in the five years prior to retirement. While this dropping of lump sum payments from the retirement calculation after five year has always occurred, the size of the lump sum payment dropped (10%) and the lack of a replacement lump sum payment in December 1994 results in a temporary reduction in the alternate benefit formula calculation. Subsequent increased credited service and 60 month final average earnings eventually recoup the reduction after three to five months of additional service (the exact amount depends on an individual’s circumstances). Upon review of this situation, Boeing has determined an employee’s benefit at retirement will not be less than the benefit the employee would have received if retirement had occurred at an earlier date. The effect of this interpretation is that the retirement benefit under the alternate benefit formula for an employee retiring sometime between December 1994 and early 1995 will generally be constant from one month to the next. By April or May, 1995, the alternate benefit retirement amount will resume its upward trend as a result of an employee’s increased service and final average earnings computation. +++ So what happened without fanfare was that Boeing in March of 1995 kicked off the Special retiremet bit- losing 9500 senior employees in the process. They added 5 years to credited service and up to 5 years of age in the formula ( same formula today ) and required all volunteers to be gone by JULY 1, 1995. ( such as yours truly ) Well about 3 years later, I discovered the bit about flatlining and guess what. It turned out that the addition of 5 years of credited service made up almost exactly for the 5 to 6 months of flatlining. ( no increase in pension for 5 to 6 months ) . So in effect, those who retired broke even with what they were supposed to get under ERISA. But the SPEEA mensas then and now never really figured out what happened. Thus the charade goes on . So what SPEEA claims they offered to Boeing as a ' fix" for the levelling bit- is the right idea- but totally wrong to the point that BA could NOT accept it as being a violation of ERISA, etc. So what is a a reasonable fix. IT takes EXPERTISE to handle the details, but ONE possibility is to simply state that the MINIMUM rate of increase re credited service be calculated as the base rate ( say $85/month/year of credited service ) figured out something like $85/2000 or 4.25 CENTS PER CREDITED HOUR OF SERVICE. The 2000 comes from the 2000 limit hours = 1 year credited service under bcerp The exact wording is critical - takes expertise- and first class ERISA lawyers to work out. SPEEA can afford to hire such- but they refuse to do so- claiming the STAFF knows ALL. So 2/3 of to be retirees in the next 4 years will get hosed out of 2 to 3 months of pension growth EVERY year- just as has been going on since the 90's</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360276689675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:38:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360276773280-183</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing up 34% stock holders up 2.5%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360275765025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:22:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"long road ahead" per NSTB on solving the 787 fire per Feb 7 reuters report</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360276773280</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360276830847-184</Id><Topic><Title>NSTB the 787 fire failure issue has a "long road ahead"</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360276659445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:37:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>team Boeing FBI we are all ready for your reply or comments any good news</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360276830847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:40:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360276872571-185</Id><Topic><Title>Expand 787 Battery Search to Chargers</Title><Username>ypresian</Username><Timestamp>1360270441943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:54:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very interesting</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1360276872571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:41:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360277197474-186</Id><Topic><Title>DHS Purchases 21.6 Million More Rounds of Ammunition</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273333166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason we are buying all the ammo for the DHS is that we are going to have to clean out a bunch of home grown terrorists sooner or later maybe the next time a black man is elected president or some similar incident and they try to take the law into their own hands. We did it before in 1865 and we can do it again</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360277197474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:46:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360277336428-187</Id><Topic><Title>USE (((EIPC))) tech for batteries in the dreamliner</Title><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1359083656473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-24 22:14:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>test flight begin hope they find the issues</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1360277336428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:48:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360277394191-188</Id><Topic><Title>Expand 787 Battery Search to Chargers</Title><Username>ypresian</Username><Timestamp>1360270441943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:54:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>test flights begin.. hey are checking the battery systems...</Msg><Username>seetheworldsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1360277394191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:49:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360277810390-189</Id><Topic><Title>DHS Purchases 21.6 Million More Rounds of Ammunition</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273333166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"we are going to have to clean out a bunch of home grown terrorists" Indeed, nuts like Tim McVeigh, and nuts like Spartakook here in this forum.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1360277810390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:56:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360277823152-190</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It makes very good sense for Obama to say something like that about the Constitution given his desire for a fascist approach to governing. The Constitution gets in Obama's way. Bush? No, conservatives believe very strongly in a strict interpretation of the constitution. The constitution benefits their desire for a free society, and an economy that promotes the health and welfare of all of our citizens.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360277823152</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:57:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360277905569-191</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Far More Popular than Obama</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244152051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:35:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gun control is an issue that the American people can only settle. Government meddling into the Constitution is always a bad idea. Nobody takes my guns! Too many Lib Roaches always spoil it for the majority with their pious, better than thou, BS! Get back to Berkeley where you belong. You don't belong in the real world.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360277905569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:58:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360278323057-192</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing up 34% stock holders up 2.5%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360275765025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:22:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will the FAA wait for the final NTSB report or are they going to recertify before then? Aren't they independent?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360278323057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:05:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360278433634-193</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir, is this the first time you showed the Fact Check dot Org recount to Genna or did you make him aware of it in the past?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360278433634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:07:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360278636635-194</Id><Topic><Title>Expand 787 Battery Search to Chargers</Title><Username>ypresian</Username><Timestamp>1360270441943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 15:54:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would want to instrument and flight test one or both of the two aircraft that exhibited the battery problems. Also add a form of fire suppression as part of the flight test instrumentation for additional safety. A thorough sneak-path analysis and failure modes analysis on the battery systems are hopefully in-process.</Msg><Username>augie_the_gasman</Username><Timestamp>1360278636635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:10:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360278727928-195</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey honeybuns, what's goin' on? I thought I'd let you know that that lisp of yours has become much more prominent in recent days! You should have your estrogen levels checked, they might be a tad high! :))</Msg><Username>alangonquins_loverboy</Username><Timestamp>1360278727928</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:12:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360278933368-196</Id><Topic><Title>Remembering The Real Ronald Reagan</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360275307133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:15:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His brain was like Swiss cheese, riddled with the holes of Alzheimer's, so he couldn't think or lead, but he was just the nicest guy! And SOOOO overrated!</Msg><Username>engineer_eds_buttplug</Username><Timestamp>1360278933368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:15:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360279024637-197</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've brought it to his attention several times. He likes to use propaganda and is oblivious to evidence and facts.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360279024637</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:17:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360279299706-198</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know a person that worked at Scott Paper(which is now out of business) and they implemented the no pension plan for new hires(401K instead). It took about 3 to 4 years when the 401K participants outnumbered the pension folks. It was all about 401K discussions in all the contract after that once they reached the majority of people in the 401K plan, Pension people had no chance at that point for negotiations in the future contracts.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360279299706</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:21:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360279425788-199</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz - Wiki isn't even an acceptable source at my kids high school. You believe Genna's #$%$ because of all the conditioning you've gone through in swallowing all of Obama's #$%$ hook line and sinker. So of course you believe it. We all knew you would. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360279425788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:23:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360279744673-200</Id><Title>Boeing and Research and Motion</Title><Msg>First good question ronanderson727 FAA -NSTB. rather than get bogged down on Boeing stock as you know I booked profits on a short term and a long term stock total gain was 115.5% no investor cared to ask me what I did with that money , a few days ago. I used the stock chart and went with all that gain into BBRY, the stock recently hit s short term bottom and for 12 days traded flat , then on 2 Feb it broke above the MA for 50 days at $13.42 and held, so that was a buy signal and in the next four days on incresing volume, but not greater volume every day(bad) it has gone to 16.96 at from a %K break out over the %D at 46% to today at 55% so with less volume and with a next resistance point at $17.67 and a close term high of $18.12 it is getting time to book profits or reduce my number of shares to what I have made on the other guys money. so far rather than getting bogged down with boing up 2.5% for the year and the worry about FAA or NSTB the SPEEA potential strike I moved my trad money to BBRY. Ronanderson727 you are right about AAPL since Steve Jobs died the stock has come back from the 6000% gain and is no longer a stock for me. However as Steve Jobs said make the best product and you will be ok. BBRY is good , 787 is 3.7years late 33 billion over budget and now grounded and below its trade group the Dow Jones up over 8% for one year . I treat stocks as a business decision not a opinion for future growth or better performance the investors who have the opinion that long term Boeing will see you their at 150 or the investors that look back to 1966 and point out that when Boeing was a 100% American engineered and parts built plane and the stock was 182 dollars forget why . Airbus did not have 50% market share and the Boeing was a Seattle based American maker of the best product like APPLE used to be , now it is managed by a type of CEO like Boeing who wants to file lawsuits and waste shareholder money and wants to make huge up front pay . Steve Jobs as you know took 1 dollar per year and made his money on stock price appreciation. So today FFRY did not trade 30% of the volume in the first hour and I am making a business decison to stay in but have a sell at the low of today and will adjust the stock price sell up if it holds tomorrow to $17.62 as I am up about 20% so far in just 4 days and have some wiggle room. waynedickenson</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360279744673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:29:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360279806729-201</Id><Topic><Title>DHS Purchases 21.6 Million More Rounds of Ammunition</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273333166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:42:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't pick on Tim McVeigh. A decorated veteran, Republican, NRA mamber.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1360279806729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360279924210-202</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and Research and Motion</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360279744673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:29:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FFRY should be BBRY typo error</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360279924210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:32:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360280919612-203</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and Research and Motion</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360279744673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:29:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ronanderson727, BBRY is a classic chart trade it made the first part of the W formation on 1-31-2013 at $12.98 and it is now moving up to the first of the middle of the w formation and that is why I am monitoring the price , it may stop and pull back a sell for me, or it could break out but there is less of a chance as volume is declining. . If it breaksdown I will sell and hope for a asending W for the next buy back, and get back in. If it breaks above $18..33 the near term high , unless on strong volume, I will sell or set very tight sell orders and walk up with it. My guess is it will pull back soon and build or go down. I would prefer a drop to an asending w formation and then another push up . Wayneanderson .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360280919612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:48:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360280921319-204</Id><Title>787 test flights approved</Title><Msg>From Joshua Reed, AP Boeing won permission on Thursday for test flights of its 787 as it tries to fix battery problems that have kept the plane grounded. The Federal Aviation Administration said the test flights will have restrictions, including pre-flight testing and inspections, and in-flight monitoring. The tests are limited to airspace over unpopulated areas. Boeing said the tests will begin "soon" on one of the six airplanes it used for testing before the 787 was certified by the FAA in late 2011. It said the batteries will get a pre-flight inspection, and battery-related status messages will be monitored. The plane, labeled ZA005, was seen on the ground at Boeing Field near Seattle with stairs leading to the two cargo doors near where the two batteries are housed, KING 5 TV reported on Tuesday. Boeing said that flying the plane will allow it to test the in-flight performance of its batteries and generate data to help the investigations. "The company has marshaled an extensive team of hundreds of experts and they are working around the clock focused on resolving the 787 battery issue and returning the 787 fleet to full flight status," Boeing said Thursday. It didn't say how many test flights are planned.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360280921319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:48:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360280993661-205</Id><Topic><Title>What does a man with Honor act like ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360273272325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:41:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpity for the man who should make a commnet we all know who you are</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360280993661</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:49:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360281128378-206</Id><Title>Voltage and heat is the key to the battery problems</Title><Msg>A better measurment of these two systems, than in the past, is the key to preventing further problems and will isolate the main problem. Be it a battery or the charging system. Myself, I feel it is a charging system malfunction.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1360281128378</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:52:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360281365045-207</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. I'm not sure what Genna has to gain by pretending that Bush said something that can't be corroborated and thus is NOT FACT. I thought Genna was a journalist and knew better but apparently he wasn't a professional journalist or even a decent journalist if he believes innuendo and a falsehood and keeps repeating it.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360281365045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360281651236-208</Id><Title>A free people can only afford to make this mistake once.</Title><Msg>...giving up their weapons to a Tyranical Government</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360281651236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:00:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360281681335-209</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad to think that after all of CG's service valor and the opportunity that presented itself to him because of it, he has become a typical Dimbecile!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1360281681335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:01:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360281683429-210</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ali_infesto, wiki allows people to correct it. Do you have a problem with the facts?</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1360281683429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:01:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360281730375-211</Id><Topic><Title>787 test flights approved</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360280921319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:48:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Songwriters: SONDHEIM, STEPHEN SEND IN THE CLOWNS !! Isn't it rich? Are we a pair? Me here at last on the ground, You in mid-air.. Where are the clowns? ++++ In the corner offices in Chicago ???</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360281730375</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:02:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360281803847-212</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BrokeDik: "written by Kurt Nimmo | December 10 2005" Point of Order BrokeDik....Kurt Nimmo writes for Prison Planet and InfoWars a Alex Jones web site....I thought they were ...how did you put it..."discredited"...There is no end to your hypocrisy</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360281803847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:03:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282010276-213</Id><Topic><Title>What does a man with Honor act like ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360273272325</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:41:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he can live without your approval. The average rodent could live without your approval.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1360282010276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282018344-214</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are naive. Even when a person has been shown to be a serial abuser of editing Wiki won't correct the situation. Some of the Science information is good but the political stuff is garbage. The bottom line in journalism is corroborating evidence and there is none in this matter but Hooz and Genna still accept #$%$ as fact.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360282018344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:06:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282183100-215</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I'm saying your full of #$%$ for believing Genna's lie about Bush saying the Constitution was just a GD piece of paper.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360282183100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:09:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282237165-216</Id><Topic><Title>We see $60 (&amp; probably lower) before we ever see $80</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1358184666247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:31:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how is that short to $60 working out for you?????? when will you cover?? $80? $90? $100. I am up nearly 5% because I ignored the noise on this board and the media. The batteries are a NON issue.</Msg><Username>rwh4fshg</Username><Timestamp>1360282237165</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:10:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282308096-217</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and Research and Motion</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360279744673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:29:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumitidy for BBRY</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360282308096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:11:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282447806-218</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing up 34% stock holders up 2.5%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360275765025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:22:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumitidy for 34% for the Boeing CEO and 2.5% for the stockholders , does the CEO loose sleep trying to figure a way to change pensions for the loyal SPEEA workers ,no he sleeps fine as he has a 100% funded 22 million dollar pension to go along with his 34% pay increase.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360282447806</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:14:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282577837-219</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump bump bump</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360282577837</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360282721549-220</Id><Topic><Title>Of Course Bush Said It...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360282323862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:12:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course you're a useful idiot operating on motivated irrationality and void of any corroborated evidence or facts, but thanks for reminding us.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360282721549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:18:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360282821180-221</Id><Title>787 test flight -are mutually exclusive for787 deliveries</Title><Msg>Feb 7 (Reuters) - U.S. safety regulators have a "long road ahead" in their investigation of problems associated with the lithium ion batteries on Boeing Co's 787 Dreamliners. National Transportation Safety Board head Deborah Hersman said at a press conference that the agency's "interim factual report" that will be filed in 30 days will not mark the conclusion of the investigation. Hersman said the NTSB has pinpointed the origin of a battery fire on a 787 in Boston last month, but has not yet determined the cause of a short circuit in that battery. The 50 Dreamliners in service have been grounded since Jan. 16 while the NTSB, FAA and other aviation regulators around the world investigate the battery failures.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360282821180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:20:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360283142762-222</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>vierzig_nachten, you mean you noticed the Boeing Management team was being less than 100% honest in their offer. How can you tell, oh , right- their lips were moving ! SPEEA should make a counter offer gie SPEEA a 34% pay raise and a 22 million per employee pension like the Boeing CEO or keep the last contract without any take away poison pills, that will be used just as soon as the members accept that offer</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360283142762</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:25:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360283281634-223</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir: "The Raven likes to use propaganda and is oblivious to evidence and facts." Not exactly news to anyone on he board Mir....</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360283281634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:28:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360283816688-224</Id><Topic><Title>President should declare All African Americans are Tax Exempt !!!!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360273125063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:38:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which Father are we referring to...Barrack Obama Sr, Lolo Soetoro or Frank Marshall Davis....any of which...at one time or another are acknowledged as the Father or our "My Administration will be the most open in history..President".</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360283816688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:36:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360283962956-225</Id><Title>Engineer opinion of the lithium battery on any airplane</Title><Msg>research of a few articles about lithium batteries combined to a conclusion as follows.1 ( from a engineer who designs airplane charging systems)"An unambiguous safety standard for the use of lithium battery or charging system systems on any airplane and the potential for a fire cause may not be found anytime soon. As a person that designs and works with lithium batteries and that designs charging and protection systems for them. I have the opinion, that with the current state of the art , lithium batteries have no place in manned aircraft For safety of flight , only. when a lithium battery is designed that can build a cell that fails to a safe condition, like other technologies-but not before., then it is safe, to use on any airplane and not before that design , is the lithium battery a safe application for electrical power.". The followwing is a group of statements about the 787, Boeing management, the problem of a fire on a 787. and general aerospace expert opinions. The engineering is not the most flawed aspect concerning the Boeing 787, this battery problem is is a symptom of the route cause for the 787 delay and excessive build cost. . It is the management of Boeing, the FAA and now the NTSB that apparently cannot be counted on to make wise risk/benefit decisions. Boeing management and their flunky’s first make up their minds , then seek underlings to support that decision. Anyone that objects or raises issues is pushed to the side while the sycophants grab the spotlight, at least until a patsy is needed to take the fall for unaware management decisions The new rules allow the shipment of lithium ion batteries weighing as much as 77 pounds, but only if they are aircraft batteries. Shipments of other lithium ion batteries greater than 11 pounds are still prohibited. The exemption makes no sense; it is a follow the money rule. The 787's two batteries weigh 63 pounds each. So if the standards need to be modified to allow the 787 to fly then instead of passenger safety, the money principal is used. Lithium-ion batteries can short circuit and ignite if they are improperly packaged damaged or has manufacturing defects. Fires involving rechargeable lithium-ion batteries can reach 1,100 degrees, close to the melting point of aluminum, or any other component that makes up a airplane, including aluminum. a key material in the construction of most airplanes the idea that smoke can be vented outside a burning battery box on a flying 787 ignores the actual cause of the ensuing crash . While the smoke can be vented a lithium fire of 1000 degrees in the vented battery section of the 787 is a crash condition at a rate of 100% . if the plane cannot land on a ground based landing strip, then on an emergency basis and over the ocean. , Since the landing strip is the ocean. You need the Sullenberger landing training at a 100% success rate, for all 787 pilots and a waiting group of rescue boats, for any out of control fire. The only realistic ocean landing would be a Chesley "Sully" Sullenberger, a former US Airways pilot famed for his precision flying that enabled passengers and crew to survive an emergency landing on the Hudson River in New York, he said in an interview that he wouldn't be comfortable flying an airliner that carried lithium ion aircraft batteries in its cargo hold. The potential for self-ignition, for uncontained fires, is huge," he said. The new regulations "need to be looked at very hard in the cold light of day, particularly with what has happened with the 787 batteries." Previously, U.S. regulations prohibited the shipment of lithium ion batteries on passenger planes in packages weighing more than 11 pounds, although heavier batteries could be shipped on cargo planes. The batteries are suspected of causing or contributing to the severity of an onboard fire that led to the September 2010 crash of a United Parcel Service plane near Dubai, killing both pilots. The two pilots of another UPS plane barely managed to escape the aircraft before it was consumed by fire moments after landing in Philadelphia in 2006. The combination of Boeing management ears wide closed , enabling FAA and NTSB self audit for Boeing and follow the money plan results in failure.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360283962956</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:39:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360284517288-226</Id><Title>Downgraded</Title><Msg>Looks like it's bend downgraded. Should sink below 75 soon enough.</Msg><Username>mrlarry626</Username><Timestamp>1360284517288</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:48:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360285100527-227</Id><Topic><Title>President should declare All African Americans are Tax Exempt !!!!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360273125063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:38:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is another post that wasn't necessary</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360285100527</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:58:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360285181082-228</Id><Topic><Title>We see $60 (&amp; probably lower) before we ever see $80</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1358184666247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:31:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks sometimes there are some sane posts on this board</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1360285181082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 19:59:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360285655962-229</Id><Topic><Title>Remembering The Real Ronald Reagan</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360275307133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:15:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of school, the offer to pay for the ESL class for you still stands. Get help. Your life doesn't have to be like this.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1360285655962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:07:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360286749584-230</Id><Title>Should ee $78-$79 tomorrow!!!!! Those $77.50 Calls where a steal!</Title><Msg>This is fun now........ let's hope!</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1360286749584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:25:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360286982181-231</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Far More Popular than Obama</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244152051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:35:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody wants your guns, sd. And you have no say in who belongs in the real world. Outside of that, you might have raised good points. But there weren't any.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360286982181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:29:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360287419517-232</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Far More Popular than Obama</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360244152051</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 08:35:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats funny, thats what Himmler said............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360287419517</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:36:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360287591883-233</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you making threats?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360287591883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:39:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360288092405-234</Id><Topic><Title>We see $60 (&amp; probably lower) before we ever see $80</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1358184666247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-14 12:31:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>60 maybe after a 2 for 1 split. You shorts are insane to say the least. LMFAO all the way to the bank</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1360288092405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:48:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360288649634-235</Id><Topic><Title>President should declare All African Americans are Tax Exempt !!!!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360273125063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:38:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and Brain Free!!!!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360288649634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 20:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360289073493-236</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:‘I Often Search Scripture to Figure Out How I Can Be a Better Man as Well as Better President'</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273779888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:49:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone who would believe that would have to be black. Just a casual observation and years of experience dealing with integration.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360289073493</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:04:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360290020274-237</Id><Title>january deliveries</Title><Msg>39 commercial planes 32 737's 1 767. 6 777's. Defense deliveries: 1 P-8 6 Apaxhe (new) 2 Apache (remanufactured) 1 C-17. 2 Chinook (new) 2 chinook (refurb) 4 F18 6 Haarpoon 3 V22 bodies.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360290020274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:20:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360290065656-238</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:‘I Often Search Scripture to Figure Out How I Can Be a Better Man as Well as Better President'</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360273779888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:49:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This guy BO hangs around the liberal hollywood bunch so much he thinks he's an actor. Remember Slick Willy's acting? He was shown at a funeral for some dignitary crying with an eye on the tv network camera. As soon as the camera turned away Slick started yucking it up. BO wants to be in that class with Slick.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360290065656</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:21:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360290989948-239</Id><Topic><Title>President should declare All African Americans are Tax Exempt !!!!</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360273125063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 16:38:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So is your Unimaginative and endless, answer to everything..namely... Race baiting..People are now immune to that propaganda</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360290989948</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:36:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360291154774-240</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven Continues Myth</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360275396039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 17:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"what does Breitbart mean"?..."no I really Don't know" ?</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360291154774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360291454898-241</Id><Title>Notice Obamas attack on the second amendment has completly BAcKFIRED</Title><Msg>Can you imagine Obame making a fabricated Photo of him SKEETSHOOTING one day after Newton ? Can you imagine Piers Morgan going to a Texas Gun Shop to get a photo of him shooting at the range ONE DAY AFTER NEWTON ? ...... Kudos to Ted Nugent, Larry Pratt, Alex Jones and the millions of Real Americans who drew a line in the sand....and will have to continue to do so.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360291454898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:44:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360291628314-242</Id><Topic><Title>Sparty and the nutjobs are at it again</Title><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1360259226309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 12:47:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey...Ye of not a single ounce of journalistic integrity.....I googled the words as ordered...the words "Sparty" and "Alex Jones" were nowhere to be found in the article. No wonder you got your A_$_$ canned !!!!</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360291628314</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:47:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360292643971-243</Id><Title>WHY LEGAL IMMIGRANTS MAKE THE BEST PATRIOTS !!</Title><Msg>GOOGLE: "Citizen Presents Eloquent Defense of 2nd Amendment Before Bureaucrats:" Video The best Patriots and those who understand what its like to live under communism are LEGAL IMMIGRANTS...and a legal immigrant gives an eye watering, goose pimple producingly eloquent defense of the second amendment to misguided politicians.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360292643971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:04:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360292764720-244</Id><Title>Down 100x arrests here and Up 10x kills there</Title><Msg>It was interesting listening to Brennan being grilled today by the Senate for confirmation as the nominee for CIA director. He was absolutely convinced that interrogation techniques, such as water boarding, are simply something that we should not be doing. He opined something to do with our values. OK I get the morality argument. But what doesn't seem to make sense is the following: 1) the Obama administration has captured and interrogated precisely "one" person (down from about a few hundred by Bush) related to terrorism; and 2) the Obama administration has increased the number of drone strikes by a factor ten to kill the suspected terrorists. So, a reasonable person might ask the following: if Obama is not interrogating anyone, how is he getting the information needed to kill folks by tenfold over Bush?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1360292764720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:06:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360293383549-245</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, it appears you do know alot about how the retirement benifits work. In my earlier post, putting new hires into a 401K instead of a pension plan will eventually cause a "no leverage position" in negotions on the pension plan benifits on future contracts once the 401K people are the majority. Pension plan benefits could be frozen reguardless of the inflation/econimic conditions. (leverage is a bad choice of words on my part, but cannot come up with another word that most fits the situation) I have no misunderstanding that this is the way things are headed(401K) with all retirement benifits with all companies, and I understand their reasoning, but current employees should know about how this could possibly affect their benefits unless the are within a few years of retiring,</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360293383549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:16:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360293524123-246</Id><Topic><Title>Notice Obamas attack on the second amendment has completly BAcKFIRED</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360291454898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Remember, the Obama administration openly claims the right to order the execution of American citizens without trial, without evidence and without any due process. A President who would justify those actions could justify anything, including nationwide gun confiscation, forced FEMA camp round-ups of citizens, military troops on the streets of U.S. cities and so on. Obama believes there is NO LIMIT to his power, and as a result he is, by definition, a totalitarianistic tyrant. But Obama does not have the loyalty of the military, nor the sheriffs, nor most police departments. He is absolutely hated by gun owners and political conservatives. His circle of followers is weak and shrinking by the day. His political supporters are largely inner city welfare recipients who, as history has shown, matter little in the equation of human history."</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360293524123</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 22:18:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360296335626-247</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA Contract Vote</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1360235467235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 06:11:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U said . . .but current employees should know about how this could possibly affect their benefits unless the are within a few years of retiring,.. SPEEAs put on that issue Is IMO basically correct- the 401k is a slippery slope as you mention. However, I see - hear NO indication that SPEEA has tried to give/present a reasonable alternative that MIGHT be acceptable to Boeing. In very general terms which I have tried to put across to many in the sPEEA camp ( difficult being the designated PITA) SPEEA could have offered a choice between the BCERP and PVP plan for all employees when they leave. While the PVP plan has some warts- lets NOT forget that BA had pushed it several years ago, and for many of the younger, it could be a better deal. I pushed that for 4 years in the annual meetings via a shareholder proposal ( approved by the SEC over BA objections ) and got 40 to 60 million votes in favor ( 8 to 12 percent ) but NO real help from SPEEA. The reason ? simple At that time the Boff was not in favor- and refused to get or use expert help. When he discoverd that the PVP plan would also give HIM and some SPEEA staff UNLIMITED credited service - he then pushed SPEEA into making a trade ( 2005) - But at that time, the legality of the plan and the whack to older employees was hidden from the team. At a council meeting in 2005 as negotiations were in play- I spoke against it except AS A CHOICE- and when the word got around - the emaiil storm caused him ( the team was totally subservient to BOFF ) had to back off the 100 percent trade And the rest is history I still believe it would be a viable choice to present to BA IF it was done in a knowledgeable and professional manner- and with Goforth and Kempf in charge, that is not likely to happen. UNLess the members suggest and demand expert help - and a close review by them of the old frankenstien movies showing torches and pitchforks !!!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360296335626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 23:05:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360297688962-248</Id><Title>The Justice Departments justifies assasination of US citizens...No Judge No Jury</Title><Msg>From Survivial Acres Today’s news is a good case in point: The U.S. Justice Department claims that “drones strikes against Americans are legal“. In an unbelievable twist of poor logic and self-interest, the Justice Department claims: “A lawful killing in self-defense is not an assassination,” the white paper reads. “In the Department’s view, a lethal operation conducted against a U.S. citizen whose conduct poses an imminent threat of violent attack against the United States would be a legitimate act of national self-defense that would not violate the assassination ban. Similarly, the use of lethal force, consistent with the laws of war, against an individual who is a legitimate military target would be lawful and would not violate the assassination ban.” Constitutional protections are of course, entirely absent. The only thing standing in the way is a “high level official” who can arbitrarily “decide” who lives and who dies, even ”even if there is no intelligence indicating they are engaged in an active plot to attack the U.S.“. There’s more of this idiocy: “The condition that an operational leader present an ‘imminent’ threat of violent attack against the United States does not require the United States to have clear evidence that a specific attack on U.S. persons and interests will take place in the immediate future,” So in the absence of evidence, and in direct violation of the assassination ban (as if that ever mattered), Americans can now be killed by drones. Bear in mind, that the government has refused to reveal any “evidence” that it has regarding its actions. We’re supposed to “trust them” with this lack of disclosure and reason. Why should we do this? What justification do we possibly have that they have can be trusted? Who gave this government the right to arbitrarily decide who lives and who dies? Did you?</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360297688962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 23:28:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360297756604-249</Id><Topic><Title>Notice Obamas attack on the second amendment has completly BAcKFIRED</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360291454898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Charlton Heston was a Hillbilly in a land of Mickey Moore's in Hollywood. You are the demented loon.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360297756604</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 23:29:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360298275170-250</Id><Topic><Title>Notice Obamas attack on the second amendment has completly BAcKFIRED</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360291454898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 21:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont be so hard Joe...BrokeDik_Hertz is More of a Cult member then a loon....incapable of any independent thought...regurgitating CNN and MSNBC talking points....thats all</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1360298275170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 23:37:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>