<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358573345233-1</Id><Topic><Title>What has the NRA done for America !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358548136299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:28:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS - lets see the link</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358573345233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:29:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358573757399-2</Id><Topic><Title>Iran needs to be nuclear armed to save itself</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358545571910</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 16:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mining_phd, You know that in love and war everything is allowed right!. Libya, was taken from the people by war style tactics, and right or wrong returned (hopefully to the people by war). This nation USA, does lie all the time, yes the USA does lie. An agribusiness I know of actually had a marine employed as a HR manager, he was working for a closely held corporation a dad and two sons in a project located in lybia. The father was a tuff old bird and his two sons were both ex military sons. The government contacted the ex marine and asked him to get a job with the company but this was to infiltrate the American organization and gather information for the government about Lybia. This HR guy did a good job.As ayoung man he made some mistakes , one was he helped the father with transportation of the agribusiness employee's to the point the Dad got mad at him for being too smart. I remember that young guy, lack of experience , but he got the job done for the government. There are many such stories of Americans that will never be told. The dead leader ofLybia , like many of these people all think they are going to control the world. They end up killing a lot of people first, then acting like Kings which is one reason why America was formed to get away from Kings. Yes I can understand why you think there is a problem Iran and Iraq were evenly matched until the USA doctrine ended up that balance and now it appears the USA has another larger problem with one of those nations making nuclear weapons. Can you say spin the concentrator. Mining_phd I can tell you don't worry the script is was set up with taking out Sadam,and the script was written by the USA . I am sure another young marine like that one I knew over 30 years ago is still on duty station and will be taking care of business. some day you might be able to see the best roman ruins in the world they are located in Lybia.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358573757399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:35:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358576721212-3</Id><Topic><Title>BATTERY PACK BATCH</Title><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358566227748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:30:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The most interesting aspect of this situation is how well Boeing's pr folks are handling the problem. For instance, the first dreamliner problems were fuel leaks, but the press has been silent on that lately. Those fuel leaks were not on the planes that had the fires, or for that matter, in the same locations as the fires. But a fuel leak and a fire would potentially be a horrible combination. Government bureaucrats would normally be very risk adverse to letting the dreamliner fly again, if such a combination was possible. But there is substantial pressure on the faa to clear the dreamliner for the sake of american jobs, prestige, and Boeing. Interesting dynamics, but one has to appreciate "value" of the almighty, silver tongued, devil pr folks when they pull one off. Let's hope and pray one of these never really catches fire, because "our" government will have them flying again, in no time - everywhere. Let's hope only a bump in the road, for the sake of at least a few hundred people.</Msg><Username>dkhrzn</Username><Timestamp>1358576721212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 01:25:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358579218494-4</Id><Topic><Title>Whoops: PolitiFact's 'Lie of the Year' Turns Out to Be True</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1358549443697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:50:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too little too late... and now Willtard is retired. Har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1358579218494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 02:06:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358579637412-5</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Reaches Endgame, Culmination Of Decade Of Problems With 'Nightmareliner'</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358560772061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much teething is really going on with the 787, here is a clear answer to the Boeing spin story. It is the first such action against a U.S.-made passenger plane since the McDonnell Douglas DC-10 had its airworthiness certificate suspended following a deadly crash in Chicago in 1979, analysts said. notice how the 6 Boeing police who monitor the message board have their thumbs down but no actual facts to dispute the facts 787. that means they are Boeing shareholders, or boeing workers or retired people with stock in Boeing most likely. Too bad these investors do not know how to read a stock chart, Boeing stock price for a full year is .03% down for a huge risk Better off with a ETF for the NASDAQ for a year up over 13%. Boeing shareholder's since 1-9-2013 have after a year of no gains lost about 3% on a stock that trades within a dead cat bounce of zip or down. Now Boeing shareholders are saddled with a potential loss of 400 million per day on a SPEEA strike and a 50 million costper day onthe grounded customer delivered revenue ofthe s of the 50 787's the the shareholders a loss per sale of 300 million for each delivery due to the cost of production 400 million per plane less the late penality and dedection for a reworked plane and the deep discount for package deals to the airplane customers , the actual customer price is 100 million the sticker209 million. If you can read a stock chart since the 1-9-2013 kill zone call and the major investment houses selling off their Boeing shares , you can see it . the Boeing stock price hasgone down from rounded 77 to rounded 75, and the volume of shares sold had gone from an average daily trade volume of 5 million (yahoo financial for BA to a average of 10 million shares traded) The stock price has been going down on a average lower high to a lower low and the %K had crossed the %D at a still high 50%, so the major investment houses are selling off as fast as they can without creating a panic. There is no time table for the 787 FAA review and the Boeing fix and battery was already certifed to work so the problem may take a redesign or millions of dollars and another long delivery delay. This is a huge risk for any boeing stockholder a labor stop strike, a grounded 787 with a firestarter record is not a teething issue , that is a crash kill issue. The U.S. Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) on Wednesday grounded Boeing's newest commercial airliner, saying carriers would have to demonstrate the batteries were safe before the planes could resume flying. It gave no details on when that might happen. BTW the MD outsourcing business plan is the 100% same now with the 787. Remember the new MD-BA saying, "If it's a MD-BA outsourced 787 plane , then I am not going.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358579637412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 02:13:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358581628928-6</Id><Topic><Title>BATTERY PACK BATCH</Title><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358566227748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:30:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the same batch.....THEY HAVE ONLY DELIVERED 47 787s. What is a batch of batteries? Smaller than a peck? cheaper by the dozen? How many Priuseseses do they build in Japan a year? Six Sigma only applied to the 1st 6? ISO 9000 errrr lets just make it ISO 9 for LEAN purposes. REALLY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! THE BIG BOYS ARE UNLOADING THE STOCK AS THEY FEED YOU THIS SPIN.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1358581628928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 02:47:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358584513858-7</Id><Topic><Title>Barclays on Boeing,how does it compare to EADS,Lockheed,Northrop</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358457136168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:12:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), announcing its decision Wednesday to ground the 787 fleet, indicated it is not satisfied that these systems worked as designed. It stated that both battery incidents resulted in the “release of flammable electrolytes, heat damage, and smoke.” ANA said Wednesday that the pilots did smell something that they thought was smoke, and that this smell was also in the passenger cabin. That, along with warnings of battery trouble on the instrument panel, is what impelled the pilot to make the emergency landing, deploy the emergency exit slides and evacuate all 137 passengers and crew. Two people with knowledge of what happened said the pilot received three battery warning messages during take-off after an initial status message. One of those messages warned that the battery was overheating. So this is not teething , any time you have to make a emergency landing and deploy emergency slides that is a life or death departure from a airplane,So if you are a airplane company, or a airline and your customer's , including children and senior's have to jump on a slide to exit a plane that is a scary situation, not a dreamliner,but a nightmareliner experience. This 787 if over the ocean can not make a emergency landing, only a matter of time, the last plane to have a certificate stop was a MD plane over 30 years ago. that was a MD plane the same people who ran MD into the ground now are running Boeing into the ground. If that is not enough outsourcing anti Hart-Smith bad management to consider, the real engineers SPEEA are being forced to strke to make sure thier pensions will not be ended. How about the Boeing CEO taking a pay cut and cancel his pension first !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358584513858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 03:35:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358588596105-8</Id><Topic><Title>BATTERY PACK BATCH</Title><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358566227748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:30:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on bro'. The Deathliner is right on schedule to meet its maker!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1358588596105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 04:43:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358588978210-9</Id><Topic><Title>Iran needs to be nuclear armed to save itself</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358545571910</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 16:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With all due respect, I am not sure of your point. Iran was attacked by Iraq in 1979, but the USA and many others helped Iraq. Don Rumsfeld flew to Iraq in 1984 to meet Saddam and sell him chemical weapons and assorted guidance systems.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358588978210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 04:49:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358592885970-10</Id><Title>On Guns, an Abuse of Power</Title><Msg>On Guns, an Abuse of Power Not a single one of the items Obama intends to implement would have stopped Adam Lanza. David Harsanyi | January 17, 2013 When Barack Obama implored Americans to "do the right thing" on gun restriction during a news conference this week, the "right thing" should have been obvious to everyone. Absolute moral authority—it's the only way to go. If you fail to see the picture as clearly as the president, you may be an extremist or, more than likely, you're too feeble-minded to withstand the Jedi mind tricks employed by gun merchants or radio talk show hosts or the National Rifle Association or all those folks "ginning up fear" on the issue, according to a president who trots out 7-year-olds to shield him from debate. Now, the 23 executive orders President Barack Obama signed that are aimed at "reducing gun violence" could be considered, at worst, cynically political or, at best, completely useless. But the way Obama treats the process, children, the debate, the Constitution and the American people is another story. Sen. Rand Paul recently remarked that "someone who wants to bypass the Constitution, bypass Congress—that's someone who wants to act like a king or a monarch." That may be a bit hyperbolic, but it is also a bit true. "There are millions of responsible, law-abiding gun owners in America," lectured Obama, "who cherish their right to bear arms for hunting or sport or protection or collection." (Or—as it must have slipped the president's mind—the right to put a gun in a case labeled "open in case of tyranny.") The president went on to profess that he believes that the Second Amendment guarantees an individual the right to bear arms. If this were true for Obama, who was once a constitutional law lecturer at the University of Chicago, why would he attempt to restrict a right that is explicitly laid out in the Bill of Rights (even if it were eminently sensible) without putting it through the republican wringer—the deliberation, the checks and balances, all of it? The president, who has often said he will work around Congress, also justifies his executive bender by telling us that Americans are clamoring for more limits on gun ownership. So what? These rights—in what Piers Morgan might call that "little book"—were written down to protect the citizenry from not only executive overreach but also vagaries of public opinion. Didn't Alexander Hamilton and James Madison warn us against the dangerous "passions" of the mob? It is amazing how many times this president uses majoritarian arguments to rationalize executive overreach. And really, speaking of ginning up fear: "If there's even one life that can be saved, then we've got an obligation to try," the president said, deploying perhaps the biggest platitude in the history of nannyism. Not a single one of the items Obama intends to implement—legislative or executive—would have stopped Adam Lanza's killing spree or, most likely, any of the others. Using fear and a tragedy to further ideological goals was by no means invented by Obama, but few people have used it with such skill. Now, when the Supreme Court solidified the right to an abortion via Roe v. Wade (now a constitutional right, unlike owning a gun in Chicago) and solidified the individual mandate found in Obamacare (now a constitutional right, unlike, say, the right of Catholics to be free of economic coercion), they became immovable legal precedents that may never be toyed with—ever. Well, even if you believe in banning "assault" weapons and high-capacity ammunition magazines, doesn't the Bill of Rights deserve at least that much deference?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358592885970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 05:54:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358594366486-11</Id><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Msg>....... you think maybe it’s time to require a background check on anybody wanting to be president? I would submit to you we still have not had a background check on Barack Obama</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358595484064-12</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Reaches Endgame, Culmination Of Decade Of Problems With 'Nightmareliner'</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358560772061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358595484064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:38:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358596866543-13</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you think of all the symbology in the recent event?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358596866543</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:01:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358600051215-14</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are people in the wrold that like to leave a "signature" of their handiwork....my best guess is that there WAS a tragedy and kids were killed at Newtown....but that Lanza did NOT act alone....and that an entire script was being built SPECIFICALLY to attack the second amendment. "We are not afraid to entrust the American people with unpleasant facts, foreign ideas, alien philosophies and competitive values. For a nation that is afraid to let its people judge the truth and falsehood in an open market is a nation afraid of its people." -President John F. Kennedy</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358600051215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:54:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358604079520-15</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>talking to yourself again, schizo?</Msg><Username>rividiot</Username><Timestamp>1358604079520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:01:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358606172005-16</Id><Topic><Title>Republican retreat kicks off with a rocky start</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358552803230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 18:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! These guys can't get out of their own way.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1358606172005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:36:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358606619845-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama’s other aholesex partners</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358536264658</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:11:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This argument looks like it came from a party that could never beat Barack Obama and has thrown in the towel.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1358606619845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:43:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358607091378-18</Id><Topic><Title>Republican retreat kicks off with a rocky start</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358552803230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 18:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take note of how they do in the midterms coming your way shortly. Country stays deep in debt, still huge unemployment numbers, and the fascists push for gun control.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358607091378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:51:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358608059429-19</Id><Topic><Title>Remeber THE Russian Dreamliner?</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358538003390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:40:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey yea aluminium vs Boeins composite material- right? same new technology I guess</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358608059429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:07:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358609299104-20</Id><Topic><Title>Remeber THE Russian Dreamliner?</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358538003390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:40:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fly by wire and super critical wings were already in use in most airbus airplanes long before the Sukhoi 100 was a gleam in an engineers eye- plus all metal- looks like they were copying Airbus dreamliners</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358609299104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:28:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358609398076-21</Id><Topic><Title>Republican retreat kicks off with a rocky start</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358552803230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 18:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>considering that people are sick of the gun #$%$ and their death and destruction Im predicting huge gains for the Dems in both houses</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358609398076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:29:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358609603586-22</Id><Topic><Title>What has the NRA done for America !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358548136299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:28:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, but I heard that multiple .223 rounds made mincemeat out of 20 6- and 7-year olds. If the crime scene photos taken when police got into Sandy Hook were ever released, we'd see assault-rifle rights people strung up from every lamp post. And don't tell me they're not assalt rifles. Any rifle for which you can buy off the Web "drop-in parts" to make them fully automatic should be illegal and the people who make and/or sell those parts should do time sleeping with Bubbas.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358609603586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:33:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610256763-23</Id><Topic><Title>Republican retreat kicks off with a rocky start</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358552803230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 18:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Democrats will regain control of the House in 2014.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1358610256763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:44:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610456890-24</Id><Topic><Title>What has the NRA done for America !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358548136299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:28:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, Chris Genna.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1358610456890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:47:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610595427-25</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>David is Floyd !</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358610595427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:49:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610695553-26</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to the "Left" from a Right wing Extremist !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358558962049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:29:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358610695553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610823057-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Second Amendment vs. the First Amendment</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358552291728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 18:38:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank God Jones switched the blame from the Z ionists...for a second I thought you would label us as antisemitic and racist</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358610823057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610965875-28</Id><Topic><Title>On Guns, an Abuse of Power</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358592885970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 05:54:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358610965875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358612598658-29</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner nighmare was due to poor company leadership</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1358604730021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:12:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot the 717 remember that one! It would be time to short this thing if it weren't for the stock manipulation. In the short run they can make the stock cost whatever they want. Be careful!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1358612598658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:23:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613139705-30</Id><Topic><Title>Whoops: PolitiFact's 'Lie of the Year' Turns Out to Be True</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1358549443697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:50:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney was a very bad candidate. The republicans are a bad joke. So we will have an expert liar and con man running this disfunctional country for a few more years. Doesnt look very good for the USA. No chance to turn things around now!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1358613139705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:32:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613392426-31</Id><Topic><Title>Christie: NRA ad with Obama daughters ‘reprehensible’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358551594881</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 18:26:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christie is a fat self centered smuck. With any luck he'll have a heart attack before the next election.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1358613392426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:36:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613661470-32</Id><Topic><Title>Whoops: PolitiFact's 'Lie of the Year' Turns Out to Be True</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1358549443697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:50:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Romney was a very bad candidate"....between the Diebold voting machines and record amount of voting "irregularities" and the lousy candidate..you would think the Global elite Bankers running the puppets WANTED Romney to lose....</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358613661470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:41:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613674319-33</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner nightmare due to bad analytics</Title><Username>vincent64</Username><Timestamp>1358547688709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:21:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bad management! LMAO You Boeing guys as so sc#@%ed! You can talk all you want. There is no easy way out of this one.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1358613674319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:41:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613821272-34</Id><Topic><Title>PREDICTIONS for BOEING !!</Title><Username>johnsonandrew384</Username><Timestamp>1358447476581</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:31:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good one</Msg><Username>markharrison196</Username><Timestamp>1358613821272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:43:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613851918-35</Id><Topic><Title>On Guns, an Abuse of Power</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358592885970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 05:54:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This one gets a C- on the Sparty Kookdom Scale (SKS) but is an atual improvement on some other posts.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1358613851918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:44:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613981864-36</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358613431889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:37:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good article.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1358613981864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:46:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358614072528-37</Id><Title>We Don't Have No Spending Problem</Title><Msg>We poor people need the government to spend more on anti-poverty programs. We see the stuff you people with jobs have and we want some of it. We deserve it and Obama and the Democrats dang sure better give it for us because those stingy greedy Republicans don't want to get it for us..</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358614072528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:47:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358614443543-38</Id><Title>By my calculations, BOEING has blown its' wad on share buy-backs.</Title><Msg>They have most likely reached their limit. Nowhere for this stock to go now but down, down, down.</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614443543</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:54:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358614513537-39</Id><Title>Have they reached their $2 billion in share buybacks yet?</Title><Msg>Me thinks so. Nowhere for this stock to go now but down, down, down.</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614513537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:55:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358614717274-40</Id><Title>The Government can Print as Much Money as it wants</Title><Msg>As long as they keep raising our welfare it ain't going to hurt nothing.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358614717274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:58:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358615391084-41</Id><Title>I Ain't Flying on no Airplane that Need to Tow a Fire Truck for Safety</Title><Msg>besides since airlines won't accept EBT cards I have to make a special trip down to the welfare office and fill out two pages of paper work just to get a travel voucher and can you believe it, they won't even let me travel in first class. That's discrimination against poor people and it shouldn't be allowed.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358615391084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:09:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616083411-42</Id><Topic><Title>I Ain't Flying on no Airplane that Need to Tow a Fire Truck for Safety</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358615391084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:09:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Food Stamps is what just as important as the dollar. The USA is gone.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1358616083411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:21:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616572677-43</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone know what ever happened to the ex-Boeing CEO who married his 1st cousin?</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1358615933335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:18:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was Phil Condit who was basically fired for haveing and affair with a co-worker. He didn't do very well as knowing about airplanes either, he was the one who moved headquarters to Chicago and we have all seen Boeing's progress since that time.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358616572677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:29:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617537505-44</Id><Topic><Title>Christie: NRA ad with Obama daughters ‘reprehensible’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358551594881</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 18:26:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said Cheney was a fat self centered smuck too...remember ? To be consistent.... I still think your an Anti American POS too.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358617537505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:45:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617571470-45</Id><Topic><Title>The dreamliner and why the batteries are so crucial.....</Title><Username>stockwizard10</Username><Timestamp>1358434832146</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:00:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vierzig, very good response. Complete and concise. It seems a lot of posters want to adopt a fake illiterate accent and make outlandish statements or questions. Anyone who reads the post above can no longer claim to not know a little about the plane.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1358617571470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:46:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617611648-46</Id><Topic><Title>The Government can Print as Much Money as it wants</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358614717274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:58:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are wrong...the GOVERNMENT DOES NOT PRINT AS MUCH MONEY AS IT WANTS...the PRIVATE central bankers at the Fed do that...not the Government.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358617611648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:46:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358618114957-47</Id><Topic><Title>What has the NRA done for America !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358548136299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:28:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If the crime scene photos taken when police got into Sandy Hook were ever released, we'd see assault-rifle rights people strung up from every lamp post." We will never see photos ...We will never see the video camera footage of Lanza doing the shootin either ...any more then we will ever see the video footage of a plane hitting the Pentagon. People and little kids died...of that I have no doubt. The real question is WHO PROFITS and WHAT is the agenda ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358618114957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:55:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619053490-48</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it's true!</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358619053490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:10:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358619437045-49</Id><Title>FLOYD is HERE</Title><Msg>Yes, it's true. David Aames is FLOYD.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619437045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:17:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619452827-50</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone know what ever happened to the ex-Boeing CEO who married his 1st cousin?</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1358615933335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:18:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't it more because of the Sears/Druyen fiasco on the tanker and his lack of leadership?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1358619452827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:17:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358619649130-51</Id><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Msg>Ask FLOYD.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358620927925-52</Id><Topic><Title>No more LWOP on snow days</Title><Username>dennysteed</Username><Timestamp>1358558591958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:23:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I woudn't like it but could put up with it as long as I knew that managers and directors weren't home sitting in their easy chair with their laptop open sipping a beer.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1358620927925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:42:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358621648333-53</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok....Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358621648333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:54:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358623196132-54</Id><Title>January deliveries (or lack of them)</Title><Msg>As of end of day on the 18th, Boeing has delivered only 14 planes. 11 737's. 1 747. 1 767. 1 787. Zero visability fog in Everett kept a lot of initial flights on the ground.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1358623196132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358624089280-55</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ayn must tell the truth. Truth speakers bring on the ire of every liberal.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358624089280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:34:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358624256008-56</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone know what ever happened to the ex-Boeing CEO who married his 1st cousin?</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1358615933335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:18:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I once worked for a large company and found it odd the CEO never looked you in the eye. His wife, I later learned, was his first cousin.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358624256008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:37:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358624338038-57</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For sure. The only thing we know about his background he told us in his autobiography..that he favored his dad's belief in communism. That he was a druggie, and sold drugs, and came to political power amongst a bunch of Chicago thugs. And one of them was his guru, a Chicago communist. Sounds like a potential Presidential candidate no?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358624338038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:38:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358624561900-58</Id><Topic><Title>The dreamliner and why the batteries are so crucial.....</Title><Username>stockwizard10</Username><Timestamp>1358434832146</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:00:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody flies a million miles a year. Obviously you never did the math before making such a stupid comment.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358624561900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:42:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358624972205-59</Id><Title>All the experts said to hold onto Bearn Stearns too!</Title><Msg>Get out now sheeple...while you can!</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358624972205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:49:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625061402-60</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the idi00ts calling for 50s today</Title><Username>hanzandfranzz</Username><Timestamp>1358441395119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 11:49:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The experts said to hold onto Bear Stearns too! Look out below!</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358625061402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:51:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358625627443-61</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner nighmare was due to poor company leadership</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1358604730021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:12:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't kid yourself. The F-22 and F-35 are the biggest POS planes ever made. The F-35 project is trying to outdo the entire cost of the war in Iraq, as a drain on the US treasury. To keep the F-35 program going, recipients of social security and medicare will have to go back to work. Why they need a $400 million plane to fight guys in turbans with 10 year old AK-47s i will never know.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358625627443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:00:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358626584805-62</Id><Title>F-35 $1.5 trillion of taxpayer money, 7 years behind schedule. Ready for $3 trillion US deficits? Gold to $15,000.</Title><Msg>The most expensive weapons program in U.S. history is about to get a lot pricier. The F-35 Joint Strike Fighter, meant to replace nearly every tactical warplane in the Air Force, Navy and Marine Corps, was already expected to cost $1 trillion dollars for development, production and maintenance over the next 50 years. Now that cost is expected to grow, owing to 13 different design flaws uncovered in the last two months by a hush-hush panel of five Pentagon experts. It could cost up to a billion dollars to fix the flaws on copies of the jet already in production, to say nothing of those yet to come. In addition to costing more, the stealthy F-35 could take longer to complete testing. That could delay the stealthy jet’s combat debut to sometime after 2018 — seven years later than originally planned. And all this comes as the Pentagon braces for big cuts to its budget while trying to save cherished but costly programs like the Joint Strike Fighter. Frank Kendall, the Pentagon’s top weapons-buyer, convened the so-called “Quick Look Review” panel in October. Its report — 55 pages of dense technical jargon and intricate charts — was leaked this weekend. Kendall and company found a laundry list of flaws with the F-35, including a poorly placed tail hook, lagging sensors, a buggy electrical system and structural cracks. Some of the problems — the electrical bugs, for instance — were becoming clear before the Quick Look Review; others are brand-new. The panelists describe them all in detail and, for the first time, connect them to the program’s underlying management problems. Most ominously, the report mentions — but does not describe — a “classified” deficiency. “Dollars to doughnuts it has something to do with stealth,” aviation guru Bill Sweetman wrote. In other words, the F-35 might not be as invisible to radar as prime contractor Lockheed Martin said it would be. The JSF’s problems are exacerbated by a production plan that Vice Adm. David Venlet, the government program manager, admitted two weeks ago represents “a miscalculation.” Known as “concurrency,” the plan allows Lockheed to mass-produce jets — potentially hundreds of them — while testing is still underway. It’s a way of ensuring the military gets combat-ready jets as soon as possible, while also helping Lockheed to maximize its profits. That’s the theory, at least. “Concurrency is present to some degree in virtually all DoD programs, though not to the extent that it is on the F-35,” the Quick Look panelists wrote. The Pentagon assumed it could get away with a high degree of concurrency owing to new computer simulations meant to take the guesswork out of testing. “The Department had a reasonable basis to be optimistic,” the panelists wrote. But that optimism proved unfounded. “This assessment shows that the F-35 program has discovered and is continuing to discover issues at a rate more typical of early design experience on previous aircraft development programs,” the panelists explained. Testing uncovered problems the computers did not predict, resulting in 725 design changes while new jets were rolling off the factory floor in Fort Worth, Texas. And every change takes time and costs money. To pay for the fixes, this year the Pentagon cut its F-35 order from 42 to 30. Next year’s order dropped from 35 to 30. “It’s basically sucked the wind out of our lungs with the burden, the financial burden,” Venlet said. News of more costs and delays could not have come at a worse time for the Joint Strike Fighter. The program has already been restructured twice since 2010, each time getting stretched out and more expensive. In January, then-Secretary of Defense Robert Gates put the Marines’ overweight F-35B variant, which is designed to take off and land vertically, on probation. If Lockheed couldn’t fix the jump jet within two years, “it should be cancelled,” Gates advised. Tasting blood in the water, Boeing — America’s other fighter-plane manufacturer — dusted off plans for improved F-15s and F-18s to sell to the Pentagon, should the F-35 fail. Deep cuts to the defense budget certainly aren’t helping the F-35′s case. Humbled, Lockheed agreed to share some of the cost of design changes, instead of simply billing the government. The aerospace giant copped to its past problems with the F-35 and promised better performance. “There will not be another re-baseline of this program. We understand that,” Lockheed CEO Robert Stevens said in May. But another “rebaselining,” or restructuring, is likely in the wake of the Quick Look Review. F-35 testing and production should be less concurrent and more “event-based,” the panelists advised. In other words, the program should worry less about meeting hard deadlines and more about getting the jet’s design right. It’ll be ready when it’s ready. Major production must wait, even if that means older warplanes — the planes the F-35 is supposed to replace — must stay on the front line longer. Needless to say, that’s got some members of Congress up in arms. “It is at this exact moment that the excessive overlap between development and production that was originally structured into the JSF program … is now coming home to roost,” said Sen. John McCain, an Arizona Republican and the ranking member of the Senate Armed Services Committee. “If things do not improve — quickly — taxpayers and the warfighter will insist that all options will be on the table. And they should be. We cannot continue on this path.”</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358626584805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:16:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358628011800-63</Id><Title>Ya'all need to quit wasting your time Talking about Boeing</Title><Msg>We have a serious problem in this country. My Welfare checks could be in jeopardy if the don't raise the debt ceiling.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358628011800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:40:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358628057907-64</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Fascists in the future will be called anti-fascists." ~Winston Churchill Liberals FEAR Rand because they aren't really liberals. They are commies.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358628057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:40:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358628724441-65</Id><Title>Canada "plans" to buy F-35's. Canada has no aerial refueling capability. Who agrees to such deals?</Title><Msg>Canada needs the F-35 like it needs more snow.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358628724441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:52:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358629834553-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ayn rand came from Russia. She KNEW how bad comminism was and feared America was headed in the same direction. We are much further down the road then when she was alive. She was one of the giants of the 20th century. "The smallest minority on earth is the individual. Those who deny individual rights cannot claim to be defenders of minorities." Ayn Rand</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358629834553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:10:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358629950250-67</Id><Title>787 Batteries- No one was injured per the FAA</Title><Msg>I thought one firefighter was injured trying to put out the battery that was on firm. FAA indicates there were no injuries, must be talking about injuries of passengers and crew members? ""The FAA used to be accused of 'blood priority'" — acting only after a disaster, Anthony said. "In this case, it's not true. The regulators are taking their job seriously. There were no accidents, there were no injuries, there were no fatalities."</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358629950250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:12:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358630456286-68</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries- No one was injured per the FAA</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358629950250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:12:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also thought there were about 5 people injured going down the ememgency slides to evacuate the second plane wiht the battery malfunction.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358630456286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:20:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358630519847-69</Id><Title>New proposal would force citizens to store weapons at Government storage sites</Title><Msg>Because you can never have too many laws, regulations and mandates, Massachusetts State Representative David Linsky has filed a new bill that would, among other things, force gun owners to undergo mental health background checks, acquire liability insurance, pay an additional 25% tax on all forms of ammunition, and require firearms categorized as “assault weapons” to be stored outside of their homes and only at government approved storage depots. “This bill is a comprehensive effort to reduce all types of gun violence – murders, intentional shootings, accidental shootings and suicides. There is not one solution to reducing gun violence – we can’t eliminate it – but there are a lot of common-sense steps that we can take to significantly reduce the everyday tragedy of gun violence and deaths,” said Linsky. … “I have spoken with hundreds of people over the past few weeks in developing this legislation – victims, police officers, criminologists, physicians, and yes – gun owners and sportsmen,” stated Linsky. “There are a lot of good ideas out there. We should all have one goal – reducing gun violence and trying to keep more tragedies from happening.” Provisions in the bill include: Having one standard of the issuance of all gun licenses, giving local police chiefs the ability to evaluate all aspects of an application for a gun license. Requires proof of liability insurance for possession of a firearm, rifle or shotgun. Requires that all large capacity weapons and grandfathered assault weapons must be stored at gun clubs or target ranges. Requires live shooting as part of the curriculum for a basic firearms safety course; this is not a current requirement. Requires all applicants for gun licenses and FID cards to sign a waiver of mental health records for review to be destroyed after decision. Imposes 25% sales tax on ammunition, firearms, shotguns, and rifles; dedicates funds towards firearms licensing, police training, mental health services, and victim’s services. Brings Massachusetts into compliance with the National Instant Criminal Background Check System (NICS). Limits gun buyers to one firearm purchase per month. Bills such as this one are being filed by irrationally driven anti-gunners all over the country. They are targeting every aspect of firearms in an effort to first reduce ownership, and then to ultimately ban it altogether. They’ll expand the definitions for mental health to include basic forms of stress and normal human mood fluctuations and designate these as mental health conditions that would disqualify you from owning a gun. They’ll tax gun purchases and ammunition like they’ve done with cigarettes (tripling the cost over a decade) and require huge insurance premiums, making ownership unaffordable for most Americans. They’ll track the sale and transfer of all firearms through registration, with unjust punishments for anyone engaging in black-market trading. And, eventually, another crisis – likely one that purports to threaten the very security and stability of the government of the United States – will be used in an attempt institute a complete roundup of the majority of modern firearms.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358630519847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:21:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358630746246-70</Id><Topic><Title>New proposal would force citizens to store weapons at Government storage sites</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358630519847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:21:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you should call them and suggest they keep the guns at the dozens of your FEMA camps.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1358630746246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:25:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358630974309-71</Id><Topic><Title>New proposal would force citizens to store weapons at Government storage sites</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358630519847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:21:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>steady......don't mention FEMA camps...just last month some jacka$$ claimed they don't even exist.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358630974309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358631205916-72</Id><Title>The real problem here...</Title><Msg>... It's called new technology using new materials. Never venture out of your comfort zone and you will never be the leader in your industry. Boeing made a bold move trying to build a mostly composite aircraft. New technology always has its problems, but Boeing is going to solve those problems and when when they do, everyone will hail BA as an innovator of great technology in the aerospace industry. Don't believe? wait and see!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358631205916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:33:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358631362999-73</Id><Title>787 Batteries probably made from CHINA</Title><Msg>EOM!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>gowiththewave</Username><Timestamp>1358631362999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:36:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358631485511-74</Id><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Msg>Boeing CEO Jim McNerney’s compensation jumped 34 percent last year as the board of the big airplane maker rewarded him for delivering the new 787, The main increase was in incentive pay the board also granted above-target incentive pay to Boeing managers for 2011, including $4.4 million for McNerney. The above-target rewards were in order because of “strong, integrated performance across the Company and better-than-expected mitigation of risks,” Boeing said in its filing. So then what will be the reason for the huge increase in 2013 the SPEEA strike and the finding that the outsourcing was not as good as they planned for cutting costs ? Is outsourcing to blame for Boeing’s 787 Dreamliner woes It’s been a miserable 3.5 year delay and a worse week for Boeing. Federal investigators have grounded all of the U.S. company’s new and much-hyped 787 Dreamliner jets after reports that the aircraft’s lithium-ion batteries were overheating and catching fire. And already, a favorite culprit has emerged: outsourcing. Although outsourcing has always been a part of commercial aviation, the difference now is the complexity and co-dependence of the electronics operating the aircraft.On the 787, the vast collection of components by hundred of suppliers that go into a 787 makes troubleshooting potentially more difficult This is where the extreme outsourcing really causes problems. How are they going to get their suppliers to be truthful? That has always been a problem in aeronautics. The 787 organization makes it much, much worse.” The first 3 years of the delay on the Boeing 787/These concerns are hardly novel. Back in 2011, Michael Hiltzik published a long piece for the Los Angeles Times questioning Boeing’s over-reliance on foreign suppliers for the Dreamliner. That piece, however, was largely focused on delays and cost overruns: “The drawbacks of this approach emerged early,” Hiltzik wrote. “Some of the pieces manufactured by far-flung suppliers didn’t fit together. Some subcontractors couldn’t meet their output quotas, creating huge production logjams when critical parts weren’t available in the necessary sequence.” Next a Boeing Engineer Hart-Smith warned Boeing management in 2001, the result of outsourcing , would be that outsourcing doesn’t cut costs and increase profits but rather does the reverse, driving profits to suppliers and increasing costs for the mother company. Only by maintaining control of its manufacturing could Boeing succeed. He notes that rival Airbus’ outsourcing procedures, a result of the company’s multinational nature, are more efficient than Boeing’s but still fraught with inefficiencies absent in a more centralized approach. Hart-Smith’s ideas were not adopted, and Boeing, led by then-executives Harry Stoneceipher and Allan Mullally (now Ford’s CEO), made a bet on short-term cost cutting. *Hart-Smith’s paper includes the best footnote ever: “The views expressed here are those of the author and not necessarily those of the Boeing management Boeing Management are still focused on short term profits , hence the SPEEA strike(CUTTING COSTS ON THE PENSION), the 787 grounding, the excessive short term executive bonus for very short term goals. It’s been interesting to watch millions of bonus paid to the Boeing executives for short term goals while the Boeing long term stock price has been flat and a loss for the entire last year. Airbus stock is up over 27% and the NASDAQ average is up 13.8% for a year , Lockheed (LMT) is up 12.26% for a year, the Dow of which Boeing is a part is up 8.51% for a year making Boeing a dog of the Dow at a loss of .69%. for a year .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358631712344-75</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone know what ever happened to the ex-Boeing CEO who married his 1st cousin?</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1358615933335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:18:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phil was fired after a long history of management problems including the 737 production fiasco. The fact that he was caught en flagrante with his secretary in his office a year earlier was incidental since this sort of behavior was nothing new for him. Harry was fired for having an affair with a subordinate. Phil is seen around occasionally but he is, wisely, keeping a pretty low profile.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1358631712344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:41:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632080258-76</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries- No one was injured per the FAA</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358629950250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:12:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup, but that stuff doesn't count.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1358632080258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:48:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632184076-77</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you are right.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358632184076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:49:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632406062-78</Id><Topic><Title>We Don't Have No Spending Problem</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358614072528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:47:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the government had more money there wouldn't be any spending problem! Wait a second! Can't the government just print more money? Sounds like that is a pretty easy fix then.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1358632406062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:53:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632485952-79</Id><Topic><Title>Have they reached their $2 billion in share buybacks yet?</Title><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614513537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:55:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>eucheme, I can tell you are right. How can I tell, 5 of the 6 Boeing Management Enablers have given you a silent reply , a thumbs down, it is silent because you are right and nothing they can argue is going to change the fact. eucheme, look at the Yahoo finance page , check the average daily volume for Boeing it is 5 million shares , since shortly after I called a boeing stock price in the kill zone and pointed out that the large institutional traders were selling their boeing stock,( prior to the fire and the strike) the volume has increased to 10 million per day while the stock price has peaked at 77 and been going lower to 75 dollars , this on lower high prices for the day and lower low prices for the day. While the yahoo stock chart does not have too many better tools I can tell you the lines %k and %d have crossed down above 50% indicating this stock over time is going down. In any event for the last 365 days any stock market inestor with a buy and hold on Boeing has lost about a 1% and the average of the Dow is up 8.5% . Now add a potential SPEEA strike and the unknown time of the 787 grounding and you are taking excessive risk to reward( actually a loss) by holding Boeing stock.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358632485952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:54:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632597182-80</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Reaches Endgame, Culmination Of Decade Of Problems With 'Nightmareliner'</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358560772061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can I tell this user comment is right, well 5 of the 6 Boeing managment enablers have given it a thubs down, they have no argument they just don't like the truth being told !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358632597182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:56:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358632718945-81</Id><Topic><Title>Barclays on Boeing,how does it compare to EADS,Lockheed,Northrop</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358457136168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:12:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is a truthful user comment, how can I tell, 4 fo the 6 Boeing Managment Enablers have given it a silent thubs down , silent because they have no facts to dispute the user comment !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358632718945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:58:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358633060052-82</Id><Topic><Title>We Don't Have No Spending Problem</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358614072528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:47:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republicans wouldn't give medicine to a dying child.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1358633060052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:04:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358633092971-83</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries- No one was injured per the FAA</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358629950250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:12:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure the 5 people who were injured would disagree, as would the rest of the terrified passengers who won't be getting on another 787 very soon.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1358633092971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:04:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358634996835-84</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for all the thumbs up guys</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358634996835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:36:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358635130915-85</Id><Title>Buy or Sell?</Title><Msg>Stock is not going down much. Why? Should we hold or buy more or sell this stock?</Msg><Username>ymsz</Username><Timestamp>1358635130915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:38:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358635849661-86</Id><Topic><Title>Barclays on Boeing,how does it compare to EADS,Lockheed,Northrop</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358457136168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:12:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing delivered the first Dreamliner to All Nippon Airways in September 2011 — three and a half years behind schedule. To conserve fuel, the Dreamliner uses five times more electricity, and more electrical systems, than other jets Wary of the aircraft paving new ground, the FAA certified the aircraft only with several "special conditions." If the FAA condemns some part of the Dreamliner, the damage, in terms of money and reputation, could be devastating. R Its caution was justified. the promise of the Dreamliner and its history of delays( 3.5 years) and counting, have focused the view of investors, government administrators, and the flying public, each stumble magnifying the impact of Chicago mismanagement, short term profits</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358635849661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:50:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358635914260-87</Id><Title>If this EDSEL of an airplane has to be written offf ...</Title><Msg>... how much will it be? When Ford wrote the Edsel off in the late 50's it was to the tune of a billion plus in those dollars. It was very bad for the time. Yet they survived and eventually thrived with the Mustang. If Boeing scraps this dog (won't even be able to get scrap metal for it since it is mainly composite fiber) how much will it cost? How much will it hurt the company? How much will the stock drop? I think it could be upwards of 50 billion, will hurt it a lot, and the stock will drop 40 to 50%. P.S. You think that they will ask for a government bailout?</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358635914260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:51:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358636749411-88</Id><Title>UNION MOOCHER BUILT</Title><Msg>Get OUT of BA NOW!!!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1358636749411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:05:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358636880358-89</Id><Topic><Title>If this EDSEL of an airplane has to be written offf ...</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358635914260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:51:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The company is based in Chicago. That alone will be a big incentive for tax payer money. But I disagree on all your other assumptions. This problem will be fixed and the 787 will fly again. How long it will take is anyones guess. If they think it will take a while then they will come up with a work around temporary fix. The U.S., Japan and China has the best people working on this problem. A bad batch of batteries may be the problem. But how do you determin what a bad battery is from a good one? Over voltage may also be a problem. Time will tell.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358636880358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:08:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637534016-90</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries probably made from CHINA</Title><Username>gowiththewave</Username><Timestamp>1358631362999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:36:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who remembers the homes built in Florida that were made with drywall that came from China. The drywall was made from toxic junk. As the temperature rose in Florida, toxic steam was being emitting from the walls in these $400,000 homes. The builder tried to dismiss it. In time, all of the homes were demolished. Be careful dealing with Chinese.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358637534016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:18:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637593732-91</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner nighmare was due to poor company leadership</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1358604730021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:12:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmm, just for a quick exercise, the 787 weighs about 10% more than the 767. I think you would be surprised about how many of the parts are made here. Instead of your denigrating remarks about the Boeing company, maybe you could focus on the many, and I do mean many, successful ventures they have completed. Or are you just some disgruntled, fired employee who has an ax to grind? HarHar!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1358637593732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:19:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637661594-92</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries- No one was injured per the FAA</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358629950250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:12:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was this incident discovered while the plane was on the taxiway or at 40,000 feet. what happens if a battery fire happens at 40,000 feet 1000 miles from land?</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1358637661594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:21:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358638274672-93</Id><Topic><Title>We Don't Have No Spending Problem</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358614072528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:47:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's right. Healthcare in N. Korea and Cuba is free.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358638274672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358638467036-94</Id><Title>You White Boy Democrats Can Stick around In Our Party....</Title><Msg>....as long as we need your votes but once we don't need your votes no more, you honks can hit the road Jack and don'tcha come back no mo.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358638467036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:34:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639240342-95</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great article. Thanks.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1358639240342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:47:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639391813-96</Id><Topic><Title>Buy or Sell?</Title><Username>ymsz</Username><Timestamp>1358635130915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:38:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pleased sell so the price I buy it at will be lower.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358639391813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639946133-97</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We are fast approaching the stage of the ultimate inversion: the stage where the government is free to do anything it pleases, while the citizens may act only by permission; which is the stage of the darkest periods of human history, the stage of rule by brute force." Ayn Rand</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358639946133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:59:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639952865-98</Id><Topic><Title>You White Boy Democrats Can Stick around In Our Party....</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358638467036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barack Obama is our guy, too.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1358639952865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:59:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640019788-99</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Floyd responded....I told ya ! :-)</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358640019788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:00:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640296183-100</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2011, news broke that notorious libertarian/objectivist Ayn Rand had accepted Social Security and Medicare in the 1970s after she was diagnosed with lung cancer (unsurprisingly she was a cigarette-cancer connection denier). Among liberal circles, a lot of attention was paid to the hypocrisy angle of all this (and much more to taking SS cheques than enrolling in Medicare). A person who spent her life railing against collectivism and dependency accepting the benefits of the very programs her beliefs called "evil." Hypocrisy isn't the important thing here. Ideological failure is. To the defenders of Rand, the most common reply is that Rand had paid into these programs through her involuntarily seized taxes, and if she was going to be forced ("at gunpoint" as libertarians always say) to pay for these programs, why shouldn't she at least get something back from them? Actually, I don't really disagree with that. Liberals didn't support the Bush tax cuts, but I doubt many liberals gave back the government the extra taxes they would have had to pay under the Clinton rates after the tax cuts passed. You're not typically morally obligated to martyr yourself for your beliefs. A Failure of Ideas, Not the Individual No, the really important fact that this episode reveals is not Rand's hypocrisy, but the utter failure of her ideas. Even she couldn't live without the social safety net. Here's how the woman who persuaded her to take part in socialism explained it to a fellow objectivist in 1998 (emphasis added): “The initial argument was on greed,” Pryor continued. “She had to see that there was such a thing as greed in this world. Doctors could cost an awful lot more money than books earn, and she could be totally wiped out by medical bills if she didn’t watch it. Since she had worked her entire life, and had paid into Social Security, she had a right to it. She didn’t feel that an individual should take help.” McConnell asked: “And did she agree with you about Medicare and Social Security?” Pryor replied: “After several meetings and arguments, she gave me her power of attorney to deal with all matters having to do with health and Social Security. Whether she agreed or not is not the issue, she saw the necessity for both her and Frank. She was never involved other than to sign the power of attorney; I did the rest.” Ayn Rand was at that point a successful author with several best sellers which continued to move well. No, she wasn't a billionaire or anything, but she was certainly not hurting for cash in ordinary people terms. This site claims* that the NY Times reported her estate as being worth $500,000 at her death in 1982. An online inflation calculator says that's worth $1.2M today. Most people would be thrilled if they were told they'd be worth that much in retirement. Yet even so, Rand looked into the giant gulping maw of the for-profit medical industry and blinked, fearing her cancer would bankrupt her. That's the failure here; Rand needed society's help. Rand ran headlong into the very premise of why Medicare was created in the first place: The for-profit insurance market is terrible for the elderly and particularly to those already stricken with serious diseases. It's not about chortling at Rand as yet another greedy right wing hypocrite, it's about realizing she implicitly acknowledged the superiority of liberalism with her actions. This is her endorsement, and as Paul Ryan's sort gears up to destroy Medicare, we shouldn't hesitate to remind them that Ayn Rand, whatever her rhetoric and books, ended her life on our side. Naturally, Rand showed no signs of rethinking anything in the face of her own personal failure to survive in the world she would see created. She strutted the high wire for a while, but when the wind picked up, she was glad to have the safety net there to catch her as she fell.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1358640296183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:04:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640322954-101</Id><Topic><Title>You White Boy Democrats Can Stick around In Our Party....</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358638467036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can be a fan but we claim the man</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358640322954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:05:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640559871-102</Id><Topic><Title>You White Boy Democrats Can Stick around In Our Party....</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358638467036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After 43 White guys, does it make a difference?</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1358640559871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:09:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358641585696-103</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz I've been to China and I disagree with Sirota. He suffers from not having had to come from nothing as he was born in CT with a silver spoon in his mouth. Maybe Sirota rightfully feels self-guilt in that he has had it handed to him and not really had to earn anything but such a person can never know what those of us who built something from nothing went through. It's a right of passage you and he will never know. He fails logic in that he bases his views on his own childish impressions and anecdotal evidence and mixes his jumbled thoughts with poor logic technique by applying inductive reasoning for his arguments. He's not very believable and he certainly has no real world experience to base his views on as he has lived in the academic and political bubble his entire life. Guys like Sirota were a joke on my college campus and we laughed at poly-sci/English majors because they were too dumb to get into science or engineering schools. People like Sirota invent nothing, build nothing, grow nothing, raise no one out of poverty and have never led anyone into life's battles, they are useless to the rest of us who are doers. Academic bubble non-doer dolts like Sirota are archaic fossils that live in a world of theory and mentally circle jerk each other and give each other awards like ego-maniacal Hollywood celebs. It's not the real world that the rest of us live in. People like Sirota have little to offer anyone and his ideas are worthless. He appeals only to you as he reinforces your confirmation bias for your inexperienced view of the world. The rest of us have accomplished more than Sirota ever will because we invent things, build things, grow things, fix things lead others, etc.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358641585696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:26:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358641784389-104</Id><Topic><Title>You White Boy Democrats Can Stick around In Our Party....</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358638467036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:34:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After 43 white guys, it's our turn to run this country and we're going to run it for a long, long time. You white boy Democrats can help us get what we deserve but we are going to do the controlling. If you crackers think we owe you something we don't see it that way any more than we owed those white Republicans boy's families that died freeing our ancestors. The Dead ones we like but the rest are just honks we don't owe them nothing.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358641784389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:29:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358641957724-105</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Delusions of grandeur on display from ali infested. Zero chance he is even any of the twisted and empty success he describes, and I have pity for such an empty humanoid. Rarely does a poster unwittingly give away such a window to his empty life.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1358641957724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:32:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358643675803-106</Id><Title>You can Save more lives by taking Pens away from politicians</Title><Msg>...then by taking guns away from citizens ...</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358643675803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:01:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358645060092-107</Id><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Msg>SPEEA offered to help Boeing resolve its nightmare problem with the 787. How can Boeing trust SPEEA when at the same time SPEEA is planning for a strike against Boeing that will severely damage the company. Can you trust someone who wants to hurt you? Isn't this a case of with friends like SPEEA who needs enemies?</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358645604122-108</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries probably made from CHINA</Title><Username>gowiththewave</Username><Timestamp>1358631362999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:36:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I beleive Yasua in Japan is responsible for the batteries, part of of Mitsubishi</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358645604122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:33:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358645645246-109</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barrack Barry Soetoro Frank Marshall David Jr Obama (pick a name ...they are all applicable at one time or another)...is an enigma and at the very least is committing fraud...at worst he is ineligible to be President ...... after years and years we STILL have not seen documents that could verify his past.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358645645246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:34:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358645668245-110</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Guys like Sirota were a joke on my college campus and we laughed at poly-sci/English majors because they were too dumb to get into science or engineering schools." I studied English, Poetry, and Music. Of course, I really wish I were you.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1358645668245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:34:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358645829225-111</Id><Topic><Title>Ya'all need to quit wasting your time Talking about Boeing</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358628011800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:40:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ignore</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1358645829225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:37:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358646251322-112</Id><Title>Don't count Boeing out.</Title><Msg>Once this problem is overcome you can expect PPS to increase a great deal. For me I'm just holding my shares. They will find out soon why this has been a problem on a few aircraft but not the rest of the fleet.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358646251322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:44:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358647298937-113</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....perhaps in the way you mean it...but not in the context of this thread where OBAMA's hypocritical double standard of an elitist getting the pass while law abiding citizens have to go through extensive background checks for simply carrying a gun...FAR LESS RESPONSIBLITY then becoming the President of the United States with a finger on the trigger of nuclear weapons.....Your so steeped in hypocrysy that you just can't see it.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358647298937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:01:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358647891808-114</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm pretty excited about Becks plan. He is so naive and delusional that a short trip to reality might do the man good. For all Rand blather she spend her final years on welfare and medicare. What's Becks plan for healthcare? cash only ? what does he do with the sick old people ? throw them in the river? what about drug addicts and crazy people? homosexuality? It's also pretty funny that he wants to grow his own food---like Castro's homophobic agrarian society. I can't wait there's gonna be some good headlines out of this one. It's gonna be one big angry guys with guns party for sure.</Msg><Username>auntie_theresa</Username><Timestamp>1358647891808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:11:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358647999080-115</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"finish his second term and, if things go well, perhaps there will be talk of a third term." I mentioned the possibility of a third term a few weeks ago and was called a crazy conspiracy theorist...A Third Term ??...I guess you STILL don't get it</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358647999080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:13:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358649302822-116</Id><Topic><Title>Have they reached their $2 billion in share buybacks yet?</Title><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614513537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:55:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpity.</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358649302822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:35:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358652346407-117</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did Rand come up again? Thought we had put her in her place already.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1358652346407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:25:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358652728328-118</Id><Topic><Title>Have they reached their $2 billion in share buybacks yet?</Title><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614513537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:55:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne boy how many IDs do you have? LMFAO</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1358652728328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:32:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358653522944-119</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pity is a useless emotion for undeveloped minds. People who feel pity usually feel it mostly for themselves. Focus your pity on yourself where it belongs since you believe in the value of pity. I could see why you and Hooz are impressed by an obscure 37 year English major with no audience and who is woefully short on talent or real world experience. You exhibit thinking patterns that are linear, two dimensional and binary and you are unable to see the bigger picture. You are easily manipulated and perfect material for useful idiot duty for do nothing no talent people like Sirota.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358653522944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:45:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>