<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357967319113-1</Id><Topic><Title>What does a coplete FAA review mean is it serious problem for Boeing ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357948202578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 18:50:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ron yes sir you got it then !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357967319113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 00:08:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357971051577-2</Id><Topic><Title>Republicons have the Constitutional Right to be idiots !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357924049514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 12:07:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But libs, who don't believe in the constitution, just do it all on their own</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1357971051577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:10:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357988951688-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why do we REALLY need a NATIONAL gun database now...whats the agenda ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357954212577</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 20:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you trying to be a funny DFC?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357988951688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 06:09:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357995316877-4</Id><Title>Think Only the Rich Will Pay More Taxes?</Title><Msg>Obama wants to raise them again. http://www.cnbc.com/id/100372837</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1357995316877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 07:55:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357996891995-5</Id><Topic><Title>747-8</Title><Username>ariel.lacson</Username><Timestamp>1357938784471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 16:13:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ole Dell George continues his hate jihad against Boeing- the company that dared fire him after catching him in his "unnatural act" in the Renton restroom HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1357996891995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:21:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357998182122-6</Id><Title>This company</Title><Msg>is making junk airplanes. the stock price will continue to go down.</Msg><Username>reorrr</Username><Timestamp>1357998182122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:43:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358002792263-7</Id><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Msg>The cold, hard numbers make it clear that when there are more guns there is less crime, but hardcore leftists such as Piers Morgan are absolutely obsessed with gun control and Morgan continues to relentlessly attack the 2nd Amendment night after night. We need to start pointing out that he is not telling the truth. The following are 18 facts that prove that Piers Morgan is flat out lying about gun control… #1 The UK has approximately 125 percent more rape victims per 100,000 people each year than the United States does. #2 The UK has approximately 133 percent more assault victims per 100,000 people each year than the United States does. #3 Piers Morgan continues to insist that there are more than 11,000 gun murders in the United States every year. But that is flat out wrong. According to the FBI, there were 8,583 gun murders in the United States during 2011. And as Ben Swann recently pointed out, 400 of those were justifiable homicides by law enforcement and 260 of those were justifiable homicides by private citizens. #4 The United States is #1 in the world in gun ownership, and yet it is only 28thin the world in gun murders per 100,000 people. #5 The violent crime rate in the United States actually fell from 757.7 per 100,000 in 1992 to 386.3 per 100,000 in 2011. During that same time period, the murder rate fell from 9.3 per 100,000 to 4.7 per 100,000. This was during an era when gun laws in the United States generally became much less restrictive. #6 The city of Chicago has some of the strictest gun laws in the United States. So has this reduced crime? Of course not. As I wrote about the other day, the murder rate in Chicago was about 17 percent higher in 2012 than it was in 2011, and Chicago is now considered to be “the deadliest global city“. If you can believe it, there were about as many murders in Chicago during 2012 as there was in the entire nation of Japan. #7 After the city of Kennesaw, Georgia passed a law requiring every home to have a gun, the crime rate dropped by more than 50 percent over the course of the next 23 years. #8 Approximately 200,000 women in the United States use guns to protect themselves against sexual crime every single year. #9 Overall, guns in the United States are used 80 times more often to prevent crime than they are to take lives. #10 Only about 3.5 percent of the gun murders in the United States are caused by rifles. #11 According to Gallup, an all-time record 74 percent of all Americans are against a total handgun ban in the United States. #12 Down in Australia, gun murders increased by about 19 percent and armed robberies increased by about 69 percent after a gun ban was instituted. #13 When Piers Morgan claims that there are only 35 gun murders in the UK per year, he isn’t exactly being accurate. According to official statistics, there were59 gun murders in the UK in 2011. It is also important to keep in mind that gun crime was already super low even before the gun ban in the UK was instituted, and that a 2009 article in The Telegraph declared that gun crime had doubledover the past decade even though it is widely acknowledged that crime statistics in the UK are massively underreported. #14 The UK has the fourth highest burglary rate in the EU. #15 The UK has the second highest overall crime rate in the EU. #16 A 2009 article in The Telegraph had this stunning headline: “UK is violent crime capital of Europe“. #17 Despite the very strict ban on guns in the UK, the truth is that the UK is a far more violent society than the United States is. In one recent year, there were2,034 violent crimes per 100,000 people in the UK. In the United States, there were only 466 violent crimes per 100,000 people during that same year. Do we really want to be more like the UK? #18 According to Gun Owners of America, the governments of the world slaughtered more than 170 million of their own people during the 20th century. The vast majority of those people had been disarmed by their own governments prior to being slaughtered. But you won’t hear many of these statistics on the mainstream news, will you?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358003613293-8</Id><Topic><Title>Man Shoots Robbery Suspect, Protects 2-Month-Old Son</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1357830787108</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 10:13:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"EXECUTIVE Privelege action is being considered!!!"........in other words there is no need for Congress and our founding fathers idea of CHECKS AND BALANCES on one man having too much power...Lets disband congress and the supremee court and lets do away with states...all power should be in the executive branch at the Federal level. Astonishing what is happenning in America</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358003613293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:13:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358003864551-9</Id><Topic><Title>"An armed man is a citizen. A disarmed man is a subject."</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357912941448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:02:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What we need to do is take freedom away from government!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358003864551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:17:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358004115894-10</Id><Topic><Title>This is my Rifle - This is my Gun</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357915157098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"this is my rifle, there are many like it but this one is mine. My rifle is my best friend. It is my life. I must master it as i master my life. Without me it is useless, without my rifle i am useless. i will fire my rifle true, i must shoot straighter than my enemy who is trying to kill me, i must shoot him before he shoots me….i will. My rifle and myself know what counts in war is not the rounds we fire, the noise of our burst, nor the smoke we make. We know that it is hits that count. We will hit… my rifle is human, even as i, because it is my life. Thus i will learn it as a brother, learn its weaknesses, its strengths, its parts, its accessories, its sights and its barrel. I will ever guard it against the raveges of weather and damage. I will keep my rifle clean and ready, even as i am clean and ready. We will become part of each other. We will… before god i swear this creed, my rifle and myself are the defenders of my counrty, we are the masters of our enemy, we are the saviors of my life. So be it, untill there is no enemy but peace."</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358004115894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:21:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358004232980-11</Id><Topic><Title>Arms, Well Regulated and Militias</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357873062755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 21:57:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The second amendment is more important then ever.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358004232980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005031973-12</Id><Topic><Title>BEAR MARKET YET stock market timing,</Title><Username>jamivelardifnky9085</Username><Timestamp>1307113763000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-06-03 11:09:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its Useful</Msg><Username>j.ivans</Username><Timestamp>1358005031973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:37:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005432063-13</Id><Topic><Title>Pay Attention - A Glimpse in the Future - The Collapse is Coming</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357938927106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 16:15:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats and half the republican are fiddling while America burns.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358005432063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:43:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358007352386-14</Id><Title>Not Many REAL AMERICANS Post on this Board</Title><Msg>Just a few like MIir, Spartacus, x6xxx and a few others. The rest are progressives/socialists/Democrats/communists/fascists.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358007352386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:15:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358008301759-15</Id><Topic><Title>Not Many REAL AMERICANS Post on this Board</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358007352386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:15:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The socialists spread their ilk wherever they can. They think by doing so on a message board they are doing their part to further socialism. What decent American wants to discuss anything with them? Facts just get in their way of furthering their ugly, destructive ideology.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358008301759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:31:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358008611705-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner uses Lithium Ion Batteries - These are unstable &amp; can start fires</Title><Username>hysailr</Username><Timestamp>1357918332765</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 10:32:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and yet, here they are, catching on fire. what you have at boeing is a bunch of managers and too few workers who actually know how to properly design electrical equipment that fall WELL within design limitations. and since the managers are more focused on time &amp; budger rather than design integrity, they choose to outsouce a lot of stuff.... and hence, the ;laqck of quality suffers even more. within boeing, it's the classic peter principle "flying-T" formation... where you have 10 managers to every competent worker. if you do not believe that, them come and work for boeing and see for yourself - HA HA HA mind explaining why, if Lithium is so safe, that they caught on fire then? LOLOLOL not just once either.... and why can't they make fuel tanks that do not leak? the auto industry doesn't make many cars with fuel tanks that leak. once again, it's the ole flying T formation - too many incompenant managers pointing held up in meeting after meeting after meeting with their eyes glazing over all of these budget &amp; schedukle charts with little or no focus on what is actually going on down in the production lab. lincompenence tends to get promoted into management positions.... and many of the highly experienced engineers have either retired or had their jobs outsourced... leaving a bunch of greenhorns who make routine mistakes &amp; get managed by the incompenant managers above.</Msg><Username>hysailr</Username><Timestamp>1358008611705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:36:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358008972712-17</Id><Title>America Needs Government but Who Should say fir it.......</Title><Msg>...how much should they pay and how should they pay it? Progressives don't want you to know the answer to those Questions. The answer would be very different if people actually knew how much of the cost of goods or services are due to taxes. That's why they have to take taxes out of paychecks before people see them.. If there were only one single tax on all goods and services people would know for sure how much of the cost of those goods and services are due to federal taxes and they would dang sure know who paid them. It would stop a lot of political corruption where legislators reward friends and donors with tax laws that favor them. It would also stop those corrupt politicians from picking winners and losers.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358008972712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:42:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358009932674-18</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have to concede the point. Morgan is lying</Msg><Username>rividiott</Username><Timestamp>1358009932674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:58:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358010887443-19</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent post Spart....thanks!</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358010887443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:14:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358011044408-20</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple basic fact....if the person spewing can be identified as a liberal...then they are lying. Lying goes with the ideology.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358011044408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:17:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358012261877-21</Id><Topic><Title>America Needs Government but Who Should say fir it.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358008972712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:42:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Before someone goes berserk and devolves into ignorant ecstasy over finding a typo on a stock message board you better let them know you meant to say "America Needs Government but Who Should pay for it?" When you're dealing with victims of socialized government education, they tend to ignore the message and act like a two year old who found their first Easter egg when they discover a typo.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358012261877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:37:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358012413245-22</Id><Topic><Title>America Needs Government but Who Should say fir it.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358008972712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:42:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post. I absolutely agree but the last thing a progressive wants is a fair system of taxation where everyone pays their fair share.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358012413245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:40:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358013719915-23</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice try Sparty, actual it is a pathetic try.</Msg><Username>rividiot</Username><Timestamp>1358013719915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:01:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358013907528-24</Id><Topic><Title>FAA is a Rubber Stamp Committee</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357919413824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 10:50:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McNerney needs to be fired</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1358013907528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:05:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358014116030-25</Id><Topic><Title>This is my Rifle - This is my Gun</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357915157098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You embarras yourself by posting such drivel.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1358014116030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:08:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358014816679-26</Id><Topic><Title>VERY SOON A 787 WILL CRASH !</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1357937337312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 15:48:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the crashes begin to happen with the Dreamliner, those coming lawsuits against Boeing will put Boeing in bankruptcy. Oh well, nothing lasts forever. Bye Boing. Better sell now while the going is still good.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1358014816679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:20:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358015627898-27</Id><Topic><Title>Not Many REAL AMERICANS Post on this Board</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358007352386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:15:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good observation.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358015627898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:33:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358015676285-28</Id><Topic><Title>This is my Rifle - This is my Gun</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357915157098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 09:39:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So which one are you?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358015676285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:34:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358017061709-29</Id><Topic><Title>VERY SOON A 787 WILL CRASH !</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1357937337312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 15:48:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is one time I agee with you I work at triumph in texas, Plow Shear, Leading Edge, FTB, FTE etc are being shipping in from china they are your new supplier. Management rubber stamps everything off knowing the work is wrong preload conditions, wrong rivets, riding condition etc etc. Triumph vision is SCHEDULE IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN QUALITY</Msg><Username>lowhigh102</Username><Timestamp>1358017061709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:57:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358017791202-30</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>excellent...but repeat after me, FACTS are meaningless to libiots, they are all about and only about emotion...especially hate...they are forced to rely on better men than themselves to make a living and protect them, that's why they crave big governemt</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1358017791202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:09:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358020104718-31</Id><Title>boeing pot use</Title><Msg>When is Boeing security going to stop the pot smoking in the Everett parking lots.?</Msg><Username>man711</Username><Timestamp>1358020104718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:48:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358020314083-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Dreamliner is turning into the NIGHTMAREliner!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753377856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The y alone had to scrap the first TWO DOZEN PLANES off the production line as beyond repair." A lie! They scraped 3, the rest are being reworked.</Msg><Username>man711</Username><Timestamp>1358020314083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:51:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358022734019-33</Id><Topic><Title>boeing pot use</Title><Username>man711</Username><Timestamp>1358020104718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:48:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not until they control the pot heads in the Bored of Direcftionless And if YOU have proof of the pot smoking in parkinglots- turn it in !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358022734019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:32:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358025414168-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Dreamliner is turning into the NIGHTMAREliner!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753377856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they just build a computer by assembling all components coming from all over the world, it is fine. Crash would not cause much roar. However, it is AIRPLANE, and they build a giant #$%$ airplane with so many problems within so short time. It is unbelievable. If they go bankrupt because of this "DREMALINER", no body would be sympathetic. From now when I take a flight, I will definitely make sure it is not "DREAMLINER".</Msg><Username>jameswyz</Username><Timestamp>1358025414168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:16:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358025867958-35</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wanted to vote for republicans but when I saw Romney was dumber, I felt hopeless and voted to let Obama to stay.</Msg><Username>jameswyz</Username><Timestamp>1358025867958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:24:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358027489087-36</Id><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Msg>The U.S. government ordered a wide-ranging review of Boeing's latest passenger jet, the 787 and Ray Goforth, executive director of the Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace (SPEEA), said Boeing's latest offer still included drastic cuts from the contract that expired in November. So while Boeing claims they are doing great , paid investors a increased dividend, are sitting on 20 billion in cash and gave millions in excessive bonus payola to executives. The workers who were not allowed to engineer the latest Boeing airplane the SPEEA represented engineers are being shorted. If Boeing had gone with SPEEA recommendations the plane would have been engineered with more safety and higher passing standard of safety that is one reason Boeing did not want to go with their own engineering employees, cheap was the most important consideration. SPEEA wanted the 787 to be built right the first time. The outsourcing result over 3 .5 years late and over 30 billion dollars in extra cost . The executives could have saved 20 billion of the excessive 787 cheap outsourcing money and gave it to themselves . The last 100% SPEEA engineered Boeing plane was the 777 which was made on time and within budget and did not need a FAA system wide review . It did not have “birthing” problems that required a government FAA complete engineering and assembly review and sure did not have about “10 incidents on 787s in six weeks, one jet suffered a cracked cockpit window on Friday”, other 787 problems oil leak, fuel leak, brake issues or false flight deck indicators , and fire. So the (SPEEA) made 777 delivery schedule ( SPEEA made the 777 , not the 787) was good, not like the sick 787. “If this is a design issue, it will be more troublesome because we need to pause the production to fix the design and then proceed," said Morningstar analyst Neal Dihora”. “The review will focus on the 787's advanced electrical systems and cover their design, manufacture and assembly, the Federal Aviation Administration said. The move comes on top of a separate probe by U.S. safety investigators into a battery fire that caused "serious damage" to an empty Japan Airlines” Are the Boeing fail safe redundancies a good thing ? “"You now have the interdependencies that you didn't have before. The systems are much better when they work but they're harder to guarantee that they will work all the time and it's harder to predict what will happen when something fails," said R. John Hansman in an interview. Are the redundancies good for the electrical systems like the lithium battery? Boeings Chief Engineer pointed out once a battery gets to the burning stage nothing will put out the fire. In fact 15 fire trucks and 40 firefighters on the ground had to remove the battery and toss it on the ground. That option is not available 30000 feet in the sky going 600 mph, and 1 hour from land over the water ! Can a 787 plane stay in the air with a fire on board for an hour? The battery only started burning for 3 minutes and it already had those small 2 foot flames !. So how’s that cheap outsourcing and not using the American engineers working out for you now Excessively paid Boeing management? The public is now of the opinion “If it’s a outsourced 787 Boeing I am not going</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358027642023-37</Id><Title>Mony people on here have asked Why Democrats Hate Freedom so Much?</Title><Msg>Democrats realize they're not smart enough to spend their own money so they had rather give up more and more of their freedom and spend less and less of the money they earn so corrupt elitist politicians can spend it for them. They also know they're not smart enough to live their lives and run their businesses with out a lot of regulations so they're quite willing to give up more freedom and hand it over to the corrupt elitist politicians who will be glad to regulate their lives and businesses more and more each year. Yes. Democrats do have a great fear of freedom.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1358027642023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:54:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358030092585-38</Id><Topic><Title>Mony people on here have asked Why Democrats Hate Freedom so Much?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1358027642023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:54:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think far more people are wondering how you got so stupid!!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1358030092585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:34:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358032736573-39</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid? plain as opposed to perfectly stupid ? Naw- nobody is perfect, but in this case they are above plain, and nearing the supremely stupid category.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358032736573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:18:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358033008933-40</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals (I choke on that word....they are Authoritarian control freaks)...Hate...and I do mean HATE facts.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033008933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:23:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358033206593-41</Id><Title>Obama arms the Muslim Brotherhood.......</Title><Msg>but doesnt want YOU as an American citizen to have an AR-15.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033206593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358033443981-42</Id><Topic><Title>Mony people on here have asked Why Democrats Hate Freedom so Much?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1358027642023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:54:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. Oh brilliant genius....why are Democrats so afraid of Freedom?........this ouughtta to be good. Don't forget more government means less freedom..</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1358033443981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:30:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358033648468-43</Id><Topic><Title>America Needs Government but Who Should say fir it.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358008972712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:42:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Question....."your Fair Share" takes on a new meaning when everyone is treated the same.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1358033648468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:34:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358033836835-44</Id><Title>Forced Redistribution of Wealth is Immoral</Title><Msg>It's thievery at best. At its worst it make a mockery out of democracy.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1358033836835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:37:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358033942580-45</Id><Title>An Administration that could stage "Fast and Furious...</Title><Msg>...to whip up sentiment to take your guns...(and there is now NO DOUBT THAT THEY DID) ....COULD HAVE STAGED THE AURORA SHOOTINGS !!! .......think about it....and think about why they would go to these lengths to disarm loyal and law abiding Americans</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033942580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:39:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358034415368-46</Id><Title>JOE BITE-ME AND HIS SILVER FOOT IN MOUTH</Title><Msg>Vice President Joe Biden said on Friday he was “shooting for Tuesday” to get President Barack Obama his recommendations on how to battle an epidemic of gun violence and warned “there’s no silver bullet” to stop the killing. Biden was meeting in the Eisenhower Executive Office Building adjacent to the White House with executives from video game companies whose products have often been blamed for making players insensitive to real-world violence. ++ Lets see - gun violence- shooting for tuesday - silver bullet - Ya can make this up - No doubt he bombed out at the meeting ;_PP</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358034415368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358035114652-47</Id><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Msg>Was against the war under Bush before they were for it under Obama !!! Thinks it is wonderful that Our Government want to take our guns but just gushs that Michael Moore and Piers Morgan have heavily armend body guards !!!! Both Want to sponge off the government and gush about how ‘compassionate” and Liberal it is to help the poor….as long as it isn’t their money….. Thinks FORCING people to have bankrupting and monstrously beaucratic health care is all part of the New Freedom in America. Thinks it is wonderful that our Government spies on all Americans and knows EVERYTHING ABOUT law abiding Americans…. but it is horrible when Americans want to ask their own President to release his records to find out who this guy really is.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358035436071-48</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much computer time do you get at the FEMA camp?</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1358035436071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:03:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358035869100-49</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BITE-ME AND HIS SILVER FOOT IN MOUTH</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358034415368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He also peppered the testifiers with whit and rapid fire questions. Joe is the loose canon of the POTUS team.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358035869100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:11:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358037499016-50</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BITE-ME AND HIS SILVER FOOT IN MOUTH</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358034415368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rapid fire with an empty magazine is difficult - as with a battle of wits, he was/is unarmed. Thus he had to use his loose cannon !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358037499016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:38:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358039624763-51</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's kids schools has 11 armed guards</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358039461020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:11:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He took the Hypocritical Oath too</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358039624763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:13:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358039743255-52</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's kids schools has 11 armed guards</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358039461020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:11:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you really that stupid? The Presidents kids (Any Presidents kids) are high profile, obvious targets. Not the same as the average school. You just keep embarrassing yourself.</Msg><Username>rividiot</Username><Timestamp>1358039743255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:15:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358040780757-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obama arms the Muslim Brotherhood.......</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033206593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its dangerous to all living things to arm the Muslim Brotherhood and to allow American citizens to have machine guns.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358040780757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358041945794-54</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I understand as the rub to Boeing, the union's wage scale demands are not realistic to the current economic climate and national market wage scales. Boeing wanted very much for the union to design and engineer the 787 but Boeing could not afford SPEEA workers. As is, Boeing will be losing money on the 787 for years to come. By the union demands it is apparent the union is not interested in Boeing being successful. The union wants to eat Boeing's lunch. How sad.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358041945794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:52:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358042728040-55</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BITE-ME AND HIS SILVER FOOT IN MOUTH</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358034415368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He blasts his critics and mows down the opposition, well he tries but he can't hit the bullseye.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358042728040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:05:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358043111667-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama arms the Muslim Brotherhood.......</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033206593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you comparing the two?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358043111667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:11:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358043240291-57</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't "they" just a couple of anti-American POS?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358043240291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:14:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358043420026-58</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you putting the Kent Raven in that category, or is he just too stupid to even make the cut?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358043420026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:17:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358044150748-59</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats a Big Rog !</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358044150748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:29:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358044276051-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obama arms the Muslim Brotherhood.......</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033206593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he is arming the Drug Cartels to demonize the second amendment...(and this is all admitted) ...and he is arming AlQaeda...(also main stream news)....and he wants to disarm Americans...what does that make Barry Soetoro ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358044276051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:31:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358044303165-61</Id><Topic><Title>An Administration that could stage "Fast and Furious...</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033942580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:39:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358044303165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:31:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358047225458-62</Id><Topic><Title>Obama arms the Muslim Brotherhood.......</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033206593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The comparison is obvious. Arms to both are dangerous to all living things.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358047225458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:20:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358047620696-63</Id><Topic><Title>Frontline PBS Tuesday night right after the ingoration his</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358042804861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 21:06:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"right after the ingoration his" Transration to Engrish prease.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1358047620696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:27:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358048108564-64</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What terrifies normal Americans is the thought of paranoid freaks like Spartaloonkook being armed. Or breeding. Or operating machinery. Or voting. Or working at a 7-11. Or driving. Or going out in public.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1358048108564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:35:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>