<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376280613098-1</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So long as you believe that only persons who meet YOUR definition of physical perfection can be effective, you show yourself to be shallow, stupid, and ... well, nuts.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376280613098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 00:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376281306232-2</Id><Topic><Title>d_proch on boeing and his credibility BIOL is his other pcik down 45% -1 month -60%-3month up 10%-5 years ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376275765278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>d_proch I just looked at your recent user comments, you have only been a member for a few months.d_proch! I lookedat your pick BIOL, for the time you have been a member and then for 5 years and the results of your opinion on BIOL stand as given. well good luck with that then. I hope you make a bundled_d-proch, on your personal ability as you described it for the message board and your personal meetings wit the "dudes" at the companies that swing the corporate doors wide open for you. I do not have to meet any company executive to learn which stocks are good . I use a sector by sector analysis d-proch, the autosector is great up about 100%, the best stock in the sector is tesla, and tesla has at least twice the range of the next best EV car or more has top of the line engineering excellence awards, and safety awards, and is beating the expected quarterly earning projection. d_proch, while whomever you met at Boeing apparently has not been a vary good stock market source as Boeing is trailing Airbus for the year to date and for 5 years now , you comment of "Airbus Who", should be "Boeing who" based on stock price gain results buy maybe you can go for a 60% loss in Boeing too. . I have made 350% ytd on TSLA this year, 1200% gain on ACAD last year and until SteveJobs died made many thousands of percent gains over 12 years. Apple is a company like Boeing now , it started to get professionally managed with incompetent key people who are kissers of the next guys up you know what. the current kiss up is a - baseball player who was not good at GE or MMM and is just as good at BA, go figure!. READ JOHN HART-SMITH, if your a big player take your jet to Australia and meet with him.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376281306232</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 00:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376281490558-3</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing volume shows that investors are leaving Boeing stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376251798684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:09:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let me guess 3 thumbs and VZ, osulinn, and domer where sparti a day off</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376281490558</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 00:24:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376300533411-4</Id><Topic><Title>How Obama turned Obamacare into a weapon</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376180736075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 20:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven is a parrot.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1376300533411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 05:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376300671036-5</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Next Missed Deadline Be the Last?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376249299702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:28:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing has changed? Really? When that article was written, over 3 years ago, the 1st 787 hadn't been delivered yet. There are now approximately 50 of 'em delivered and flying all over the globe you douche bag. I don't need to do any research. I work for the company you idiot. Hey, why don't you impress us all with your vast resources and tell us whose A/Ps are now moving through the Renton factory on Line 2, if you can that is. I fully expect silence from you because as everybody here knows, you're just a #$%$ artist. Go back to grade school and learn how to write you whack job. I have 5 y/o nieces and nephews who write better than you. Jesus.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376300671036</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 05:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376300783172-6</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everything the parrot was against, now the parrot is for. That makes the parrot either a hypocrite or crazy.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1376300783172</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 05:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376303310768-7</Id><Title>The Gov't Cry's Wolf</Title><Msg>During the height of criticism being leveled on the NSA by many members of Congress and the public, our Gov't found away to quell public criticism. The Gov't reported that they intercepted chatter of a major al Qaeda plot in the next several days raising the terror alert and requiring the closing of some 19 embassies and cautioning US travelers to let the State Dept know of their whereabouts. The scare tactic worked. Conveniently now 18 embassies are reopened, The embassy in Lahore Pakistan will remain closed, as it should be. Lahore Pakistan has been a terrorist hotspot going back before the Crimean War. So now the NSA supporters can boast the secret but claimed unconstitutional NSA methods saves us.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376303310768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 06:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376304731173-8</Id><Title>USAA Insurance sinks to new low!! Higher Premiums and mis-management under Robles</Title><Msg>and "his gang" have left the insurer depending on tv ads and no open door policy under Robles mis-management</Msg><Username>consumercon101</Username><Timestamp>1376304731173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 06:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376310867474-9</Id><Title>Who is the Real Patriot</Title><Msg>General Alexander reminds me of General James Mattoon Scott in the movie Seven Days in May. Like Gen Scott, General Alexander runs secret operations that he feels are necessary to protect our nation. Until the whistleblower and Patriot Edward Snowden came along Congress was deliberately kept in the dark by the NSA that all Americans were under surveillance. Once the Director of Intelligence was caught with his pants down he admitted he had been making erroneous errors to Congress. Now President Obama comes along and wants to take credit for what Edward Snowden has accomplished. Obama announced that he was planning all along to to make the secret NSA more transparent and in line with the Constitution and did not need Snowden's revelations. Now with Snowden's leaks the process of NSA transparency is being forced to move faster. The truth is without the uproar coming to the White House resulting from Snowden revelations our government was turning fascist.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376310867474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 08:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376314513845-10</Id><Topic><Title>USAA Insurance sinks to new low!! Higher Premiums and mis-management under Robles</Title><Username>consumercon101</Username><Timestamp>1376304731173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 06:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's Robles? There's an easy fact to understand. It is estimated now under Obama that 80% of the public will experience poverty at some point in their lives. Who can afford insurance? The poor folks that think ObamaCare will be free will have to pay for it. Free was just another Obama lie.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376314513845</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 09:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376317814103-11</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Next Missed Deadline Be the Last?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376249299702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:28:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Del. It's got to be depressing to know that the people that don't have you on ignore just automatically give you a TD when they see you've posted some of your usual drivel. I would be very humiliated, embarrassed and not likely to show myself on this board if it were me. But, no doubt you will soon be taking a new user name!! HarHarHar!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1376317814103</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 10:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376317856520-12</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Next Missed Deadline Be the Last?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376249299702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:28:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>vierzig_nachten you said '"I don't need to do any research.{(and) that you}" I work for the company you idiot" well BA stock price is, as my research shows, continuing to be going down, BTW what do you do for Boeing ???????since you just admitted you work for Boeing . Usually a worker would admit that if he were honest, and since you work for Boeing????? I suggest you review the ethics agreement you were required to sign and also review the policy on using vulgar language and then get back to me Now that you admitted that you work for Boeing you are required to refrain from any and all vulgar words and disclose in any user comment per your ethics agreement , that you are a Boeing employee, to not do so is a termination offense. Next Vierzig_nachten, Boeing Employee, Reference to your lack of research, and your claim about the Approximate" 50 787 delivered" your off by a huge amount, as of july ist 73 =787 planes built and delivered. Vierzig_Nachten I will be referencing your claim of being a Boeing worker from now on !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376317856520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 10:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376319377040-13</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing volume shows that investors are leaving Boeing stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376251798684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:09:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about that, I said that Boeing was done at or around the 107 stock price range , per Tom OBrien and would retrace to 71 dollars over time. last moth Boeing share price was negative and the price keeps falling too, learn to read a stock chart and watch volume, very easy to do , you just have to stop the hopey- changy wish thing, and become a stock trader . Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376319377040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 10:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376324414074-14</Id><Topic><Title>God Help America If the Next President is A Democrat</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1376261664688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:54:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans are going to need more than a God to help them to Win the Presidency.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376324414074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 12:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376326147109-15</Id><Title>oh oh more bad news</Title><Msg>A prominent scientist who was skeptical of the evidence that climate change was real, let alone that it was caused by humans, now says he has made a "total turnaround." Richard Muller, a professor of physics at the University of California, Berkeley, says he has become convinced that "the prior estimates of the rate of warming were correct," and that humans are "almost entirely the cause" of that warming. Muller co-founded the Berkeley Earth Surface Temperature (BEST) team two years ago in order to independently assess what he viewed as questionable evidence of global warming. In a series of papers published last year, BEST presented their statistical analysis of 1.6 billion temperature reports spanning the last 200 years, controlling for possible biases in the data that are often cited by skeptics as reasons to doubt the reality of global warming. Their analysis indicated that global warming is real — that the average global land temperature has risen by 2.5 degrees Fahrenheit (1.4 degrees Celsius) since 1750, including 1.5 degrees F (0.9 degrees Celsius) in the past 50 years. The numbers closely agree with the findings of past studies by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), NASA and others; but finally, they were rigorous enough to satisfy Muller. Now, in a brand new study that probed the causes of that warming, the BEST team says it has cleared from blame the natural variations in Earth's climate that so often get implicated by skeptics. Muller and his colleagues implicate carbon dioxide emissions by humans as essentially the sole cause of global warming. "The carbon dioxide curve gives a better match than anything else we've tried," he wrote Saturday (July 28) in a New York Times editorial. "Its magnitude is consistent with the calculated greenhouse effect — extra warming from trapped heat radiation. These facts don't prove causality and they shouldn't end skepticism, but they raise the bar: To be considered seriously, an alternative explanation must match the data at least as well as carbon dioxide does." That's a high bar indeed. In graphs released with the new study, a red line representing the atmoaspheric concentration of CO2 crawls across the decades almost exactly tracing the black line representing the observed warming of the Earth. [What Are Climate Change Skeptics Still Skeptical About?] By comparison, the study found that natural variability, including variations in the solar cycle, El Niño events and the Atlantic multidecadal oscillation (shifts in sea-surface temperatures that run in cycles), could have accounted for no more than 0.17 degrees Celsius of temperature variation — either warming or cooling — during the past 150 years. These natural forces are much subtler than the warming seen during the same time period. In fact, the new results indicate that humans have been warming the Earth for longer than climate scientists previously thought certain. "In its 2007 report, the [United Nations Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change] concluded only that most of the warming of the prior 50 years could be attributed to humans," Muller wrote. "It was possible, according to the I.P.C.C. consensus statement, that the warming before 1956 could be because of changes in solar activity, and that even a substantial part of the more recent warming could be natural." Not so, according to the new findings; variations in solar activity have a negligible effect on Earth's temperature. The handiwork is almost all our own. "I embarked on this analysis to answer questions that, to my mind, had not been answered," Muller wrote. "I hope that the Berkeley Earth analysis will help settle the scientific debate regarding global warming and its human causes. Then comes the difficult part: agreeing across the political and diplomatic spectrum about what can and should be done."</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376326147109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 12:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376326351645-16</Id><Title>AMERICANS RENOUNCING CITIZENSHIP AT RECORD LEVELS</Title><Msg>Globally, more U.S. citizens have renounced their citizenship in the first and second quarters than all of 2012 combined, and 2013 is already on track to becoming a record year for renunciations. A total of 1,130 names appeared on the latest list of renunciations from the Internal Revenue Service, according to Andrew Mitchel, a tax lawyer who tracks the data. That is far above the previous high of 679, set in the first quarter, and more than were reported in all of 2012. While those numbers are still a fraction of the estimated six million Americans living abroad, lawyers say the main trigger for cutting ties with U.S. recently is the Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act, or Fatca, which requires foreign institutions to disclose the overseas assets of U.S. green-card holders and citizens to the U.S. government.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376326351645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 12:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376328280867-17</Id><Topic><Title>Someone needs to tell Rand Paul that Milton Friedman isn't... well, alive</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376257847560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 17:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chris_genna2 would pick the guy in tub number 3 at the Kent bath house.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376328280867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376328510229-18</Id><Title>DOG DAYS: BO AIRLIFTED TO OBAMA HOLIDAY HOME...</Title><Msg>Bo, the president's Portuguese Water Dog, arrived separately on one of two MV-22 Ospreys, a hybrid aircraft which takes off like a helicopter but flies like a plane.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376328510229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376329199207-19</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My Crystal Balls are telling me Hillary won't even get the progressive communist nomination for president.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376329199207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376329796718-20</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Next Missed Deadline Be the Last?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376249299702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:28:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do I do for Boeing? As I've told you at least once before, I'm an engineer. Is your inability to write a grammatically correct sentence in the English language surpassed only by your inability to read and comprehend it? It would appear so. Time to adjust that tinfoil hat you're wearing because ethics has absolutely nothing do with my comments to you ... "... you are required to refrain from any and all vulgar words and disclose in any user comment per your ethics agreement , that you are a Boeing employee, to not do so is a termination offense." #$%$ The policy concerning the use of "salty" language applies only when I'm on company property or representing the company in an official manner. What I do on my own time when I'm representing only myself is none of their business.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376329796718</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376329837438-21</Id><Title>41%: Obama's Approval Drops to Lowest Level in Gallup Poll</Title><Msg>Makes you wonder if 41% is the total percent of people are on welfare, food stamps, disability, government jobs and in mental institutions.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376329837438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376331255037-22</Id><Title>"Socialism requires that government becomes your god"</Title><Msg>In a fiery address over the weekend, Sen. Ted Cruz's father told a crowd of Christian conservatives in Iowa that the United States is edging toward socialism under President Barack Obama, as he joined his son in denouncing Obamacare. According to ABC News, Texas pastor Rafael Cruz also offered a veiled comparison of Obama to Cuban leader Fidel Castro as he spoke of being a Cuban immigrant who fled the perils of socialism at the time of Castro's communist revolution and later became a U.S. citizen. In an apparent reference to Obama's 2008 campaign theme of "hope and change," Cruz told the annual summit of the conservative Family Leader group that Castro was "a young charismatic leader" who "rose up, talking about hope and change" to convince people to follow his revolution. "Socialism requires that government becomes your god," he said at one point. "That's why they have to destroy the concept of God. They have to destroy all loyalties except loyalty to government." Referring specifically to Obama's healthcare-reform law, the elder Cruz said it likely would kill some older Americans. "Let me tell you, our lives are under attack," he said, adding: "Obamacare is going to destroy the elderly by denying care, by even, perhaps, denying treatment to people who are in catastrophic circumstances."</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376331255037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376331364458-23</Id><Topic><Title>Fred Thompson, Hero of the Right... wants to sell you a reverse mortgage!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376329810018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, You must be bored and having a difficult time thinking of subjects to post. Or, this is a test? Did I pass? BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376331364458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376331643685-24</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary who?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376331643685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376332344027-25</Id><Topic><Title>"Socialism requires that government becomes your god"</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376331255037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:14:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>neither pastor Cruz or yourself have got a clue as to what Socialism is. All you have is the arrogance of ignorance- which causes you to preach about Socialism- go to the internet and look up the word socialism. BTW if you are in BA's psychdept then that department is indeed f....ked up</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376332344027</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376332462795-26</Id><Topic><Title>"Socialism requires that government becomes your god"</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376331255037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:14:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBTW its doubtful if any country on the planet wants to be socialist- don't believe it ask some folks who ought to know like Cubans, Beylo Russians Zimbabweans</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376332462795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376332869913-27</Id><Topic><Title>Fred Thompson, Hero of the Right... wants to sell you a reverse mortgage!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376329810018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would anyone waste their time with Fred Thompson when they can get a face lift from Debbie Boone.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376332869913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376333093761-28</Id><Topic><Title>"Socialism requires that government becomes your god"</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376331255037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:14:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wen to internet and did a search for socialism and I kept getting redirected to the DNC website.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376333093761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376333719106-29</Id><Topic><Title>"Socialism requires that government becomes your god"</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376331255037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:14:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh - I forgot to tell you you have to know how to read when you get the internet site up- and maybe be able to wipe your own sas too</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376333719106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376334317325-30</Id><Title>Deliveries improving</Title><Msg>It seems that there may be a surge in deliveries starting this week. A mix of plane models have had test flights and should be ready for delivery in the next 5 days.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376334317325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376334780830-31</Id><Title>Tac communications is a big thing!</Title><Msg>I was in the the Air Force and was in the communicatiions field and later an Avionics tech. They flew me all over the world to fix grounded aircraft. The Air Force is the best!</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376334780830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376334872379-32</Id><Topic><Title>41%: Obama's Approval Drops to Lowest Level in Gallup Poll</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376329837438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, the sequester is causing reduction of federal benefits to a lot of people who rely on them. The people are not happy about this.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376334872379</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376335195996-33</Id><Topic><Title>41%: Obama's Approval Drops to Lowest Level in Gallup Poll</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376329837438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He had lower approvals only once, in September 2011, and it was 38% then. What has caused this recent drop?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376335195996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376335306202-34</Id><Topic><Title>AMERICANS RENOUNCING CITIZENSHIP AT RECORD LEVELS</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376326351645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 12:52:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can leave also if you don`t want to pay taxes and contribute to society, Good riddance I say!! 1,130 out of over 300 million is nothing anyway I bet more people come here every month if not daily than that .</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376335306202</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376335401476-35</Id><Topic><Title>41%: Obama's Approval Drops to Lowest Level in Gallup Poll</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376329837438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He still doubles what the last Republican President got for approval ratings.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376335401476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376335852496-36</Id><Topic><Title>All of the tech indicators are pointing to a bull run in SFPI</Title><Username>efitzpatrick720</Username><Timestamp>1376319304841</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 10:55:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What tech indicators specifically?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376335852496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376335945265-37</Id><Topic><Title>41%: Obama's Approval Drops to Lowest Level in Gallup Poll</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376329837438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot of people are afraid to express disapproval of a black president. Bush INVITED disapproval with his yokel act.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376335945265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376337026864-38</Id><Topic><Title>Fred Thompson, Hero of the Right... wants to sell you a reverse mortgage!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376329810018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of those Hollywood types get an enormous lift into fame, success, and quick money. But, it is often not long lived. How many houses did Nicolas Cage have to sell recently? Fred Thompson has a "presence" and that should have generally been salable to Hollywood. Maybe he is too conservative for some folks' taste? Gotta make a buck somewhere. Of course, there is always the Bieber Burn Out path. There is a disaster looming that everyone can see - save Justin. Or maybe he sees it and can't stop. There but for the grace of God go I. There is infinite wisdom in the Tenth Commandment.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376337026864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376337335000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Fred Thompson, Hero of the Right... wants to sell you a reverse mortgage!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376329810018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reverse mortgages are a terrible financial transaction for over 90% of the homeowners conned into them. It helps to have an experienced con man like Fred Thompson peddling them on infomercials. Fast Freddy even successfully impersonated a law enforcement officer on a TV series.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1376337335000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 15:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376337647981-40</Id><Title>A Challenge to the Board's Biggest #$%$, Wayne</Title><Msg>Not all that long ago, you posted the spew below ... "waynedickenson961 • Jul 30, 2013 3:07 AM student vierzig_nachen, as a pimp and nothing more, , you just made a bold statement, you said' several of their new (American) airline Boeing 737 planes recently? moved through the factory floor. that is a out right lie veirzig_nachen, so put up or shut up, you are nothing but a Boeing barker clown, keep that big nose and those huge shoes on and paint your face white with red lips, I worked the 737 line in Renton for over 5 years and know it much better than you claim, and I can look up any American planes made at Renton for American and what plane number and delivery date tht they were taken, so demonstrate, Vierzig_nachen, your false claim, tell the message board, which 737 planes were purchased by American and when they were "recently" delivered or stop being a ignorant Boeing pimp. Wayne for Boeing 737 line" ... and it is now my turn to ask that you "put up or shut up". If you can really do that which you claim, tell me Wayne which operator's A/Ps are currently moving through the Renton factory on Line 2. I'll be waiting for your answer. If you really are as all-knowing and all-powerful as you claim to be, this ought to be an easy one for you. If, as I suspect, you're just full of bs and hot air however, then all I'll hear is crickets. Let the games begin. You've got 24 hours.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376337647981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376337677444-41</Id><Topic><Title>AMERICANS RENOUNCING CITIZENSHIP AT RECORD LEVELS</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376326351645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 12:52:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The America haters can be easily replaced if Congress would enact an immigration reform bill.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1376337677444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376337781078-42</Id><Topic><Title>"Socialism requires that government becomes your god"</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376331255037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 14:14:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As much as they like to ramble on about socialism the GOP seems to have no problem dabbling in it themselves.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1376337781078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376337806838-43</Id><Title>I Love Obamacare !!</Title><Msg>it works for the 99% - plus it drives Republicans koo koo !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1376337806838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376337821391-44</Id><Topic><Title>41%: Obama's Approval Drops to Lowest Level in Gallup Poll</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1376329837438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 13:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The thing that stands out is how brain dead the 41 % have to be. Obama is screwing govt workers, union workers....no one is exempt from the pain, and suffering BO has brought on.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376337821391</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376337836366-45</Id><Topic><Title>Someone needs to tell Rand Paul that Milton Friedman isn't... well, alive</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376257847560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 17:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody expects an honest representation of Milton Friedman's record from a Ky Republican Senator. McConnell and Paul are one of the country's worst Senate tandems.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1376337836366</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376337854453-46</Id><Title>Airbus is killing Boeing</Title><Msg>I really feel that Airbus will put Boeing out on a shoe string. I have seen Airbus execute very well. Boeing on the other hand has been selling assets and resorting to suppliers. Soon Boeing will fade away because skills are really not there as strong as I have seen. USA is heading to third world status. I think Europe is replacing USA as the place to be.</Msg><Username>cmps309</Username><Timestamp>1376337854453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376337996091-47</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party’s paranoid aesthetic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376140769507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how a lot of these so called Tea Partiers would scream bloody murder if you were to purpose eliminating social security, medicare, farm subsidies or unempoyment insurance.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1376337996091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376338345546-48</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul’s week of delusion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376092864716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 20:01:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He gets rid of the fed, which he does not have the power to do, then what?</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1376338345546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376338433974-49</Id><Topic><Title>The new Boeing!</Title><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376258632721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That dismissive attitude is the reason Airbus exists in its present form. I'm sure the boys in Tolouse welcome it.</Msg><Username>revtrst</Username><Timestamp>1376338433974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376339229703-50</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK'S STUPIDITY....</Title><Msg>Dickwaynedick thinks that since boeing hit $ 107+ and now down to $ 104+ for a little corrective action.....tom obrien is right...the stock is going to $ 71.....my lord what a dumb jerk this waynedick is! Wake up smarty!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376339229703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376339840223-51</Id><Topic><Title>The new Boeing!</Title><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376258632721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are talking about France, then you need to take your BS to the French border. The only thing the French were good at is cutting off heads!</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376339840223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376340051911-52</Id><Topic><Title>The new Boeing!</Title><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376258632721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I said, that dismissive attitude is why Airbus exists in its present form.</Msg><Username>revtrst</Username><Timestamp>1376340051911</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376340284568-53</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK'S STUPIDITY....</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376339229703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:27:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So true.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376340284568</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376340622009-54</Id><Topic><Title>The new Boeing!</Title><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376258632721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AirBus exists because Boeing lets it. Boeing needs competition to keep them on the edge of technology. I could tell you much about the technology at Boeing, but then again, I would just sound like a pumper of the company!</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376340622009</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376341000993-55</Id><Topic><Title>The new Boeing!</Title><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376258632721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They exist because Boeing lets it. Put the kool aid down.</Msg><Username>revtrst</Username><Timestamp>1376341000993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376341223480-56</Id><Topic><Title>The new Boeing!</Title><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376258632721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They exist because the Germans let it.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376341223480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 17:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376341413322-57</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Hillary</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376341413322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 17:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376342226893-58</Id><Topic><Title>A Challenge to the Board's Biggest #$%$, Wayne</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376337647981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He may be too busy talking to Burt Rutan about his invention "that will be a giant step forward in aerospace technology". Collier Trophy selection committee is holding their breath. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376342226893</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 17:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376342264901-59</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who'll be the intern to lay claim to being the first to #$%$ dive a President in the Oval office!?!?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376342264901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 17:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376342601913-60</Id><Title>Boeing is killing Airbus</Title><Msg>I really feel that Boeing will put Airbus out on a shoe string. I have seen Boeing execute very well. Airbus on the other hand has been selling assets and resorting to suppliers. Soon Airbus will fade away because skills are really not there as strong as I have seen. Europe (France) is heading to third world status. I think the USA is replacing Europe as the place to be. Less</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376342601913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376342655823-61</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus is killing Boeing</Title><Username>cmps309</Username><Timestamp>1376337854453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 16:04:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yeah?? Har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376342655823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 17:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376349018467-62</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is killing Airbus</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376342601913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can say this today your feelings are delusional very likely stoned out on drugs. Boeing also has sold assets those assets today has a new name Spirit. Stupid is as stupid does and zosima is stupid</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376349018467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 19:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376349848177-63</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is killing Airbus</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376342601913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 17:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anybody siding with Waynedickensen has to be as stoooopid and q u.e,e.r as wayne is- that obviously is you gregjanetommax-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376349848177</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 19:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376353000452-64</Id><Title>KKK=Democrat Party lie to stupid people and they just might believe you. Like Obamacare and the last election</Title><Msg>now we know its going to cost more and like the Democrat Party Obama lies too.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376353000452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 20:16:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376353306314-65</Id><Topic><Title>Who is the Real Patriot</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376310867474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 08:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me make it plain and simple. The worst violation of a democracy is when the gov't lies to the American people and to Congress. The Patriot Snowden exposed the lies and what many constitutional experts consider violations of the 4th Amendment to the US Constitution. Established politicians don't like when upstarts make them look bad. That's the real reason why they view him as a criminal. Snowden has done more to benefit the country by stating the truth than Obama and Congress has done in years.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376353306314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 20:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376353841623-66</Id><Title>MFI is interesting</Title><Msg>In the last 5 years, MFI has only gone this low when MACD was below zero; never when MACD was above zero as it is now.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376353841623</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 20:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376355157924-67</Id><Title>GOP = jobs even Bernanke said Obama's policies do not support a recovery, but heathcare even the poor can't afford</Title><Msg>$21T in debt that's going to keep the poor, poor. Americans are grow weary of these phony unemployment numbers. Carter handed Reagan a $1T debt which caused 18% mortgage rates. What do you think Obama's $21T debt going to do? This Obama will go down in our history books as the worst of the worst once the interest rates take off. So many lies Americans have stopped counting.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376355157924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 20:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376355703211-68</Id><Topic><Title>GOP’s rodeo of racism blows up</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376351730752</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 19:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That shrill and xenophobic base is a real problem for the GOP. They are loud but their numbers are too small to win an election.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1376355703211</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:01:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376355803662-69</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = jobs even Bernanke said Obama's policies do not support a recovery, but heathcare even the poor can't afford</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376355157924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 20:52:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This Obama will go down in our history books as the worst of the worst Only if you are writing that history book.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1376355803662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:03:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376356027345-70</Id><Topic><Title>Who is the Real Patriot</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376310867474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 08:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>according to an WSJ article Obama does not want Snowden, Snowden has a good chance to Win a court battle.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376356027345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376356892274-71</Id><Title>July defense deliveries</Title><Msg>1 P8 2 Apache (new) 5 Apache (remanufactured) 5 Chinook (new) 2 Chinook ( remanufactured) 4 F-18E/F/G 6 Harpoon missiles 1 Satelitte 2 Osprey</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376356892274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376357145070-72</Id><Title>deliveries thru July</Title><Msg>358 planes 253 737's. 12 747's. 14 767's. 55 777's. 24 787's. They have a ways to go to exceed 600 planes for the year.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376357145070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376358248481-73</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh: Christians ‘cannot believe in manmade global warming’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376350103171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 19:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, I wouldn't go as far as Limbaugh with dogmatism, but for those that believe the Bible record of truth, he is essentially correct. God commanded man to go be "fruitful and multiply". Genesis, chapter 1. Read what it says and you will see that no limit was established. Man has done an exceedingly fine job of that and has filled the earth to approximately 7.104 billion people (per the WIKI). What is problematic is the notion that that same level of human beings could be sustained without deploying carbon products into the atmosphere - CO2 or HCs. Everyone can't go back to loin cloths made of animal skins and chop down trees for warmth. And, given the proclivity (or urge) of humans to "merge" (per Ann Landers, remember her?), the human population is going to push 9 to 14 billion somewhere between 2050 and 2100, maybe sooner. Without the essential value of petroleum and its gases, there is a problem. So here is really the real question: did God run all the numbers? Did He miscalculate? Did He know that man's obedience to the Genesis 1 "prime directive" would kill the earth? (sarcasm here) And, yet, He created everything and knows and has counted every hair on your head - on everyone's heads (Luke 12:7). You can see that, for the Christian, the notion that man is going to subvert the creation because he was following God's directive to be "fruitful and multiply" is basically absurd and the benefactor of that is Satan. For those that do not have such faith, your only solution is to be fearful. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376358248481</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376359009871-74</Id><Title>Global warming is nothing but a tax money grab from acedemia.especially when you consider the facts.</Title><Msg>Why did global warmers play with the number and got caught? Concerning the warming and cooling periods of World history. Ice formed on the Siberian and N American continents and the Indians crossed over. The ice melted and water returned. Ice formed again and the Eskimos crossed, even to this day the Alaska and Canadian Indians nor Eskimos get along. The warming and cooling periods of time took thousands perhaps millions of years. What academia is looking at today is a very short period of time.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376359009871</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376359132647-75</Id><Title>I've lived on a plane, flying all over the world to fix computer problems!</Title><Msg>AirBus builds the the worst aircraft in the industry!</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376359132647</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376360752581-76</Id><Topic><Title>I've lived on a plane, flying all over the world to fix computer problems!</Title><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376359132647</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 21:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If that were true they would not be in business.</Msg><Username>revtrst</Username><Timestamp>1376360752581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 22:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376360808872-77</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh: Christians ‘cannot believe in manmade global warming’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376350103171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 19:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christians? How about air breathing humans that made it through the 5th grade? Pretty ignorant,arrogant to believe humans can control the temperature of the sun. Only a liberal can get conned into believing that.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376360808872</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 22:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376362243063-78</Id><Title>NSA Spying Scandal Hurts Boeing</Title><Msg>Brazil is outraged that its country's internet communications has been targeted by the NSA with surveillance and spying. Brazil no longer trusts the US and therefore has decided not to acquire from Boeing its F-18 fighter jets, a deal worth more than $ 4 billion. We can all thank General Alexander for running an elaborate spying program at the NSA that makes the US appear untrustworthy to our foreign neighbors and allies.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376362243063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 22:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>