<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369285327767-1</Id><Topic><Title>one month return JRCC 91% Boeing 13.5% which is better ?cnnmoney chart</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369167810199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 16:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeveritas on May 21, 2013 @9:20 pm you claim my stock suggestions were after the fact and bugus, So FYI as a troll freeveritas and a mulitple avatar name user here is my original suggestion dated May 3, some 12 days after i made the real time recomendations as usual your simply a evil boeing pimp and a liar so easy to show " here is my original suggestion "by waynedickenson961 • May 3, 2013 9:46 PM Flag Boeing stock price up under 1% for the week humm attention Boeing Hacks the truth hurts , Airbus stock price increased 2.8% this week, AMD up 36% for the week,DDD up 15% this week, JRCC up 16% this week, tesla which uses lithium batteries and has beat Boeing all the way is up 6.7% again as usual and par for the Boeing hacks a lot of gibberish and s\no substance, been in these stocs for a month and the troll and Boeing hacks should get some now ans learn to read a stock chart . they are not going to make what I am over the next few weeks Once more freeveritas and your many avatar names, your exposed as the fraud that you are !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369285327767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 01:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369287412048-2</Id><Topic><Title>Flying on the 787 today especially wow what a thought</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369078902465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>revtrust , yep just like when the CEO of Boeing pronounced that the customer would wait for the all new 737MAX, what a deranged CEO the reslut was a fast turn about as Airbus started eating boeing lunch from 2005"The company had intended to replace its single-aisle aircraft with an all-new plane. It switched strategies after the Airbus neo became the fastest-selling jet ever, winning more than 1,000 orders and commitments from December through July. The neo also prompted American to order Airbus planes for the first time since 1987.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369287412048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 01:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369287642659-3</Id><Topic><Title>Flying on the 787 today especially wow what a thought</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369078902465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>conservative_influence, thank you all these evil boeing Hack can do is post troll replies they have no truth or facts on their side a troll-someone who posts inflammatory, extraneous, or off-topic messages in an online community, such as a forum, chat room, or blog, with the primary intent of provoking readers into an emotional response or of otherwise disrupting normal on-topic discussion.[</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369287642659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 01:40:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369288115446-4</Id><Topic><Title>Why isn't the Tea Party and its leaders in the Hot Seat</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369269177999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes they paid what the law says is their fair share, otherwise obama's jackboots would have had them on a waterboard. That is unless they paid obama indirectly which is the route the financials and big banks took, both of which have done rather well. Did you ever wonder why that is?</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1369288115446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 01:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369288413248-5</Id><Topic><Title>cash flow</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369231633021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 10:07:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welch's income and assets came under scrutiny during his divorce from his second wife Jane in 2001 Welch adopted As a result of the media attention his divorce proceedings brought to his retention package, particularly claims that such a package made him look "greedy", Welch chose to renounce the benefits Welch adapted the Motorola's Six Sigma quality program in late 1995.Welch has stated that he is not concerned with the discrepancy between the salaries of top-paid CEOs and those of average workers.AS I said Mcnerney, as a devotee of Welch , is a deranged millionaire who wants to be a deranged billionaire. So mix in the MD outsource business plan adn ignore Hart-Smith and you have the worst of Welch applied by Jim to Boeing a supercharged Md bankruptcy in the offing ! Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369288413248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 01:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369290185498-6</Id><Title>Another lib embraces W's economics</Title><Msg>I have been seeing TV commercials begging businesses to come to low tax NY, now they are for the city of Buffaloe, which after years of failed big gov social spending, has decided to do what W did before Buffalo out Detroits Detroit. Cutting taxes for everyone is only for those who work, so it really is a buzz kill for many libs, but take heart my pinko friends the commercial were paid for by taxes on those still actually working. From BuffaloeNews: In an ambitious move aimed at changing New York’s high-tax reputation, Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo on Wednesday proposed to eliminate taxes for many startup companies and businesses coming from other states. The proposal would eliminate sales taxes and property, business and corporate taxes – for 10 years – for companies that set up shop on or near State University of New York campuses. Employees at those businesses wouldn’t pay income taxes for as much as 10 years.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1369290185498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 02:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369304582138-7</Id><Title>ARMED DOMESTIC DRONES IN THE NEAR FUTURE</Title><Msg>Despite the message of assurance regarding the promise that domestic drones would never turn into government-controlled war machines, Eric Holder decided to go ahead and announce that it would actually be entirely ‘legal’ for Obama to issue a drone strike on a US citizen on domestic soil. In fact, CNN reports that Holder does not ‘rule out’ the possibility of domestic drone strikes, and that a scenario could occur in the future. And to strike someone with a drone, of course, you would need weaponry. You would need an armed drone. In other words, Holder is going against the major promise by the FAA official who ‘promised’ that no armed drones will be flying on domestic soil. But don’t worry, Holder says the government has ‘no intention’ right now of issuing drone strikes on US soil. Just like the government never targeted Constitution and conservative-based groups through the IRS and would never use domestic drones to spy on you. Quite simply, if any power is given to these individuals in government, be sure of one thing: they will use it.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369304582138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 06:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369304740659-8</Id><Topic><Title>What Freedom of the Press !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369246136016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh I forgot..When the Secretary of Defense (and by Default our President) says that we take orders to go to War from NATO...not CONGRESS...isn't that sedition too ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369304740659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 06:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369305950264-9</Id><Title>China Clears Boeing 787s for Commercial Service</Title><Msg>HONG KONG—China's aviation regulator has granted approval for Boeing Co.'s BA -0.84%787 aircraft to begin commercial service with the nation's airlines, people familiar with the situation said Thursday. The move will help Chinese carriers to speed up the replacement of their older planes and expand their fleet to meet the nation's rising demand for air traffic. Chinese airlines have ordered a total of 35 Boeing 787s, including 10 each for Hainan Airlines Co. 600221.SH -1.02%and its bigger rival China Southern Airlines Co., 600029.SH -0.86%Boeing said. "The regulator has issued an airworthiness certificate for the aircraft today," a person familiar with the situation told The Wall Street Journal. China Southern will be the first Chinese carrier to receive the Dreamliner jets, though it wasn't clear when the delivery would take place. Guangzhou-based China Southern, the nation's largest carrier by fleet size, had expected to take delivery of the first jet last year after several rounds of production delays, but the plan was held up because Chinese authorities hadn't issued an airworthiness certificate for the aircraft. The grounding in January of the global 787 fleet after lithium-ion batteries burned on two planes further delayed Chinese regulatory approval.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1369305950264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 06:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369309749730-10</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Has Lost It... Again</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369155455404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:57:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= there are now more mosques in southern france than churches? = Another bumper lie. The truth is that more mosques than churches have been _built_ in recent years, which isn't really saying much when most of the churches are 200 years old or more. Who brainwashes you with all that #$%$?</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1369309749730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 07:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369310237009-11</Id><Topic><Title>End the Term Limit for Presidents !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369230750505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:52:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could give you dozens but since you only asked for three that is real easy/. 1. Without the approval of Congress, as required by the Constitution, Obama ordered the U.S. military to attack Libya. 2. Healthcare waivers for over 2000 of Obamas bcronies and political contribuotrs 3. NDAA grants indefinite detention and suspension of Habeus Corpus</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369310237009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 07:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369312057907-12</Id><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Msg>If you say Sunni militants or if you say I ranian led militants, You are correct. Both I slamic terrorist movements seek world conquest through violent jihad. I ran is moving ahead with its nuclear weapons program and no sanctions has stopped them. I ran must be stopped soon before they get nuclear weapons to use against US cities. Think about it what if the Boston terrorists had a suitcase nuclear weapon instead of their home made bomb. Suicide missions are these militant org specialties.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369312140474-13</Id><Topic><Title>End the Term Limit for Presidents !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369230750505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:52:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus responds to spazticus, err stikdik don't be confused just cause spazticus likes it both ways, it gets mighty lonely when he's one sided, he's needs lots of IDs to keep his threads alive and pimp his own response. don't be confused by the back n forth, spazticus is garbage peddler for the ONE, his jihad is financed by taxpayers and debt...the msg board equivalent of ACORN</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369312140474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369312462797-14</Id><Topic><Title>Signs of an Insecure Person/Investor</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369260906404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 18:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Sigmund, ...What kind of person posts useless psycho-babble on an aerospace investment message board ???</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1369312462797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369312587920-15</Id><Topic><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now that you mention it, our enemy friendly gov't dependent libs, err dumbos, haven't done much for world peace either, not to mention LIBERTY and PROSPERITY</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369312587920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:36:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369312669005-16</Id><Topic><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Z ionists and central Bankers</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369312669005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369313125898-17</Id><Topic><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a sleeper cell waiting for your call from Bin Ladin. I hope you know he no longer among the living..</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369313125898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369313392024-18</Id><Topic><Title>Signs of an Insecure Person/Investor</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369260906404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 18:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That all sounds like an on-spot description of "mir_roguns"</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1369313392024</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369314211003-19</Id><Topic><Title>End the Term Limit for Presidents !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369230750505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:52:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FDR was a 4 term President and the most respected President of the 20th Century. We are basking in the sun due to the accomplishments of his administrations.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369314211003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369314885969-20</Id><Topic><Title>Signs of an Insecure Person/Investor</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369260906404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 18:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The psycho babble is definitely coming from this gambler that compares gambling in the penny stock to that of investing in Boeing.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369314885969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369314994361-21</Id><Topic><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Withouit a doubt, liberals, and their support for their failed ideology of liberalism is the biggest threat. It has bankrupted Europe, and now our liberal/fascist President, and his Regime' are bankrupting the USA.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369314994361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369316170659-22</Id><Title>FERN looks prime for a huge breakout</Title><Msg>Checked out FERN yet? Looks like it is ready to go. All of the technical indicators are showing signs of a bull run.</Msg><Username>cameronharrison385</Username><Timestamp>1369316170659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369316213543-23</Id><Topic><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is a Z ionist? A Z ionist is any person who believes the J ewish people have a right to a country in the land of I srael. President Truman was a Z ionist in recognizing the establishment of Israel as a new country in 1948. Since 1948 all Presidents and the overwhelming members of Congress have been Z ionists. We Americans are I talian Americans, I rish Americans, Latin Americans Haitian Americans and can be all proud of our backgrounds, That's what makes our country so great.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369316213543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369316353834-24</Id><Topic><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" What is the greatest Threat to World Peace " Neocons !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369316353834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369316539505-25</Id><Title>Buy the dips boys but wait till friday!</Title><Msg>China gave the approval on the 787 and Boeing will raking in the money next year but wait for it I say $95 will hold$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1369316539505</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369316605829-26</Id><Topic><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Democrat Party</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369316605829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369317006810-27</Id><Title>Chalk Up another Loss for Der Fuhrer Obama</Title><Msg>House Passes Bill to Bypass Obama on Keystone.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369317006810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369317172360-28</Id><Topic><Title>ARMED DOMESTIC DRONES IN THE NEAR FUTURE</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369304582138</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 06:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... Marking an abrupt shift in tone from his epic March filibuster, Sen. Rand Paul (R-Ky.) said late Monday that he would be fine with a drone killing a run-of-the-mill armed robber...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369317172360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369317311369-29</Id><Topic><Title>What is the greatest Threat to World Peace</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369312057907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>find their agenda on the cpusa website, it is more devious of course, but if they were honest it wouldn't be the cpusa, err dumbocrat party</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369317311369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369317330907-30</Id><Title>New York Deserves a Weiner</Title><Msg>.....after all they are a blue state.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369317330907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369317560102-31</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk Up another Loss for Der Fuhrer Obama</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369317006810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:50:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you mean chalk up another expensive waste of time and money for the House. (Like repealing Obamacare for the 37th time). The House, "we will do anything, no matter how stupid or how much tax payer dollars we waste, to show how much we hate the President".</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1369317560102</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:59:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369317629990-32</Id><Title>WHAT? IT CAN'T BE....DOWN DOWN 110+</Title><Msg>...and our stock boeing up a dime..albeit up in a down day! waynedick-feb what did u do? Wrote a book again?</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369317629990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369317843160-33</Id><Title>Lois Lerner tied to past scandals before IRS</Title><Msg>Seems to be a coomon thead here http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2013/05/23/irs-official-who-refused-to-testify-facing-more-scrutiny-over-scandal-past/</Msg><Username>susank875</Username><Timestamp>1369317843160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369318049784-34</Id><Topic><Title>New York Deserves a Weiner</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369317330907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike So. Carolina, where they've elected a man who abandoned his job at the governor's office to go play with his So. American babe.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369318049784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369318313055-35</Id><Title>Is Obama a Liar or Just Stupid</Title><Msg>....he never know anything about anything going on in his administration.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369318313055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369318574435-36</Id><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Msg>Could it be poli tiks or demog rafics? Hmm. Go to gaggle and enter "red states beat"</Msg><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369318714692-37</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.......Democrats have abused the power of government.....and have proven big government just means big corruption and legalized theft.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369318714692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369319299904-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Freedom works better than socialism</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369319299904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369319526465-39</Id><Topic><Title>End the Term Limit for Presidents !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369230750505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:52:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Obama do that NDAA thing all by HIMSELF! Wow. He MUST be a tyrant! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369319526465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369319579908-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People from Blue States are far more educated and people from these states are not desperate to accept burger jobs and Wallmart jobs at pauper wages.</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1369319579908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369319611725-41</Id><Topic><Title>What Freedom of the Press !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369246136016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did he say that? Why did only Wing Nut Daily hear it?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369319611725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369319669638-42</Id><Title>Republican Sates have outperfomed Democrats States over the Past Decade</Title><Msg>Texas outperformed every other state in the nation on jobs and growth over the past decade, according to the latest annual report on state economic performance released Thursday by the American Legislative Exchange Council. Michigan came in dead last. The rankings are based on state GDP growth, population shifts, and changes in non-farm payroll jobs between 2001 and 2011. The ALEC report also finds that Utah has the best economic outlook this year, and Vermont the worst. That outlook ranking is based on more than a dozen public policies that the authors say are closely related to economic growth — including various tax rates, workers compensation costs, minimum wage laws, right to work laws, government jobs as a share of the workforce, and debt service as a share of tax revenues. In addition, an IBD analysis of the data finds that conservative, Republican states vastly outperformed liberal, Democratic states over the past decade on jobs and economic growth, and attracted more people to their states. In fact, of the 10 states that had the best economic performance over the past decade, all but two — Nevada and Washington — are solid red states, based on the past four presidential elections. Other top economic performers include Utah, Wyoming, North Dakota, Idaho and Arizona.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369319669638</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369319755995-43</Id><Topic><Title>Is Obama a Liar or Just Stupid</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369318313055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:11:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a total liar. He never tells the truth about anything. That's because the truth doesn't work for him.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1369319755995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:35:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369319868008-44</Id><Topic><Title>What Freedom of the Press !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369246136016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're confusing sedition with treason, Loon. "In law, sedition is overt conduct, such as speech and organization, that is deemed by the legal authority to tend toward insurrection against the established order. " And YOU are a seditionist. You'd probably be arrested if anyone thought you were sane enough to really act on your ravings.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369319868008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369319906474-45</Id><Topic><Title>New York Deserves a Weiner</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369317330907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are going to get it shoved up their @@@. They do deserve it.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1369319906474</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369320004841-46</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many good jobs in the reds too, and more are NOT gov't jobs. You'd just rather stay home and suck on the teats (taxes) of those working in red states. You do have your pride, right? No matter that your votes shoot you in the foot Wake up!.</Msg><Username>not_2_needy_1</Username><Timestamp>1369320004841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369320017063-47</Id><Title>Polls: Obama Approval Slides Amidst Scandals</Title><Msg>- The president's job approval rating has dipped underwater at 45/51, an eight-point negative swing since last month. He's at 40/52 among independents. - Attorney General Eric Holder's job approval has plummeted to 28/40 with approximately a third of voters not knowing enough to answer. This may fuel whispers that Holder may be on his way out. - Obama's trustworthiness quotient is now split evenly, down from positive territory in the months leading up to the election. - A whopping 68 percent of Americans believe the federal government is "out of control" and threatening basic liberties. Republicans ought to concentrate on articulating an agenda that speaks to that widespread disaffection. - More Americans label Obama a "lame duck" president than say he's still effective.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369320017063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369320208046-48</Id><Topic><Title>Lois Lerner tied to past scandals before IRS</Title><Username>susank875</Username><Timestamp>1369317843160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:04:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe she needs to spend some time in jail to serve as an example for what happens to corrupt civil servants. Nobody seems to be enforcing the laws anymore. That works out well for the crooks.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1369320208046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369320463531-49</Id><Title>Most Americans Don't Want Obamacare</Title><Msg>22. Do you think it would be better to leave the new health care law in place, or would it bebetter to go back to the health care system that was in place in 2009? Better to keep law: 34 percent Better to go back to previous system: 56 percent</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369320463531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369320502936-50</Id><Topic><Title>Why isn't the Tea Party and its leaders in the Hot Seat</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369269177999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 20:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a pretty twisted view of IRS corruption. Sounds like you might be a lefty if you believe something like that.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1369320502936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369320952402-51</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT? IT CAN'T BE....DOWN DOWN 110+</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369317629990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:00:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep writing waynedick and keep thumbs down w/ zillion diferent id's triple digits soon.. Lol...my waynedick-feb!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369320952402</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369321146540-52</Id><Topic><Title>Is Obama a Liar or Just Stupid</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369318313055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:11:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's both.....and incompetent too.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321146540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369321171252-53</Id><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Msg>Just ask any American who cant afford the insurance pirates or who has been dropped or refused insurance for a preexisting condition. Parents especially want Obamacare for their children. Its only the RWNJs and baggers who don't want it because they are Gods chosen ones and don't get sick or they have so much money they can pay for a quarter million bypass operation out of their own pocket and never notice the dip in their balance</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369321450743-54</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima you might benefit from the mental health benefits but Most Americans who don't have a car would also want free government supplied Cadillacs too. However most sane Americans and most Americas who have to pay for it don't want Obamacare.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321450743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369321668820-55</Id><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Msg>......why does he think someone else should pay for his medical care.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369321723190-56</Id><Topic><Title>Black Man: If Obama was White He Wouldn't Be President</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369227150872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:52:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now I know why you chose your name. LOL</Msg><Username>headsdownpuffisinboundin15</Username><Timestamp>1369321723190</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369321742584-57</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pay4 if you were sane you would want Obama care too. When you have to go to one of your readneck hospitals down there in the swamps and get turned away because you cant afford the quarter million you need to pay for it- then the logic will sink in. As it is you need someone to act as your keeper to make sure you are provided for including having insurance as long as you aren't institutionalized</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321742584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369321917298-58</Id><Title>Darling of the DOW</Title><Msg>Boeing is now the second highest gainer on the DOW ytd.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1369321917298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369322020320-59</Id><Title>ALAS ! 52 WEEK HIGH...</Title><Msg>AND TRIPLE DIGITS ((TICK TOCK TICK TOCK....))</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369322020320</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322032555-60</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole idea which is over your head pay4 is to create an insurance user pool which is large enough to offer a kind of group insurance(Obama Care) to the poor and the sick at an affordable price and that cant drop you. The cost to the taxpayer is minimal. The fact that you currently pay twice the price for the people getting emergency care (for free?? who do you think pays for that) will be eliminated</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369322032555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322057290-61</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps he is not thinking of himself here and, unlike you, is not selfish and would like to see that every American has access to quality medical care. Seems like a noble goal.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369322057290</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322078521-62</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you want to pay for other people's medical care you are free to do so......what's the problem? Do you want to make slavery legal like the Democrats did before 1868?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369322078521</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322118139-63</Id><Topic><Title>Black Man: If Obama was White He Wouldn't Be President</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369227150872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 08:52:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give it up rednecked racists we will not reinstitute slavery under any circumstances</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369322118139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322122920-64</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those that have studied Obamacare don't want it. Requests for waivers, including most labor unions and government agancies, are skyrocketing. Most people will be buying their own plans off state exchanges and many will be unable to afford it and have to pay fines that increase each year. Zosima has no clue. I have been to several seminars and almost everyone in medicine sees a looming disaster with Obamacare.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369322122920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322215048-65</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are talking about a handful of people- what about the other 35-40 million who do want it and do need it</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369322215048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322239802-66</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He will have to pay for it or incur an annual fine which increases every year forward that he doesn't pay for insurance.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369322239802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322243030-67</Id><Topic><Title>Darling of the DOW</Title><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1369321917298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:11:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait till China starts ordering some 787's then we'll be number one Leader$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1369322243030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322293096-68</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disregard my post I see the tpic is Medicare not Obamacare.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369322293096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369322349052-69</Id><Title>Why do Republicans hate Free Men...</Title><Msg>What is it about free thinkers that Republicans hate With free thought comes free speech and freedom to choose - absolutely drives the GOP batty !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369322349052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322444380-70</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post pay4......not sure zosima has enough brain cells to have the mental capacity to connect the dots. If he wants a big insurance pool he and his LWNJ Libtards are free to form one and fund it.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1369322444380</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322466408-71</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insurance was invented to provide coverage for loss by charging a nominal fee which would accumulate and pay benefits to those who needed it and the whoe thing would be affordable because the benefits paid out would not exceed the accumulated fees. That is Obbama Care I know that due to your 70 IQ that this concept is way over your head but ask your keeper or the person you gave power of attorney to and have them explain it to you</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369322466408</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322487771-72</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the update. I didn't realize theree are no burger and Wallmart jobs in blue sates.</Msg><Username>susank875</Username><Timestamp>1369322487771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322576080-73</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shouldn't every American have access to a Mercedes too.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1369322576080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322680976-74</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Infestid I will say it again for you the exchanges will work and if the person is too poor to afford it there will be subsidys to take care of it. Seminar?? bagger seminars aren't seminars- they are a gathering of hate filled idiots.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369322680976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322791630-75</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Disregard my post" That's always good advice.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369322791630</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322821427-76</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obviously you are short enough braincells to understand how any insurance works-typical hate filled bagger.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369322821427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322837950-77</Id><Topic><Title>Darling of the DOW</Title><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1369321917298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:11:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every time they should hire him for the P.R. position$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1369322837950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369322970350-78</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father_zosima. Your message reveals your ignorance of insurance. Insurance has to be purchased BEFORE the to be insured event occurs. You cannot buy fire insurance when the house has started to burn. You cannot buy health insurance when you are sick. This insurance principle gives an incentive to cover yourself when you are healthy. 0therwise everybody would just wait till they get sick and then buy the insurance.</Msg><Username>mailinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1369322970350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369323021472-79</Id><Title>Who Should Be Forced to Provide Healthcare?</Title><Msg>In totalitarian countries it would be Doctors, Nurses And Hospitals......in tyrannical countries it would be be the average hard working citizens.......the producers would be forced to provide for the non producers (Democrats).</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1369323021472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369323341999-80</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The best solution would be just be done with it and have a single payer system.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1369323341999</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369323507300-81</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Don't Want Obamacare</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369320463531</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since most Americans don't want Obamacare........the elitists are giving them the finger and telling them to shut up.......they know what'ts best for them.......and freedom to make you own choices ain't good.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1369323507300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369323694629-82</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good spelling! I think you have proven the point on education.</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1369323694629</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369323801868-83</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Subsidies. Red states take in more from the Federal Government than they give. The Blue states support the red states. RWNJ's are all for the free market, except when the free market hurts them. Look at oil and gas, look at the "Dealer Laws" in Texas and NC to un-level the market against Tesla. Look at all their free market hypocrisy.Look at the ultimate hypocrite, Tennessee (R) Stephen Fincher. Example are numerous.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1369323801868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369323981883-84</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans Do Want Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369321171252</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not everyone is a communist like you oldbuck. Countries that have gone single payer are slowly pulling back and shifting more and more service to the free market. The latest are Great Brittan and Canada.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369323981883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369324072595-85</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without adequate health care an 18 year-old could conceivably die. Without a Mercedes he/she could easily find a cheaper car or use public transportation. Do you really not see the difference?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369324072595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:47:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369324214892-86</Id><Title>The Myths of Single-Payer Health Care</Title><Msg>Here are some of the more prominent single-payer myths: • Myth No. 1: Everyone has access to health care a single-payer system. • Myth No. 2: Claims of rationing are exaggerated. • Myth No. 3: A single-payer system would save money on administrative costs. • Myth No. 4: Single-payer will provide fair and quality care for everyone. • Myth No. 5: Single-payer leaves medical decisions to patients &amp; doctors. • Myth No. 6: Single-payer systems achieve better health outcomes. • Myth No. 7: The U.S. systems also engages in rationing. • Myth No. 8: A single-payer system will not hamper medical research. • Myth No. 9: Single-payer will save money as patients seek care earlier. • Myth No. 10: The free market in health care has failed in the U.S.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324214892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369324419504-87</Id><Topic><Title>End the Term Limit for Presidents !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369230750505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 09:52:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey bumper, did you ever notice it's always the least intelligent posters who think it's clever to imagine that everybody is a sock puppet?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369324419504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369324637996-88</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Cause the red states never had much of an economy to begin with, so it stays pretty stable.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369324637996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369324672920-89</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Cause there's big, big money in used tires!</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369324672920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369324682665-90</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama care was passed based on lies......it is fare more costly than the democrats claimed and will not improve healthcare for Americans......it should be repealed. We have a lot more options to take care of people than turning to socialism.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324682665</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369324715019-91</Id><Topic><Title>The Myths of Single-Payer Health Care</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324214892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why do virtually all seniors apply for Medicare the day they become eligible?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369324715019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369324937419-92</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, I can forego the Mercedes for a cheaper car but I don't like having to go on public transporatation because I now have to pay for some fat lazy slobs poor health choices.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1369324937419</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369325102601-93</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TAKE THE BIG GULPS AWAY FROM THEM THAN!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369325102601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369325167137-94</Id><Topic><Title>The Myths of Single-Payer Health Care</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324214892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty, err chrissie, is a big fan of anything OTHER people have to pay for</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369325167137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369325174723-95</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans abuse power too only difference is when democrats do it you cry when Republicans do it you Wave a flag.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369325174723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369325211568-96</Id><Topic><Title>The Myths of Single-Payer Health Care</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324214892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because they are forced to pay into it. Galveston municipal employees who opted out of Social Security and medicare for private retirement benefits now enjoy 4 times the benefits for the same money social security and medicare would have provided. Socialism doesn't work near as well as the free market.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325211568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369325213188-97</Id><Topic><Title>If Zosima Wants Medicare Care why Doesn't he Just Pay for it?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369321668820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you currently have health insurance which I doubt since you are one of Gods chosen ones (a bagger) and wont get sick you might have a case but if that isn't so then you do have insurance and you are now paying for fat lazy slobs poor health choices who are insured by your company and your insurance premium is increased because of it</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369325213188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369325633739-98</Id><Title>Why do Blue States beat Red States on economy, jobs?</Title><Msg>Could it be poli tiks or repug rafics? Hmm. Go to google and enter "blue states beat red states by magnitudes with exception of Texast" Texas wouldn't have made it except for its Oil and wind energy production which hasn't got a thing to do with politics or state laws</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369325633739</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369325665982-99</Id><Title>Who Loves Medicare?</Title><Msg>From 2009 Matt Yglesias points out today that socialistic single-payer healthcare is actually quite popular in the United States. It's called Medicare. The chart below, from a Mark Blumenthal column last month, shows that Medicare users are far more satisfied with their healthcare than users of private insurance. So why is it so hard to persuade Americans to simply expand the program? Blumenthal explains: The higher scores for Medicare are based on perceptions of better access to care. More than two thirds (70 percent) of traditional Medicare enrollees say they "always" get access to needed care (appointments with specialists or other necessary tests and treatment), compared with 63 percent in Medicare managed care plans and only 51 percent of those with private insurance. ....If the Medicare experience is so positive, why are people so easily talked out of expanding on it? First, younger Americans not enrolled in Medicare do not share the enthusiasm of seniors for the program. Six years ago, the Kaiser Foundation asked a national sample of adults to rate the Medicare program. Medicare was hugely popular among those aged 65 or greater....Those under 65, however, had very different views. Only 45 percent rated Medicare favorably. Only 36 percent considered it well run, as compared to 47 percent who said the same about private health plans. While 73 percent of those over 65 said Medicare allowed patients to choose any doctor, only 28 percent of those under 65 agreed. There's a pretty obvious political dynamic that's responsible for this. Seniors, who actually use Medicare, know perfectly well that it's a good program. They can see any doctor they want, they get care when they need it, and the quality of service is high. So why do younger Americans have such a negative attitude toward Medicare? Answer: because conservative politicians have been bellowing for years about what a terrible program it is. And since younger workers don't actually use it themselves, the bellowing works. They figure it must suck. In reality, Medicare works fine. Not perfectly, but fine. It offers service at least as good as private insurance despite serving the highest-risk population there is, and it does at least as good a job of reining in costs — slightly better, in fact. Sure, it could be improved, but it's already probably better than the employer insurance that you have right now. I'd switch in a second if I could. But I can't, and neither can you. And nothing like it will be offered to you anytime soon. After all, if you actually used it, you'd probably like it. Which is exactly what conservative politicians are afraid of.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369325665982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369325862170-100</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Red states beat Blue states on economy, jobs?</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1369318574435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 10:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does Bangladesh beat Red states on economy, jobs?</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1369325862170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369325945250-101</Id><Topic><Title>The Myths of Single-Payer Health Care</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324214892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everything what you said is a big BS. If you do some research you will find out that: "Retirement benefits are generally lower under the Galveston Plan. Under the Galveston Plan, initial retirement benefits are lower for many workers than under Social Security. Furthermore, unlike Social Security, the Galveston plan does not adjust benefits from year to year to reflect increases in the cost of living. As a result, according to a Social Security Administration study, “After 20 years, all of Galveston’s benefits are lower relative to Social Security’s.” The SSA study also noted that “there are no additional spousal or dependent benefits… benefits are not portable to future employers; benefits are not adjusted for inflation; and, in general, benefits are lower for those with lower earnings and/or with a greater number of dependents who qualify for Social Security.”</Msg><Username>zaksh91</Username><Timestamp>1369325945250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369326146464-102</Id><Title>If Medicare is so popular, Why not make it Voluntary and Self Funding?</Title><Msg>.......and what ever you do don't look at the unfunded liability of this ponzi scheme.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369326146464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369326255996-103</Id><Title>freeveritas • the DOW is the lagger index and Hewlet Packard is up 70% and Boeing only 32% for Dow gainer</Title><Msg>Freeveritas • 53 minutes ago, you said, Boeing is now the second highest gainer on the DOW ytd. Wow and bark freeveritas, how can I tell your a hack for Boeing ? why not suggest the best dow gainer, freeveritas/ if you want slow gainers THEN at least pick the number one dow jones stock hpq, it is twice as good as Boeing, talk about blowhards, FREEVERITAS AND YORU AVATOAR NAMES, a troll is the most evil person on the face of the earth. Hewlett Packard is up 70% year to date then , eh ! I told the viewers to sell JRCC yesterday, a gain of 80% in 13 days so a 32% 153 day gain on boeing is very short, all the picks I suggested on May 3 in just 12 days beat Boeing by at least double your troll statement in just 12 trade days freeveritas and you avatar names, you need to learn how to pick good stocks and swing trade to make money . I said how to get out you missed it all.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369326255996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369326652177-104</Id><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Msg>"Love how all the Electric Vehicle haters act like EV's are liberal folly when it was Bush Admin. who granted Tesla 1/2B$ loan. EV's=future" Liz Claman</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369326669158-105</Id><Topic><Title>The Myths of Single-Payer Health Care</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324214892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ss will soon go broke sasha, medicare/medicaid worse, too many people taking advantage of the collective and all dem false promises a third of our national debt is comprised of IOUs written to our so called "trust" funds</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369326669158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369326767268-106</Id><Topic><Title>freeveritas • the DOW is the lagger index and Hewlet Packard is up 70% and Boeing only 32% for Dow gainer</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369326255996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:24:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Freeveritas you fancy yourself as a stock picker/ and missed hewlet packard at 70% year to date gain? ,freeveritas you only had to review 30 stocks in looking for the best dow jones stock and you missed/ wow and bark you missed a 70 per cent gainer, oh, wait , wait you are a boeing hack and a very poor stock picker then</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369326767268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:32:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369327020804-107</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bussssshhhhhhh, got a link there #$%$, other than liz claman (was this loan buried somewhere in the dumbo constructed CRA bailout / pork fund?)</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369327020804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369327024118-108</Id><Title>Galveston vs. Social Security</Title><Msg>Galveston officials held meetings that included debates with Social Security officials and put it to a vote: Galveston County employees passed it by a 3-to-1 margin in 1981 - just in time. The Galveston Plan was implemented just before the U.S. Congress passed a reform bill in 1983 that closed the door for local governments to opt out of Social Security. To be sure, our plan wasn't perfect, and we have made some adjustments. For instance, a few of our retired county workers are critical of the plan today because they say they are making less money than they would have on Social Security. This is because our plan allowed workers to make "hardship" withdrawals from the retirement plan during their working years. Some workers withdrew funds for current financial problems and consequently robbed their own future benefits. We closed that option in January 2005. Galveston vs. Social Security. Upon retirement after 30 years, and assuming a 5 percent rate of return - more conservative than Galveston workers have earned - all workers would do better for the same contribution as Social Security: • Workers making $17,000 a year are expected to receive about 50 percent more per month on our alternative plan than on Social Security - $1,036 instead of $683. [See the Figure.] • Workers making $26,000 a year will make almost double Social Security's return - $1,500 instead of $853. • Workers making $51,000 a year will get $3,103 instead of $1,368. • Workers making $75,000 or more will nearly triple Social Security - $4,540 instead of $1,645. • Galveston County's survivorship benefits pay four times a worker's annual salary - a minimum of $75,000 to a maximum $215,000 - versus Social Security, which forces widows to wait until age 60 to qualify for benefits, or provides 75 percent of a worker's salary for school-age children. In Galveston, if the worker dies before retirement, the survivors receive not only the full survivorship but get generous accidental death benefits, too. Galveston County's disability benefit also pays more: 60 percent of an individual's salary, better than Social Security's. Two government studies of the Galveston Plan - by the Government Accountability Office and the Social Security Administration - claim that low-wage workers do better under Social Security. However, these studies assumed a low 4 percent return, which is the minimum rate of return on annuities guaranteed by the insurance companies. The actual returns have been substantially higher.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369327024118</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369327178142-109</Id><Topic><Title>The Myths of Single-Payer Health Care</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324214892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In my case, unrelated to any pros or cons of Medicare, when I turned 65, my Boeing retiree Aetna coverage automatically went from primary to secondary coverage, so it was a no-brainer to pick up Medicare. I have had no problems with Medicare coverage or availability of doctors. I recently had a pacemaker implanted and a prostatectomy, which were covered without a hitch. Medicare pays 80% and Aetna pays 80% of the remaining 20%, leaving me with a net liability of 4%.</Msg><Username>dkmax</Username><Timestamp>1369327178142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369327181641-110</Id><Topic><Title>freeveritas • the DOW is the lagger index and Hewlet Packard is up 70% and Boeing only 32% for Dow gainer</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369326255996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:24:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Investors are flat out lousy investors if they want to portray Boeing as a lousy investment over the last 6 mo. let's say. Any investment that has risen as fast as Boeing has could be regarded as junk bond status with that kind of return. Lots of shorts got burnt when the electrical problems surfaced, and they were sure Boeing stock would tank. Now the BS comes out frolm those that got burnt.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369327181641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369327215771-111</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although Bush was a far better president than the dufus and corrupt Marxist we now have, he was no conservative.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369327215771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369327584068-112</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think he's was more conservative than MANY people give him credit for, though less than I'd like, the President has to set priorities and his priority was the war which dumbocrats were actively trying to sabotage, particularly during the last two years when they controlled both houses of congress, i'm sure he swallowed more than he would have liked, so as not to turn his back and negate the sacrifice and progress already made in the war against terror.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369327584068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369328028865-113</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The loans need to be made to private industry. The loans need to be made to the folks that understand profit/loss, and have the moxie to develop renewable energy. The loans shouldn't be made to govt set up crony capitalist companies that reward rich, fatcat liberal contributors that haven't the knowledge as to how to run a successful co. Many fail, and the fatcat steals the money from tax payers, and investors. Up to now, more energy is USED developing an electric car than the electric car saves on energy. And they are very expensive, and most only affordable by some fatcat liberal that gets a feelie-good out of owning one.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369328028865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369328167459-114</Id><Topic><Title>The Myths of Single-Payer Health Care</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369324214892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:50:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Single payer systems eliminate competition, and the only thing that drives down cost. Signle payer systems provide pathetic healthcare, and many die waiting for care that can take months before they are cared for. It has proven to smell like other liberal policy programs...stinky-poo, and abject failures.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369328167459</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369328246134-115</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tesla’s loan was part of the government’s 2010 Advanced Technology Vehicle Manufacturing Program, a $25 billion fund authorized by Congress, signed by President George W. Bush, and awarded under President Obama."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369328246134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369328463408-116</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got that right!</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369328463408</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369328502464-117</Id><Title>100 - 0.01?</Title><Msg>LMAO..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1369328502464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369328825529-118</Id><Title>Should Obama and Holder be Charged with Voter Suppression?</Title><Msg>Holder refused to prosecute the New Black Panthers and Obama abused and intimidated with the IRS and other government agencies.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369328825529</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369328831880-119</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, #$%$. You saved me from having to print that. The only thing wrong with early payoffs is: the government doesn't earn their interest. Good for tsla, though. Now they can use the interest money elsewhere.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369328831880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369328905689-120</Id><Title>share price target raised</Title><Msg>Oppenheimer has reportedly upped its price target on the already buy-rated stock, and now thinks Boeing shares are going to $120.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369328905689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369329044856-121</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree, the government has no business "investing" other people's money, time and time again they've proven to be lousy investors/crooks, all i'm saying is unless the President gets line item veto powers, he's gonna have to accept more than he'd like...dumbos intentionally withheld budget until the last minute, and inserted #$%$ at the last minute so the President would be blamed if he didn't pass the bigger picture, they also inserted surrender language in a whole bunch of bills intended to extort their wants.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369329044856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369329176903-122</Id><Title>joedokes says Boeing shorts got burnt on the ee problems well he does not know shorts then</Title><Msg>joedokes45,! you just said about Boeing, "Lots of shorts got burnt when the electrical problems surfaced, and they were sure Boeing stock would tank. Now the BS comes out from those that got burnt.'JOEDOKES45, YOU JUST DEMONSTRATED YOUR IGNORANCE OF TRADE SKILLS. Boeing has never been a short candidate, if you were a real stock trader you would know that Boeing has a very small number of shorts 1.2 per cent . that is of the total outstanding shares available to trade and if you understood shorting you would know better than to make that BS ignorant claim. Go to shortsqueeze and look it up . However Joedokes45 you lack the skill, knowledge and ability to understand what a short candidate is or you would never have made that comment today or when the 787 was grounded. Boeing is a stay away stock better stocks to trade cc to you avator names spartacus99991 and domerrrrr45,</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369329176903</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:12:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369329307875-123</Id><Topic><Title>freeveritas • the DOW is the lagger index and Hewlet Packard is up 70% and Boeing only 32% for Dow gainer</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369326255996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:24:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>attention joedokes45 I explained shorting to you attention joedokes class is in session</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369329307875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369329314949-124</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So who is it we're supposed to hate...Socialists or Capitalists?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369329314949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369330292329-125</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what freedom have you lost ?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369330292329</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369330321332-126</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's this for the biggest cajone's the world has ever known. Obama took it upon himself to eductate young people on how to save money, how to be frugal, and conserve their money. Obama has run up the biggest debt by far in USA history. The total of all the debt from all the Presidents doesn't equal the debt Obama has supported, and run up. And the biggest spender, and contrbutor to renewable, green energy? BIG OIL!!!! Big OIL that Obama bad mouths, and wants to punish with higher taxes, and lawsuits. If Green Energy becomes profitable it will be because of Big Oil, not Obama stealing money from the tax payers setting up Green Energy companies.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369330321332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369330333902-127</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumper, if the government has no business "investing" other people's money and bankrolling crooks, then I'm sure you'll agree with me that the Pentagon budget should be cut by 80%. Otherwise, you're a hypocrite.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369330333902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369330474240-128</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wannna start with freedom to chose not to buy medical insurance without being fined.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369330474240</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369330492914-129</Id><Title>Bank of America Merrill Lynch</Title><Msg>Has increased price target of BA to $120, based on increased deliveries of 737's and 787's.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369330492914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369330550933-130</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Chevy Spark is only $20,000</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369330550933</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369330830698-131</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big and Little Oil have have both contributed to reducing the amount of foreign oil consumed in this country, due to measures taken by and permits granted by the Obama administration. The US now provides at least 50% of it's own oil, making us less vulnerable to actions and reactions in other countries. Investment in Green and Alternative Energies is making us even less reliant on foreign oil.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369330830698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369331022410-132</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you just love the Democrat's moral equivalency argument base on non facts.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369331022410</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369331253783-133</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and if you get hurt and need to go to the hospital and don`t have insurance who pays? and if that is all you can come up with as far as freedoms lost you`re a joke</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369331253783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369331260818-134</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See "weapons of mass destruction...."</Msg><Username>shill_repellent</Username><Timestamp>1369331260818</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369331352238-135</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, big government just means big corruption and legalized theft. That's why we need to cut military spending by 80%.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369331352238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369331398467-136</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So I suppose you should not be required to have a drivers license to drive either ? or a pilots license to fly a plane , and doctors should not need medical degrees ?? your argument about losing freedoms is about as lame as it gets lmao It`s called being part of society if you can`t accept that than leave and find something better</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369331398467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369331682234-137</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And given the 100% failure of heavy doses of socialism what does that say about a lbieral's IQ? It is one thing to predict the future, but when you have hindsight to look back on, and still can't get it?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369331682234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369331769065-138</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Translation: Freedom to go to the Emergency Room at my expense.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369331769065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369331813883-139</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it should never have been passed given that one party was happy to pass 1/6 of our economy with no support from the other party....rammed through in a very corrupt way with corrupt folks concocting the bill.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369331813883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369331988097-140</Id><Title>Cuomo Flogs Weiner: 'Shame On Us' If We Erect Him</Title><Msg>Democrats are obviously not happy with the idea of disgraced former Congressman Anthony Weiner running for mayor of New York City. In an editorial meeting with some local newspapers, New York governor Andrew Cuomo said "shame on us," if Weiner is elected.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369331988097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369332323560-141</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you will be able to do that you just have to pay a fee/ tax to have that special privilege if you can afford to pay for your own health care with cash than you should have no trouble paying a fee to be special. so all this crying about freedoms do you have anymore you have lost under Obama ?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369332323560</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369332465345-142</Id><Topic><Title>ALAS ! 52 WEEK HIGH...</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369322020320</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$ 100..tick tock tick tock tick tock...waynedick-feb zip zip....zip zip....lol</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369332465345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369332962021-143</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, I suppose shortly you will want to apply that same logic to food, housing, clothing and transportation. If not why not?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369332962021</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369333156399-144</Id><Title>PAR = $100 (is coming) :)</Title><Msg>patiently waiting...</Msg><Username>ibcnu2nite</Username><Timestamp>1369333156399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369333263684-145</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about the freedom not to be assassinated by presidential decree with no court proceedings whatsoever?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369333263684</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369333343119-146</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think socialism is immoral then you should demand that the US socialistic military be cut to a size so you can drown it in your bathtub--otherwise you're a hypocrite.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369333343119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369333489101-147</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My response was in regard to freedoms Rebel has lost. Here's the deal: a trip to the er could cost upwards of $100,000, depending on the reason. I want you insured so I don't have to pay for that. A trip to the grocery store is hardly ever going to cost that, so I'm willing to take the risk you can pay for it. If you don't have a regular Dr, you will go to the er for a broken leg, which will cost me about 3 times what it would cost you if you use your own Dr. People without insurance almost never have their own Dr.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369333489101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369333507897-148</Id><Topic><Title>tesla up 12% pre market and Boeing is not</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368710628428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 09:23:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrr45 aka spartacus99991 aka joedokes45, as a Boeing pimp you dont like ti when I show 12 day trades that beat your pimp on Boeing do you so sad for you then. a troll and a boeing hack domerrrr45-"is someone who posts inflammatory,[1] extraneous, or off-topic messages in an online community, such as a forum, chat room, or blog, with the primary intent of provoking readers into an emotional response[2] or of otherwise disrupting normal on-topic discussion. Too bad you think your some kind of Boeing pimp them</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369333507897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369333637488-149</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being part of society you have some responsibility if you can`t handle that leave and find a better place to live. If You don`t want to be part of society and want to stay here with the special privilege of not having to purchase healthcare for your well being and health, pay your dang fee and stop crying about what a poor victim you have become. it would not be logical to discuss this any further with you.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369333637488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369333734335-150</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing or JASO which is better today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369075538315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing is better plus ok into GE they supply those engines to Boeing plus GE bought out that jet manufacture in Europe five years from now we won't be needing any more tips.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1369333734335</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369333839867-151</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why can't the ER just say, no money, no insurance.....no care the same way you want to tell a starving man no money, no bread?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369333839867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369333897730-152</Id><Title>alass Boeing is 50% behind another Dow Jones stock hewlet packard and at a high wow and bark then for domerrrr45</Title><Msg>Domerrrr45, you fancy yourself as some kind of Boeing pimp and yet you miss Hewlett Packard up 70% domerrrr45 HPQ is a better Dow Jones stock by double the gain of Boeing in ytd. what is up with that Mr Boeing pimp fail / alas and heavy on the horse manure from domerrrrrr45 as usual and cc to yoru avatoars joedokes45 and spartacus99991, you like your avatar number names it must be easier to keep all 12 of you different id names to congratulate yourself with, keep talking to yourself and rating yourself then HPQ up 70% and boeing is not even half that good YTD in the DOW jones Average some pimp fail you are domerrrr45</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369333897730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369334082421-153</Id><Title>rockstar lives on welfare and wants you to buy his medical insurance</Title><Msg>.....he believes some citizens should be obligated to buy other citizens medical insurance. Obviously he doesn't value freedom.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369334082421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369334115081-154</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing or JASO which is better today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369075538315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tucsonlighting747 you want me to sell my avon products somewhere else so you can pimp boeing then eh and so neutral a name 747 tell me your not a Boeing pimp then eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369334115081</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369334242634-155</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The CIA director that told George Bush there were WMD's was a Democrat. George should have know better than to trust a Democrat.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369334242634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369334298441-156</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has been legislated that ERs can not do that. They are required by law to provide emergency assistance for humanitarian reasons. However, they also know the difference between an emergency and a head cold. They make people wait as long as possible in hopes they will go away.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369334298441</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:38:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369334337071-157</Id><Topic><Title>Cuomo Flogs Weiner: 'Shame On Us' If We Erect Him</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369331988097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:59:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Weiner is "disgraced", then why are Mark Sanford and David Vitter not too "disgraced" to be in office ( or seeking )?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369334337071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369334409820-158</Id><Topic><Title>joedokes says Boeing shorts got burnt on the ee problems well he does not know shorts then</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369329176903</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:12:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joedokes45 er I mean domerrrr45 have you taken your basic short class this morning , you really need to learn more than boeing pimp and troll stuff to be here with any credibility</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369334409820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369334557783-159</Id><Topic><Title>rockstar lives on welfare and wants you to buy his medical insurance</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369334082421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Feminine men always want the collective to pay for stuff they want but don't want to pay for themselves.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1369334557783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369334810073-160</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you guys cry about death panels , jeezez your saying no care let them die if they don`t have money?. I`m pretty sure I don`t want you part of society.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369334810073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369334937606-161</Id><Title>I thoughts NIKEEI Fell 7% this am???</Title><Msg>WallStreet with pink glass again??? lol</Msg><Username>jpmhedgefund</Username><Timestamp>1369334937606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369335212711-162</Id><Topic><Title>rockstar lives on welfare and wants you to buy his medical insurance</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369334082421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rebel must be getting angry with me he`s spouting misinformation and stuff he knows absolutely nothing about , just ordinary day in a spoon fed Republicans world. and of course Rover our ole buddy has to toss in a little name calling because he is not mature enough to deal with facts. little does he know I could crush his skull like a pimple with one hand.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369335212711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369335314400-163</Id><Title>The long list of Freedoms lost under Obama</Title><Msg>1. I have to buy health care 2. silence</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369335314400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369335451310-164</Id><Topic><Title>The long list of Freedoms lost under Obama</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369335314400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:55:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The freedom not to be assassinated by presidential decree free of any judicial supervision. The freedom not to have all our emails and phone calls hoovered up by the NSA.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369335451310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369335630267-165</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need a driver's license id you want to drive. But that's not analogous to requiring everyone to have health insurance. The analogy is to require everybody to have driver's licenses just on the chance that they might want to drive someday.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369335630267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369336067296-166</Id><Title>.........................U.S. Manufacturing Growth Slips to 7-Month Low</Title><Msg>.................................U.S. Manufacturing Growth Slips to 7-Month Low keep buying...you deserve it...lol</Msg><Username>jpmhedgefund</Username><Timestamp>1369336067296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:07:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369336212845-167</Id><Topic><Title>I thoughts NIKEEI Fell 7% this am???</Title><Username>jpmhedgefund</Username><Timestamp>1369334937606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:48:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moron!</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1369336212845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369337128833-168</Id><Topic><Title>The long list of Freedoms lost under Obama</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369335314400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:55:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The freedom not to be assassinated by presidential decree free of any judicial supervision" DON`T declare WAR and support a war against the USA and you will have nothing to fear once you support war against the USA you loose your freedom and hopefully your life! "The freedom not to have all our emails and phone calls hoovered up by the NSA." not long ago this was brought up and we were told by a bunch of flag wavers that if your not doing anything wrong you have nothing to hide or worry about IT WAS A PATRIOTIC THING TO DO. we don`t live in the 1950`s anymore this is 2013 there are many people that want to do us harm and we must do what needs to be done to protect us from people who will do us harm. anyways those are quite a stretch as being a freedom lost</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369337128833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369338670184-169</Id><Topic><Title>The long list of Freedoms lost under Obama</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369335314400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:55:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. You buy your subsidized insurance with welfare money 2. LMAOL</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369338670184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:51:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369338734499-170</Id><Topic><Title>The long list of Freedoms lost under Obama</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369335314400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:55:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The right that has constantly been eroding for decades, don't blame any administration more than any other, is the right to privacy. There are less and less places privacy can be expected.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369338734499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369338800496-171</Id><Title>The freedom of Speech without unjustified audits and Intimindating agencies</Title><Msg>...pilfering through our private affairs.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369338800496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369339067301-172</Id><Title>How about the freedom to pay a much smaller percent of income in taxes</Title><Msg>.....just because one chooses to work harder, smarter, longer hours, more skillfully and take greater risks.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369339067301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369339146731-173</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a big flag waver for the democrats. So when you say something like this, It just shows you are a hyoocrite. Actually even worse, because nobody waves flags as mindlessly as Obamabots.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1369339146731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:59:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369339443659-174</Id><Topic><Title>Now That it's Clear Democrats are a Party of Deceit, Dishonesty and Abuse.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1369236369340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 11:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You all just wave the flags. Rah for us! Beat the others! It's meaningless. Remember Spy v. Spy in MAD Magazine?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369339443659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369339744108-175</Id><Topic><Title>The long list of Freedoms lost under Obama</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369335314400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 14:55:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And who did Abdulrahman al Awkali declare war on? He was 16 years old. You are rationalizing away the loss of freedoms. Why? What makes you such a traitor and a coward? You're trying to claim that it's a stretch to say loss of the right not to be assassinated is a lost freedom? You're trying to claim that it's a stretch to say loss of the right not to have your communications hoovered up is a lost freedom?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369339744108</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369339789860-176</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Republicans hate Free Men...</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369322349052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 11:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's so messed up. You must be on some kind of medication. Don't drive.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1369339789860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369339942027-177</Id><Topic><Title>How about the freedom to pay a much smaller percent of income in taxes</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369339067301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, why not? Let's have a consumption tax instead of a work tax. Buy a Chevy, pay 1% tax. Buy a Destino, pay 20% tax. It will increase the prestige of the Destino.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369339942027</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369340083155-178</Id><Title>How about the freedom to not rob children and granchildren</Title><Msg>....just so Obama can use their money to pay off campaign donors?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369340083155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:14:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369340257455-179</Id><Topic><Title>How about the freedom to pay a much smaller percent of income in taxes</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369339067301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here in Washington state at Boeing, we do not pay any state income taxes.....how is that? You can go to South Carolina and work at Boeing and pay an additional 7% state taxes on top of the federal. Think I will live here in Washington. congrats to any and all long holders of Boeing stock. Wow. $99.99......</Msg><Username>grgsvll</Username><Timestamp>1369340257455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369340352609-180</Id><Topic><Title>How about the freedom to pay a much smaller percent of income in taxes</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369339067301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you trade in you Zaporozhet for a Destino?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369340352609</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369340360934-181</Id><Topic><Title>How about the freedom to not rob children and granchildren</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369340083155</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:14:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about the freedom to not rob children and granchildren to make the Masters of War richer?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369340360934</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369340524048-182</Id><Title>What a #$%$ message board</Title><Msg>Its all the same ol #$%$ political arguments...who friggin cares? This stock is pushing $100 bucks for gods sake!</Msg><Username>grgsvll</Username><Timestamp>1369340524048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369340687617-183</Id><Topic><Title>How about the freedom to pay a much smaller percent of income in taxes</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369339067301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would I want to do that? Any idiot can buy a Destino.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369340687617</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369340756133-184</Id><Topic><Title>joedokes says Boeing shorts got burnt on the ee problems well he does not know shorts then</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369329176903</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 13:12:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suck a big one Wayne....I hope you lost alot of cash you worthless POS..</Msg><Username>tallicat9300</Username><Timestamp>1369340756133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369341118348-185</Id><Title>Sweden's Government Health Care</Title><Msg>Government health care advocates used to sing the praises of Britain's National Health Service (NHS). That's until its poor delivery of health care services became known. A recent study by David Green and Laura Casper, "Delay, Denial and Dilution," written for the London-based Institute of Economic Affairs, concludes that the NHS health care services are just about the worst in the developed world. The head of the World Health Organization calculated that Britain has as many as 25,000 unnecessary cancer deaths a year because of under-provision of care. Twelve percent of specialists surveyed admitted refusing kidney dialysis to patients suffering from kidney failure because of limits on cash. Waiting lists for medical treatment have become so long that there are now "waiting lists" for the waiting list. Government health care advocates sing the praises of Canada's single-payer system. Canada's government system isn't that different from Britain's. For example, after a Canadian has been referred to a specialist, the waiting list for gynecological surgery is four to 12 weeks, cataract removal 12 to 18 weeks, tonsillectomy three to 36 weeks and neurosurgery five to 30 weeks. Toronto-area hospitals, concerned about lawsuits, ask patients to sign a legal release accepting that while delays in treatment may jeopardize their health, they nevertheless hold the hospital blameless. Canadians have an option Britainers don't: close proximity of American hospitals. In fact, the Canadian government spends over $1 billion each year for Canadians to receive medical treatment in our country. I wonder how much money the U.S. government spends for Americans to be treated in Canada. "OK, Williams," you say, "Sweden is the world's socialist wonder." Sven R. Larson tells about some of Sweden's problems in "Lesson from Sweden's Universal Health System: Tales from the Health-care Crypt," published in the Journal of American Physicians and Surgeons (Spring 2008). Mr. D., a Gothenburg multiple sclerosis patient, was prescribed a new drug. His doctor's request was denied because the drug was 33 percent more expensive than the older medicine. Mr. D. offered to pay for the medicine himself but was prevented from doing so. The bureaucrats said it would set a bad precedent and lead to unequal access to medicine. Malmo, with its 280,000 residents, is Sweden's third-largest city. To see a physician, a patient must go to one of two local clinics before they can see a specialist. The clinics have security guards to keep patients from getting unruly as they wait hours to see a doctor. The guards also prevent new patients from entering the clinic when the waiting room is considered full. Uppsala, a city with 200,000 people, has only one specialist in mammography. Sweden's National Cancer Foundation reports that in a few years most Swedish women will not have access to mammography. Dr. Olle Stendahl, a professor of medicine at Linkoping University, pointed out a side effect of government-run medicine: its impact on innovation. He said, "In our budget-government health care there is no room for curious, young physicians and other professionals to challenge established views. New knowledge is not attractive but typically considered a problem (that brings) increased costs and disturbances in today's slimmed-down health care." These are just a few of the problems of Sweden's single-payer government-run health care system. I wonder how many Americans would like a system that would, as in the case of Mr. D. of Gothenburg, prohibit private purchase of your own medicine if the government refused paying. We have problems in our health care system but most of them are a result of too much government. Over 50 percent of health care expenditures in our country are made by government. Government health care advocates might say that they will avoid the horrors of other government-run systems. Don't believe them. The American Association of Physicians and Surgeons, who published Sven Larson's paper, is a group of liberty-oriented doctors and health care practitioners who haven't sold their members down the socialist river as have other medical associations. They deserve our thanks for being a major player in the '90s defeat of "Hillary care."</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341118348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369341459028-186</Id><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Msg>Most politicians, and probably most Americans, see health care as a right. Thus, whether a person has the means to pay for medical services or not, he is nonetheless entitled to them. Let's ask ourselves a few questions about this vision. Say a person, let's call him Harry, suffers from diabetes and he has no means to pay a laboratory for blood work, a doctor for treatment and a pharmacy for medication. Does Harry have a right to XYZ lab's and Dr. Jones' services and a prescription from a pharmacist? And, if those services are not provided without charge, should Harry be able to call for criminal sanctions against those persons for violating his rights to health care? You say, "Williams, that would come very close to slavery if one person had the right to force someone to serve him without pay." You're right. Suppose instead of Harry being able to force a lab, doctor and pharmacy to provide services without pay, Congress uses its taxing power to take a couple of hundred dollars out of the paycheck of some American to give to Harry so that he could pay the lab, doctor and pharmacist. Would there be any difference in principle, namely forcibly using one person to serve the purposes of another? There would be one important strategic difference, that of concealment. Most Americans, I would hope, would be offended by the notion of directly and visibly forcing one person to serve the purposes of another. Congress' use of the tax system to invisibly accomplish the same end is more palatable to the average American. True rights, such as those in our Constitution, or those considered to be natural or human rights, exist simultaneously among people. That means exercise of a right by one person does not diminish those held by another. In other words, my rights to speech or travel impose no obligations on another except those of non-interference. If we apply ideas behind rights to health care to my rights to speech or travel, my free speech rights would require government-imposed obligations on others to provide me with an auditorium, television studio or radio station. My right to travel freely would require government-imposed obligations on others to provide me with airfare and hotel accommodations. For Congress to guarantee a right to health care, or any other good or service, whether a person can afford it or not, it must diminish someone else's rights, namely their rights to their earnings. The reason is that Congress has no resources of its very own. Moreover, there is no Santa Claus, Easter Bunny or Tooth Fairy giving them those resources. The fact that government has no resources of its very own forces one to recognize that in order for government to give one American citizen a dollar, it must first, through intimidation, threats and coercion, confiscate that dollar from some other American. If one person has a right to something he did not earn, of necessity it requires that another person not have a right to something that he did earn. To argue that people have a right that imposes obligations on another is an absurd concept. A better term for new-fangled rights to health care, decent housing and food is wishes. If we called them wishes, I would be in agreement with most other Americans for I, too, wish that everyone had adequate health care, decent housing and nutritious meals. However, if we called them human wishes, instead of human rights, there would be confusion and cognitive dissonance. The average American would cringe at the thought of government punishing one person because he refused to be pressed into making someone else's wish come true. None of my argument is to argue against charity. Reaching into one's own pockets to assist his fellow man in need is praiseworthy and laudable. Reaching into someone else's pockets to do so is despicable and deserves condemnation.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369341885341-187</Id><Topic><Title>What a #$%$ message board</Title><Username>grgsvll</Username><Timestamp>1369340524048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you here looking for some good advice?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341885341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369342192650-188</Id><Title>tesla motors or Boeing company which is better? 6/5% or 1.86% or 290% or 22% five years</Title><Msg>For the investors here . a review please . tesla motors is up for the day 6.5%, BA up 1.86%,for the month tesla motors is up 85%, boeing 14%,for 3 months testla motors is up 163% ,boeing up 31% for the yar to date tesla motors is up 174% , boeing up 32% for 6 months tesla motors is up 185% , boeing up 36% for one yar tesla is up 200% , boeing up 39% for 5 years tesla motors is up 298% , Boeing up 22%. For those continual users with similiar names who fancy themselves as Boeing enthusiasts learn to trade stocks and stop spinning troll and Boeing gibberish BTW i told you to buy tsla on May 4 since then you should have made over 80% and got out if you followed by trade guidline. Today the stock broke above the pre market high at $85.55(read my trade guideline0 and closed at $92.73, then went up in after market so far to $ 92.94 so read my trade guideline and you will know what to do tomorrow. Notice I did not comment on the other 3 stocks as they have not met a minimum day trade parameter. you could have joined me when I purposly responed to a Boeing troll on a earlier tsla comment. that was your head up too bad the boeing adveertisement agents are like mice in a skinnerian box , dumb mice I drop a food lellet in and they can not mouse over and pick it up just like apple for 15 years they missed</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369342192650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369342336144-189</Id><Topic><Title>What a #$%$ message board</Title><Username>grgsvll</Username><Timestamp>1369340524048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm with you my friend. I haven't been here in ages, and with Boeing hitting 99.99 today, I thought I'd take a look. There is not one frigging thing here related to the stock. I started buying Boeing in 2008, and have had a nice ride up. My investment style is to scale in, and scale out, so I sold 10% of my position today at 99.60. I still think this company has some upside, but I am sticking to my exit strategy, as Pigs get slaughtered.</Msg><Username>firemon2001</Username><Timestamp>1369342336144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369342790301-190</Id><Title>Breraking thru resistance of 100</Title><Msg>Almost made it today, but no cagar! If we can have a hot maket tomorrow and bread thru I see us moving to 110 in 2 wkks. Must close above 100 tomkorrow!</Msg><Username>rrpjds</Username><Timestamp>1369342790301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369343100758-191</Id><Title>here is what a Troll comments on all day long tallican9300 , same as domer45,spart9991 joedokes45 all #</Title><Msg>tallicat9300, I means spartacus99991, I mean domerrrrr45 I mean joedokes 45, you sure like you same old fake name adn number handle wow bark and ouch your the same troll, give it up and get out of your mom's spare bedroom and get a job or get a parole and go to work . Sort: Newest | Oldest | Highest Rated Expand all messages Reply to Scooby says nobody wants to sell. LOL! by tallicat9300 •8 hours ago tallicat9300 • 16 minutes ago Flag 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts0Reply Nobody wants to sell under 2 cents..lol....I guess nobody wanted to sell under 15 cents either huh? Or 14 or 13 or 12 all the way down to less than 1. You are a bufoon and a liar... Reply to joedokes says Boeing shorts got burnt on the ee problems well he does not know shorts then by waynedickenson961 •3 hours ago tallicat9300 • 28 minutes ago 2users liked this postsusers disliked this posts0Reply Suck a big one Wayne....I hope you lost alot of cash you worthless POS.. Reply to FDA WAIVER... by toppedout2000 •7 hours ago tallicat9300 • 34 minutes ago 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts0Reply #$%$ moron, so now you flip flop...400k shares my #$%$..You are a #$%$ moron. A troll - number 9300/,9991/,45 and 45/ domer-spart,joe,tallicat and enter the number and all your other avatar names is In Internet slang, a troll is someone who posts inflammatory] extraneous, or off-topic messages in an online community, such as a forum, chat room, or blog, with the primary intent of provoking readers into an emotional response] or of otherwise disrupting normal on-topic discussion like you hope I lost money wow I just showed you how I made over 100% I traded the stock each day from may4 and actually was in a month earlier and got in today for tsla and am up over 6.5% living in denial in you mom's hosue or prison is not the best way to go , get a life and learn how to trade stocks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369343100758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369343564938-192</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A twisted analogy and very sad case of selfishness, if you don`t want to contribute to society either pay the fine/tax to be special or leave and find someplace better.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369343564938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369343623086-193</Id><Topic><Title>What a #$%$ message board</Title><Username>grgsvll</Username><Timestamp>1369340524048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The best advise on this stock bar none came from Mir_roguns. When every one said it was going to the moon he said sell and short at $105. I did and then he said to cover and go long at $34. I did. My new Ferrari is very nice. Just waiting for him to tell me when to sell and short so I can do it again.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1369343623086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369343667559-194</Id><Topic><Title>Trying to Tell a Liberal that Socialism is Immoral is the same as.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1369325930965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or maybe VOTE someday?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369343667559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369343818975-195</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why can't he stay here and work to change this utterly stupid law?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1369343818975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:16:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369343973817-196</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A twisted analogy and very sad case of selfishness" Well said.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369343973817</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369344258548-197</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>health care cost were spiraling out of control before this law it would of cost more doing it the old way and the cost would of kept rising to the point a majority of Americans would not be able to afford even basic health insurance , is that what you want ? to spend more money on health care? this was an attempt to do something and listening to all the fortune teller republicans who never get anything right , I say win an election! there is still more to do to make it a better system but first we must remove all obstructionist from office. just because health care sucks in other countries does not mean that it has to be that way here (in my best Bill Murry Voice WEEEEEEEEEEEEARRRRRE AMERICANS!!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369344258548</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369344309625-198</Id><Topic><Title>What a #$%$ message board</Title><Username>grgsvll</Username><Timestamp>1369340524048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing Business Jets (BBJ) is displaying a BBJ 3 for the first time at the 2013 European Business Aviation Conference and Exhibition (EBACE) in Geneva, Switzerland. The airplane, based on the 737-900ER, was outfitted with its custom VIP interiors at Jet Aviation in Basel, Switzerland. The BBJ 3 is currently for sale, so the exterior remains "green" or unpainted, ready for a livery to be selected by a new owner. The range of the BBJ 3 exceeds that of other business jets in its class. It can fly 4,900 nautical miles; more than 1,500 nautical miles (3 hours) farther than its direct competitor.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369344309625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369344419265-199</Id><Topic><Title>How about the freedom to pay a much smaller percent of income in taxes</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369339067301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 15:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you still have not provided one single FREEDOM you have lost . trying to be stupid makes you funny.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369344419265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369344441294-200</Id><Title>Why Can't DFCs Grow a Pair?</Title><Msg>Is it because their panties are too tight?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369344441294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369344741599-201</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it twisted? Why is it selfish to not want to burden my fellow man with paying for my healthcare?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369344741599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369345118223-202</Id><Title>Charity be Voluntary or Forced at the threat of Guns?Should</Title><Msg>Reaching into one's own pockets to help someone is Charity. Using a government gun to take a person's earnings so you can use it to help someone is theft.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369345118223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369346070768-203</Id><Title>GOP Ariz. rep. who supports Medicaid is threatened</Title><Msg>GOP Ariz. rep. who supports Medicaid is threatened By Bob Christie PHOENIX (AP) — A Republican member of the Arizona House says she received an obscene and threatening voicemail at her office because she supports Gov. Jan Brewer’s push to expand Medicaid. A visibly shaken Rep. Kate Brophy McGee, of Phoenix, urged fellow members Thursday to tell their constituents to be civil. She told them she should not be frightened to come to work. The message came after Republican Rep. Bob Thorpe, of Flagstaff, sent an email urging his constituents to call Brophy McGee and five other GOP House members who support Medicaid expansion. Thorpe says he sent an apology late Wednesday to the lawmakers for naming them. GOP House Speaker Andy Tobin says threatening any lawmaker or any Arizonan is inappropriate. He says he spoke with Thorpe and he sent the apology.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369346070768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369346811344-204</Id><Title>Oklahoma Is Fortunate To Have Obama as President</Title><Msg>By E.J. Dionne, Jr. WASHINGTON—While listening to an NPR report out of Moore, Okla., this week, I was genuinely shocked. Not by the scale of the devastation or the tenacity of people who have grown stoically accustomed to the damage tornadoes can do, but by a political sentiment that, in almost any other era, would not have been surprising at all. Rep. Tom Cole, a Republican who lives in the very neighborhood that was overwhelmed, was talking about a call he received from President Obama. Hearing Cole, I realized how strange it is these days for politicians to speak in human terms about someone in the other political party—especially if that someone is named Barack Obama. “He was very kind,” Cole said. The president, Cole added, “ticked off very quickly that the assets were available ... and said, ‘You know, you’re going to have everything you need and if something—you have a problem, just call me directly at the White House.’ It was an exceptionally kind, thoughtful and gracious call.” Imagine: a solid conservative Republican declaring that Obama did something “kind, thoughtful and gracious.” This takes courage in the GOP these days. New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie learned as much last fall. He was ostracized by large parts of the right (and pronounced unwelcome at March’s Conservative Political Action Conference) because he praised Obama’s response to Hurricane Sandy. I hope Cole escapes this fate. A 64-year-old with a Ph.D. in history from the University of Oklahoma, he spent years in loyal service to the Republican Party, including a stint as state party chair in the 1980s. Back then, he was a straight-talking source for many journalists around the country (including me). He was never anything but a conservative. Advertisement And except for one moment in our past, there has never been anything un-conservative or controversial about helping the victims of disasters. In fact, federal disaster relief is as old as our republic, as Brian Balogh, a University of Virginia historian, noted in his seminal book “A Government Out of Sight.” The practice goes back to the 1780s, he writes, and “by the mid-1820s, general relief bills were directed at entire classes of victims.” The sensible justification “was the victims’ inability to foresee or predict these sudden events, and the recipients’ innocence of any responsibility for them.” It was only between 1840 and 1860 that disaster relief from Washington became contentious as a particularly extreme brand of states’ rights politics reared its head. Southerners, Balogh notes, began fearing that “extending federal power” in this way “might establish a precedent for national intervention in the slavery question.” Although we resolved the slavery debate, our nation seems in many ways to be regressing back to the politics of that era. Disaster relief is not a slam dunk anymore because an issue of basic decency has become entangled with a renewed assault on federal power and a belief that cutting the budget is the nation’s single highest priority. Sen. Tom Coburn, R-Okla., is so philosophically consistent that his office let it be known that he believed even assistance to those suffering in his home state should be offset by budget cuts. He later said he would not get in the way of relief, but it’s astonishing that emergency spending on behalf of innocent people would be used as a vehicle for more austerity. Cole, in a very different way, is also consistent when it comes to disaster relief. He was one of just 49 House Republicans who voted in January for a $50 billion Hurricane Sandy aid package; 179 voted no. “There’s clearly a federal responsibility to act in this case,” Cole said in a speech on the House floor. “We’ve always acted after disasters.” And then he offered this piece of prophesy: “It’s pretty unusual in my state to go through a year without a tornado disaster, and it’s pretty unusual to go through a year without a drought disaster. Each time, we’ve come and asked for help from the federal government; each time, we received that help. Undoubtedly, we’ll be doing that again in the near future. It would be hypocritical, in my view, to fail to do for people in the affected region what I and, I know, many others have routinely asked for our own regions.” Empathy, honesty and common sense: We could use more of all three. May the people of Oklahoma get the help they need. Rigid ideology is no substitute for generosity of spirit.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369346811344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369347263082-205</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369326652177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:30:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scientists have done a complete assessment on impacts of raw materials and production processes on EVs and found that they actually produce more pollution and green house gases than gas cars when driven under 120,000 miles. If you buy an EV thinking you are not polluting you are an uninformed unscientific moron. The question then becomes why waste the money on technology which has no net benefit? Also why make poor people subsidize rich people (only rich people can afford $120,000.00 Tesla) by giving rich people tax rebates?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369347263082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369347445427-206</Id><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Msg>Have you ever noticed that all the female guests and hosts on FOX Business look like cheap #$%$ or pole dancers? Dumber than dirt, too. Take a look and see if you don't agree...hilarious!</Msg><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369347467283-207</Id><Topic><Title>Oklahoma Is Fortunate To Have Obama as President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369346811344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As are we!</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1369347467283</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369347970133-208</Id><Topic><Title>What a #$%$ message board</Title><Username>grgsvll</Username><Timestamp>1369340524048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and Mir(de). Suuuuuure.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1369347970133</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369348014477-209</Id><Title>The Latest Lie: IRS Targeted Conservatives</Title><Msg>Remember the video of the guy in the “pimp costume” who got advice from ACORN employees on how to run his prostitution ring? Turns out the whole story was just a lie, a doctored-video smear job on an important organization. The guy never wore a “pimp costume” and the real, undoctored videos showed that ACORN employees did nothing wrong. But a lie travels around the world before the corporate media bothers to check the facts. The “news” media blasted the story everywhere, and Congress was so outraged they forced ACORN to close its doors. And here we are again. The corporate media is blasting out the story that the IRS “targeted conservative groups.” Some in the media say there was “IRS harassment of conservative groups.” Some of the media are going so far as claiming that conservative groups were “audited.” This story that is being repeated and treated as “true” is just not what happened at all. It is one more right-wing victimization fable, repeated endlessly until the public has no choice except t believe it. Conservative Groups Were Not “Targeted,” “Singled Out” Or Anything Else You are hearing that conservative groups were “targeted.” What you are not hearing is that progressive groups were also “targeted.” So were groups that are not progressive or conservative. All that happened here is that groups applying to the IRS for special tax status were checked to see if they were engaged in political activity. They were checked, not targeted. Only 1/3 of the groups checked were conservative groups. Once again: Only 1/3 of the groups checked were conservative groups. Conservative groups were not “singled out,” were not “targeted” and in the end none were denied special tax status — even though many obviously should have been. From last week’s House hearings on this: Rep. Peter Roskam, R-IL: “How come only conservative groups got snagged?” Outgoing acting IRS commissioner Steve Miller: “They didn’t sir. Organizations of all walks and all persuasions were pulled in. That’s shown by the fact that only 70 of the 300 organizations were tea party organizations, of the ones that were looked at by TIGTA [Treasury Inspector General for Tax Administration].” Bet you didn’t see that blasted all over your TV news that night. Click here to watch the video clip of this. It’s worth it. And from Bloomberg reporting: IRS Sent Same Letter to Democrats That Fed Tea Party Row, (emphasis added, for emphasis) One of those groups, Emerge America, saw its tax-exempt status denied, forcing it to disclose its donors and pay some taxes. None of the Republican groups have said their applications were rejected. Progress Texas … faced the same lines of questioning as the Tea Party groups from the same IRS office that issued letters to the Republican-friendly applicants. A third group, Clean Elections Texas, which supports public funding of campaigns, also received IRS inquiries. In a statement late yesterday, the tax agency said it had pooled together the politically active nonpartisan applicants — including a “minority” that were identified because of their names. “It is also important to understand that the group of centralized cases included organizations of all political views,” the IRS said in its statement. Again, for emphasis: “It is also important to understand that the group of centralized cases included organizations of all political views,” the IRS said in its statement.” But no matter, its conventional wisdom now that “the IRS targeted conservative groups.” And it’s very useful to the right if people believe this. But it just is not true. (If you want to see conventional wisdom at work watch this clip from the most recent Saturday Night Live.) What Did Happen? Here’s the story. After the “Citizen’s United” decision allowed unlimited corporate money into elections there was a flood of applications to get special tax status that allowed an organization to hide its donors from the public, and in some cases even be tax-exempt. But the rules say that political groups can’t get this special tax status. The IRS has to check out applications for tax status to see if it is really a political group trying to sneak in to a special tax status. Because they were flooded and couldn’t check out every applying organization, the IRS group looked for things in the applications that “flagged” an organization as a possibly a political group. These flagged applications were then passed along to specialists to look deeper and determine if they were legit or not. So What Was The “Wrongdoing”? The Treasury Inspector General for Tax Administration (TIGTA) has issued a full report: Inappropriate Criteria Were Used to Identify Tax-Exempt Applications for Review that looked into the accusation that the IRS “targeted” tea party groups that were applying for special tax status for extra scrutiny. The report is not all that long. You should read it. (Apparently most the people you are hearing from in the media haven’t read it.) According to the report, the swamped IRS group involved in this came up with ways — “criteria” — to identify groups that really needed to be checked further because it was possible they might be engaged in the kind of political activity that would exclude them from getting the special tax status. (The rules for what constitutes political activity that would keep a group for getting special tax status are, to say the least, not clear. See the PS below.) Some groups were chosen to receive the required scrutiny because they had “political-sounding” names. Some of the “political-sounding names” included the words “tea party.” Others included “We the People” and “Take Back the Country.” (The IG report does not disclose if or which other “political sounding names” were also used as criteria.) And the other problem was that the scrutiny these groups received involved some “unnecessary, burdensome questions.” That was the extent of the wrongdoing. At a time when they couldn’t give all applying groups the necessary scrutiny they used criteria that included the names of an applying group to decide if it would get the required scrutiny. And they asked “unnecessary, burdensome questions.” That’s it. That’s the whole thing. Normally all groups applying for special tax status would and should all get looked at to see if they were really political groups. In this case no groups received any extra scrutiny as has been accused, instead many received less than usual. No group was “singled out” or “targeted” for extra scrutiny, instead they were not given the free pass others were getting because of the overload of applicants. The IG report concluded that it was wrong to use a group’s name as a criteria to help determine if an applicant would be checked out at a time when there were so many applications that every group was not being checked out. (However the IG report did say that most of the groups forwarded with this criteria in fact should have been forwarded.) Again, that’s the wrongdoing that has triggered the absolute frenzy of outrage you are hearing from … everyone. They said it was silly to use a group’s name as criteria for deciding if they should be checked out thoroughly at a time when the IRS was too busy to thoroughly check all applications as they usually do. And they said groups filing for a special tax status but suspected of political activity were then asked “unnecessary, burdensome questions.” And again, that’s it, That’s the whole “scandal.” That’s the whole “IRS harassing conservative groups.” That;s the whole “Obama the dictatorial tyrant going after his enemies” hissy-fit. (Pleasee read Digby’s The Art of the Hissy-Fit) A Few Facts Fact: The IRS is required to determine whether organizations applying for special tax status are “social welfare” groups or are instead engaged in political activity. Political groups cannot get the special tax status these groups were applying for. Fact: Only 1/3 of the groups that were passed to specialists for a closer look were “conservative.” Lots of other organizations were also checked, including progressive organizations. Fact: No groups were audited or harassed or “targeted” or “singled out”. This was about applications for special tax status being forwarded to specialists for a closer look to see if they were engaged in political activity that would disqualify them for the special tax status. This closer look is the kind of review all organization should get, but the IRS was swamped because of the flood of groups applying for a status that let them mask their donors, after Citizens United. Fact: No groups were harmed. There were delays while the groups were checked to see if they should have special tax status. That’s it. But the rules are that they are allowed to operate as if they had that status while they waited for official approval. Fact: The only groups actually denied special tax status were progressive groups, not conservative groups. In 2011, during the period that “conservative groups were targeted” the NY Times carried the story, 3 Groups Denied Break by I.R.S. Are Named . The three groups? Drum roll … “The I.R.S. denied tax exemption to the groups — Emerge Nevada, Emerge Maine and Emerge Massachusetts — because, the agency wrote in denial letters, they were set up specifically to cultivate Democratic candidates.” Fact: The IRS commissioner in charge at the IRS at the time this happened was appointed President George W. Bush. Fact: According to the IG Report (p. 10) in the “majority of cases, we agreed that the applications submitted included indications of significant political campaign intervention.” Other scandals? The stage for this story to take off at this time was set by other “scandals” in the news. The scandal frenzy began when ABC News’ Jonathan Karl falsely reported that White House emails had “taken out” “all references to al Queda and all references to CIA warnings before the attack about the terror threat in Benghazi.” He said that these emails “show that many of these changes were directed by Hillary Clinton’s spokesperson …” Click here to see the video of this report. But a couple of days later CNN broke the news that the emails Karl used for his ABC report were edited by Republicans to make it appear they said these things. Parts of the edited emails Karl used were “inaccurate” and “invented” to make the administration and State Department look bad. (The word “fabricated” comes to mind.) Next came a story that the Justice Department had looked at records of AP reporters to see who in the administration had leaked a story. The story was that an informer high up in al Queda in Yemen had delivered a new kind of bomb to target airliners, while the government was still analyzing how to detect it and the informer was still in Yemen. The Justice Department looked at call records — phone numbers only — to see if they cold spot who had called AP. This became a “scandal” with accusations that the government was “wiretapping” reporters and “secretly monitoring” or “listening in” on their calls — with the “scandal” gaining traction with its conjunction with the “Benghazi scandal” story promoted by ABC. Driving Right-Wing Themes Out To Wider Audiences It is worth noting that Jonathan Karl is a graduate of a conservative-movement “media training” program, the Collegiate Network. The significance of this is explained by Fairness and Accuracy In Reporting (FAIR), in A Right-Wing Mole at ABC News: Jonathan Karl and the success of the conservative media movement, Conservatives don’t just complain loudly, endlessly and inaccurately about liberal media bias. They also train right-leaning journalists to make their way into the supposedly hostile terrain of Beltway media. And one of the most famous alums of a conservative media training program is now a major star at a network news outlet: ABC’s senior political correspondent Jonathan Karl. Karl came to mainstream journalism via the Collegiate Network, an organization primarily devoted to promoting and supporting right-leaning newspapers on college campuses – such as the Rutgers paper launched by the infamous James O’Keefe. The network, founded in 1979, is one of several projects of the Intercollegiate Studies Institute, which seeks to strengthen conservative ideology on college campuses. William F. Buckley was the ISI’s first president, and the current board chair is American Spectator publisher Alfred Regnery. Several leading right-wing pundits came out of Collegiate-affiliated papers, including Ann Coulter, Dinesh D’Souza, Michelle Malkin, Rich Lowry and Laura Ingraham. ABC’s Jonathan Karl is also one of the reporters driving the “IRS scandal” story to a wider audience, with on-air reports like “Document Draft Shows IRS Targeted Conservative Groups,” “IRS IG Report: Targeting Conservatives Began In 2010,” “IRS Scandal Spreads Wider Than Cincinnati Officers” and more such stories, usually with inflammatory headlines and sensationalist scandal-hyping story lines.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369348014477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369349054484-210</Id><Title>Boeings BBJ 3 buisness jets flys 3 hours longer than competitors</Title><Msg>This should really be good for the bizjet market for Boeing. Flying 1,500 (3 hours) miles further than anyother bizjet is a great advance. Not having to stop for extra fuel is big. Lotta lost time refueling and taking off again.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369349054484</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369349115476-211</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I have not noticed that at ALL. I do know that some people with low self esteem tend to project their own short comings onto others to make themselves feel better.</Msg><Username>prybarbq</Username><Timestamp>1369349115476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369349159525-212</Id><Topic><Title>The Latest Lie: IRS Targeted Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369348014477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:26:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>love the article. thanks. I read this board every day but never write. I love these foaming at the mouth Obama haters. They really should seek help.</Msg><Username>penmouse68</Username><Timestamp>1369349159525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369349513949-213</Id><Topic><Title>The Latest Lie: IRS Targeted Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369348014477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:26:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're welcome, sir. And thank you.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369349513949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369350463367-214</Id><Title>IRS replaces official in tea party controversy By STEPHEN OHLEMACHER | Associated Press – 11 mins ago Lerner won't implicate the President</Title><Msg>She tried to stop it, but was unsuccesful, but she is the boss right? Tes Party, Patriots, Constitution and Bill of Rights. Obviously Obama is trying to over throw this government. Lerner learned in June 2011 that agents were singling out groups with "Tea Party" and "Patriots" in their applications for tax-exempt status, according to a report by the agency's inspector general. Lerner ordered agents to scrap the criteria immediately, but later they evolved to include groups that promoted the Constitution and the Bill of Rights.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369350463367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 19:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369351411717-215</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suggest you pay closer attention. Ah...I get it...you're are a FOX follower who actually believes that those bimbos are class acts. My self esteem couldn't be higher, by the way. And my observational skills are second to none...they are pole dancing bimbos.</Msg><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369351411717</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 19:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369351554086-216</Id><Topic><Title>The Latest Lie: IRS Targeted Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369348014477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:26:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you think posters are going to believe you over Lerners statement. Not only Tea Party and Conservitives but those who also support the Constitution and the Bill of Rights. You are one stupid libturd, trying to throw out misinformation.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369351554086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 19:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369351645345-217</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>typical dimwit... put down your comic book copy of sol alinsky rules as to how to handle- demean those you do not understand or agree with. With your attitude and IQ- you too could lead the Senate..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369351645345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 19:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369351755775-218</Id><Topic><Title>Charity be Voluntary or Forced at the threat of Guns?Should</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369345118223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:38:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least black bart was a gentleman and apologized to the ladies and gents while robbing them.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369351755775</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 19:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369352237568-219</Id><Topic><Title>Charity be Voluntary or Forced at the threat of Guns?Should</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369345118223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:38:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ooops minor word issue- did not mean to say he robbed the ladies and gents who were riding in the wells fargo stagecoach- just the money in the wells fargo strongbox The lone bandit continued to stop Wells Fargo stages with regularity, always along mountain roads where the driver was compelled to slow down at dangerous curves. It was later estimated that Bart robbed as much as $18,000 from Wells Fargo stages over the course of his career, striking twenty-eight times. He left no clues whatsoever, although he did leave a spare gun after one robbery. He was always extremely courteous to passengers, especially women travelers, refusing to take their jewelry and cash. He made a favorable impression on drivers and passengers alike as a courteous, gentlemanly robber who apparently wanted to avoid a gunfight at all costs. +++ The IRS makes bart look like a amatuer</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369352237568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 19:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369352440778-220</Id><Topic><Title>Charity be Voluntary or Forced at the threat of Guns?Should</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369345118223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:38:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I've labored long and hard for bread, For honor and for riches But on my corns too long you've tread, You fine-haired sons-of#$%$. Black Bart, the P o 8" Needs updating . . .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369352440778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 19:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369354670908-221</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I've noticed that. Fox hired Sarah Palin, biggest #$%$ of them all.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1369354670908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369354979926-222</Id><Topic><Title>Oklahoma Is Fortunate To Have Obama as President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369346811344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1369354979926</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369355228390-223</Id><Topic><Title>Charity be Voluntary or Forced at the threat of Guns?Should</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369345118223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 17:38:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please go back to your cave, sonny. Where's William Tecumseh Sherman when we need him to take another little hike through Dixie? Great general, that one.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1369355228390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369355441639-224</Id><Topic><Title>Sweden's Government Health Care</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341118348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another cut &amp; paste from an industry-funded think tank. Moving on . . . .</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1369355441639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369356669156-225</Id><Title>Obamacare premiums in California lower than predicted</Title><Msg>http://money.cnn.com/2013/05/23/news/economy/california-obamacare-premiums/index.html</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369356669156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369356718853-226</Id><Title>Thank God for the Affordable Care Act!</Title><Msg>The prices in California, along with those announced in Washington, Vermont and other states, show that premiums under Obamacare can be more affordable than had previously been thought. Consumer advocates welcomed the new exchange. "It's a revolutionary improvement to move from a broken market where people are charged by how sick they are, to a competitive market where people pay what they can afford, based on a percentage of their income, on a sliding scale," said Anthony Wright, executive director of advocacy group Health Access. "Most consumers buying coverage in the individual market will get financial help and see their premiums go down," he said. Here is what the cry baby RepubliCon's soiled their diapers over: "Congressional Republicans who oppose the law had warned that high premiums would sink Obamacare as the uninsured would not be able to afford coverage even with federal subsidies." Really it is, "Congressional Neo-Con Republicans oppose the law and would like to see high premiums sink Obamacare and kill affordable coverage and federal subsidies and let those with pre-existing conditions suffer in squalor and misery, while the R'Cons live in relative luxury because they will have coverage their entire life. The rising new heads of the R'Con party, Paul and Rubbio, have planned for a 2016 presidential win. They've already hired the southern Red state wrecking company's to come in and desimate the blue states and end the obstruction of the Democrats protective shield over 401k's, Social Security and Medicare.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369356718853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369356770651-227</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare premiums in California lower than predicted</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369356669156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU STOLE MY THUNDER! Oh, well, double the good news is even better.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369356770651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369356840557-228</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare premiums in California lower than predicted</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369356669156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did you get that link in there? When I try my post is rejected.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369356840557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369357070381-229</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare premiums in California lower than predicted</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369356669156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not sure. That's the first link I've been able to post.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369357070381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369357377984-230</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare premiums in California lower than predicted</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369356669156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you just type it in? I think I've done it that way, rather than copy and paste. But you can't just click it from there.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369357377984</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369357592088-231</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare premiums in California lower than predicted</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369356669156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So yolu feel ObamaCare is starting to look like a success? HAHAHA It is guaranteed to be a disaster in all respects from quality care, to cost, to high levels of corruption to bankrupting states that accept it. All that guaranteed when it was passed.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369357592088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369357760909-232</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare premiums in California lower than predicted</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369356669156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was a copy and paste. I clicked post and it actually posted.</Msg><Username>daspadoni</Username><Timestamp>1369357760909</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369357938911-233</Id><Topic><Title>Oklahoma Is Fortunate To Have Obama as President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369346811344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oklahoma is fortunate to have successful folks that Obama attacks, and wants to remove their disposable cash, by over taxing them. Folks with disposable cash that have contributed millions in relief money. FEMA? Another big govt failure that heads of state like Obama, and that Palitono show up, and get their mugs in the news, then leave, and we see months later how little they've done, and accomplished. Hurricane Sandy was a complete failure by the Feds, and FEMA after Obama showed up, and got his PR coverage.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369357938911</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369357989351-234</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If We the People establish something as a Right, such as the right to vote, then it becomes a right. Remember, not all adults always had the right to vote, but finally we saw to it that they did, unless they have done something to cause themselves to lose that right. People have a right to remain silent when apprehended, but that right was not always clear. They have a right to public education, in fact education, one way or another is required. Now health insurance is, and like education, it's for the good of the country.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369357989351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369358144817-235</Id><Topic><Title>tesla motors or Boeing company which is better? 6/5% or 1.86% or 290% or 22% five years</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369342192650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:49:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like when I recommended apple for 15 years until Steve jobs died, these Boeing hacks are inviting me to go to TESLA to comment on TSLA, well attention, Boeing hacks , I suggest you go post your gibberish on the TSLA Yahoo message board and get laughed off the board there too. well bark and ouch Boeing hacks , you say Boeing is up for a Dow stock over 30% year to date and I point out Hewlett Packard a Dow stock, is up over 70% year to date end of story. then Boeing hacks , . you say Boeing is about to go to triple digits and I say any time a stock is that close to a even number and cant break through for days, well then Boeing hacks, that is bad sign that the lemon has been squeezed so hard it is not a good stock, it cant ring the bell for days or weeks . . This whole Boeing stock price run up is on Boeing shareholders money, it is a stock buyback rally. You Boeing hacks think your some kind of advertisement for Boeing you fancy yourself as some kind of salesman for Boeing, you guys could not do worse if you tried . Attention Boeing hack learn to trade a stock chart .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369358144817</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369358147026-236</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368917907589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 18:58:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might be correct about bush NOT being responsible for slavery, the fall of troy, pearl harbor, eruption of st Helens, the san francisco earthquake, or the civil war. However, Bush is responsible to nearly 5000 US combat deaths and many thousands more on the other side. He is responsible for those who hired the TSA agents that let 19 terrorists board and take over 4 airliners, and the nearly 3000 fireman and civilian deaths from that attack. Bush is responsible for the use of torture in Guantanamo Bay detention camp. Bush is responsible for the poor response to Katrina and the deaths attributed to that. Bush is responsible for letting the deteriorated electric power grid lapse in integrity to the point of a multi-state blackout. I'm sure there were deaths attributed to that. Bush is responsible for running up the debt more than any other president in history, and which caused the 2006 second largest stockmarket crash since the 29 crash. Bush is such a criminal and evil monster and this is just the stuff I can remember the shrub. Volumes could be written about your beloved President Shrub. More will hate him for eternity than love him. I hope the second coming happens while Shrub and I are still alive so I can get a glimpse of Bushs shame just before the he is cast into the eternal damnation by the flames .... of hell.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369358147026</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369358505631-237</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya FOX has hot chicks and they dig guys unlike the koolaid drinking boy girls on PMSNBC &amp; CNN. Becky Quick CNBC is pretty hot also, I loved the time she gutted Bill Richardson. Do you have a poledancer, hot looking chick fantasy thing? If so there are some porno boards you may enjoy more than the BA stock board.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1369358505631</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369358969259-238</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very well written. Thanks</Msg><Username>penmouse68</Username><Timestamp>1369358969259</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369359121788-239</Id><Topic><Title>Who Loves Medicare?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369325665982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:14:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like a very good evaluation and argument- You are dead right- I know of no senior citizen who is against Medicare- we love it-- One of the most obvious areas for Medicare to do its thing is in cardiovascular surgery where bills that average a couple hundred thousand are handled with ease and the senior has a copay that is manageable and likely covered by his "supplemental insurance"</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369359121788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369359437552-240</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a looonatik argument- we aren't talking about the law of gravity here or some physical law- American seniors have a "right" because WE SAY THEY HAVE A RIGHT and we have provided Medicare to pay the benefits-- I would think that you holier than thou RWNJs would want to at least do the Christian thing- but talk about hypocrites.......</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369359437552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369359497598-241</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey team ?? please use the correct letters for MSDNC - otherwise you will be hammered for gender discrimination :-PP</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369359497598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369359784262-242</Id><Topic><Title>Is Health Care a Right?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341459028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a tip Padre. They only imitate Christianity on Sunday for an hour or so on the church grounds. Its handshakes, hugs, brother this and brother that, but when their car leaves the parking lot, it all goes out the window until next Sunday. This is why they aren't true conservatives or even Republicans. They are in the Neo-Con club of whats best for me at his very moment.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369359784262</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369360011052-243</Id><Topic><Title>Sweden's Government Health Care</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1369341118348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 16:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rebel you got to be Gawd awful slow- both Britain and Sweden are democracys and if the voters didn't like their single payer plans they would elect politicians who would give them what they want in health insurance- so why is it they haven't done this very thing- is it possible that you have been selective in your choice of health insurance news and have chosen only the bagger, RWNJ news stories??? and you are trying to make these stories stand up for the truth?? My Gawd!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369360011052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 21:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369361757191-244</Id><Title>Boeing larger 787-9 to begin assembly later this summer</Title><Msg>Parts arriving ahead of shedule across across entire supplier chain. New bird to be 20 ft longer and hold 40 more passengers. Approx 355 order for new 787-9 already recieved by Boeing. Things seem to be going well. Learning curve on 787-8 should really start kicking in to a higher degree soon.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369361757191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 22:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369363696363-245</Id><Title>70 Billion dollars expected to be spent next 10 years 60 heavy rocket launches</Title><Msg>Hopefully the ULA joint venture with Lockheed and Boeing will capture 50 - 75% of launches. Space X is progressing, but some of these satellites are so expensive, it could be wiser to go with a decades long proven source---especially for the heavy lift defense satellites. They should probably buy Space X.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369363696363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 22:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369365796657-246</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare premiums in California lower than predicted</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369356669156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 20:51:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to Censored (Fascist/Bumper) Yahoo has "acorns" who screen his (and probably your) posts. So they must have approved yours. HAR HAR HAR. He also claims he has to tunnel in from alternate world-wide internet locations, so the sanity level from Censored may indeed be suspect. Come to think of it, he has also defended Senator McCarthy, so . . . .</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1369365796657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 23:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369365904239-247</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds a bit narcissistic to me.</Msg><Username>applup</Username><Timestamp>1369365904239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 23:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369366234341-248</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh by the way narcissism, that's a personality disorder, you don't have one....right?</Msg><Username>applup</Username><Timestamp>1369366234341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 23:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369366309983-249</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!</Msg><Username>prybarbq</Username><Timestamp>1369366309983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 23:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369366462350-250</Id><Topic><Title>freeveritas • the DOW is the lagger index and Hewlet Packard is up 70% and Boeing only 32% for Dow gainer</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369326255996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 12:24:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayneker, there are 28 other corporations on the DOW that are not performing as well a Boeing. Why is it you come here and bash Boeing and Boeing investors instead of these other 28 underperforming DOW corporations? What is your purpose? Did Boeing do something to you? Were you abused, neglected and unappreciated when you worked there or as a child?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1369366462350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 23:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369367317405-251</Id><Topic><Title>Women on FOX Business Channel</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369347445427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There you go, see... there it is again. Trying to feel, more than the worthless piece of wasted skin that they have morphed by projecting their own reality onto someone else. Lets see... lipstick on a pig, that.....s your wife, ha you poor sucker......... LOL!</Msg><Username>prybarbq</Username><Timestamp>1369367317405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 23:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>