<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357537063746-1</Id><Title>And the most popular new book in America is???????????????</Title><Msg>??????????????$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$??????????????</Msg><Username>disgracedpublicist757</Username><Timestamp>1357537063746</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 00:37:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357537392828-2</Id><Topic><Title>I do not know those people</Title><Username>coldax111</Username><Timestamp>1223686371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2008-10-10 20:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the score in 1980 was 3-2 plese insert anothe on trillion coin in to the slot b4 we as in US beat you although many Ukraiinian probbal J's and some former Soviets wiith failed root canals made of a meta;l which has not been analyzed befoirerd this side of The Pecos unbless their radiation is off the charts and their snow dont;t stink as much as those above we,, as in US... are IN F++++ Soschi from lol</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357537392828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 00:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357538255706-3</Id><Topic><Title>I do not know those people</Title><Username>coldax111</Username><Timestamp>1223686371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2008-10-10 20:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bless their losing ic-e-skating hearts 3-2w thwe british are worth 1///point</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357538255706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 00:57:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357538911808-4</Id><Topic><Title>I do not know those people</Title><Username>coldax111</Username><Timestamp>1223686371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2008-10-10 20:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I meant US is gonna whoop you collectiv #$%$ dis-counting the South Carolinians</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357538911808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 01:08:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357539827267-5</Id><Topic><Title>I do not know those people</Title><Username>coldax111</Username><Timestamp>1223686371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2008-10-10 20:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looking foolish in a red coa\t even if dyed-blue has no buttons smelted in to bullets - the US revoulutionairies</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357539827267</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 01:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357542340649-6</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Expanding Rapidly</Title><Username>bearnz1</Username><Timestamp>1357334652937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:24:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Way off trasck on new programs. 787 read about that failure in any publication you chose and the 747-8. Will the 737 and current 777 make up for thees economic failures? What happens if they have similar results when they go ahead with the 777X? Off track with their employees a strike is very possible shortly, then the cost of what management must have up their sleeve with the recent land purchase in SC. 777X will be designed and built there is my personal guess. Why, because they can't seem to "profit" here and won't accept the responsibilities of their own management failures, so they will spen even more money and upset work relations even more with this move.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357542340649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 02:05:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357547266896-7</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Expanding Rapidly</Title><Username>bearnz1</Username><Timestamp>1357334652937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:24:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gamblin09, the 737 accounts for most of Boeing profit, followed by the 777 so while Boeing management is failed, for sure, can they be that bad to transfer the 777 to Carolina? I hope not, the wage was never an issue, read up on it. The Washington State governor said she was told by the top Boeing executive in Washington that money was not an issue. Boeing Management in Chicago does not want workers to have a labor contract like the executives do. Boeing wants to go to a non union state, but that has been a failure too. Frankly, for the 787 which the union said they could build for 5 billion dollars just like they did with the like the 777. was the best deal Boeing could have taken. Boeing executives who are inexperienced with how Boeing works and from MMM or MD, a is a failed aerospace and bankrupt outsourcing company that now runs Boeing Boeing SPEEA union offered to build the 787 on time and at 5 billion dollars. SPEEA tried to tell Boeing Executives that the technology was not ready and Boeing management would not listen the result is BA stock price for a year is less than other aerospace companies BA for a year is up about 5% , while NOC Northrop is up over 18%, Lockheed is up over 19% for a year (LMI), NASDAQ average is up over 17%, Dow average is up over 8%, and another dow stock Bank of America(BAC) is up about 100% so Boeing is not a company to hold stock in. 787 will not break even until 2021 and cost shareholder 116K for each late delivery a SPEEA strike will cost shareholders 250K per day ,not a stock to own</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357547266896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 03:27:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357550185644-8</Id><Title>deep poling</Title><Msg>... and a toaster-oven but then she was a real blonde hottie 77.77 to 88.88 live long and prosper</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357550185644</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 04:16:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357552901012-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama President For Life? H.J. Res 15 Bill</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357486760784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 10:39:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well dummy if you had botherd to google it you would have seen that this congressman has done this rather consistently over the years and has gotten no where.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1357552901012</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 05:01:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357553747360-10</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: The clowns are in charge</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357517692343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 19:14:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look who's talking, the cut and paste king who is to #$%$ stupid to think for himself.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1357553747360</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 05:15:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357557085455-11</Id><Topic><Title>I do not know those people</Title><Username>coldax111</Username><Timestamp>1223686371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2008-10-10 20:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The NImitz I know it was named after an Admrlal in the USN whom the #$%$ wished they sunk...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357557085455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 06:11:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357558733858-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama President For Life? H.J. Res 15 Bill</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357486760784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 10:39:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dik...Dave brought up the fact that there was a proposal to ELIMINATE term limits...essentially meaning "stay for life" if you can keep getting elected...not LIMITING their terms. Try to keep up PS...Roosevelt had 4 terms ...so Barry can claim there are precedents</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357558733858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 06:38:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357561630094-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama-Backed Syrian Rebels Praise Bin Laden, Celebrate 9/11 Attacks</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357398835787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 10:13:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still in all a good post</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357561630094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 07:27:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357561804467-14</Id><Topic><Title>Marine Afgan Veteran/Hero Writes letter to Feinstein. "You will NOT get my Guns" Awesome Read</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357259357826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 19:29:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do the grabbers share the same agenda as the Russians and Chinese? Because deep down they know they are authoritarian and dictatorial....and hate us for DARING to be free. If they can break America they know they ve won. Have you noticed that the Russians have been putting the hammer and syckle back on their tanks ? Looks like the old timers were right....the commies were just playing possum...and our boy Barry is cozying up real well to em.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357561804467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 07:30:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357563082045-15</Id><Topic><Title>snake hard-on</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357558720504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 06:38:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unless,,, ba-da-bing underage my #$%$ slep with the fish add price of concrete shoes.... and chains</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357563082045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 07:51:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357563088911-16</Id><Topic><Title>Marine Afgan Veteran/Hero Writes letter to Feinstein. "You will NOT get my Guns" Awesome Read</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357259357826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 19:29:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Cold War never ended.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357563088911</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 07:51:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357563247386-17</Id><Topic><Title>snake hard-on</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357558720504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 06:38:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God is my lawyer Jesus is my savior bulky-blob is my shield....,</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1357563247386</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 07:54:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357563307579-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama President For Life? H.J. Res 15 Bill</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357486760784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 10:39:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't the elimination of term limits Un-American?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357563307579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 07:55:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357564144846-19</Id><Title>*******NULLIFICATION*******</Title><Msg>..................at the local, county and State level could be the constitutional remedy to Unconstitutional and dictatorial Federal laws.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357564144846</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:09:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357564318513-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama President For Life? H.J. Res 15 Bill</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357486760784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 10:39:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>H.J.Res. 15: Proposing an amendment to the Constitution of the United States to repeal the twenty-second article of amendment, thereby removing the limitation on the number of terms an individual may serve as President. Introduced: Jan 04, 2013 (113th Congress, 2013–2015) Sponsor: Rep. José Serrano [D-NY15] Status: Referred to Committee We’re still a couple of weeks from the inauguration, but Rep. Jose Serrano (D-N.Y.) is already looking forward to 2016 and beyond. The congressman yesterday reintroduced a bill to repeal the 22nd amendment establishing term limits for the president.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357564318513</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:11:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357565347426-21</Id><Title>Hey black_mariah777, Hoozdik is After You</Title><Msg>He says you remind him of his dates with his blow up doll except you don't make as much sense as the doll does.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357565347426</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:29:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357565421540-22</Id><Title>Boeing 787 delivery delayed to China and stock report</Title><Msg>HONG KONG, Jan 7 (Reuters) -" Boeing declined comment on its customers' delivery plans”. China said it has yet to approve Boeing's 787 Dreamliner, which has put on hold the delivery of the jet to the world's fastest growing aviation market. China Southern Airlines Co Ltd , , had expected to receive its first plane in 2012, but that has been delayed as the Boeing . has yet to receive certification from Chinese authorities. , Hainan Airlines , which aimed to get five B787 airliners last year, did not take delivery of the troubled 787 plane due to delayed certification. So hows that outsourcing working for Chicago now ?. China has been increasingly concerned with Boeing 787 planes and is exercising its right to independently certify the airworthiness of the Boeing built aerospace equipment.. . . The purpose of stock ownership is to make money. So how does owning stock in Boeing compare? for one year BA is up 5%, Northrop (NOC) up over 18%, Lockheed(LMI) up over 19%, the NSADAQ up over 17%, STP for a quick profit up 40% in 5 days and 117% in one month and move on. Investors should take a look around the stock world, you could do worse but making 5% in a year is not anything to brag about. The Dow Jones average beats Boeing up by 8% for the last year. BA compared to the DOW or another DOW stock BAC missed a gain of over 90% for the year, in fact BAC has gained more than Boeing made in a year in the last five trade days, BAC up more than 5%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357565421540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:30:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357566244083-23</Id><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Msg>If you earn a middle class paycheck like a lot of Americans do, you saw your Social Security taxes increase last week thanks to the so called fiscal cliff deal passed by Congress and signed into law by President Obama. Considering the system is totally broke, losing that extra cash to the government "lock box" makes you think about where that money, and the rest of your tax dollars are actually going. The New York Post has discovered through an investigation that welfare recipients using EBT cards (which work like debit cards filled with taxpayer money, just swipe and buy) pulled out cash to use at strip bars, to buy alcohol and to use at porn shops. They’re on the dole — and watching the pole. Welfare recipients took out cash at bars, liquor stores, X-rated video shops, hookah parlors and even strip clubs — where they presumably spent their taxpayer money on lap dances rather than diapers, a Post investigation found. A database of 200 million Electronic Benefit Transfer records from January 2011 to July 2012, obtained by The Post through a Freedom of Information request, showed welfare recipients using their EBT cards to make dozens of cash withdrawals at ATMs inside Hank’s Saloon in Brooklyn; the Blue Door Video porn shop in the East Village; The Anchor, a sleek SoHo lounge; the Patriot Saloon in TriBeCa; and Drinks Galore, a liquor distributor in The Bronx. The state Office of Temporary and Disability Assistance (OTDA), which oversees the “cash assistance program,” even lists some of these welfare-ready ATMs on its Web site. One EBT machine is stationed inside Club Eleven, an infamous Hunts Point jiggle joint known as much for its violent history as its girls in pink thongs. Club Heat, another Bronx strip club that dispenses EBT cash, is also no stranger to violence. A 33-year-old woman was fatally shot in the head outside the club in December 2011. Welfare recipients receive food stamps and cash assistance under the federal Temporary Assistance for Needy Families program. Both benefits are accessed through an EBT card, but only cash assistance — meant for housing, utilities and household necessities — can be accessed at ATMs. The fact that welfare ATMs even exist is insane. Giving out cash with zero oversight? Really? And the idea that some of these ATMs are actually located inside strip clubs is ludicrous. This investigation comes just one month after we found a record $168 per day is being spent in taxpayer money on welfare services per household living below the poverty line and that welfare was the single largest budget item of 2011. Pavlich</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357567914724-24</Id><Title>Union complaint</Title><Msg>One week before negotiations are scheduled to resume between Boeing and one of its biggest unions, the engineers union has filed another unfair labor practices complaint with the National Labor Relations Board. The Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace (SPEEA) filing on Wednesday contends that Boeing took surveillance photos of union members marching inside and outside Boeing’s Everett factory on Dec. 12, and after that as well. But Boeing Co. (NYSE: BA) spokesman Doug Alder said the charges are without merit. “Boeing has followed all labor laws throughout the negotiations process and SPEEA’s claims have been baseless,” he said in an email. “Right now, our team is focused on getting back to the table on January 9.”</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357567914724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:11:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357568851911-25</Id><Title>Obama Is A Destroyer</Title><Msg>Ever heard of a scraper? That’s a term that’s used here in Naples to describe a decades-old house that is targeted for destruction. The owner of the property wants to scrape the house off the property with a bulldozer so he can build something more to his liking. Obama looks at America as a scraper. This dangerous man was not just playing around when he said that he was going to fundamentally transform our country. If you’re going to fundamentally transform a structure -- a scraper, for instance – you first hjave to destroy what’s there. That is precisely what Obama is doing with America right now. He’s working on the destruction of our Republic so that he can then build an economy and a government structure that is more to his liking. And just what would be more to Obama’s liking? To make it simple – an egalitarian society. A European welfare society. A government-run economy where economic decisions are made by government officials and politicians who will tell you that they have society’s best interests at heart, not by millions of consumers exercising their individual choices with no regard for what’s good for society. Obama’s dream? A society where individualism – and individual achievement – is demonized and where groups and collective achievement are praised. Obama was raised – by his father, his mother, his communist mentor Frank Marshall Davis, his college professors and the Marxist student groups he associated with in college – taught him that America was basically evil, and that those who succeed and become wealthy in this climate of oppression and evil did so by exploiting and suppressing others. Obama came to America in 1979 determined to work for a Marxist revolution – violent, if necessary. The one thing he learned from his Marxist friends in college was that if there was to be a Marxist revolution in America it would have to come through the political process, not through violent revolt. He is now working the political process to tyranny almost perfectly, with no small amount of help from a fawning ObamaMedia. Obama is a destroyer. A sneering, menacing, arrogant destroyer. Many Americans already know this. Others are learning every day. Some will never learn. All who value liberty will suffer. NEAL</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357568851911</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:27:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357569145778-26</Id><Topic><Title>Union complaint</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357567914724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:11:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unfair labor complaint makes it a protected strike for SPEEA if affirmed. Boeing should not have taken pictures of peaceful rest time and break time protests , that is free time, not paid worker time, now Boeing will have to work to meet SPEEA as the strike would be protected .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357569145778</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:32:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357569352589-27</Id><Title>The Latest on Gun Control</Title><Msg>Here is some of the latest in the liberal charge to curb Second Amendment rights. First we have this from the White House. The White House is weighing a far broader and more comprehensive approach to curbing the nation’s gun violence than simply reinstating an expired ban on assault weapons and high-capacity ammunition, according to multiple people involved in the administration’s discussions. A working group led by Vice President Biden is seriously considering measures backed by key law enforcement leaders that would require universal background checks for firearm buyers, track the movement and sale of weapons through a national database, strengthen mental health checks, and stiffen penalties for carrying guns near schools or giving them to minors, the sources said. How does Obama plan to accomplish this? By working with companies like Wal-Mart to appeal to their possible business gains from closing the fictitious “gun show loophole.” I’ve been through this charade before, but let me remind you of why I call this gun show loophole fictitious. From Nealz Nuze December 20, 2012: Obama says he will introduce legislation to close “The Gun Show Loophole.” There IS NO gun show loophole. The federal laws pertaining to purchasing a firearm at a gun show are exactly the same at a gun show as they are anywhere else in this country. When a private individual sells a firearm to another private individual there is no requirement for a background check. When a licensed firearms dealer sells a gun to an individual a background check must be performed before the weapon is transferred. When a private individual at a gun show sells a firearm to another private individual there is no requirement for a background check. When a licensed firearms dealer at a gun show sells a gun to an individual a background check must be performed before the weapon is transferred. The operation of law is EXACTLY the same at a gun show as it is anywhere else. Therefore, as I said, there is no “gun show loophole.” The true purpose behind this “close the gun show loophole” idea is to make the sale and transfer of firearms between individuals impossible by requiring a private individual to conduct a background check before selling a privately owned gun to another individual. Private individuals do not have the legal authority to access the information necessary to perform the background check. This would mean that Americans could only obtain a firearm through a federally licensed firearms dealer. Now are you starting to understand how Obama will try to appeal to big businesses to “close” this loophole? If closing the loophole essentially makes the sale of firearms between individuals impossible, more sales will be forced to go through … the very companies that Obama is appealing to! What’s more … when all gun sales between individuals have to involve a background check, the government will have a record of all of these sales. What does this mean? It means the next step – gun registration – will be that much easier. After registration, where do we go? One word. Confiscation. Neal</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357569352589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:35:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357569727517-28</Id><Topic><Title>Union complaint</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357567914724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:11:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new filing reflects the continued tension between the union and company, which have been negotiating since April with little movement on substantive issues of wages, benefits and retirement. Before the holidays, the two sides agreed to work with a federal mediator and took a break from direct negotiations. But over the holidays, union members openly prepared for a possible strike.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357569727517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:42:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357570164258-29</Id><Title>Get a load of this Economic Illiterate Who Makes our Laws</Title><Msg>Princess Pelosi said the unemployment rate remaining flat at 7.8 percent shows a “good pace” and that the country is “going in the right direction.”</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357570164258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:49:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357570559944-30</Id><Topic><Title>MORE EVIDENCE "DEREGULATION" DOESN"T WORK</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357570005053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why hasn't Foxvda reported this yet?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357570559944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:55:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357570690887-31</Id><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Msg>“Power concedes nothing without a demand. It never did and it never will. Find out just what any people will quietly submit to and you have found out the exact measure of injustice and wrong which will be imposed upon them, and these will continue till they are resisted with either words or blows, or both. The limits of tyrants are prescribed by the endurance of those whom they oppress.” Frederick Douglass</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357570690887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:58:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357571198685-32</Id><Title>Did you Vote for Romney...</Title><Msg>were you conscious when you voted.... most Americans were...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357571198685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:06:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357571367403-33</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Gun Responsibility laws' what a concept !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357571367403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357571420945-34</Id><Topic><Title>MORE EVIDENCE "DEREGULATION" DOESN"T WORK</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357570005053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO.....you libtards are a riot. No wonder the country is in the shape it's in when your vote counts as much as someone's who actually has a brain.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357571420945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:10:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357571706322-35</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We are simply asking Americans ( the real ones) to be responsible with your firearms... or thou rights to bear shall be adjusted... Again !" Ahh.....the liberal logic on the road to tyranny. When some one breaks the law.....use it as an excuse to make another law that restricts the rights of those who didn't break the law.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357571706322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:15:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357571836008-36</Id><Topic><Title>The rich should pay more not only because</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357338492668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 17:28:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>‘for unto whom much is given, much shall be required.’ Luke 12:48</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357571836008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357571845453-37</Id><Topic><Title>MORE EVIDENCE "DEREGULATION" DOESN"T WORK</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357570005053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I luv the smell of burning bagger in the morning!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357571845453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:17:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357571950236-38</Id><Topic><Title>The rich should pay more not only because</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357338492668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 17:28:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>vey iz MIR,</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357571950236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:19:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357572187235-39</Id><Topic><Title>The rich should pay more not only because</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357338492668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 17:28:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Creating a whip from some cords, "he drove them all out of the temple, with the sheep and the oxen, and poured out the changers’ money and overturned the tables".</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357572187235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:23:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357572258017-40</Id><Topic><Title>The rich should pay more not only because</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357338492668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 17:28:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it greed for one to want to keep their own, hard earned money, and somehow not greed when you leftists want to take other folks' hard earned money? And for your information duffus, there are trillions of dollars invested in foreign funds. Just normal, everyday investing.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357572258017</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:24:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357573061049-41</Id><Title>Uh OH.....Another Obama Failure</Title><Msg>A local North Carolina business that was championed last January by Obama as an example of a recovering economy, is shutting its doors. A local North Carolina business that was championed last January by President Obama as an example of a recovering U.S. economy, is shutting its doors, putting 50 people out of the work. Lincolnton Furniture Company closed Thursday due to factory upgrades that drained start-up capital quicker than expected. The company will slow down operations until it closes later this year in attempt to accomodate laid off workers. The company’s owner, Bruce Cochrane, entered the public scene last winter when the White House invited him to a business roundtable on bringing American jobs back home. Cochrane was seated with First Lady Michelle Obama during the 2012 State of the Union Address.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357573061049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:37:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357573545112-42</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice post,when will our government wake the H*%L up?</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1357573545112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:45:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357573864160-43</Id><Title>United flying 787, so are fuel efficiencies really working?</Title><Msg>Anyone know what the new 787 is doing for United? New route from L.A. to Tokyo has begun. I'm curious if the fuel efficiencies and use is really lower as projected in the real world use? Anyone know?</Msg><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1357573864160</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:51:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357574129962-44</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Expanding Rapidly</Title><Username>bearnz1</Username><Timestamp>1357334652937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:24:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have another explanation for the purchase of three office bldgs last month and now the land purchase with options up to a little over 1000 acres? I don't want to see this happen either but as Boeing has recently stated "We do not bank land" what do you think the purchases are for? 1000 acres is not needed for the 787 program.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357574129962</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:55:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357574584334-45</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If there is any doubt.....just read their posts.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357574584334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:03:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357574915600-46</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you thinik you can change the world like Obama thinks he can to fascist socialism that is far worse than a corrupt politician. And YES, liberals have sign on, taken the pledge that they will be stupid.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357574915600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:08:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357575101648-47</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the soviet of washington state- the money goes to casinos and ipods also</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357575101648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:11:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357575596625-48</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ooops forgot no doubt the new legal Pot shops.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357575596625</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357575609527-49</Id><Title>they got a plane on the news in boston, looks like its a BA plane fire on it</Title><Msg>maybe thats why stock falling</Msg><Username>goodeal4u2002</Username><Timestamp>1357575609527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:20:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357575662837-50</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, don't knock welfare recipients!f That's where libs think jobs will be created. They think redistributing wealth to the downtrodden will then make them capable of creating jobs. They had better, because successful folks are pulling their money out because of the fascist, socialist regime' overseeing the economy.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357575662837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:21:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357576262643-51</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If there is any doubt.....just read their posts.</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1357576262643</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:31:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357576535737-52</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, it sounds like they are creating jobs for dancers and bartenders.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1357576535737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:35:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357576827751-53</Id><Title>Just now a Boeing 787 caught on fire at Logan airport</Title><Msg>this is the 4th incident on a Boeing and FAA certified airplane so hows that cheap outsourcing working for you now Cicago Boeing Managment ~!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357576827751</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:40:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357576921481-54</Id><Title>Boston 787 Fire today</Title><Msg>A fire has been reported in an empty airplane parked at a gate at Logan International Airport, a Massport spokesman said this morning.The affected aircraft was a Japan Airlines Boeing 787 Dreamliner, spokesman Richard Walsh said. The 787 is used on a nonstop flight from Boston to Tokyo, which has been a pivotal part of Governor Deval Patrick’s efforts to expand trade between Massachusetts and Asia.No smoke was showing from the plane late this morning, but it remained surrounded by fire engines. A Federal Aviation Administration spokesman said the fire occurred while the plane was sitting at a gate. State Police said there were no crew and no passengers on the plane, which was sitting at Gate E8. Boston Fire Department spokesman Steve MacDonald said his department had responded at 10:40 a.m. to assist the Massport Fire Department with a report of an electrical fire on a plane.MacDonald said his department had one engine and one ladder truck at the plane and another engine staged at the airport’s North Gate.He said the Boston firefighters on the scene reported the fire was in the belly of the aircraft</Msg><Username>auagboy</Username><Timestamp>1357576921481</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:42:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357576986278-55</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is mass hynotism. It is a cult. It is the Emporer's New Clothes" on the hoof.</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1357576986278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:43:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357577137107-56</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry me a river. You doofs just can't seem to get over it and move on with life. What Spartapus has must be contagious. You get it through your keyboard. Harharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357577137107</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:45:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357577140222-57</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alinski in action. "never let any crisis got to waste" Increase it, personalize it then drum it in."</Msg><Username>sparrowgt</Username><Timestamp>1357577140222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:45:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357577146150-58</Id><Topic><Title>they got a plane on the news in boston, looks like its a BA plane fire on it</Title><Username>goodeal4u2002</Username><Timestamp>1357575609527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:20:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Japan airlines JA829 787. REports say plane was parked and no one was on the plane. Smoke reported coming from the cargo hold. initial reports say fire started in cockpit. There is supposed to be more news at 1145 am.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357577146150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:45:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357577160997-59</Id><Title>So empty Dreamliner caught fire, spontaneous combustion?</Title><Msg>#$%$ is going on with this plane?</Msg><Username>profiteer</Username><Timestamp>1357577160997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:46:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357577171702-60</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 delivery delayed to China and stock report</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357565421540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:30:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for the last two thumbs down , a 787 just was reported on fire at logan airport that is the 4th incident how is your Boeing stock price working for you now thumb down yourself, get smart invest in better stocks Boieng stock price down 1.33% today</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357577171702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:46:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357577623333-61</Id><Topic><Title>Optimism: 50 Percent of Americans Say Best Years Are Behind Us</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357259795829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 19:36:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure they think this because the manufacturing sector of our economy has been sold off to international interests, and the financial sector has loaded the US with unsustainable levels of debt, so that much of the total economic output flows to the unproductive financial sector as interest payments. Then there is the wide spread corruption in government and industry, that results in bad investment of our shrinking capital. You can't hope for very much in a country like that. Still many people are enjoying an alternative life style by living on unemployment checks and food stamps. At least they will be happy.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1357577623333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357577653501-62</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And civil laws need to identify their mental cases, and prevent them from harming the public. Gun control will do no good, although I, as a many gun owner would vote to ban the UZI type guns, and the high bullet capacity clips.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357577653501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:54:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357577701150-63</Id><Topic><Title>they got a plane on the news in boston, looks like its a BA plane fire on it</Title><Username>goodeal4u2002</Username><Timestamp>1357575609527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:20:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they are talking flight deck and cargo I'm betting fwd EE bay.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1357577701150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:55:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357578112886-64</Id><Title>This Plane reminds me of Fisker Karma. Catches on fire while parked</Title><Msg>Bad thing is if it catches on fire in air, 300 passengers die vs. one Justin Bieber. What kind of electrical problems / design is the plane hiding. There is over 3000 miles of wire in this plane.</Msg><Username>moneymeyka</Username><Timestamp>1357578112886</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:01:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357578154792-65</Id><Topic><Title>Union complaint</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357567914724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:11:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting the Boeing executives don't want to do anything with their most valuble resouce the Boeing SPEEA union workers the best in the world and just now a 4th incident with the 787 a fire on a first customer plane the 4th incident. Too bad Boeing did not take the original deal SPEEA offered to control the design and make the 787 for 5 billion and bring it in on time. Instead Chicago went with that cheap outssourcing, well the went cheap and the cost so far is total failure of customer confidence in the 787, 30 billion dollars and counting to fix outsource ddesign and parts and 3years late. Each 787 cost the shareholder 116K to deliver , no profit, same problem with the spit shine on the 747, 2 billion over budget and two years late and not enough customers with the just as bad A380 taking orders. So Boeing executives when you negotiate take aways from your workers in Washington State remember to continue to give yourselfs bonus payola, I am sure that will make more investors leave Beoing stock</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357578154792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:02:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357578345818-66</Id><Topic><Title>Union complaint</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357567914724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:11:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Break time is paid. Lunch time is unpaid. Unions have to be very careful about any protest on company property.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357578345818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:05:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357578877188-67</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then what are we arguing about, dokes? That's what two-thirds of Americans want for "gun control." Welcome to the mainstream ! :-D</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357578877188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:14:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357578954691-68</Id><Topic><Title>they got a plane on the news in boston, looks like its a BA plane fire on it</Title><Username>goodeal4u2002</Username><Timestamp>1357575609527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:20:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The noontime report said the fire was in the cargo bay. No mention of the cockpit. One comment said a battery exploded. At this point, it is all speculation until the investigation is completed by the FAA and others.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357578954691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:15:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357578962904-69</Id><Title>Just bought in 500 at $75.93!!!!!! asy should end Green panic selling blah blah</Title><Msg>$78 by Friday</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357578962904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:16:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357579002577-70</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Non automatic Uzi or assault weapons and larger capacity clips are not the problem, IMO. That cat is out of the bag and can't be put back. Holding gun owners responsible for proper storage and use is a plausible way to curb the casual access to these weapons by theives and crazies. Registration with background checks for both new and resold weapons would also be a big help...JMHO... In America the chances of Gubmint going door to door taking away guns would create a revolution. Back during WW! the Japanese commander stated they never would attack the US homeland because 'there would be a gun behind every bush', so I would not want to be someone that goes door to door trying to collect personal legally owned weapons. It would be an impossible task and many would not cooperate.</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1357579002577</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:16:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357579137845-71</Id><Title>McNerney says " This is Normal".......What a Dichead</Title><Msg>787 is a Joke and it's McNerney's baby. He has been on the board of directors, ceo, or chairman of the board, or all of the above during the entire history of the 787. He was one of the nincompoops that outsourced this high tech fiasco all over the planet.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357579137845</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:18:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357579157124-72</Id><Topic><Title>So empty Dreamliner caught fire, spontaneous combustion?</Title><Username>profiteer</Username><Timestamp>1357577160997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:46:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We wont know till the investigation is complete. One report said a battery exploded. Tee plane landed at about 1040 AM and was "empty".</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357579157124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:19:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357579196823-73</Id><Title>EASY SHORT</Title><Msg>Already had a 10% run. Take profits before order cancellations.</Msg><Username>pdoty728</Username><Timestamp>1357579196823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357579362719-74</Id><Title>787 fire</Title><Msg>boston mechanic reports that a battery exploded</Msg><Username>aerodog1</Username><Timestamp>1357579362719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357579510324-75</Id><Topic><Title>Union complaint</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357567914724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:11:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>albucucu are you an attorney then? paid or not paid rest time or meal time is for whatever the employee wants to do in rest time or unpaid lunch time. Harassing a SPEEA member during his free time , lunch or break is against the law"WAC 296-126-092 Meal periods -- Rest periods. (1) Employees shall be allowed a meal period of at least thirty minutes which commences no less than two hours nor more than five hours from the beginning of the shift. Meal periods shall be on the employer's time when the employee is required by the employer to remain on duty on the premises or at a prescribed work site in the interest of the employer. (2) No employee shall be required to work more than five consecutive hours without a meal period. (3) Employees working three or more hours longer than a normal work day shall be allowed at least one thirty-minute meal period prior to or during the overtime period. (4) Employees shall be allowed a rest period of not less than ten minutes, on the employer's time, for each four hours of working time. Rest periods shall be scheduled as near as possible to the midpoint of the work period. No employee shall be required to work more than three hours without a rest period. (5) Where the nature of the work allows employees to take intermittent rest periods equivalent to ten minutes for each 4 hours worked, scheduled rest periods are not required.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357579510324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:25:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357579610204-76</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' another law that restricts the rights of those who didn't break the law ' .. what restrictions?... and if your not breaking the law then why worry...?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357579610204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:26:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357579899719-77</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Just Plain Stupid?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357418349346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do birds have feathers?</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357579899719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:31:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357580024688-78</Id><Topic><Title>787 fire</Title><Username>aerodog1</Username><Timestamp>1357579362719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:22:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah watching video on cnbc of firefighters putting smoldering fire out....thanks goodness it was on the ground....4th serious incident already with Dreamliner...</Msg><Username>losangdude</Username><Timestamp>1357580024688</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:33:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357580042326-79</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>' going door to door taking away guns ' thats what the paranoid spartacus types want America to think...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357580042326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:34:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357580069191-80</Id><Topic><Title>Union complaint</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357567914724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:11:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All that is true. But in regard to protest, it makes a difference whether it's on company property or not. Go to that page of the book.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357580069191</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:34:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357580412584-81</Id><Title>Boeing is now the second worst performing stock in the Dow -systemic electrical 787 problems ?</Title><Msg>in just 34 days 3 customers have had 4 indidents with the 787. This plane was desined outside of SPEEA and most parts were also made with contractors design. How is that outsourcing working for you now Boeing shareholders and Boeing Chicago executives . To compare the last all Boeing designed plane the 777 came in on time and and budget has just about a perfect flight record. And yet Boeing Chicago is talking tuff to the best workers in the world SPEEA engineers about a very small amount of money. Wow Chicago you have cost the shareholders an extra 30 billion dollars by outsourcing the work away from SPEEA. Your own expert warned you of that you will not listen and your stock price adn the lack of confidence in Boeing by the world now is growing China will not accept the 787 without first certifing it by their own group, they do not trust Boeing or the FAA to get it right and for good reason. BA down over 2% so far today</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357580412584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:40:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357580986711-82</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 delivery delayed to China and stock report</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357565421540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:30:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for the 3 thumbs down Boeing executive enablers, how is that over 2% stock price down today working for you now eh! You coulda should would had LMI or NOK or the etf that follows the NASDAQ all up around 17-18% for a year Boeing is now less than 1% gain for a year , get smart get oout of BA it soes not move tight dead cat bouce range poorly managed no future 787, 747, no effort to make 777X no reson to expect the 737 max will come in on time or on budget jet endinges are out of Boeings control. And the CEO of Boeing was passed over when he ran the GE engine department and was required to step down by his boss so figure it out a loser is running Boeing he also failed at MMM since he left teh company stock price has done much better as long at the current DEO and BOD is in charge of BA the stock price will not move or go down at best</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357580986711</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:49:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357581259422-83</Id><Title>The giant, gaping hole in Sandy Hook reporting</Title><Msg>by David Kupelian But where, I’d like to ask my colleagues in the media, is the reporting about the psychiatric medications the perpetrator – who had been under treatment for mental-health problems – may have been taking? After all, Mark and Louise Tambascio, family friends of the shooter and his mother, were interviewed on CBS’ “60 Minutes,” during which Louise Tambascio told correspondent Scott Pelley: “I know he was on medication and everything, but she homeschooled him at home cause he couldn’t deal with the school classes sometimes, so she just homeschooled Adam at home. And that was her life.” And here, Tambascio tells ABC News, “I knew he was on medication, but that’s all I know.” As I documented in “How Evil Works,” it is simply indisputable that most perpetrators of school shootings and similar mass murders in our modern era were either on – or just recently coming off of – psychiatric medications: •Columbine mass-killer Eric Harris was taking Luvox – like Prozac, Paxil, Zoloft, Effexor and many others, a modern and widely prescribed type of antidepressant drug called selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors, or SSRIs. Harris and fellow student Dylan Klebold went on a hellish school shooting rampage in 1999 during which they killed 12 students and a teacher and wounded 24 others before turning their guns on themselves.Luvox manufacturer Solvay Pharmaceuticals concedes that during short-term controlled clinical trials, 4 percent of children and youth taking Luvox – that’s 1 in 25 – developed mania, a dangerous and violence-prone mental derangement characterized by extreme excitement and delusion. •Patrick Purdy went on a schoolyard shooting rampage in Stockton, Calif., in 1989, which became the catalyst for the original legislative frenzy to ban “semiautomatic assault weapons” in California and the nation. The 25-year-old Purdy, who murdered five children and wounded 30, had been on Amitriptyline, an antidepressant, as well as the antipsychotic drug Thorazine. •Kip Kinkel, 15, murdered his parents in 1998 and the next day went to his school, Thurston High in Springfield, Ore., and opened fire on his classmates, killing two and wounding 22 others. He had been prescribed both Prozac and Ritalin. •In 1988, 31-year-old Laurie Dann went on a shooting rampage in a second-grade classroom in Winnetka, Ill., killing one child and wounding six. She had been taking the antidepressant Anafranil as well as Lithium, long used to treat mania. •In Paducah, Ky., in late 1997, 14-year-old Michael Carneal, son of a prominent attorney, traveled to Heath High School and started shooting students in a prayer meeting taking place in the school’s lobby, killing three and leaving another paralyzed. Carneal reportedly was on Ritalin. •In 2005, 16-year-old Native American Jeff Weise, living on Minnesota’s Red Lake Indian Reservation, shot and killed nine people and wounded five others before killing himself. Weise had been taking Prozac.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357581259422</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:54:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357581419312-84</Id><Topic><Title>The giant, gaping hole in Sandy Hook reporting</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357581259422</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:54:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>•In another famous case, 47-year-old Joseph T. Wesbecker, just a month after he began taking Prozac in 1989, shot 20 workers at Standard Gravure Corp. in Louisville, Ky., killing nine. Prozac-maker Eli Lilly later settled a lawsuit brought by survivors. •Kurt Danysh, 18, shot his own father to death in 1996, a little more than two weeks after starting on Prozac. Danysh’s description of own his mental-emotional state at the time of the murder is chilling: “I didn’t realize I did it until after it was done,” Danysh said. “This might sound weird, but it felt like I had no control of what I was doing, like I was left there just holding a gun.” •John Hinckley, age 25, took four Valium two hours before shooting and almost killing President Ronald Reagan in 1981. In the assassination attempt, Hinckley also wounded press secretary James Brady, Secret Service agent Timothy McCarthy and policeman Thomas Delahanty. •Andrea Yates, in one of the most heartrending crimes in modern history, drowned all five of her children – aged 7 years down to 6 months – in a bathtub. Insisting inner voices commanded her to kill her children, she had become increasingly psychotic over the course of several years. At her 2006 murder re-trial (after a 2002 guilty verdict was overturned on appeal), Yates’ longtime friend Debbie Holmes testified: “She asked me if I thought Satan could read her mind and if I believed in demon possession.” And Dr. George Ringholz, after evaluating Yates for two days, recounted an experience she had after the birth of her first child: “What she described was feeling a presence … Satan … telling her to take a knife and stab her son Noah,” Ringholz said, adding that Yates’ delusion at the time of the bathtub murders was not only that she had to kill her children to save them, but that Satan had entered her and that she had to be executed in order to kill Satan.Yates had been taking the antidepressant Effexor. In November 2005, more than four years after Yates drowned her children, Effexor manufacturer Wyeth Pharmaceuticals quietly added “homicidal ideation” to the drug’s list of “rare adverse events.” The Medical Accountability Network, a private nonprofit focused on medical ethics issues, publicly criticized Wyeth, saying Effexor’s “homicidal ideation” risk wasn’t well-publicized and that Wyeth failed to send letters to doctors or issue warning labels announcing the change.And what exactly does “rare” mean in the phrase “rare adverse events”? The FDA defines it as occurring in less than one in 1,000 people. But since that same year 19.2 million prescriptions for Effexor were filled in the U.S., statistically that means thousands of Americans might experience “homicidal ideation” – murderous thoughts – as a result of taking just this one brand of antidepressant drug.Effexor is Wyeth’s best-selling drug, by the way, which in one recent year brought in over $3 billion in sales, accounting for almost a fifth of the company’s annual revenues. •One more case is instructive, that of 12-year-old Christopher Pittman, who struggled in court to explain why he murdered his grandparents, who had provided the only love and stability he’d ever known in his turbulent life. “When I was lying in my bed that night,” he testified, “I couldn’t sleep because my voice in my head kept echoing through my mind telling me to kill them.” Christopher had been angry with his grandfather, who had disciplined him earlier that day for hurting another student during a fight on the school bus. So later that night, he shot both of his grandparents in the head with a .410 shotgun as they slept and then burned down their South Carolina home, where he had lived with them.”I got up, got the gun, and I went upstairs and I pulled the trigger,” he recalled. “Through the whole thing, it was like watching your favorite TV show. You know what is going to happen, but you can’t do anything to stop it.”Pittman’s lawyers would later argue that the boy had been a victim of “involuntary intoxication,” since his doctors had him taking the antidepressants Paxil and Zoloft just prior to the murders.Paxil’s known “adverse drug reactions” – according to the drug’s FDA-approved label – include “mania,” “insomnia,” “anxiety,” “agitation,” “confusion,” “amnesia,” “depression,” “paranoid reaction,” “psychosis,” “hostility,” “delirium,” “hallucinations,” “abnormal thinking,” “depersonalization” and “lack of emotion,” among others.The preceding examples are only a few of the best-known offenders who had been taking prescribed psychiatric drugs before committing their violent crimes – there are many others. Whether we like to admit it or not, it is undeniable that when certain people living on the edge of sanity take psychiatric medications, those drugs can – and occasionally do – push them over the edge into violent madness. Remember, every single SSRI antidepressant sold in the United States of America today, no matter what brand or manufacturer, bears a “black box” FDA warning label – the government’s most serious drug warning – of “increased risks of suicidal thinking and behavior, known as suicidality, in young adults ages 18 to 24.” Common sense tells us that where there are suicidal thoughts – especially in a very, very angry person – homicidal thoughts may not be far behind. Indeed, the mass shooters we are describing often take their own lives when the police show up, having planned their suicide ahead of time.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357581419312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:56:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357581486490-85</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is now the second worst performing stock in the Dow -systemic electrical 787 problems ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357580412584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:40:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two observations: You obviously trust the chinees certfication board...why? Don't you think they are looking for more technical details to steal? The refusal is based on leverage/tehft, not compliance. Second , 777/7878 is real apples and grapefruit comparison for anyone who knows what they are talking about.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1357581486490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:58:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357581492386-86</Id><Topic><Title>The giant, gaping hole in Sandy Hook reporting</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357581259422</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:54:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, what ‘medication’ was Lanza on? The Sandy Hook school massacre, we are constantly reminded, was the “second-worst school shooting in U.S. history.” Let’s briefly revisit the worst, Virginia Tech, because it provides an important lesson for us. One would think, in light of the stunning correlation between psych meds and mass murders, that it would be considered critical to establish definitively whether the Virginia Tech murderer of 32 people, student Cho Seung-Hui, had been taking psychiatric drugs. Yet, more than five years later, the answer to that question remains a mystery. Even though initially the New York Times reported, “officials said prescription medications related to the treatment of psychological problems had been found among Mr. Cho’s effects,” and the killer’s roommate, Joseph Aust, had told the Richmond Times-Dispatch that Cho’s routine each morning had included taking prescription drugs, the state’s toxicology report released two months later said “no prescription drugs or toxic substances were found in Cho Seung-Hui.” Perhaps so, but one of the most notoriously unstable and unpredictable times for users of SSRI antidepressants is the period shortly after they’ve stopped taking them, during which time the substance may not be detectable in the body. What kind of meds might Cho have been taking – or recently have stopped taking? Curiously, despite an exhaustive investigation by the Commonwealth of Virginia which disclosed that Cho had taken Paxil for a year in 1999, specifics on what meds he was taking prior to the Virginia Tech massacre have remained elusive. The final 20,000-word report manages to omit any conclusive information about the all-important issue of Cho’s medications during the period of the mass shooting. To add to the drama, it wasn’t until two years after the state’s in-depth report was issued that, as disclosed in an Aug. 19, 2009, ABC News report, some of Cho’s long-missing mental health records were located: The records released today were discovered to be missing during a Virginia panel’s August 2007 investigation four-and-a-half months after the massacre. The notes were recovered last month from the home of Dr. Robert Miller, the former director of the counseling center, who says he inadvertently packed Cho’s file into boxes of personal belongings when he left the center in February 2006. Until the July 2009 discovery of the documents, Miller said he had no idea he had the records. Miller has since been let go from the university. Although Cho’s newly discovered mental-health files reportedly revealed nothing further about his medications, the issues raised by the initial accounts – including the “officials” cited by the New York Times and the Richmond paper’s eyewitness account of daily meds-taking – remain unaddressed to this day. Some critics suggest these official omissions are motivated by a desire to protect the drug companies from ruinous product liability claims. Indeed, pharmaceutical manufacturers are nervous about lawsuits over the “rare adverse effects” of their mood-altering medications. To avoid costly settlements and public relations catastrophes – such as when GlaxoSmithKline was ordered to pay $6.4 million to the family of 60-year-old Donald Schnell who murdered his wife, daughter and granddaughter in a fit of rage shortly after starting on Paxil – drug companies’ legal teams have quietly and skillfully settled hundreds of cases out-of-court, shelling out hundreds of millions of dollars to plaintiffs. Pharmaceutical giant Eli Lilly fought scores of legal claims against Prozac in this way, settling for cash before the complaint could go to court while stipulating that the settlement remain secret – and then claiming it had never lost a Prozac lawsuit. All of which is, once again, to respectfully but urgently ask the question: When on earth are we going to find out if the perpetrator of the Sandy Hook school massacre, like so many other mass shooters, had been taking psychiatric drugs? In the end, it may well turn out that knowing what kinds of guns he used isn’t nearly as important as what kind of drugs he used. That is, assuming we ever find out.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357581492386</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:58:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357581668260-87</Id><Title>Sounds like a fleet of AirTrans</Title><Msg>They are going to start dropping like balls of fire.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581668260</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:01:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357581744546-88</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Expanding Rapidly</Title><Username>bearnz1</Username><Timestamp>1357334652937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:24:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good god and now a fire on a 787 on top of the other electrical problems reported. It is about time that the FAA steps in and haults all deliveries of 787's. How long to figure this out?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357581744546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:02:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357581772734-89</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is now the second worst performing stock in the Dow -systemic electrical 787 problems ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357580412584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:40:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne #$%$ is a former fired Boeing employee...what u expect?</Msg><Username>pfemerko</Username><Timestamp>1357581772734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:02:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357581780663-90</Id><Title>Plane fires are over rated</Title><Msg>No big deal.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581780663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:03:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357581967102-91</Id><Title>The Dreamliner will be grounded and then scrapped !</Title><Msg>TOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO many problems.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581967102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:06:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357582139349-92</Id><Topic><Title>The giant, gaping hole in Sandy Hook reporting</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357581259422</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:54:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Janet Hasson should publish a map of where all people on psychiatric medications live so that we know where the real potential mass murderers live.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357582139349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:08:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357582952587-93</Id><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Msg>We know our elected and esteemed elitist central planers know far better than you about what kinds of foods you should be eating. That's why we have the FDA protecting us. However, since more people die from heart disease than any other cause and we know diabetes has become an epidemic that cripples more people than all the American guns put together. Why mess around regulating guns that only do a minute fraction of harm to our citizens than do deadly carbohydrates that cause heart disease, obesity and diabetes . Shouldn't they begin to regulate the amount of carbs you take in. Shouldn't you be required to register your potato chips and your grocery sacks be limited to no more than 2% carbs by weight. And anyone with carb-laden products such as Fruit Loops should protect children by making sure they have no access to these dangerous and deadly products.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357583069701-94</Id><Topic><Title>BA can go high!</Title><Username>adamsjoe593</Username><Timestamp>1357577919221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:58:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>props!</Msg><Username>carmenreed726</Username><Timestamp>1357583069701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:24:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357583089735-95</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner will be grounded and then scrapped !</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581967102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:06:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of amps being generated then re-routed through the central distribution network amid-ship on 787. No way to detect overloads or faults??? Crazy!</Msg><Username>bobncarol1</Username><Timestamp>1357583089735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:24:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357583231500-96</Id><Topic><Title>BA can go high!</Title><Username>adamsjoe593</Username><Timestamp>1357577919221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:58:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good luck with that! Better sell while you are up.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357583231500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:27:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357583569353-97</Id><Topic><Title>Plane fires are over rated</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581780663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:03:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A plane sitting by the gate catches fire and you comment "no big deal"? You are joking, right? Burning plastic is hazzadous to any fire fighter's health even in open spaces. One man was taken to hospital, according the report. Fire fighters may not want to go near a flaming 787 without full protective gear. How about passengers and crew safety? They are trapped in a capsule and will have to breathe fumes as they try to escape.</Msg><Username>bobncarol1</Username><Timestamp>1357583569353</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:32:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357584111772-98</Id><Title>A Well Regulated Militia !</Title><Msg>in the USA, the well regulated militias are called Hells Angels, ms-13, bloods &amp; cribs, neonuts... etc.... no one else (average civilians) comes close to being well regulated and organize...!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584111772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:41:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357584384117-99</Id><Title>Welfare recipients allegedly using money at nudie clubs, liquor stores</Title><Msg>msnNOW: Hey, just because you're a little down and out doesn’t mean you should have to miss amateur night at the Slippery Dolphin, right? Many welfare recipients don't seem to think so, according to a New York Post report that found some beneficiaries using their government assistance to make cash withdrawals at liquor stores, sex shops, hookah parlors and other nonessential locations. The investigation examined 200 million Electronic Benefit Transfer records from 2011 to July 2012, discovering some recipients making dozens of cash withdrawals at saloons, porn stores, bars and strip clubs. The viral report prompted an explosion of outrage on Twitter by folks who say the money should be better monitored. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- It would be nice if the Dems and Repubs could get past their phony compassion to make sure that $$$ meant to feed hungry kids actually gets to the hungry kids rather than ending up in some pole dancer's G string.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357584384117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:46:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357584392151-100</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584392151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:46:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357584411259-101</Id><Topic><Title>Plane fires are over rated</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581780663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:03:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so right. Burning Aluminum is much better than burning plastic. Too bad they didn't make these planes out of scented candle wax. That would really smell good.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357584411259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:46:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357584742293-102</Id><Title>"it is their duty, to throw off such Government"......</Title><Msg>...historically that's that's been almost impossible when 'such government" has been the only ones with weapons. A well armed citizenry is the best guard against tyranny. "When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny."</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357584742293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:52:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357584998537-103</Id><Title>More Neoconservative Paranoia on 'totalitarianism' !!</Title><Msg>Diana West Warns Obama is Fostering 'Totalitarianism' and 'The End of Liberty' Conservative columnist Diana West returned to Frank Gaffney’s show, Secure Freedom Radio, where the two agreed that President Obama is going to gut the Constitution in order to bring about a “dictatorship.” Gaffney pointed to an op-ed by Louis Michael Seidman which criticized the Constitution’s “archaic, idiosyncratic and downright evil provisions,” and then connected Seidman to…Obama. How you might ask? Well, they are both constitutional law professors, Gaffney explains, so they must share the same views on the suitability of the Constitution in today’s society and both support “a kind of post-constitutionalism.” West agreed with Gaffney’s claim that Obama is putting Seidman’s take on the Constitution into practice and went on to argue that he is undermining the rule of law and promoting “totalitarianism.” Gaffney also warned that “freedom of speech” is “very much on the line.”</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584998537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:56:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357585424914-104</Id><Topic><Title>"it is their duty, to throw off such Government"......</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357584742293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think that means even if the tyranny comes from a majority?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1357585424914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:03:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357585703488-105</Id><Topic><Title>"it is their duty, to throw off such Government"......</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357584742293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it means especially if the tyranny is from a majority. That's why we have a Republic.....Democracy is nothing more than mob rule when it abuses the minority. "The majority, oppressing an individual, is guilty of a crime, abuses its strength, and by acting on the law of the strongest breaks up the foundations of society." -- Thomas Jefferson</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357585703488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:08:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357585934041-106</Id><Title>787 had just completed a 12 hour flight.....WHAT IF ????????</Title><Msg>This is getting serious !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! They said battey exploded. Any of you techs know just what type and size of battery the are talking about. I'm just about ready to close the book on this company.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357585934041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:12:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357586129466-107</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He makes a lot more sense than you stickman. You might try addressing issues by some other means than name calling......assuming you're even remotely capable of such a response.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1357586129466</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:15:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357586286892-108</Id><Title>Bursts into flames on Runway....</Title><Msg>Sometimes it's better to be lucky...than competent. Does Boeing have Irish roots? Somebody was looking out for them in BeanTown.</Msg><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1357586286892</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:18:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357586446138-109</Id><Topic><Title>787 had just completed a 12 hour flight.....WHAT IF ????????</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357585934041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:12:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is double A batteries.... hahahaha</Msg><Username>thulucydao</Username><Timestamp>1357586446138</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:20:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357586523433-110</Id><Topic><Title>A Well Regulated Militia !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584111772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's look at the stick.man militias in detail. Hells Angels = Founded in California and proponents of good concert security and decriminalization of drugs like all Progs. ms-13 = Founded in California and representing blue state immigration success at its finest something the open borders Prog crowd wants. bloods and crips = born in California and used as proof by Progs that gun free zones and gun bans prevent shootings. Yep it's nice to see Blue State California militias thriving especially the darker skinned ones as Progs like to see discrimination. But what about Obama's favorite militia the one protected by Eric Holder, the New Black Panthers? Don't be dis'n Obama's homies and not pay'n tribute to them too. Thanks stick.man, for providing such laughter to the board. ROTFLOL</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357586523433</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:22:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357586528509-111</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said rover!</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357586528509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:22:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357586528992-112</Id><Title>latest fire report</Title><Msg>BOSTON (AP) -- An electrical fire filled the cabin of an empty Japan Airlines Boeing 787 with smoke on Monday after it landed in Boston following a non-stop flight from Tokyo. The Massachusetts Port Authority's fire chief, Bob Donahue, said the fire began in an auxiliary battery pack that supplies the plane with power when the engines are shut down. Fire crews using infrared equipment found flames in a small compartment in the plane's belly and quickly brought the fire under control, he said. "Something caused this battery pack to overheat, ignite," Donahue said, adding it's too soon to know the cause. The flight landed normally at about 10:15 a.m. Its 173 passengers and 11 crew members had already gotten off the jet when a mechanic spotted light smoke about 15 minutes later and notified Massport. "When we arrived, it was a heavy smoke, and that was in three minutes, so this was advancing," Donahue said. The mechanic was the only person in the cabin when the fire broke out. One firefighter had skin irritation after contact with the chemical used to douse the fire, Donahue said. The 787 is Boeing's newest plane, and the first one was delivered in late 2011. In November 2010, a test flight had to make an emergency landing after an in-flight electrical fire. The fire delayed flight tests for several weeks while Boeing investigated. Last month, a United Airlines 787 flying from Houston to Newark, N.J., diverted to New Orleans because of a mechanical issue. No one was injured. Ed Freni, Massport's aviation director, said JAL officials reported that the plane that caught fire was delivered to the airline in late December. Eric Weiss, a spokesman for the National Transportation Safety Board, said the agency is sending several investigators to Boston on Monday to look at the airplane. The Federal Aviation Administration also said it was investigating. Boeing Co. spokeswoman Lori Gunter said the company was aware of the fire and was working with JAL. She said she couldn't immediately answer other questions because Boeing's technical team was focused on the investigation.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357586528992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:22:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357587073340-113</Id><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Msg>Since the Boeing top executives and Boeing BOD came not from the successful Boeing Company . They have prooved their worth , nothing. . . The problem with a background in MD is it a failed and bankrupt aerospace company. MD went out of business due to the failed business plan called outsourcing. . So easy to understand why Boeing is the second worst stock of the Dow Jones, Boeing executives made the rookie mistake of going with a failed MD business model for the 787. . The result is this terrible 787, not designed or built by Boeing. . SPEEA offered to build the 787 on time and at 5 billion dollars. SPEEA tried to tell Boeing Executives that the technology was not ready , instead Boeing management would not listen the result is BA stock price for a year is now less than other aerospace companies BA for a year is up about 1% , while NOC Northrop is up over 18%, Lockheed is up over 19% for a year (LMI), NASDAQ average is up over 17%, Dow average is up over 8%, and another Dow stock Bank of America(BAC) is up about 90% If you want to make money on your stock market investment then Boeing is not a company to hold stock in. The 787 will not break even until 2021 and cost shareholder 116K for each late delivery a SPEEA strike will cost shareholders 250K per day This 30 billion dollar mistake is all on Chicago management and they need to be replaced the 30 billion dollar excessive cost on the 787 is a slap in the face of every past, present and future Boeing employee. and Shareholder</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357587554944-114</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is calling on banning guns? I have heard some would like more gun control and a way to keep dangerous weapons out of bad peoples hands but I have not heard much about a total gun ban. once again you folks like to exaggerate facts to the point that it`s now a lie.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1357587554944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:39:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357587568281-115</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"250K per day" I think it would be a lot more than that. What's your source for such a low amount?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357587568281</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:39:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357587676804-116</Id><Topic><Title>Plane fires are over rated</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581780663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:03:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last I checked aluminum doesn't burn.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1357587676804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:41:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357587978396-117</Id><Topic><Title>latest fire report</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357586528992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:22:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing has opened up a floodgate of failed 787's. Result stock price for one year is now at 1% gain. Customers and shareholders are angry with Boeing for failure to make a working plane 34 days and 4 incidents on a FAA-Boeing certified plane. A new plane should not be breaking down on delivery or with the frequency of thsi plane. Boeing reputation under the MD managment is damaged .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587978396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:46:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357588079704-118</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>750 milion shares out - estimated 400 million $/day cost-deferral = about 50 cents/day/share " loss" 16000 strikers averaging 90k/2080 hours about 350/day times approx $ 5.5 million day savings in payroll check YOUR math</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357588079704</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:47:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357588108834-119</Id><Topic><Title>Plane fires are over rated</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581780663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:03:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's much better when the plane catches fire on the ground.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1357588108834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:48:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357588742433-120</Id><Topic><Title>A Well Regulated Militia !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584111772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one Hells Angel is worth a thousand teabaggers...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357588742433</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:59:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357588890683-121</Id><Topic><Title>latest fire report</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357586528992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:22:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because there has been a lot of innovation in batteries and the last 8 years or so, we've had a lot of bugs to work out of everything from computers to electric cars to planes. In the Chevy Volt? it was learned that after any collision from the side, an automatic change out of the batteries would be required, not cancellation of the Volt.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357588890683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:01:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357588900339-122</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of the proposals, I've heard from the left are going to "keep dangerous weapons out of bad peoples hands." It might work if you're talking about putting AG Holder and the big wigs in ATF in jail for putting guns in the hand s of bad guys.......naw, it's the common citizens you need to control, right?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357588900339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:01:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357589008807-123</Id><Topic><Title>A Well Regulated Militia !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584111772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, that's some well-aimed irony!</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1357589008807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:03:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357589197130-124</Id><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Msg>Why don't we put Holder and the ATF in Jail for putting guns in the hands of drug dealers who actually used them to kill people. It's the government we should be afraid of.....not law abiding citizens. It's the government that needs to be controlled, not gun owners who haven't committed any crimes.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357589466802-125</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... when Repubs grow up, plus get their heads out of their butts... then we can discuss a more mature response that your capable of understanding..</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357589466802</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:11:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357589611912-126</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A walkout by the union could stop production and could cost the company about $400 million a day at current production rates and prices." http://www.reuters.com/article/2012/12/01/us-boeing-strike-idUSBRE8B00F120121201</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357589611912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:13:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357589619751-127</Id><Title>How is this not down 30%? The product is on fire?</Title><Msg>This is unreal!</Msg><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1357589619751</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:13:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357589932374-128</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is correct, shuper. At this point, a lot of the engineering is done for the time being. A strike would be payroll savings.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357589932374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:18:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357589947164-129</Id><Title>Japan Airlines 787</Title><Msg>An electrical fire filled the cabin of an empty Japan Airlines Boeing 787 with smoke on Monday after it landed in Boston following a non-stop flight from Tokyo.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357589947164</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:19:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357589948592-130</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you running for the BA Board Sissy with all your pussified posts? If so, you will win in a landslide.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357589948592</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:19:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357589952791-131</Id><Topic><Title>A Well Regulated Militia !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584111772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha - its the truth !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357589952791</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:19:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357590058512-132</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No d... the honor is all yours !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357590058512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:20:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357590060769-133</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so how about we work together to find a common solution to the problem instead of pointing fingers at each other.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1357590060769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:21:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357590105273-134</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"116K for each late delivery" I believe each 787 will cost shareholders many tens of $millions per plane, not $116,000.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357590105273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:21:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357590180711-135</Id><Topic><Title>A Well Regulated Militia !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584111772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't that Obama's plan..to provide a free college education for people, and then have them obligated to join his civilian militia fro so many years to pay it off. Some type of communist program of Obma's.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357590180711</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:23:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357590438913-136</Id><Title>Delivery of Boeing Dreamliners to China held up</Title><Msg>China said it has yet to approve U.S. planemaker Boeing's 787 Dreamliner, which has put on hold the delivery of the jet to the world's fastest growing aviation market. China Southern Airlines Co Ltd , which has outstanding orders for 10 Dreamliner B787s, had expected to receive its first plane in 2012, but that has been delayed as the U.S. company has yet to receive certification from Chinese authorities.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357590438913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:27:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357590787359-137</Id><Topic><Title>Plane fires are over rated</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581780663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:03:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flames about two feet (0.6 meter) high shot out of an avionics compartment in the jet’s belly, and there was a small explosion afterward, Massachusetts Port Authority Fire Chief Robert Donahue said today in an interview.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357590787359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:33:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357590973706-138</Id><Topic><Title>MORE EVIDENCE "DEREGULATION" DOESN"T WORK</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357570005053</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 09:46:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since he was not only drunk but "disorderly" and bragged about being the son of a senator as well, maybe all he needs is a stint in the military to learn something about self discipline.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357590973706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:36:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357591008771-139</Id><Topic><Title>Plane fires are over rated</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357581780663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:03:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe your sarcasm meter was turned off?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357591008771</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:36:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357591066618-140</Id><Topic><Title>How is this not down 30%? The product is on fire?</Title><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1357589619751</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:13:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dreamliner has suffered a string of mishaps with electrical systems in recent weeks. On Dec. 4, a United Airlines flight from Houston to Newark, New Jersey, made an emergency landing after it appeared that one of its power generators failed. On Dec. 13, Qatar Airways said it had grounded one of its three 787 jets because of the same problem United had experienced. On Dec. 17, United said that a second 787 in its fleet had developed electrical issues.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357591066618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:37:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357591116629-141</Id><Title>Question for the board</Title><Msg>If the over all market turns south on us or the uncertainties of the looming debt ceiling cause the market to roll over ... can someone suggest a stock that would be a good short candidate,thanks in advance..OIL!</Msg><Username>oil042004</Username><Timestamp>1357591116629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:38:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357591142763-142</Id><Topic><Title>The rich should pay more not only because</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357338492668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 17:28:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bulky bob/bin spouting the old pious boloney again.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1357591142763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:39:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357591225712-143</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$250,000 per day is "roundoff error" for Boeing.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357591225712</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:40:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357591488349-144</Id><Topic><Title>Question for the board</Title><Username>oil042004</Username><Timestamp>1357591116629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:38:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357591488349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357591823660-145</Id><Title>This Once Proud American Company is Now An International Joke</Title><Msg>This 787 program is a real fiasco, the likes of which I've never seen. I would not fly on one of these crates. I would guess right about now the Boeing board wishes it never head the word " Outsourcing" Boeing should never have given contracts for high tech aerospace systems that have to operate at 30000 ft, 500mph, and for hours on end to third world countries 15 years out of the stone-age. The only reason this company survives is that its one and only competitor is a european government-subsidized jobs program. The only reason jim McNerney still has a job is....well....I can't think of any. The 787 is his baby. He was a director, ceo, board chairman, or all of the above during the entire 787 episode, from inception to first deliveries. As a matter of fact , Boeing has done nothing right since he arrived. Think about it: this 787 meltdown, the 747-8 failure, the hideously handled AF Tanker bungling, McNerney claiming airlines will wait for his decision on 737 redesign, and then watch airbutt take the lead with its neo option and now this dimwit says airlines will wait on his 777x decision. And all the while, this pig has greased his pockets with record compensation. Worst of all, this jack #$%$ is the chairman of the board. Who's gonna fire him ???? I think it is time to exit this investment before this dreamliner financial fiasco into a truly horrific nightmare.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357591823660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:50:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357591905101-146</Id><Topic><Title>787 fire</Title><Username>aerodog1</Username><Timestamp>1357579362719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:22:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Firefighters used infrared equipment to determine the source of the smoke and found a strong heat signature in the underbelly of the aircraft, Walsh said. “It was in the area where the auxiliary power unit is located,” he said. A second fire erupted after a battery exploded, Walsh said. The fires were fought for 30 to 40 minutes by about 40 personnel belonging to the Massport Fire Rescue Department and Boston Fire Department. The job involved 15 vehicles. In December, the Federal Aviation Administration ordered inspections of fuel line connectors on Dreamliners because of risks of leaks and possible fires.</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357591905101</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:51:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357591945458-147</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The payroll saving you mention will be more than offset if the fleet gets grounded without any engineers to look into the fire today</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357591945458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:52:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357592151365-148</Id><Title>Teething problem</Title><Msg>“Anything that involves a fire does not get the luxury of being called a teething problem,” Carter Leake, an analyst at BB&amp;T Capital Markets in Richmond, Virginia, said by telephone. “Boeing needs to get ahead of this quickly, because now you run the risk of getting into a passenger aversion issue.”</Msg><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357592151365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:55:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357592200879-149</Id><Topic><Title>This Once Proud American Company is Now An International Joke</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357591823660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:50:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So sell it.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357592200879</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:56:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357592871455-150</Id><Topic><Title>Question for the board</Title><Username>oil042004</Username><Timestamp>1357591116629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:38:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks ,but I'm holding puts on Boeing...but wow they sure don't move a lot...I've seen stocks tank after some analyst downgraded a stock...let alone their product burning up in smoke</Msg><Username>oil042004</Username><Timestamp>1357592871455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:07:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357593522194-151</Id><Topic><Title>This Once Proud American Company is Now An International Joke</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357591823660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:50:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear ya bro'! This composite tube with wings is a disaster just WAITING TO HAPPEN. Can anyone here say they're not scared as 'ell to take a ride in this thing? I'll fly it when I want to meet my maker and not a minute sooner!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1357593522194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:18:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357593583702-152</Id><Topic><Title>787 fire</Title><Username>aerodog1</Username><Timestamp>1357579362719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:22:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, fire at 35,000 feet. That must be quite titillating to say the least!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1357593583702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:19:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357593610472-153</Id><Topic><Title>A Well Regulated Militia !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584111772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you tested this belief or is this born out of some teabagging fantasy of yours involving a Hells Angel and one thousand teabaggers?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357593610472</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:20:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357593785000-154</Id><Title>Huge order by HA .... LOL see you over $78 by Friday!!!!!!! The fire was a great opp to get in</Title><Msg>Cheap.</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357593785000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:23:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357593817810-155</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good god, but that's a stupid post. Too stupid to even contemplate a reply.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1357593817810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:23:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357593885508-156</Id><Title>January deliveries (or lack of them)</Title><Msg>With Boeing cranking out more than one 737 a day, you could expect that there would have been a number of deliveries in teh first 6 days. But there have been none. They must be parking them somewhere. Granted that the weather has been lousy and the ceilings low and there are restrictions on first flights under those conditions, but there were soem 737's flying today. Hopefully we see some deliveries tomorrow.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357593885508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357594205140-157</Id><Topic><Title>This Once Proud American Company is Now An International Joke</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357591823660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:50:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now there is trading your opinion, and not looking at the chart , your a strong buy, for a year now, BA has lagged most of the Dow stocks the nasdaq , the S and P average, and other aerospace companies like LMI and NOK, you deserve all you lag by trading your opinion instead of looking at the stock chart</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357594205140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:30:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357594357020-158</Id><Topic><Title>"it is their duty, to throw off such Government"......</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357584742293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are "the People"? If Spartakook, is one of "The People", I think I'd take up arms with the goverment, against Spartakook and his army of deluded McVeigh wanna-bes!</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357594357020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:32:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357594419687-159</Id><Topic><Title>This Once Proud American Company is Now An International Joke</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357591823660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:50:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the reason the CEO so far has not been replaced is he is both the CEO and BOD chairman, so he can control the termination deal, hard to fire the CEO-Charman of the board. The stockholders can make some motions to change the way a director gets to keep his job but not likely to pass. So you need to buy other stocks until the BOD and the CEO are gone. LMI NOK or the averages of the NASDAQ and sand P are far better for the last full year than Boeing.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357594419687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:33:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357594670872-160</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ron since you are going on your belief ,no help for you, google it, the cost is clearly stated by aerospace analysts Ron cant you do anything for yourself , guessing does not count, stop believeing in yourself and research it</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357594670872</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:37:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357594778104-161</Id><Title>Lithium Batteries, I thought they were banned in the cargo area of airplanes</Title><Msg>Amazing they can ban small lithium shippments on planes but they use them for auxiliary power on the 787 The 787 uses two lithium ion batteries — including one for the auxiliary power unit, according to a Boeing guide for firefighters dealing with the 787. The rechargeable batteries, widely used in consumer devices, have some pilots worried because batteries being shipped as cargo are suspected to have caused or contributed to the severity of fires in cargo planes. When Boeing proposed using the batteries in the 787, the Federal Aviation Administration issued special rules, including a requirement that they be designed to prevent overheating. The FAA noted in its 2007 rule that, "In general, lithium ion batteries are significantly more susceptible to internal failures that can result in self-sustaining increases in temperature and pressure. ... The metallic lithium can ignite, resulting in a self-sustaining fire or explosion." The severity of overheating is higher in larger batteries, the FAA said in the rule.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357594778104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:39:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357594986561-162</Id><Topic><Title>More Neoconservative Paranoia on 'totalitarianism' !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584998537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:56:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FREAKS is all I can say...Bachmannoid freaks.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357594986561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:43:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357595050987-163</Id><Topic><Title>This Once Proud American Company is Now An International Joke</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357591823660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:50:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I trade BA alot.I buy it when its oversold like today I bought short term at 75.50.Anybody want to bet me that BA don't go up tomorrow?</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357595050987</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:44:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357595422815-164</Id><Topic><Title>More Neoconservative Paranoia on 'totalitarianism' !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584998537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:56:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do gay guys keep wanting to clutters up this board with left-wing #$%$ caca and brainless posts?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357595422815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:50:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357595664662-165</Id><Title>President Obama's Pledge Never to Raise Taxes on Anyone Making Less Than $250,000</Title><Msg>Turned out to be just another one of his many BS lies that lefties swallowed.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357595664662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:54:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357595962072-166</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ron , the figures chage as time goes forward so since you want higher numbers I found the maximum for both for you but I hope you will do this for yourself . here you go, "Including advance payments to suppliers and some tooling costs, the average direct cash cost to Boeing of manufacturing the airplanes built so far — excluding those first three off the line — is $400 million each. Consulting firm Avitas estimates those planes sold for about $100 million or less so giving Boeing the best possible gain, since Boeing web page says the list price on the 787 is 206 million, the cost to build it 400 million , the list price is 206 million the discount , 100 million less , 106 million loss per plane so the maximum loss per plane is rounded at 300 million. , Cost of a SPEEA strike maximum “SPEEA v Boeing: The Seattle Times reported that there is a very high chance of a strike by SPEEA against Boeing come February. This is, of course, bad news for all concerned. SPEEA is already talking about a 60 day strike and says this would cost Boeing $400m per day</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357595962072</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:59:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357596126410-167</Id><Topic><Title>Will Liberals want to out law Carbohydrates?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357582952587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:22:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talkin about sisies; Anal, I recognize your über-sissified style anywhere. So why did you chamge your momiker?</Msg><Username>i_dream_of_edema</Username><Timestamp>1357596126410</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:02:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357596396788-168</Id><Title>To a frighten Republican - Gun Control means</Title><Msg>'take away gun' - 'no more gun' - 'no penile enhance' even tho America has no such intention of taking something so small away from their hands... heh heh heh !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357596396788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:06:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357596564337-169</Id><Topic><Title>The rich should pay more not only because</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357338492668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 17:28:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why is it greed for one to want to keep their own, hard earned money, and somehow not greed when you leftists want to take other folks' hard earned money?" Because in most cases of the very rich it isn't "their own, hard earned money", it's the result of grand theft.</Msg><Username>r_all_christians_morons</Username><Timestamp>1357596564337</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:09:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357596708986-170</Id><Topic><Title>More Neoconservative Paranoia on 'totalitarianism' !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357584998537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:56:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>toad ... why do you hate freedom</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357596708986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:11:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357596742054-171</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and cost shareholder 116K for each late delivery a SPEEA strike will cost shareholders 250K per day" Wayne, all I was doing was questioning your posted figures of $116,000 for each 787 and $250,000 per day for a SPEEA strike. Seems like you have been using the symbol "K" for a "million" when most people use it for "thousand". Try to spell it out it you are confused on using shorthand notation.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357596742054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:12:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357596767448-172</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The odd part is that Shuper is a retired engineer who stabs in the back the union that gave him the wages that allows him to live the good life. Pathetic.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1357596767448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:12:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357596876645-173</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doke would argue... even if a liberal peed on him to save his life !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357596876645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:14:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357597127266-174</Id><Topic><Title>Welfare recipients allegedly using money at nudie clubs, liquor stores</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357584384117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:46:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is always some who abuse the system and give a black eye to those who are worthy recipients of government help.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357597127266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:18:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357598835383-175</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants gun control !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357419455638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 15:57:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing managers have machine guns. The grunts carry knives.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357598835383</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:47:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357599327944-176</Id><Title>Boeing Still having Problems with the "DREAMliner"!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>FIRE on the Ground in Boston READ All About IT and SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO Much MORE Where "The REAL News Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1357599327944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:55:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357600099243-177</Id><Topic><Title>Welfare recipients allegedly using money at nudie clubs, liquor stores</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357584384117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:46:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget buying iPads at walmarts as an OK use of EBT cards. There needs to be a lifetime limit on how much you can be a drain on society and then you are expelled from that society for life.</Msg><Username>goofahead</Username><Timestamp>1357600099243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:08:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357600270313-178</Id><Topic><Title>Welfare recipients allegedly using money at nudie clubs, liquor stores</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357584384117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:46:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is that it is probably a 5 to 1 margin in fvor of the abusers rather than the worthy.</Msg><Username>goofahead</Username><Timestamp>1357600270313</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:11:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357600632356-179</Id><Title>About that 787 fire</Title><Msg>It was two fires. First in an electric equipment area associated with the APU. Second when a battery exploded. Reports refer to the problem plagued AP. McNerney will say normal for a new airplane.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357600632356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:17:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357600864393-180</Id><Topic><Title>About that 787 fire</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357600632356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:17:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Anything that involves a fire does not get the luxury of being called a teething problem," Carter Leake, an analyst at BB&amp;T Capital Markets in Richmond, Va., said by telephone. "Boeing needs to get ahead of this quickly, because now you run the risk of getting into a passenger aversion issue."</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357600864393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:21:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357601025817-181</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Still having Problems with the "DREAMliner"!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1357599327944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:55:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA exuctives will have it burried.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1357601025817</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:23:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357601168652-182</Id><Topic><Title>This Once Proud American Company is Now An International Joke</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357591823660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:50:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES I will take that bet, whats your wager and how do you plan on paying? I will meet you at any Seattle area establishment and buy you a beer to cry in. Put your money wear your mouth is.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357601168652</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:26:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357601434124-183</Id><Topic><Title>This Once Proud American Company is Now An International Joke</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1357591823660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:50:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry, should be put your money where your mouth is. Well you backing out?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357601434124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:30:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357601665147-184</Id><Topic><Title>787 fire</Title><Username>aerodog1</Username><Timestamp>1357579362719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 12:22:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, the battery exploding was a result of the fire.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357601665147</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:34:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357601767506-185</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Still having Problems with the "DREAMliner"!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1357599327944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:55:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How Many More Problems Before the Boeing 787 Dreamliner Is Grounded? Just ADDED about a Half Dozen POSTS on the Dreamliner!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1357601767506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:36:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357601817769-186</Id><Title>It was a battery fire..... the Dream liner is fine and HA ordered 18 more</Title><Msg>$78 by Friday</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357601817769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:36:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357601882664-187</Id><Topic><Title>It was a battery fire..... the Dream liner is fine and HA ordered 18 more</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357601817769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:36:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>read the new again. There was fire then the battery exploded as a result of that fire.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357601882664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:38:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357602120484-188</Id><Topic><Title>"it is their duty, to throw off such Government"......</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1357584742293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 13:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whats your version of "the people" Chairman Maos "Peoples Army" ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357602120484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:42:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357602469653-189</Id><Topic><Title>It was a battery fire..... the Dream liner is fine and HA ordered 18 more</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357601817769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:36:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOSTON -- Officials are investigating a fire Monday aboard a Boeing Co. 787 Dreamliner in Boston after a Japan Airlines Co. flight from Tokyo, the latest setback for the jet following electrical faults on other planes last month. Flames about two feet high shot out of an avionics compartment in the jet's belly, and there was a small explosion afterward, Massachusetts Port Authority Fire Chief Robert Donahue said Monday. No passengers were aboard as the plane sat at a Logan International Airport gate. Bloomberg News</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357602469653</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:47:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357602529146-190</Id><Topic><Title>Obama-Backed Syrian Rebels Praise Bin Laden, Celebrate 9/11 Attacks</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357398835787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 10:13:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dont know if Obama is the Anti Christ as you suggest ? Im not an End Times biblical scholar...although I DO believe we ARE on the precipice of a catyclysimc apolaclytic event we will witness in our lifetime if not within the next 10 years....HOWEVER...I view most of this from a secular perspective. In otehr words, as an American I do not see I-srael as requiring any special favoritism over any other country...and especially since I-srael already had way to much ..and I do mean WAY TOO MUCH influence over American politics via APAC etc.....If we were unbiased we would recognise that we have done a lot of I sraels dirty work in the region....and judging by the number of UN human rights violations, they are not on my number one list of "God's chosen People"</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357602529146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:48:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357603125321-191</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you are ? the critic then ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357603125321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:58:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357603587450-192</Id><Topic><Title>About that 787 fire</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357600632356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:17:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>considering the fire broke out shortly after the passenger deplaned , if that is accurate, then this plane could have possibly crashed if on a longer flight. I would never go on a outsourced 787 it only has the Boeing decal on the front but the plane is not engineered or built by Boeing 34 days 4 major incidents by 3 carriers this plane was certified by the Boeing Company and the FAA. The FAA and Boeing need to ground it now, before one crashes , this is the Boeing comet BOAC same deal brought to market without proper testing and engineering for a dangerous build. SPEEA pointed out that the testing was relaxed by Boeing and FAA , being in support of air industry signed off on the weak testing.. Sell Boeing stock and stay away until the BOD and CEO are replaced .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357603587450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:06:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357603680228-193</Id><Topic><Title>It was a battery fire..... the Dream liner is fine and HA ordered 18 more</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357601817769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:36:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think HA probably ordered those before today's news. That was then, this is now.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357603680228</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:08:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357603710841-194</Id><Topic><Title>January deliveries (or lack of them)</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357593885508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:24:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets hope its not a 787 or 747 they lose money for the shareholders on delivery.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357603710841</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:08:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357603854327-195</Id><Topic><Title>How is this not down 30%? The product is on fire?</Title><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1357589619751</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:13:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>abd the Chinese refuse to accept the 787 without first having theri own version of the FAA certify the 787, because like the rest of the world no one trusts Boeing Executives, this plane has destroyed Boeing credibility</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357603854327</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:10:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357603957714-196</Id><Topic><Title>United flying 787, so are fuel efficiencies really working?</Title><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1357573864160</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:51:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a better question will the 787crash going to any destination</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357603957714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:12:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357604167841-197</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UHHH OLDBUCK ?? - If you believe my FACTS about some of the corrupt STAFF and apathetic Officers are against the union- please spell them out ! Or do you believe that 10 percent/year average base raise for the curent exec director is in the best interest o/f the members. Or that he shoots off his mouth claiming to be a leader- he has ZIP NADA authority to speak for the union. AS did the previous Ex Director play the crony game by ripping off the union by allowing FOB staff to provide janitor service at 5 times the going rate- and signing up himself for teamsters benefits ( paid by SPEEA ) without the knowledge of the Board who didn't have enough members willing to fire him when they found out. Or the 80's exec dir playing footsie with BA via a seperate room during negotiations etc Or the FACT that the current majority of members who are nearing retirement have been hosed re the pension plan formula for decades . I support the members- but not the corrupt staff. Do a google search on Q4SPEEA for some of the documents that back up most of the above. When you find an material error, let me know !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357604167841</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:16:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357604319965-198</Id><Topic><Title>A350 XWB going to cause the 777 headaches</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357079909525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-01 17:38:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is another CEO the customer will wait by James McNerney, last timeon the 737, Airbus got 1500 orders and Boeing lost 3 all Boeing customer on that decision so more of the same , you wat too long your behind the ball. Boeing CEO been there done that and still can't learn from his prior mistake he has verified what Jack Welch thought of him McNerney had to leave GE when he was not picked for the top job and Lewis Platt had no experience with aircrat so he went with a guy and did not know better McNerney has been a window dressing Bush roomate and like Bill Gates college roomate just as incompetent</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357604319965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:18:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357604850226-199</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Face it the feds are afraid of a armed citizenry,don,t forget the cruel and oppresive government part of the 2nd ammendment......ks</Msg><Username>kingslmon6</Username><Timestamp>1357604850226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:27:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357605562213-200</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Operation Fast and Furious was a False Flag event ...to steal our liberties (in this case giving guns to Mexican Drug Lords as a Pretext for deomonization of the second amendment)...just like 9-11 was a False Flag...just like Operation Northwoods was a False Flag...Just like the Gulf of Tonkin...Just like the Underwear bomber or the batman shooter.....get it straight....we have criminals in very small parts of the Government and the rest are compartmentalized.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357605562213</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:39:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357605634584-201</Id><Topic><Title>January deliveries (or lack of them)</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357593885508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:24:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone recently posted that Boeing loses $116,000 per 787 delivered.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357605634584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:40:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357605822190-202</Id><Topic><Title>About that 787 fire</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357600632356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:17:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The APU that caught fire is one that is turned on after the plane is shut down at the gate.</Msg><Username>eggs_acklee</Username><Timestamp>1357605822190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:43:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357605876335-203</Id><Topic><Title>Delivery of Boeing Dreamliners to China held up</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357590438913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:27:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>China will not accept Boeing 787 deliveries as they rightly don't trust Boeing and the FAA 4 incidents in 34 days this outsoourced 787 is a plane that Boeing and the FAA allowed to fly without proper testing and with a weakoned standard SPEEA engineers pointed this out to Boeing Chicago.Now Boeing good name is gone , counties that still have to produce a large Airplane like China refuse to accept Boeing or the FAA certification process they don't want their people to die in one of these firemakers</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357605876335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 19:44:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357607320374-204</Id><Topic><Title>About that 787 fire</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357600632356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:17:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it is also used as a backup power source for in-flight problems just like other planes</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357607320374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 20:08:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357607896947-205</Id><Topic><Title>Delivery of Boeing Dreamliners to China held up</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357590438913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:27:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and this was before the news about todays fire, good luck delivering those planes.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357607896947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 20:18:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357608528490-206</Id><Topic><Title>Delivery of Boeing Dreamliners to China held up</Title><Username>fortuneking1</Username><Timestamp>1357590438913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:27:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More than likely, the Chinese are holding delivery of the aircraft hostage to technology transfer inquiries. "We will gladly accept the aircraft as long as you tell us how you made it."</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1357608528490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 20:28:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357609761665-207</Id><Topic><Title>About that 787 fire</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357600632356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:17:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hang on, the next one probably will.</Msg><Username>dukdre23</Username><Timestamp>1357609761665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 20:49:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357609970594-208</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quem deus vult perdere, dementat prius Whom the gods would destroy, they first make mad</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357609970594</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 20:52:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357609989491-209</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!! losers!</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1357609989491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 20:53:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357612315094-210</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We didn't start the fire. It was always burning since the world was turning....,</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357612315094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:31:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357612827345-211</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well fighting mad we likely will have to take away your guns as screwy as you are. When we get things like background checks in place for every kind of gun sales outlet and for gun owners you will be blocked from owning a gun due to your mental instability and we will take your guns away- from your cold dead hand if necessary</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1357612827345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:40:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357612922239-212</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not only the feds but the entire citizenry- especially the fruitcakes who think more guns means more security</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1357612922239</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:42:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357613118070-213</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Prius over your W_O_N's Volt CG? You're not mad that you threw your gun down into the crotch of Charlie now are you Ghost Rider? Puzzy...</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1357613118070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:45:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357613289199-214</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaeces just because you can no longer get welfare doesn't mean its a bad thing- all the poor people supposedly spending their welfare money on booze and broads is bool sh.t and you know it. Some welfare assistance does get wasted but there is no way to prevent it- the majority of the money is for survival. I would think that even tho you are no longer eligible for welfare you make you go out and find a job yourself instead of wasting your life in that tin shack down in the swamps</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1357613289199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:48:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357613336861-215</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you inbred toothless hicks from the welfare states take the political BS somewhere else ---some of us are trying to make a buck on this stock</Msg><Username>auntie_theresa</Username><Timestamp>1357613336861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:48:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357613342193-216</Id><Topic><Title>Your Money at Work: Welfare Cash Spent on Strippers, Booze and Porn Shops</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357566244083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 08:44:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You flunk in your pretend hippism MBField! ONCE AGAIN, YOU REMAIN A FOOL!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1357613342193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:49:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357613441077-217</Id><Topic><Title>Obama-Backed Syrian Rebels Praise Bin Laden, Celebrate 9/11 Attacks</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357398835787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 10:13:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhh...CgGs type for realzzzz!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1357613441077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:50:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357613466795-218</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Damn...that had to leave a welt</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357613466795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:51:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357613507838-219</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Statistics prove it beyond a shadow of a doubt</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357613507838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:51:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357613783828-220</Id><Topic><Title>United flying 787, so are fuel efficiencies really working?</Title><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1357573864160</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:51:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First and foremost route for UAL's first 787's was direct from IAH to AKL! Why hasn't that happened yet?</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1357613783828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 21:56:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357614112960-221</Id><Topic><Title>About that 787 fire</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1357600632356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:17:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gamblin09, your right, China has refused their 787 until their own versio of the FAA decides is the Boeing 787 is airworthy, as you probably know customers are anry with Chicago Management for the indidants, delays and are very unhappy. This plane is a if its a coutsources 787 I am not going now . Systemic electrical problems 4 incidents in 34 days with 3 carriers on a FAA-Boeing new certified plane is not normal it is a disaster</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357614112960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:01:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357614318662-222</Id><Title>Alex Jones just Humilated Piers Morgan on Gun Control....CNN goes into revisionist mode</Title><Msg>Using cheap ploys Piers Morgan tried to trap Alex Jones in an entertaining debate on CNN tonite. Counter-attacking aggressively, AJ reminded everyone watching that Freedom is at stake.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357614318662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:05:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357614497329-223</Id><Topic><Title>January deliveries (or lack of them)</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357593885508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:24:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ron, , if I told you once I told you twice it is 300 million out of the shareholder pocket for each deliverd 787 and the SPEEA strike will cost the shareholders of Boeing 400 million per day how many times do I have to korrect u HA I dont believe it is 116k . Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357614497329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:08:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357615184982-224</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones just Humilated Piers Morgan on Gun Control....CNN goes into revisionist mode</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357614318662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:05:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another one of your paranoid rewrites of reality? Remember, you are the whackjob of who used to claim Orly Taitz was rational and won arguments on TV and in court. That also never happened.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1357615184982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:19:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357615390321-225</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones just Humilated Piers Morgan on Gun Control....CNN goes into revisionist mode</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357614318662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:05:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Put the crack pipe down and slowly back away from the Keyboard.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357615390321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:23:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357615574887-226</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones just Humilated Piers Morgan on Gun Control....CNN goes into revisionist mode</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357614318662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:05:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just watched it...AJ tore Piers a new #$%$.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357615574887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:26:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357615698281-227</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones just Humilated Piers Morgan on Gun Control....CNN goes into revisionist mode</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357614318662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:05:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try psycho, you are the whackjob, as proven by your (mental) medical ejection from the Air Force. You would not know reality if it bit you in the butt.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1357615698281</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:28:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357616353905-228</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones just Humilated Piers Morgan on Gun Control....CNN goes into revisionist mode</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357614318662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:05:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL...are you paid more then minimum wage to write this nonsense troll ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357616353905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:39:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357616650463-229</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones just Humilated Piers Morgan on Gun Control....CNN goes into revisionist mode</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357614318662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:05:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I knew he would from the outset....They even had to bring Alan Derschowitz and claim...lamely as usual...that Alex Jones was a wackjob...repeated over and over, as if repeating it made it real....the usual Gaslighting Cointelpro psyop tactics when CNN hosts are getting their clocks cleaned...AJ didnt back down and showed over and over that countries like heavily armed countries Switzerland had the lowest crime rates , and countries with massive gun control, like MEXICO had the highest...he even brought up Fast and Furious ...which made Morgan turn Red...Awesome job by Alex</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357616650463</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:44:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357617935129-230</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot fluoride in the water and the faked moon landing. Sparty--we expect better from you.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1357617935129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:05:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357618805604-231</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones just Humilated Piers Morgan on Gun Control....CNN goes into revisionist mode</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357614318662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 22:05:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I knew he would ... They even had to bring in Alan Derschowitz and they repeated over and over how Alex was a "wackjob"...as if repeating it relentlessly made it true. Lame Cointelpro Gaslighting Psyop techniqes by CNN and typical tactics when their hosts get their clocks cleaned. Alex made great use of statistics like Switzerland having one of the lowest murder rates in the world despite per capita populace being heavily armed...Mexico having one of the highest murder rates despite draconian gun laws....IE: Only the Drug Lords and criminals have the guns in Mexico.....Speaking of False Flag events and Mexico...Piers Morgan went Red in the face when Alex brought up False Flag Fast and Furious as the Government tried to demonize the second amendment. Awesome job by Alex Jones.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357618805604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:20:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357619193488-232</Id><Topic><Title>January deliveries (or lack of them)</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357593885508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:24:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and cost shareholder 116K for each late delivery a SPEEA strike will cost shareholders 250K per day" Wayne, so now you deny that you posted those numbers today? A little revisionist history?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357619193488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:26:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357619216805-233</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Still having Problems with the "DREAMliner"!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1357599327944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:55:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NTSB Investigating Japan Airlines Dreamliner Fire The National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) is investigating the cause of a fire in the underbelly of a Japan Airlines Boeing 787 Dreamliner at Boston's Logan International Airport on Monday. READ All About IT Where "The REAL NEWS Matters"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1357619216805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:26:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357620807941-234</Id><Topic><Title>If We Don't Want Bad Guys to Have Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357589197130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:06:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was there, dolt. I didn't see you there.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357620807941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:53:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357621178912-235</Id><Topic><Title>Statistics Prove: More Guns = Less Crime !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357602742526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:52:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a load of #$%$ !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357621178912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 23:59:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>