<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372918481107-1</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Capitalism is NOT a form of government., idiot.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1372918481107</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 02:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372921515609-2</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do I fear obama justice, ask the Duke Lacrosse team, or the guy who made the Benghazi youtube vid (still in jail), or the contributors to Mitt who got audited by the IRS &amp; Labor Dept, or the voters who are afraid to vote due to intimidation by black panthers, or border agent Brian Terry to name a few.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1372921515609</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 03:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372921526136-3</Id><Topic><Title>Still waiting for Wayne's invention to change airplane technology</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372807174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it for Wayne's invention to "jump the evolution of airplane technology".</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372921526136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 03:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372921659688-4</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne - NYSE actually closed early today</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372876409737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder when Wayne will spread more disinformation about markets closing early. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372921659688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 03:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372922046751-5</Id><Topic><Title>Paris Air Show- Vote on Boeing vs Airbus Stock Price</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371247771854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aviation Week (in its Paris roundup issue) says Boeing outsold Airbus 245 to 235 in firm new orders. (Does not include MOUs, options, previously announced orders, or conversions of existing orders.) Airbus outsold Boeing in value $36.6B to $30.2B, at list price. But we all know what that is worth.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372922046751</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 03:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372922500827-6</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does Obama have to do with this case?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372922500827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 03:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372929284732-7</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get a life. Levon isn't coming down for breakfast anymore.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1372929284732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 05:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372933682708-8</Id><Title>Electrical problem grounds 787 flight july 4 2013 (today)</Title><Msg>The plane is not fit to fly. The plane is a flying coffin. There will be one at the bottom of the pacific this summer.</Msg><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372933682708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 06:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372937758763-9</Id><Topic><Title>Electrical problem grounds 787 flight july 4 2013 (today)</Title><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372933682708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 06:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The press had hidden the incident until</Msg><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372937758763</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:35:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372937958277-10</Id><Title>Press hiding july 4th electrical problem until boeing and the FAA can put spin on it.</Title><Msg>For 3 hours all major new agencies (cbs,nbc.fox) are hiding it until Boeing and the FAA can put a spin on the facts. The plane is DOOMED.</Msg><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372937958277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372940815621-11</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NAW, no threat when a big Black kid, not the 12 yr. old you libtards wanted the public to believe Zimmerman was attacked by, is on top ot you pounding your head in the ground, and then reaches for your gun that you are legally entitled to carry.....no life threatening attack at all. Zimmerman probably should have just handed the gun to the young drug usin thug, and had him look at it whiile on the bottom with Trevon on top of him.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372940815621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372942440156-12</Id><Topic><Title>Press hiding july 4th electrical problem until boeing and the FAA can put spin on it.</Title><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372937958277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree that the plane is a winged coffin, but do you have any further info on this incident at all? Flight #, Airline, destination, etc.....?</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1372942440156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372942475727-13</Id><Title>Happy 4th</Title><Msg>from CNS... "Don’t forget that The Washington Post recently reported that the Obamas’ trip to Africa in the week just before July 4 could cost what they called a “kingly sum,” anywhere from $60 million to $100 million. “Military cargo planes will airlift in 56 support vehicles, including 14 limousines and three trucks loaded with sheets of bulletproof glass to cover the windows of the hotels where the first family will stay,” the Post reported. “Fighter jets will fly in shifts, giving 24-hour coverage over the president’s airspace, so they can intervene quickly if an errant plane gets too close.” Those funds would have covered every federal Fourth of July event nationwide with plenty left over for a president’s vacation." got budget?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372942475727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372943140797-14</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry, Paul Ryan, Anti-Abortion Politics and Kicking the Poor</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372801078195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 17:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No answer from econprofhked is equivalent to a YES. He's a pretty dumb unit. Probably home-schooled in a Tea Potty household? That would explain a lot.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1372943140797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 09:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372947378210-15</Id><Topic><Title>Press hiding july 4th electrical problem until boeing and the FAA can put spin on it.</Title><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372937958277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH B pucky re hiding WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Polish airline LOT has cancelled one trans-Atlantic flight and postponed another after technical problems on two of its Boeing 787 planes, the carrier's spokeswoman said Thursday. Barbara Pijanowska-Kuras confirmed that a flight to Chicago was cancelled on Wednesday because of problems with the power system, while another to Toronto was postponed due to issues associated with the plane's tracking system. She said the problems were minor and not linked to the battery problems behind the global grounding of the 787 fleet earlier this year. The Toronto flight took off Thursday morning after the problem was fixed, while the other plane was still undergoing checks on Thursday and passengers were put on other flights, she said. LOT has four 787s and was the first European airline to buy the plane, dubbed The Dreamliner by Boeing. All four are making dozens of long-haul flights each week to New York, Chicago, Toronto and Beijing, Pijanowska-Kuras said. However, the plane has proved something of a headache for the cash-strapped company, which is currently going through a restructuring that involves layoffs. LOT is in talks with Boeing over how much it should be compensated for the grounding of the world's fleet.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1372947378210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 10:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372947473683-16</Id><Topic><Title>Press hiding july 4th electrical problem until boeing and the FAA can put spin on it.</Title><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372937958277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Technical glitches delay two Dreamliner flights from Poland inShare0Share this Email Print Related NewsUPDATE 2-Bombardier delays CSeries 1st flight again, up to a month Wed, Jun 26 2013 UPDATE 2-AIRSHOW-Airbus wins order battle at Paris Airshow Thu, Jun 20 2013 Airbus bags firm orders worth $39 billion at show Thu, Jun 20 2013 Orders top $100 billion as Ryanair gives Boeing a boost Wed, Jun 19 2013 United Dreamliner diverted due to possible oil filter problem Tue, Jun 18 2013Analysis &amp; OpinionAn Indian pivot in Afghanistan after troop drawdown It’s Superman over California Related TopicsStocks » Markets » Airlines » Bankruptcy » WARSAW, July 4 | Thu Jul 4, 2013 4:08am EDT WARSAW, July 4 (Reuters) - Polish airline LOT had to cancel or postpone two Boeing Dreamliner flights because of technical glitches with the aircraft, an airline spokeswoman said on Thursday. A flight from Warsaw to Chicago that was scheduled to fly on Wednesday was cancelled because the aircraft had "problems with the power supply," said LOT spokeswoman Barbara Pijanowska-Kuras, without giving more details. LOT, which is state-controlled, has four Dreamliner flights a day, according to its schedule. Last year it became the first European airline to add the Dreamliner to its fleet. The Dreamliner has been beset with problems since its launch. The spokeswoman would not say if the latest technical problems were related to over-heating batteries which forced the grounding of all Dreamliners for over three months. After Boeing re-designed the battery system, regulators cleared the jets to fly again. The LOT spokeswoman said another Dreamliner flight that was scheduled to fly on Wednesday, from Warsaw to Toronto, had been pushed back to Thursday. "With the Toronto flight, there occurred a need to remove some questions regarding the airplane's identification in the air," she said. She said passengers booked on Wednesday to fly to Toronto and Chicago were being transferred to other flights.</Msg><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372947473683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 10:17:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372948056466-17</Id><Topic><Title>Happy 4th</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372942475727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate trickle-down econ?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1372948056466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 10:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372948565932-18</Id><Topic><Title>Press hiding july 4th electrical problem until boeing and the FAA can put spin on it.</Title><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372937958277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WARSAW, Poland — Polish airline LOT has cancelled one trans-Atlantic flight and postponed another after technical problems on two of its Boeing 787 planes, the carrier’s spokeswoman said Thursday. Barbara Pijanowska-Kuras confirmed that a flight to Chicago was cancelled on Wednesday because of problems with the power system, while another to Toronto was postponed due to issues associated with the plane’s tracking system. She said the problems were minor and not linked to the battery problems behind the global grounding of the 787 fleet earlier this year. The Toronto flight took off Thursday morning after the problem was fixed, while the other plane was still undergoing checks on Thursday and passengers were put on other flights, she said. LOT has four 787s and was the first European airline to buy the plane, dubbed The Dreamliner by Boeing. All four are making dozens of long-haul flights each week to New York, Chicago, Toronto and Beijing, Pijanowska-Kuras said. However, the plane has proved something of a headache for the cash-strapped company, which is currently going through a restructuring that involves layoffs. LOT is in talks with Boeing over how much it should be compensated for the grounding of the world’s fleet. Read more: \</Msg><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372948565932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 10:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372951457030-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Company is flailing around trying to work out what to do," said Airbus as they better Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372868770153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:26:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayneker, Once again you show your lack of reading comprehension and math skills. Boeing is not flailing (suggest you look up the word) nor is Airbus doing better than Boeing. Deliveries YTD: Boeing - 306 Airbus - 295 I laugh when I think of how that must stick in your craw.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1372951457030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372952925997-20</Id><Title>July 4 787 delivery</Title><Msg>NORTH CHARLESTON, S.C., July 4, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] and Hainan Airlines today celebrated the delivery of the airline's first 787 Dreamliner. The delivery is the first of 10 787s for Hainan Airlines. "Today is a great day for Hainan Airlines as the most technologically advanced and fuel efficient airplane in the world joins our fleet," said Mu Weigang, vice chairman of Hainan Airlines. "The 787 will allow Hainan Airlines to open new routes from Beijing to North America and provide our unique 'Eastern-style' five-star in-flight experience for global passengers." Hainan Airlines will first operate the Dreamliner on a domestic route from Beijing to Haikou. Thereafter, the airline will deploy the 787 on its North America routes, increasing the frequency of its Beijing-Seattle, Beijing-Toronto and Beijing-Chicago services, with several new destinations.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1372952925997</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 11:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372953851518-21</Id><Topic><Title>Happy 4th</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372942475727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 08:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>got spaz err got brains err got delusions err got spazmo err got islaMOspaz err got brain damage censored bumper fascist?</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1372953851518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372953980792-22</Id><Title>EADSY and EAD.PA and investions, and the angry Boeing barker and IGZ</Title><Msg>, The angry Boeing Barker needs another spanking and I am gland to give spartacus what he wants. Spartacus99991 said He “predicted Airbus stock (EAD.PA) would outperform BA (percentagewise) during the 5 days of the Paris Air show, which was the OPs question. It didn't. Big deal. next, so as usual spartacus9991 was wrong and I Wayne was right , done deal, when Spartacus99991 is wrong its no big deal, it is unimportant wow and bark for Spartacus99991, who then said” Wayne compares Boeing to Airbus (EADS) and comparing to Boeing with a stock symbol (EADSY) that trades about 8,000 shares a day around $50. He doesn't even know that the official symbol for EADS is EAD.PA. And he calls himself a stock trader. “ Next, to save space and more angry gibberish from sparticus99991, I am now addressing his other factual issue. . So Spartacus nope your wrong as usual no surprise. Actually EADSY trades an average of 6000 shares not 8000. For inexperienced traders, like spartacus99991 (to make it easy to understand) or people who want a quick easy price EADSY is converted from the euro to the dollar, within a few cents. It is the quickest way to compare accurately ,Airbus stock performance is much better than Boeing stock, with using the CNN Money stock chart( spartacus99991. A question for you, wake up now , did you try EAD.PA on the CNN money stock chart? Ha ha ) Spartacus99991 learning to be a successful stock trader skill set , a clue, It does not require your angry, and mad and loser attitude rather being a experienced stock trader is all I need. To purchase Airbus stock, since you found EAD.PA, spartacus99991, while I know you have no intention of actually buying Airbus and are just being a troll, EAD.PA , that is the Paris stock market, you can use any American Stock brokerage with an international trade desk , once you have set up your international account and trade EAD.PA online, Airbus trades a very liquid 3 million shares per</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372953980792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372954541213-23</Id><Topic><Title>EADSY and EAD.PA and investions, and the angry Boeing barker and IGZ</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372953980792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>day. On the invention, (your word), spartacus99991, yes, both Burt and Forrest are in my backyard and easy to get with the Sandpoint and CDL area, has been great for me and it is a great area for aero, inventions. many famous aviators and inventors' are from this area. . . Since your not an investor, the first time you will know about any invention is when say, a company , say, Airbus deploys the invention. but that is all I can say and that was all I needed and wanted to say.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372954541213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372955541094-24</Id><Topic><Title>EADSY and EAD.PA and investions, and the angry Boeing barker and IGZ</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372953980792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IGZ is a stock spartacus9991 claimed was better than my ACAD , ACAD made me 1200% in one year so spartacus99991 looked around on the stock market and found IGZ and said big deal , IGZ is up 144% in one day. So I pointed out , that as usual, Spartacus 99901 was a fraud and a fake and a Boeing barker, IGZ is a stock symbol tool for the stock market to check their system while EADSY is a real stock . here is a summation of the Spartacus 99901 fake trade claim, one of many, spartacus99991, also at different times, says he does not own Boeing and at other times goes back in time to the lowest point and claims he bought Boeing then sold in the past and make huge.. I post current trades like the then ACAD where I was up 25% in a day and called it a rocket and it did as I said, it made me 1200% in one year , I did the same may 3 with TSLA in 15 days made 100% on a short squeeze and if you read me I gave all a one sentence how to trade TSLA on a day trade basis until it break out or down on the Bollinger bandk yesterday was the first day I could have made more shorting TSLa I made 800 long and the high is $119.35 so now reading a stock chart it is critical positive news could push it up or negative news could make it a great short to maybe 109, I could trade Boeing as I have said many times it moves so slow it is not a buy or a short it is 90% bettered over 3 years by Airbus so go with EADSY LOOK AT THE PRICE, COMPARE TO BA ON THE CNN MONEY STOCK CHART THEN CALL YOUR STOCK TRADER AND SET UP YOUR INTERNATIONAL ACCOUNT AND TRADE EAD.PA AT 3 MILLION LIQUID SHARES TRADED PER DAY TO MAKE SPARTACUS99991 HAPPY CAMPER NOW SPARTACUS99991, HOW DID THAT WORK OUT FOR YOU</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372955541094</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372956170439-25</Id><Topic><Title>Press hiding july 4th electrical problem until boeing and the FAA can put spin on it.</Title><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372937958277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The issue is the 787 was outsourced- read hart-smith, not designed and controlled by boeing engineers in everett and the puget sound area like the 777 was.. So the control was lost, no surprise the 787 is ,so far a major lemon. The leadership james mcnerney had zero airframe production experience he was an average ge jet engine man, appointed by a temporary ceo who knew nothing of areospace lewis platt, so failure was a great probablity. Look at airbus they appointed allan mcartor , read his bio for americas ceoof airbus he is an american hero and then highly qualified , that is a guy with problably the type of credential needed to run boeing and he will be great for airbus, james mcnerney , not so good, we did not need a college baseball plauyer from a ivy leage scholl that jack welch showed the door to at ge.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372956170439</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372956308640-26</Id><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Msg>......the Democrat party. Freedom is about the ability to make your own choices. More and more the Democrat Party wants to take away your choices and give them to government bureaucrats to make for us. They now force us to save a certain amount for retirement, for life insurance, for an out of work fund, for medical care. They tel you how much you can charge for your labor, how much you must pay for someone else's labor, who you can can and can't loan money to and who can have contracts with the government based on nothing other than the color of your skin. Not to mention they force you to pay for the living expense of the nation's parasites. These are all Democrat installed losses of freedom. This party has always been in a war to limit, confine and control liberty. We must continue to fight against these despicable enemies of liberty.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372956650454-27</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please get a life and a dictionary and a brain. And stay away from the republican party as there are serious folks trying to regain that party's sanity.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1372956650454</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372956721460-28</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>July 4th reminds us that there are repugnant people like playwithyourself who hates democracy. If he didn't, he'd know that his ideas are in the MINORITY and he is a LOSER.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1372956721460</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372958021910-29</Id><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Msg>is it because they are stupid right wing bigots or crazy assed RWNJ crackers</Msg><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372958179969-30</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Democracy without morals and respect for the rights of individuals is nothing more than mob rule. Remember Hitler was Democratically elected. I thought you Democrats were all about protecting the rights of minorities but you can see by oldbuck56's comment that's just a minute speck of the Democrat's hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958179969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372958229644-31</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile, the RWNJ's export oil from American lands so that people like Lee Raymonde can get a $500M retirement bonus or others can pollute our, land, air, and seas Let Freddom Ring! End the RWNJ idiocy and hypocracy...</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1372958229644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372958356658-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are Democrats such bigots they want to lynch a man just because he's a Hispanic that defended himself against a thug?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958356658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372959852210-33</Id><Title>Happy 4th of July</Title><Msg>Everybody have a nice day.. Sorry Wayneker. You'll have to wait until the 14th of July.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1372959852210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:44:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372960168050-34</Id><Topic><Title>EADSY and EAD.PA and investions, and the angry Boeing barker and IGZ</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372953980792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>notice almost right away, two thumbs down and spartacus99991 has 2 names his other name is neospart99, so when he is replied to, with the facts and shown for what a barker and troll he is , nothing to say, take your time make something up, use your usual half truths and fraud, you know like you have been dogging me for 10 years and you say spartacus99991 has only been here for 6 years instead of listing your other user names , what a weak and stupid lair you are spartacus99991. propaganda, neospart99, if you actually think any other reader but your barker crew is going with that, well good luck then, your going to need it. that is all you have certainly not 90% better stock price gain by Airbus over Boeing in 3 years . spartacus99991, that is on EADSY or EAD.PA or any other stock market board too. neospart99, and as I told you the 787 is a lemon, as in another 787 was just now not able to leave the gate, neospart99, as I said , this lemon 787 plane to prove my point was a MD business plan , which was already proven to fail, MD outsource failure equaled MD company bankruptcy, the same business plan that bankrupted MD read hart-smith a boeing engineer will bankrupt Boeing, just as soon as all the legacy planes like the 747, 777 and 737 are no longer competitive. Airbus has already conquered the 737 single aisle market and over time the 737 will not be the huge money maker for Boeing, Airbus has pretty much taken away the 747 market along with Boeing assist on the 777, and Airbus has built the perfect plane the A350 to eat away market share from Boeings 787 and 777X over time. Spartacus99991-neospart99 and all your other user names, , like the Airbus stock Boeing will continue to lose to Airbus in plane orders Airbus stock will better Boeing by over 200%in another 3 years not just 90% like now over 3 years</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372960168050</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372960729412-35</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone who wishes a war with other Americans because their politics differ has missed the whole point of Independence Day. Our founders wanted a nation in which everyone could express their ideals for Democracy. But we'll let you grill your burgers, guzzle tour beers, and set off fireworks even if you don 't get. That's the kind of nation we are.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372960729412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372960825321-36</Id><Topic><Title>Our Founding Fathers Thought rhe Term "Democrat" was an Epitaph or an Insult</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958629226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How odd, then. that Thomas Jefferson founded the Democratic movement. But it's OK, we don't rely on you for any iota of truth, putz.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372960825321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372961001962-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because when you get in trouble with a thug because you ignore the advice of a 911 dispatcher, and because you were so brave because you knew you had an edge the thug didn't (that you were packing a piece -- way more efficient than an iced tea and Skittles), then your character is something less than honorable.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372961001962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372961082448-38</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then Zimmerman may be the worst kind of mobster.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372961082448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372961331831-39</Id><Topic><Title>EADSY and EAD.PA and investions, and the angry Boeing barker and IGZ</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372953980792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HaHa Finally Wayne admits that he has been using a symbol (EADSY, less than 8,000 shares per day) which isn't even the real EADS stock. I've been pointing that out for the last few weeks. His symbol includes the Euro to dollar conversion which has fluctuated from 1.29 to 1.34 over the last month. Talk about inducing errors into calculations. Then he uses CNN money to compare stocks when CNN doesn't even track EAD.PA. Why not use the Yahoo finance charts which does show both and one can use the defaults or put in the actual dates to get the exact comparison. CNN only uses week ending prices to do comparisons for 3 years, another inaccuracy. "On the invention, (your word), spartacus99991" waynedickenson961 waynedickenson961 • Jun 24, 2013 4:31 PM Flag "and probably will sell an invention soon that will be a giant step forward in aerospace technology", So Wayne is lying again when he claims I used the word "invention" when he's the one bragging about it. "and claims he bought Boeing then sold in the past and make huge" The only BA stock I've bought and sold has been through the VIP savings plan after the merger occured. When the price was low the plan bought more with my contributions and when high it bought less. I've voluntarily got partially out near the high and later atsome lower prices, but on average made decent money on the BA holdings (especially with the 75% company matching). Since being retired and no longer contributing to the VIP I no longer own BA stock.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372961331831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372961462073-40</Id><Topic><Title>Press hiding july 4th electrical problem until boeing and the FAA can put spin on it.</Title><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372937958277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne - replying to another of his "avatars". So lame.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372961462073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372961703860-41</Id><Topic><Title>Electrical problem grounds 787 flight july 4 2013 (today)</Title><Username>lgbt_2b_free</Username><Timestamp>1372933682708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 06:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's Wayne to post his agreement to his "friend"? LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372961703860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372961853524-42</Id><Topic><Title>Still waiting for Wayne's invention to change airplane technology</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372807174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, now Wayne's backtracking and saying he never used the word "invention" (anonther post). His own words now make him to be a liar.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372961853524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372962962322-43</Id><Topic><Title>Our Founding Fathers Thought rhe Term "Democrat" was an Epitaph or an Insult</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958629226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thomas Jefferson was a slave owner.....no wonder the Democrat Party fought a war to keep slavery legal.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372962962322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:36:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372963163005-44</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with ......the Democrat party." Judging from the last two presidential elections, you're losing.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372963163005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372963292130-45</Id><Topic><Title>Our Founding Fathers Thought rhe Term "Democrat" was an Epitaph or an Insult</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958629226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since we get over 90% of the African-American vote, obviously they have forgiven us. Why can't you let it go?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372963292130</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372963568227-46</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yes, we are losing our freedom because the other side cheats" You didn't pursue it in court. So it's a baseless accusation... like all of the rest of your accusations.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372963568227</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 14:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372964540320-47</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"guaranteed the black community will riot and burn and loot if not guilty.." Does the word "guaranteed" really apply there? What do you base that on?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372964540320</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372964624090-48</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The jury was carefully chosen. We can't know how they are reacting and interpreting the information they are being given.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372964624090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372964791322-49</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, dock.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372964791322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372966909226-50</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The majority of Republicans wouldn't support Ted Nugent...he's a far out fringe fellow that is upset with the Hooz radical left. But the pinko hooz's? They support the radical left, the Pelosi's, the Harry Reids, the Chuckie Schummer's t hat have ruined the Democrat Party.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372966909226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372967435513-51</Id><Topic><Title>EADSY and EAD.PA and investions, and the angry Boeing barker and IGZ</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372953980792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can't teach stupid, spartacus99991, notice how spartacus99991 attempts to turn the use of EADSY a symbol used to compare in US dollars Airbus to Boeing here in America. and , on an American stock exchange into something I never said I used to trade . I have said many times both Boeing and Airbus don't make me enough money to bother with. it was aapl, up multiple thousands of percent as he knows, he argued me all the way too, making himself nothing all the way too. next spartacus9991 argued with me on acad for one year up 1200% he argued me all the way up that too using at one time, the IGZ fake stock symbol, then tsla so far up 215% year to date, where he finally told me good trade begrudgingly, and I am still trading TSLA , as a day trade. however since stupid, spartacus9991, continues to make gibberish statements ,propaganda, , Spartacus9991, today in Germany, if I wanted , I could have purchased EAD:GR that is the German stock exchange symbol for EADS or Airbus or EADSY so for airbus it is up 3.2% today. I would have done that if I wanted to . the reason is Europe' men in charge of the money, said their version of QE is still on so the stock market took off, that is the equivalent of Ben Bernanke, in the USA. . Spartacus99991, so are you still, stupid , yes you are still printing propaganda and spinning stories Once more Airbus is better than Boeing by 9% year to date and 90% better than Boeing over 3 years that is on EADSY 6000 shares average, EAD.PA 3 million shares average or Germany EAD.GR 144000 share average volume . Spartacus99991 how does it feel to be incredibly so stupid over time ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372967435513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:50:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372968084675-52</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to zimmerman( see his interview on Fox last year ) - he was not following trevon, had parked his car and was going from back of building to front of buildings on circle to get specific address for police. It would sure help IF the likes of Jess J and a few other nut jobs would quit using an outdated pic of trevon, and forcing race into the issue.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1372968084675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372969698031-53</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps if you admitted your own lies, then you might realize that the only thug is Zimmerman, who lied to police about having a clear record when in fact he had been arrested for assaulting a police officer/resisting arrest, lied to detectives about not knowing the Stand Your Ground law despite having specific class instruction in such, who lied to his best friend etc about Trayvon having grabbed his gun, and who lied to the judge when he said had no money yet had $135K in donations from other RWNJ's which he told his wife to use to pay off the American Express Card and Sam's Club account instead of for bail or legal defense... How easliy duped and misled RWNJ's are, trying to defend a serial liar and thug who racially profiled an innocent kid, without any probable cause and against direct order to not follow Trayvon continued to do so anyways, who never identified himself as being with the neighborhood-watch program, in contact with the police or about him being armed, who said "I have no problem" in response to Trayvon asking what his problem was and why he was following him and then claims to have been sucker punched and beaten within inches of his life by a kid holding an ice-tea, a cell phone, and a bag of Skittles...therby needing to rob Trayvon of his inalienable rights to life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness...by murdering the kid</Msg><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372969698031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:28:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372970834270-54</Id><Topic><Title>EADSY and EAD.PA and investions, and the angry Boeing barker and IGZ</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372953980792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has the phrase "anger issues" ever been used to describe you? How's the patent for your invention coming?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372970834270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372971048017-55</Id><Title>Happy Independence Day</Title><Msg>Politics Plus Overcoming right wing insanity, one day at a time. To ensure out continued liberty and freedom.</Msg><Username>furtherprog</Username><Timestamp>1372971048017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372971557936-56</Id><Title>Global temperature, 2001-10: 14.47C</Title><Msg>Global temperature, 1901-10: 13.59C = 2.5 degrees F keep it cool stop global climate change make it an issue</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372971557936</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971561637-57</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"According to zimmerman( see his interview on Fox last year ) - he was not following trevon" Did you expect him to admit guilt?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372971561637</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971779510-58</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trevon could have looked like The Creature from the Black Lagoon, but he still would not have deserved to be shot for walking in a neighborhood he had every right to be in, carrying only Skittles and iced tea. On what planet of fear and loathing are you living these days? Anyway, the jury is going to decide this as a jury should, and I am not voting for Zimmerman to spend a couple of year's being Bubba's boyfriend. I hope the jury does tjat. :-D</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372971779510</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971856701-59</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He never followed the kid. Except for: 1. in his car 2. then on foot</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1372971856701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971900589-60</Id><Topic><Title>EADSY and EAD.PA and investions, and the angry Boeing barker and IGZ</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372953980792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:06:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Waynedickenson961" has only been on the Yahoo board since August 2012. What are the other "avatars" that you have been using for "10 years"? Maybe that explains why your posts get thumbs up soon after posting and other posters get thumbs down. And you think up/down thumbs has any meaning on an anonymous board. More delusions. Are "mining_phd" and "lgbt_2b_free"some of your other nicks? You agree with them soon after they post negative Boeing comments. Hmmm... BTW, how's the "wife" or maybe the board already has some clues. Did she get half of your "$28M" from the Apple shares?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372971900589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372971934745-61</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably the agenda from last night's meeting at the Klavern.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1372971934745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972103692-62</Id><Topic><Title>July 4th Reminds us We are Still In a War for Freedom.....This time it's a War with</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372956308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not a matter of labeling, dunderhead. It's a matter of reasoning people watching what the Repugnantcons are doing to women's rights. There was a lot of debate about what to call the Korean War and the Vietnam War too, but in the end, reasonable people KNEW that war is war. When American women consider what the right-fringe is up to, you'll know that also.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372972103692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972155892-63</Id><Topic><Title>Our Founding Fathers Thought rhe Term "Democrat" was an Epitaph or an Insult</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958629226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Times change. Try to keep up, putz.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372972155892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372972190350-64</Id><Title>Democrat Pride</Title><Msg>Democrats are proud of the fact they are too dumb to spend the money they earn and need government bureaucrats to spend it for them. Especially dumb ones like Genna/hoozdik. Maybe it's because she/he/it doesn't really earn the money it spends.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372972190350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972328789-65</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly. If Zimmerman had not racially profiled and/or not followed Travon Martin without any probable cause...then none of this would have happened. Zimmerman(under oath): “I wanted to say I am sorry for the loss of your son. I did not know how old he was. I thought he was a little bit younger than I am…(28)" Zimmerman when aske by the police the night of the murder: “how old would you say he (Trayvon Martin) is?” Zimmerman responds, “…late teens.” The dispatcher confirms “Late teens? Ok.” Zimmerman replies in the affirmative, “Uh, huh…” This is recorded proof positive that Zimmerman did know that the “real suspicious guy” he was identifying was in fact nowhere near Zimmerman’s own age. Title XLVI, Chapter 827 of the Florida Statutes defines the terms and circumstances of ABUSE OF CHILDREN. 827.01 (2) states “Child” means any person under the age of 18 years.” 827.03 (1) very succinctly states that “Child abuse” means: (a) Intentional infliction of physical or mental injury upon a child; and (b) An intentional act that could reasonably be expected to result in physical or mental injury to a child. Having been born on February 5th, 1995, Trayvon Benjamin Martin was - in the state of Florida – at 17 years of age physically, legally and technically a child. No reasonable adult who is in possession of a deadly semiautomatic firearm should be justified in initiating the pursuit (harassment) of a child. No reasonable individual could fire a hollow point bullet from a 9mm semiautomatic firearm point blank into the chest of a child and not expect the result to be great physical or mental injury.</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1372972328789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972497061-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to Title XLVI Chapter 784.048 (a) of the Florida Statutes concerning crimes of ASSAULT; BATTERY; CULPABLE NEGLIGENCE; “Harass” means to engage in a course of conduct directed at a specific person that causes substantial emotional distress in such person and serves no legitimate purpose. Further, (b) states “Course of conduct” means a pattern of conduct composed of a series of acts over a period of time, however short, evidencing a continuity of purpose.” These *** ****’* they always get away. – George Zimmerman February 26th, 2012 By these statute definitions GEORGE MICHAEL ZIMMERMAN fits the legal requirements of an individual who engaged in the harassment of a child and who engaged in a course of conduct that caused substantial emotional distress to that child insomuch as to cause the child to flee from the presence of an unknown and potential assailant. The perpetrator of the crime exited his vehicle or conveyance with a fully loaded semiautomatic firearm and gave chase after the child who was fleeing perceived danger. No legitimate purpose existed for such pursuit as the child (Trayvon Martin) was not engaged in any type of illegal conduct at the time in which George Zimmerman continued to harass the child by subsequently giving chase. Even though the initial chase is alleged to have been terminated shortly after its beginning, 784.048 (b) clearly allows no exception for the duration of the conduct that would cause it to be exempted under the terms of harassment. Again it states “a series of acts over a period of time, however short.” Every step in the initial pursuit is a separate and intentional act that conveys a continuity of purpose which was to catch and or confront another individual.</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1372972497061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972559524-67</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TITLE XLVI, Chapter 776 concerning the JUSTIFIABLE USE OF FORCE in the instance of home protection absolutely excludes the use of deadly force by reason of the presumption of fear of death or great bodily harm if: 776.013 (2) (b) The person or persons sought to be removed is a child or grandchild… of, the person against whom the defensive force is used. Section .013 (2) (b) is irrelevant to George Zimmerman’s defense for two reasons. First, the section applies to the defense of a dwelling, residence, or occupied vehicle those are defined as a structure with a covering. Secondly, it sets forth guidelines that assume that a minor or child is co-occupying said dwelling, residence or occupied vehicle and that the force is used against an adult. 776.013 (2) (b) is relevant however in that it establishes that the intent of the law is to protect a child from the use of deadly force. Particularly, the defense of George Zimmerman under 776.013 (3) is also excluded as the statute clearly states: “A person who is not engaged in an unlawful activity and who is attacked in any other place where he or she has the right to be has no duty to retreat and has the right to stand his or her ground and meet force with force,..” As previously documented, George Zimmerman was and or had been pursuing a child, without legitimate purpose, in a manner that is consistent with the immediate definition of harassment. Harassment, a crime of stalking, is a first degree misdemeanor and is unequivocally prohibited as unlawful activity as defined by the “Stand Your Ground” statute. Therefore, the protections yielded by JUSTIFIABLE USE OF FORCE are excluded from this event, do not apply and are not a viable affirmative defense. According to the State of Florida prosecution, it is alleged that GEORGE MICHAEL ZIMMERMAN lied to law enforcement officers concerning the actual homocide. In THE STATE’S MOTION FOR PROTECTIVE ORDER filed in Seminole County District Court May 24th, 2012, State Attorneys Angela B. Corey and Bernardo de la Rionda assert: “Defendant has provided law enforcement with numerous statements, some of which are contradictory, and are inconsistent with the physical evidence and statements of witnesses.”</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1372972559524</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372972879361-68</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Pride</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372972190350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We know that your kind, the RWNJ/chickenhak kind do not truly support the military or the Vets letalone the disabled vets who in the line of duty sacrificed so much for this country</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1372972879361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973249099-69</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Pride</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372972190350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We voluntarily give far more to veterans than does the whole Democrat Party. Check out the philanthropic Index and see who gives most to our veterans. Democrats are the most stingy people in the world. Joe Biden gave less than $500 to charity.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372973249099</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973696271-70</Id><Topic><Title>Our Founding Fathers Thought rhe Term "Democrat" was an Epitaph or an Insult</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958629226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why we're winning; we've moved into the 21st Century while you're stuck in 1674.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372973696271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973915112-71</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Pride</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372972190350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. Finally, something you can be proud of.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372973915112</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372974054071-72</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Pride</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372972190350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You throw verbal punches around MMA style but none of them ever land on your target. Is that what Joe B 'gave' or only what he 'declared' on a tax return... and yes, Virginia...(or is that S.C.) there is a difference... one form of 'giving' is for show only, and is disdained in the Bible... like many a repube who chastises gov't spending/pork on the one hand yet takes it for themselves or their constituents with the other hand</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1372974054071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372974313941-73</Id><Topic><Title>Our Founding Fathers Thought rhe Term "Democrat" was an Epitaph or an Insult</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958629226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stuck in 1674 and predictably but unwittingly campaigning for Hillary 2016.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1372974313941</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372974455657-74</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Pride</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372972190350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like Mittens Rawmoney who dodged the draft and hid out in chateau in france and or his five able-bodied sons not a one who chose to serve, but only 'give' monies from mostly ill-gotten gains but hey, that Paul Ryan fella can run a sub 3 hour marathon and still fight the RWNJ fight with his tongue wagging the words...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372974455657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372974535361-75</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently the RWNJ's can't handle The Truth!</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372974535361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372974639640-76</Id><Title>Debunking the Generosity Index</Title><Msg>The most frequent cited “proof” that conservatives are more charitable than liberals is the generosity index from the Catalogue for Philanthropy. I’d like to put the debunk here for general reference. Here’s the way it works. The IRS reports for the states are assembled, and both the average AGI (total AGI divided by population. called AAGI) and average claimed deductions for charitable giving (same by population division, called AICG) are calculated. So far, so good. Both are ranked from most to least, then the RANK of giving is subtracted from the RANK of income. If your state has the highest average income it is impossible to have a score higher than 0, which can happen only if your state is also the highest in giving - it’s more likely to be negative. If your state has the lowest income it’s impossible to have a negative score. Since the states that vote predominately Republican also tend to be in the lower half of the income ranking, it becomes inevitable that they’ll tend to get a better Generosity Score. On the surface it would seem a more equitable ranking would be made by calculating each state’s AICG:AAIG ratio and ranking the results. The legitimate objection to that ratio goes even further to demonstrate how poor a measure this is. Basically, only higher income people tend to itemize deductions and so have itemized charitable giving. As a result, the rank of ratios is remarkably similar to the rank of AAGI, allowing the claim that the rich give more of their income than the poor. It’s a bad index, proving nothing.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372974639640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372974862435-77</Id><Title>Did the Democrat President CnC ever learn what a corpsmans is or even how to pronounce it?</Title><Msg>Obama is the most unqualified Preside to ever serve as CnC.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372974862435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372974991919-78</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Zimmerman(under oath): “I wanted to say I am sorry for the loss of your son. I did not know how old he was. I thought he was a little bit younger than I am…(28)".. Uhh just when was zimmerman under oath ???? - he has not yet testified in court- nor does he have to. So where was he under oath- and why hasn't prosecution revealed that yet ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1372974991919</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975072417-79</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and youve also seen the ' re- enactment " video shown in court ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1372975072417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975159900-80</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THE TRUTH WILL SET YOU FREE Zimmerman iniated the chain of events despite specific instructions not to, or even his own inner-self should have known better, which led directly to the murder and robbing of the Trayvon Martin child of his inalienable rights concerning Life, Liberty. and the Pursuit of Happiness...</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1372975159900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:59:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975183360-81</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the Generosity Index</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372974639640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:50:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try but complete BS. If Democrats were halve as generous as Conservatives they could fund their causes with out passing laws to force others to fund them for them.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1372975183360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975488802-82</Id><Topic><Title>Did the Democrat President CnC ever learn what a corpsmans is or even how to pronounce it?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372974862435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:54:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ewe can't even spell corpsman no wonder you must be a SRWB is yo' momma as ugly as Paula Dean's rascist behaviour?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372975488802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975596911-83</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so it was at the bond hearing- OK- but that has NO bearing on the case- note the word " I thought " . . . Anyone can think of anything- and picking at such nits usually does not carry much weight. Has it ( statement at bond hearing ) been entered into evidence ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1372975596911</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975641297-84</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the Generosity Index</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372974639640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:50:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are ewe willing to give up all your id's today</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372975641297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372975971856-85</Id><Title>Conservative groups can’t find 2014 candidates</Title><Msg>Conservative groups can’t find 2014 candidates Many potential GOP primary challengers have chosen not to run, leaving conservatives without viable alternatives By Jillian Rayfield Conservative groups like the Senate Conservatives Fund and Club for Growth are having trouble recruiting viable candidates to challenge Republicans in the 2014 primaries, with most of the favored candidates declining to run. In South Dakota, for instance, Tea Party favorite Rep. Kristi Noem decided not to enter the primary against Gov. Mike Rounds, a Republican making a bid for the Senate seat of retiring Sen. Tim Johnson, a Democrat. In Iowa, Rep. Steve King, a well-known immigration hard-liner, decided not to run for Democratic Sen. Tom Harkin’s seat when he retires that year, leaving no clear front-runner among conservatives — or Republicans, for that matter. The Hill reports: -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Though Tea Party activists in Kentucky insisted earlier this year that they’d have a candidate by June, no one has yet launched a primary challenge against Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R). And Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.), a top target for conservatives looks safer after two conservative congressmen — Reps. Joe Wilson and Mick Mulvaney — ruled out a run. “There is a sliver of truth … in the sense that, maybe compared to other cycles, the conservative candidates have not come on line as quickly,” Matt Hoskins, executive director of the Senate Conservatives Fund, told the Hill.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372975971856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372975981788-86</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under Oath, GEORGE MICHAEL ZIMMERMAN lied about his material knowledge of Trayvon Martin. During the same bond hearing on April 20th, 2012, in which he lied about his mobility/passport issue as well as his monetary/bond issue, George Zimmerman raised his right hand and swore to tell the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth. He then took the stand and stated: “I wanted to say.... I did not know how old he was. I thought he was a little bit younger than I am…” The bigger question...is why won't the self-described stand-your-ground/self-defence Zimmerman defendant not take the stand in his own defence, isn't it???!? You are not the average stupid RW bigot are u///</Msg><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372975981788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372976235117-87</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More importantly to some: Is Boeing About to Eat Airbus' Lunch? 96 or 114, which comes first? Boeing (NYSE: BA ) and Airbus have been locked in a long-running battle for supremacy in the market for widebody aircraft. With new airplane models like Boeing's 787 and Airbus' A350, both manufacturers have increased their use of lightweight composite materials to produce significant fuel-efficiency improvements. At the Paris Air Show last month, Boeing announced a new, larger version of its popular 787 Dreamliner, with initial orders from several airlines including United Continental (NYSE: UAL ) . The new plane -- dubbed the 787-10 -- attacks the Airbus A350's largest market segment. Moreover, it is expected to offer better fuel efficiency than the comparable Airbus product. Will this new version of the Dreamliner allow Boeing to eat Airbus' lunch? In the following video, Motley Fool industrials bureau chief Isaac Pino and Motley Fool contributor Adam Levine-Weinberg discuss the competition between Boeing and Airbus and the prospects for Boeing's new plane. With the American markets reaching new highs, investors and pundits alike are skeptical about future growth. They shouldn't be. Many global regions are still stuck in neutral, and their resurgence could result in windfall profits for select companies, including Boeing. A recent Motley Fool report, "3 Strong Buys for a Global Economic Recovery," outlines three companies that could take off when the global economy gains steam. Click here to read the full report!</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372976235117</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372976402505-88</Id><Title>BA is going to break historical high tomorrow..</Title><Msg>booooooooooooooooooya.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1372976402505</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372976621471-89</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative groups can’t find 2014 candidates</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372975971856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:12:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of them RWNJ potential candi-dates are so belligerenlty right-wing that they would rather try and reap beaucoup d'arget from the RWNJ media than to actually try to make America better like Obama, Joe Biden, et al have... You can bet your sweet behind that Rawmoney and the RWNJ's would be taking credit for the continuing improvement in the U.S. economy and downplying the potential of the FED to ease</Msg><Username>furtherprog</Username><Timestamp>1372976621471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372977016749-90</Id><Topic><Title>Our Founding Fathers Thought rhe Term "Democrat" was an Epitaph or an Insult</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1372958629226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the jury is still out knock, knock who's there Hillary Hillary who? Hillary the Awesome wife, first lady, Senator, Secretary of State...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372977016749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372977298513-91</Id><Topic><Title>bagger turd polishers</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361583371783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 20:36:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it !</Msg><Username>trickledown_is_a_hoax</Username><Timestamp>1372977298513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:34:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372977411687-92</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...The bigger question...is why won't the self-described stand-your-ground/self-defence Zimmerman defendant not take the stand in his own defence, isn't it???!?.. ONE reason is that he cannot say or DO anything UNTIL the Prosecution rests. Second reason- He need not say anything- its up to the state to prove its case "beyond any reasonable doubt" such that the JURY agrees. Failure to testify cannot be used against him under law. How many juries have you been on ? - Criminal cases ? - Civil cases ? I've been on both types ...</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1372977411687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372977869181-93</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you only got two hands... Trayvon:Why are you following me? What is your problemo? (I am not dropping either the iced-tea nor the cell-phone unless provoked...o\under Inalienable Rights, the bag of Skittles was found where..as well as the iced-tea, the cell phone(s)!!! etc. in relation to the actual homicide...) and as the liar Zimmerman said, the Trayvon kid was 'reaching' for my gun wrll...personally I would knock his hand/arm out of the way with one hand and knock his othe hand and him off of mee, if i were to be believable instead of some stand your ground RWNJ cop wannbe thug/killer</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372977869181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372977917695-94</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dunno, I thought Sarah Plain looked pretty hot after she got those two implants. A lot hotter than Nugent in any case.</Msg><Username>prince_of_pastrami</Username><Timestamp>1372977917695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372978256725-95</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you such an insignificant snivelling weenie? Have you gotten lost from your Mama?</Msg><Username>prince_of_pastrami</Username><Timestamp>1372978256725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372978357755-96</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It can be entered into evidence for the JURY, but already hear, if the delf-proclaimed self-defence defendant will take the witness stand in his own defence...which he won't.. so in summary the child martin was brutally killed and robbed of his ianalinble god-given rights by the thug Zimmerman who beliigerently disregarded the police dispatcher and initiated the chain of events by his overzealous racial-profiling edit for content/etc. 96 or 114 ? and screw mangement as they are a mangey lot</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372978357755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372978763554-97</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"- he has not yet testified in court- nor does he have to" One would think that the self-proclaimed stand-your-ground/self-defence child MURDERER in the 2nd degree defendant who would not accept Mansalughter2 would want to testify under oath, unless he was hiding something, n'ect ce pas? As for the Zimmerman father, one would expect that a Judge would want Justice to be served, wouldn't they? And what about BA price and/or management, zombie fry-day leads to AA Monday etc.. and eating somebody's lunch...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372978763554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372979160381-98</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>T. Nugent is but a RWNJ boil on the behimnd of all good America Rock n' Roll.. like so may otters...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372979160381</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372979650593-99</Id><Title>'Men Who Made America'</Title><Msg>On the History Channel. Very well done. Shows capitalism at it's absolute best and worst. Happy 4th.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1372979650593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372979797431-100</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"ONE reason is that he cannot say or DO anything UNTIL the Prosecution rests" Exactly, but will he, if not the prosecution can and will use that in it's summary, as should be the case. And the defence is gonna tell knock-knock jokes ?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1372979797431</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372980746356-101</Id><Topic><Title>'Men Who Made America'</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1372979650593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:14:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should have read 'Men Who Built America'.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1372980746356</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:32:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372984486397-102</Id><Topic><Title>'Men Who Made America'</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1372979650593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 19:14:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eventually those menmetrosexual men of today are gonna wanna build up not out over here too... and the worst ? -the bisbee angler</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372984486397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372984790221-103</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ted Pungent an otter Hardly, more like a one-hit RWNJ wonder rodent land beaver</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372984790221</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372985177791-104</Id><Title>The Bisbee 4th</Title><Msg>we go over to Tomstone light some portable oven-fired pizzas drink and eat until dusk not daylight savings time then hoop and holler while lighting some rockets red glare un less deputy sherrif spaztacus shows up</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372985177791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372985253456-105</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Schwag!</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372985253456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372986113877-106</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You, sir, are a poet!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372986113877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372986579255-107</Id><Topic><Title>Why do RWNJ's believe all the Zimmerman lies...</Title><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1372958021910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 13:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is convicting him (or successfully defending him either) on this board. We are stating our reactions to what we THINK we know -- and so are you, Don. This game is as American as apple pie; the same thing happens after ever aircraft accident among people who don't know squat *like in this case). Re-enactment my #$%$br /&gt; This sounds like jailhouse lawyerism at it very worst.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372986579255</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372986667914-108</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>however if my head had hit a rock or was being 'pouded' into the sidewalk i don't think i would be feeling okay unless i was a rwnj</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372986667914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372986806587-109</Id><Title>the Zimmerman's should sue the Trayvon Martin parents</Title><Msg>in right wing nut job civil court for losers</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372986806587</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372987224579-110</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative groups can’t find 2014 candidates</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372975971856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:12:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It'll be Cruz and Paul or Paul and Cruz." John and Paul were a much better team.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1372987224579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372987344454-111</Id><Topic><Title>When I was 17. it was a very good year</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372984312620</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:31:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you seen the Zimmerman's wife no wonder he was out racially-profiling especially the 'new' kid blam blam blam blam blam and blam law officer -bisbee anglers</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372987344454</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372987541972-112</Id><Topic><Title>When I was 17. it was a very good year</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372984312620</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:31:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>woulda fired more thasn on shot... just sayin'///</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372987541972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372987855421-113</Id><Topic><Title>The Bisbee 4th</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372985177791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and have a laugh with the 7th Signal Corpsgals if we can</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372987855421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372989134337-114</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative groups can’t find 2014 candidates</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372975971856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 18:12:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i wish I knew what that meant half as much you think in bisbee on the 4th Keep Up The Good Work in Chicago too even though should the Philly A's</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372989134337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372989147548-115</Id><Topic><Title>Did the Democrat President CnC ever learn what a corpsmans is or even how to pronounce it?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1372974862435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:54:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No he's not unqualified. He was elected by a majority. Twice. Harharharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372989147548</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372989511610-116</Id><Topic><Title>What difference does it make anyway ?</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1372989021373</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>on the down side don ]they don't get live where you do nor how the fools</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372989511610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 21:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372990696767-117</Id><Topic><Title>The Bisbee 4th</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372985177791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 20:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now that it is dusk and playing Bolero</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372990696767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:18:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372992721456-118</Id><Title>I have decided to run on the RWNJ ticket, being bumped off a MAC-flight in Crete</Title><Msg>just to see what happens, bolero....</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372992721456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372992916534-119</Id><Topic><Title>I have decided to run on the RWNJ ticket, being bumped off a MAC-flight in Crete</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372992721456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't tell crete they were of strattgic importance once upoin a time bolero</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372992916534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:55:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372995185057-120</Id><Title>Do Not be Denied</Title><Msg>this 4th...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372995185057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372995768695-121</Id><Topic><Title>Do Not be Denied</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372995185057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they say it was a pretty good rendition of Ravel's Bolero so far... and it is still near dusk over hear in Bisbee ever since they don't want DST and all of AZ but then who are we gonna listen too some S.C. beyatch-ho's ho's just you wait</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1372995768695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>