<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360559392511-1</Id><Topic><Title>WHO SAID ANYTHING ABOUT LANDING IN SOSCHI 2014 UNDER TWO MINTUES</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360558634513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 23:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EAT THEIR HEARTS FI9VE CLIBS</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360559392511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 00:09:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360560196187-2</Id><Topic><Title>WHO SAID ANYTHING ABOUT LANDING IN SOSCHI 2014 UNDER TWO MINTUES</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360558634513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 23:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under two minutes by more than 4 sec0onds knees to chest flying 4 all it's wirth</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360560196187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 00:23:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360563145320-3</Id><Title>Blasck girls in combat - kindasleazytrice call me</Title><Msg>shesitd in a corner by a door] grid coordinmaste Coiesmo/Lesbo magazine ] t tszake you timer oh yeah ] ]lord my body]] been a good frfiend</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360563145320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 01:12:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360564888996-4</Id><Topic><Title>WHO SAID ANYTHING ABOUT LANDING IN SOSCHI 2014 UNDER TWO MINTUES</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360558634513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 23:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>flying with knees to chest landing one foot at a time boot and ski two ski boot and foot not too shabby for over 60 mph</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360564888996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 01:41:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360565850619-5</Id><Topic><Title>Soischi 2014</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360547918882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:58:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>some say i threwe an axe abnd split a tree from oslo</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360565850619</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 01:57:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360566050881-6</Id><Topic><Title>Soischi 2014</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360547918882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:58:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jkim bowie or danl boones if oslo show up here throwan axsplit a tree powdder gun no fair</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360566050881</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 02:00:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360566156986-7</Id><Topic><Title>Soischi 2014</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360547918882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:58:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>e3as7y gamwe</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360566156986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 02:02:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360566963407-8</Id><Topic><Title>WHO SAID ANYTHING ABOUT LANDING IN SOSCHI 2014 UNDER TWO MINTUES</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360558634513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 23:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's all it takes...old sackof bones</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360566963407</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 02:16:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360569841352-9</Id><Title>This is what we are up to the year of the snake</Title><Msg>kurt russell and goldie hawn no blod on the ice until soschi 2014 zero/none</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360569841352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:04:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360570200760-10</Id><Topic><Title>WHO SAID ANYTHING ABOUT LANDING IN SOSCHI 2014 UNDER TWO MINTUES</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360558634513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 23:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remind \oiurselves</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360570200760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:10:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360570849472-11</Id><Topic><Title>This is what we are up to the year of the snake</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360569841352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:04:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the house of zion will be happy</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360570849472</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:20:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360573474246-12</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>michaelprice845</Username><Timestamp>1360573474246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 04:04:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360573822207-13</Id><Topic><Title>For Whom The Bell Tolls</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360542491954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:28:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we have not been nowhere and should we go somewwhere we'll alert the ray-gun media viza vizp issshles although IAM 110% totally sure of yu'r intentions which are...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360573822207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 04:10:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360574302508-14</Id><Topic><Title>For Whom The Bell Tolls</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360542491954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:28:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>200,000 T3 1-18 personally q 6 hrs as neeeded for pain</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360574302508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 04:18:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360574997363-15</Id><Topic><Title>For Whom The Bell Tolls</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360542491954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:28:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>although called her Toyota becuase her name was Carolla ]she was barely 17 caught a scalpel in her shoe one day the rest I cannot say</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360574997363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 04:29:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360575312004-16</Id><Topic><Title>For Whom The Bell Tolls</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360542491954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:28:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>beczasueit innolvesd te f;king of est germsnyand oluve russia</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360575312004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 04:35:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360577837978-17</Id><Topic><Title>For Whom The Bell Tolls</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360542491954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:28:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shhh oluverussuaf'2 kansas state fair some blind joxefeliciano upstagede the entire band calledSAlalabama</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1360577837978</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 05:17:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360581576863-18</Id><Title>787 Drealiner news to sink stock today.</Title><Msg>Time man up and realize the 787 is jack up and will not fly for a year at best</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581576863</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:19:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360581668811-19</Id><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Msg>The plane is a mess. 1 month with zero to show. I bet they will still be scratching their heads a year from now.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360581802613-20</Id><Title>787 Dreamliner : You can not fix what you do not understand</Title><Msg>This problem has been goiing on for 5 years. It is a lost cause. I can not be fixed.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581802613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:23:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360583663104-21</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, that was very hepful</Msg><Username>harrisonrowley</Username><Timestamp>1360583663104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:54:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360586931008-22</Id><Title>BA closes above 77</Title><Msg>The shorts are still trying,,,ROTFLMAO</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360586931008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 07:48:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360586983804-23</Id><Topic><Title>787 Dreamliner : You can not fix what you do not understand</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581802613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:23:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will easily fix the problem after they have figured out how to break batteries. The set of likely failure mechanisms all point back to flaws in the manufacturing process of the battery. The question is, can the battery be produced economically w/o the defects? Limits testing and power cycle testing will induce failures, eventually. It's got nothing to do with the airplane.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1360586983804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 07:49:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360587890392-24</Id><Title>The Ignorance Caucus</Title><Msg>Last week Eric Cantor, the House majority leader, gave what his office told us would be a major policy speech. And we should be grateful for the heads-up about the speech’s majorness. Otherwise, a read of the speech might have suggested that he was offering nothing more than a meager, warmed-over selection of stale ideas. To be sure, Mr. Cantor tried to sound interested in serious policy discussion. But he didn’t succeed — and that was no accident. For these days his party dislikes the whole idea of applying critical thinking and evidence to policy questions. And no, that’s not a caricature: Last year the Texas G.O.P. explicitly condemned efforts to teach “critical thinking skills,” because, it said, such efforts “have the purpose of challenging the student’s fixed beliefs and undermining parental authority.” And such is the influence of what we might call the ignorance caucus that even when giving a speech intended to demonstrate his openness to new ideas, Mr. Cantor felt obliged to give that caucus a shout-out, calling for a complete end to federal funding of social science research. Because it’s surely a waste of money seeking to understand the society we’re trying to change. Want other examples of the ignorance caucus at work? Start with health care, an area in which Mr. Cantor tried not to sound anti-intellectual; he lavished praise on medical research just before attacking federal support for social science. (By the way, how much money are we talking about? Well, the entire National Science Foundation budget for social and economic sciences amounts to a whopping 0.01 percent of the budget deficit.) But Mr. Cantor’s support for medical research is curiously limited. He’s all for developing new treatments, but he and his colleagues have adamantly opposed “comparative effectiveness research,” which seeks to determine how well such treatments work. What they fear, of course, is that the people running Medicare and other government programs might use the results of such research to determine what they’re willing to pay for. Instead, they want to turn Medicare into a voucher system and let individuals make decisions about treatment. But even if you think that’s a good idea (it isn’t), how are individuals supposed to make good medical choices if we ensure that they have no idea what health benefits, if any, to expect from their choices? Still, the desire to perpetuate ignorance on matters medical is nothing compared with the desire to kill climate research, where Mr. Cantor’s colleagues — particularly, as it happens, in his home state of Virginia — have engaged in furious witch hunts against scientists who find evidence they don’t like. True, the state has finally agreed to study the growing risk of coastal flooding; Norfolk is among the American cities most vulnerable to climate change. But Republicans in the State Legislature have specifically prohibited the use of the words “sea-level rise.” And there are many other examples, like the way House Republicans tried to suppress a Congressional Research Service report casting doubt on claims about the magical growth effects of tax cuts for the wealthy. Do actions like this have important effects? Well, consider the agonized discussions of gun policy that followed the Newtown massacre. It would be helpful to these discussions if we had a good grasp of the facts about firearms and violence. But we don’t, because back in the 1990s conservative politicians, acting on behalf of the National Rifle Association, bullied federal agencies into ceasing just about all research into the issue. Willful ignorance matters. O.K., at this point the conventions of punditry call for saying something to demonstrate my evenhandedness, something along the lines of “Democrats do it too.” But while Democrats, being human, often read evidence selectively and choose to believe things that make them comfortable, there really isn’t anything equivalent to Republicans’ active hostility to collecting evidence in the first place. The truth is that America’s partisan divide runs much deeper than even pessimists are usually willing to admit; the parties aren’t just divided on values and policy views, they’re divided over epistemology. One side believes, at least in principle, in letting its policy views be shaped by facts; the other believes in suppressing the facts if they contradict its fixed beliefs. In her parting shot on leaving the State Department, Hillary Clinton said of her Republican critics, “They just will not live in an evidence-based world.” She was referring specifically to the Benghazi controversy, but her point applies much more generally. And for all the talk of reforming and reinventing the G.O.P., the ignorance caucus retains a firm grip on the party’s heart and mind. NYT / 10 Feb '13</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360587890392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:04:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360588314919-25</Id><Topic><Title>Will BA Bounce? SEE OUR IN DEPTH BA BOUNCE REPORT</Title><Username>kyledurham521</Username><Timestamp>1360012053563</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very useful,Thanks</Msg><Username>reedjames541</Username><Timestamp>1360588314919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:11:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360589664998-26</Id><Topic><Title>The Ignorance Caucus</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360587890392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Hooz_beef _dude, the CBO has just published an update on the Social Security Trust Fund. You might want to read it to learn that the SS Trust Fund date when payouts exceed income has been moved up anothe 2 years to 2016. Wasn't Obamacare sold as something that would preserve SS? The reality of Obamacare and the "Waivers for friends of the Dems" program is not seeing much press coverage. If you are a champion of reality when are you going to accept the reality of why so many Obama supporters are getting waivers to Obamacare? At the moment, Washington DC is the "Twilight Zone" where reality is the enemy of both political parties at the moment.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360589664998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:34:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360590641183-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Ignorance Caucus</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360587890392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First off you're rather ignorant as to anything meaningful that comes from GOP policy suggestions in the way of being accepted by you libtards. Our fascist President, and your leftist Senate leader just schitcan anything suggested. The country could have had good healthcare reform had you not decided before hand you would ram through a miserble socilalist, corrupt bill. The wasted $800 Billion dollar stimulus bill, that Obama admitted was wasted would not have haqppened given you had listened to Republicans.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360590641183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:50:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360591261508-28</Id><Title>New CBO Report Shows Social Security Trust Fund Worse Than Thought</Title><Msg>Do the Dems have a plan to fix Social Security? The year that payouts will exceed revenues has been moved up to 2016 from the 2018 date reported last year by the CBO. At this rate people will see reductions in SS checks before the next election which is good because that may anger seniors enough to the reality that their government is asleep at the wheel on the issue of fixing Social Security. Hopefully President Obama will address this urgent problem honestly in his SOTU but I'm not holding my breath as thus far he has been in denial of the problem.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360591261508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:01:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360591364616-29</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus getting a head start on looking at an alternatie battery and 787 stuff</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360530319433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:05:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the problem with the 747-8 is that the bulk of orders have come from cargo customers, and for the past 18 months or so world cargo demand has been awful...negative or flat demand numbers. The -8F, given that market, has been lucky just to avoid cancellations. The passenger -8I certainly looks promising, but the market for large passenger planes has been in the doldrums for some time, and doesn't look like it will change. A real problem is Airbus's heavily discounted A380 prices.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360591364616</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:02:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360591517178-30</Id><Topic><Title>New CBO Report Shows Social Security Trust Fund Worse Than Thought</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360591261508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:01:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fund is not any worse than Paul "Ryan knew it was, and had a plan to reform it. But the do nothing, only destroy the economy democrats?...let it go belly up, and destroy the lifes of millions upon millions of folks to say nothing of the integrity of the United States.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360591517178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:05:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360591797548-31</Id><Title>Boeing Headed off a Cliff</Title><Msg>yet investors still hold this stock dreaming Boeing figures out major electrical problems with the Dreamliner before its too late. Fact: BA 787 problems will take 4 to 6 months to correct, thus building up huge delayed delivery/penalty fees and pending lawsuits. yet investors still hold this stock dreaming the the sequestration defense hit (50% chop) will some how disappear and go away. Fact: Sequestration will kick in March 1st or in three months. Federal deficit is out of control and Congress knows the only real fat to cut is on the defense side. yet investors still hold this stock thinking Boeing three to five billion pension payout will go away. Fact: Boeing doesn't have the cash reserves to pay off its pension obligation. In fact Boeing is in denial regarding its overall pension payout. yet investors still hold this stock thinking FAA inspectors will only concentrate of Dreamliner electrical problems and not focus on 787 fuel leaks, cracked windshields and overall mechanical problems. I could go on but I've given investors far more information then they need to sell there long position before this stock drop 30%.</Msg><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360591797548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:09:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360592628683-32</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>kaur.thomas</Username><Timestamp>1360592628683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:23:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360592924690-33</Id><Topic><Title>New CBO Report Shows Social Security Trust Fund Worse Than Thought</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360591261508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:01:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is it not worse than Paul Ryan knew when the the funding shortfall has been moved up another 2 years just since the CBO report in October 2012? The "run dry" date when SS Trust Fund funds will be exhausted has also been moved up 2 years to 2031 from 2033. By comparison the date was 2042 in 2004. Obama has gotten to kick the can down the road but the next presidential candidates won't.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360592924690</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:28:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360594644332-34</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Headed off a Cliff</Title><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360591797548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:09:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can say that again brother. Obama will come out tomorrow night and say the sequestration cut coming in three weeks should be postponed for three months. Problem is tea party republicans see the sequestration as they best chance to cut runaway federal deficit. Tea party republicans will not cave and not vote for a sequestration extension. So in three weeks or less Defense companies will take a major hit and their stock value will tumble.</Msg><Username>youbgone</Username><Timestamp>1360594644332</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360594661220-35</Id><Topic><Title>787 Dreamliner : You can not fix what you do not understand</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581802613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:23:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would look into the wiring if it allows for a free flow of lithium-ion energy or does it create a blockage that puts the lithium ion battery into cardiac arrest.</Msg><Username>mbfield50</Username><Timestamp>1360594661220</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:57:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360596934401-36</Id><Topic><Title>California lacks doctors to meet demand of Obamacare...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360594429908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:53:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My God son do you ever stop complaining? Angry white people are so pathetic its beyond funny.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360596934401</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:35:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360596983935-37</Id><Topic><Title>America owes communists $1.2 Trillion...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360593531054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently the Chinese are better at being communists than is the Obama Administration. My suspicion is that they are also a lot better at being capitalists.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360596983935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:36:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360597143838-38</Id><Title>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety</Title><Msg>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety In a blunt briefing Thursday, the chief of the National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) said the government and Boeing badly underestimated the possibilities for failure of the 787’s lithium-ion batteries. . The sweep of the NTSB investigation, and the agency’s critique of the plane’s testing and certification, suggest the jet-maker has a long way to go before passenger flights can resume. The NTSB chief said the safety assessments Boeing and the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) made while certifying the 787 lithium-ion batteries for commercial service “were not borne out by what we saw in flight experience.” Boeing estimated, for instance, that a battery problem would cause smoke less than once during 10 million hours of flight, while the plane so far has experienced two incidents in less than 100,000 hours. safety-board member John Goglia said in an interview afterward the briefing that the statistical standard for safety of the 787 batteries had been set too low by the FAA — and “Boeing didn’t even meet the reduced standard.” The NTSB briefing suggested that Boeing will have to redesign and recertify the jet’s battery system for a long-term fix. “The assumptions used to certify the battery must be reconsidered,” said NTSB Chairwoman Deborah Hersman. “The design and certification assessment, and the assumptions that were made, were not borne out by what we saw in flight experience.” The FAA grounded the plane Jan. 16 after a Jan. 7 battery fire at the Boston airport, followed just over a week later by a second event, when a battery smoldering on a flight in Japan forced an emergency landing. Those incidents make clear, said Goglia, that “Boeing didn’t identify and mitigate all the failure modes.” One in 10 million Hersman said Thursday the investigation has pinpointed the start of the Japan Airlines battery fire as a short circuit inside a single cell of the eight-cell battery. The overheating of cell No. 6 spread to all the others and caused the fire, she said. Hersman said Boeing had studied the possibility of such a single-cell short circuit and its effects, in tests during the certification process. Boeing concluded that these tests “showed no evidence of cell-to-cell propagation or fire in the battery,” she said. However, in the fire on the Japan Airlines jet at Boston’s Logan airport, that’s exactly what happened. In another certification test, Hersman said, Boeing studied the possibility that a failure in a single cell would result in smoke emission from the battery and estimated this would happen “less than once in every 10 million flight hours.” “The 787 fleet has accumulated less than 100,000 flight hours,” she said. “Yet there have now been two battery events resulting in smoke less than two weeks apart on two different aircraft.” Goglia said the standard FAA safety requirement to cover the failure of any system critical to flight is that it must not occur more than once in a billion flight hours — which means such a failure is not expected to occur in the life of the fleet. So the 787 battery-safety requirement that assumed a failure once every 10 million flight hours — 100 times more frequently — is already a low bar by FAA standards, he said. Hersman said the NTSB will “examine the safety certification process used by both the FAA and Boeing for the 787 battery design and determine why the hazards identified in this investigation were not mitigated.” Root cause sought The NTSB still hasn’t identified the cause of the initial short circuit Looks like the FAA has some explaining to do. NTSB called them out. Too bad they went with passive monitoring rather than active control (i.e. Tesla's battery cooling system). There will be no weight savings over NiMH if they have to add that, which they should have done in the first place. Hindsight's damned expensive in the airplane manufacturing business When all is said and done, including compensation to carriers with grounded aircraft, this will be a costly lesson for Boeing on their ill-considered rush to outsource, and as with any large corporation, those aresponsible for this debacle need to take the fall. That is why the 2 billion stock buy back is in full protect the stock price for as long as the money holds out, if the stock price drops enough then the CEO’s job is on the line, for those who are asking why the stock price has held as well as it has so far. The last time this much disaster happened Phil Condit lost his job.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360597143838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360597495074-39</Id><Topic><Title>America owes communists $1.2 Trillion...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360593531054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it will continue to increase under Obama until the govt goes under. Liberalism/fascism goes under unless they continue to increase the debt spending hard working folks' money.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360597495074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:44:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360597634744-40</Id><Topic><Title>America owes communists $1.2 Trillion...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360593531054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course they are better at being capitalists. They've got mountains of our dollars buying up our debt. Obama is destroying the value of the dollar that they hold..So?...they invest it in our real estate, housing etc. When Obama, and the leftists are thrown from power, the eocnomy recovers, the Chinese will be holding valueable US assets.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360597634744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:47:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360597776652-41</Id><Topic><Title>California lacks doctors to meet demand of Obamacare...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360594429908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:53:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What decent DR. would want to go through the time, and debt to become a DR. and then practice medicine in California, or even in much of the USA? First off, it turns you into a #$%$ to make ends meet, and there will be lots of corruption.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360597776652</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:49:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360598025403-42</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup, you are the "idiot of the day".</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1360598025403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:53:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360599456629-43</Id><Title>Tax Avoidance is Perfectly Legal</Title><Msg>If you've ever got money back after filing your tax return, you've engaged in tax avoidance. If you've ever used itemized deductions, you've engaged in tax avoidance. It's perfectly legal as long as you obey they law. Our tax system with over 50,000 pages of rules and regulations was designed by Democrats and RINO Republicans to allow some classes of people to avoid taxes that other classes of people can't avoid in order to by votes and campaign donations from the favored classes. They have done this from 1913 forward. The more complex they can make the system the more it favors rich guys like myself and big corporations like GE who can afford to take advantage of the complexity of the system's design. After giving huge donations to Obama and Democrats GE was able to pay ZERO taxes on over $ 5billion of profits. This happens with thousands of huge corporations and many wealth individuals Less sophisticated people and small businesses are left to pay what they owe plus the taxes not paid by more successful tax avoiders. That's the way the system is designed to work. The Amazing thing is, their propaganda has absolutely convinced the ignorant and naive masses of people this is all in the interest of the preserving and growing the mediocre class. The system assuages their jealousy and envy by making the masses think the system is designed to hurt and punish high income achievers. Meanwhile we rich guys keep getting richer and the mediocre income achievers keep sinking lower on the food chain and the politicians can keep taking the votes of the ignorant and naive for granted. What a system?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599456629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599466664-44</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Headed off a Cliff</Title><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360591797548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:09:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody with half a brain, and was short this stock, would cover in a hurry. The stock price is holding very steady even with all the uncertainty surrounding the investigation. A true nightmare for shorts. Will love to see the burning pants on fire as soon as the grounding is lifted.</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1360599466664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599480078-45</Id><Topic><Title>787 Dreamliner : You can not fix what you do not understand</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581802613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:23:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Progress in the past 4 weeks = Zero</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360599480078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:18:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599601200-46</Id><Topic><Title>Make no mistake. We are Greece.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360551143640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only that, but the Pope is part of the conspiracy and probably got exposed by Sheriff Joe and WND. The Vatican is hiding the Kenyan birth certificate from Sparty and Orly Taitz and Trump and Willard and Santorum and Gingrich and Batsh*t Bachmann.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1360599601200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599618671-47</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look in the mirror for the real idiot. Yep that would be you floy!</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1360599618671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:20:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599781419-48</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Avoidance is Perfectly Legal</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599456629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs got money back that didn't even file! They had no taxes to pay, but yet libs insisted they get a rebate just as folks that paid in got a 10% rebate under the Bush stimulus plan. Everyone that paid in got a 10% rebate. That seemed very fair to Republicans, but libs insisted folks that didn't pay in also get money back! ..called corrupt lib reasoning. And the rebates stimulated the economy so well that it began the longest, and strongest economic growth period in our nation's history.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360599781419</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:23:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599789108-49</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, "The founding fathers did not have skeet shooting in mind when they wrote the Second Amendment to the Constitution." A look at the third amendment will give you some concept as to what the founding fathers really had in mind: "No Soldier shall, in time of peace be quartered in any house, without the consent of the Owner, nor in time of war, but in a manner to be prescribed by law." They were more concerned about oppressive government than occasional nut cases. For good reason: "It was around 5 a.m. in Torrance on Thursday and police from nearby El Segundo had seen a pickup truck exit a freeway and head in the general direction of the Redbeam Avenue residence of a high-ranking Los Angeles police official, which was being guarded by a group of LAPD officers. As the vehicle approached the house, officers opened fire, unloading a barrage of bullets into the back of the truck. When the shooting stopped, they quickly realized their mistake. The truck was not a Nissan Titan, but a Toyota Tacoma. The color wasn't gray, but aqua blue. And it wasn't Dorner inside the truck, but a woman and her mother delivering copies of the Los Angeles Times...Police were on the lookout for Christopher Jordan Dorner, a disgruntled ex-cop suspected of hunting down members of the LAPD and their families in a twisted campaign of revenge." (from L.A. Times). No questions. No "come out with your hands up" Etc. Just open fire. Wrong truck type, wrong color, wrong people (two old Hispanic women, not a 300 lb black dude). Hooz, you and the rest of the liberals try to make the case that we should be able to implicitly "trust" the government into "taking care of us"; therefore all we might need are guns for sport and the threat of a single intruder. The government authorities "get it wrong" and there is a limp-wristed apology.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1360599789108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:23:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599929801-50</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Avoidance is Perfectly Legal</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599456629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir(de) is most thankful for the Earned Income Tax Credit. The only real tax "advantage" to him and his family.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1360599929801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:25:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360599943044-51</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're very useful if needed to fulfill our duty to overthrow a government that becomes abusive to citizens.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599943044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:25:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360600331497-52</Id><Topic><Title>Make no mistake. We are Greece.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360551143640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 21:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What there is no mistake about is how liberals are perfectily happy to see the country go into BK, and the health and welfare of all Americans be destroyed...just so their elitist liberals stay in power.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360600331497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:32:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360600333015-53</Id><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Msg>Awesomeness !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360600333015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:32:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360600391706-54</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Avoidance is Perfectly Legal</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599456629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surely you're not insinuating people can spend the money they earn better than the politician can spend it are you?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360600391706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:33:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360600779362-55</Id><Title>Why the Rich Keep Getting Richer</Title><Msg>The secret to wealth creation is to always produce more than you consume. The rich keep getting rich because they keep doing what made them rich, The poor who stay poor stay poor because they keep doing what made them poor. The mediocre class......never mind......just keep gulping the kool-aid.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360600779362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:39:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360600861655-56</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Rich Keep Getting Richer</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360600779362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. That post is like all of your other posts. Useless.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1360600861655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:41:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360601272342-57</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'They're very useful if needed to fulfill our duty to overthrow a government that becomes abusive to citizens.' I'm betting on the government.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1360601272342</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:47:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360601603689-58</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very helpful info, thank you</Msg><Username>leohaynes674</Username><Timestamp>1360601603689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:53:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360602269609-59</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing solves battery problem! Hires Energizer Bunny!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360359667150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 16:41:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many bunnies will it take to power one Nightmare liner? How many bunnies in total? Can Everready breed them fast enough? Also what about the noise from those drums?</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1360602269609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:04:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360602412251-60</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both that truck shooting and the storming of an apartment building are incidents for which law enforcement will not be finished apologizing for and paying for. They may have had a warrant for going into that apartment building, but if they did, the judge granted it too liberally. We all knew the shooting of that truck was a foolish mistake from the instant we heard about it. Dorner killed 3 people. Sad to say, 3 people are killed often and everywhere. It is no reason to panic. Law enforcement has been in panic mode. No one needs law enforcement to be in panic mode. Do you think the answer was for the paper delivery to respond with AK 47 fire?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360602412251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:06:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360602457029-61</Id><Title>Questions about Boeing's new battery solution</Title><Msg>If they are going to use the Everready Energizer bunnies, I have some questions. Who will be the CBE (Chief Bunny Engineer)? How many bunnies does it take to power a Nightmareliner? How many in total for them all? Can Eveready breed enough fast enough? And what about the noise from those drums?</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360602457029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:07:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360602655215-62</Id><Topic><Title>Sally Jewel, Obama's total hypocracy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1360544823565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:07:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strangely, most of the members and shoppers at REI are fairly wealthy, not due to socialism. The thing that REI members have in common is love of outdoors and environment, not socialism.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360602655215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:10:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360603184267-63</Id><Topic><Title>Sally Jewel, Obama's total hypocracy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1360544823565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:07:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over 2,000 companies got waivers from ObamaCare. Basically what you had to do was tell Obama lots of layoffs would take place if they were forced to comply with ObamaCare. And that is a big reason the economy is shrinking. Favortism for some, and not for others.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360603184267</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:19:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360603979385-64</Id><Topic><Title>Karl Rove says he directed the 1980 Reagan campaign in Texas. Oops.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360600342658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:32:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rove needs to go. He's a disaster for everyone.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360603979385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360604272189-65</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Rich Keep Getting Richer</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360600779362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Warren Buffett has been carrying water for Obama for years. The pay-off, he owns billion of dollars worth of Bank Stocks . Mr. Buffett leaned long ago the best investment he could consistently make was buying politicians. This knowledge has served him well financially. It's the main reason he and a number of the super rich are Democrats. They are all investors looking for bargains. Democrat politicians are cheaper, easier to buy, more immoral and therefore better investments. They don't mind at all taking the money of hard working Americans and giving it to large banks and corporations owned by the super wealthy.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360604272189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:37:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360604467931-66</Id><Topic><Title>787 Dreamliner : You can not fix what you do not understand</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581802613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:23:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was once told by a plant manager that anyone could design an airplane wing. That's funny because he couldn't, but I guess he could take credit for having done it, which at Boeing is even better than doing something. That is just the way they roll at Boeing.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1360604467931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:41:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360604559804-67</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus getting a head start on looking at an alternatie battery and 787 stuff</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360530319433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:05:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On February 6 I suggested to a wise guy, Boeing Financial message board user who said I should have told him a year ago about WNR. I had just sold WNR after a one year gain of 100% and had compared WNR to Boeing for a year and showed how any Boeing investor had made nothing. (BTW WNR is up 29% YTD but in a short term top out correction so I am out and I did go into ZNGA,) So, after I explained to Mr. Fartz, how a chart user can handicap stock trades and why it would not help him unless he first learns how to use a stock chart to trade. Mr. Fartz, came back to me with the second wise guy statement, that he had actually sold his Boeing stock two weeks prior to making his wise guy comment, So I suggested on that date, February 6th that he should be invested back into the stock market with a better short term stock until he figures what long term stock like WNR he should get into . I suggested that Mr. Fartz might take a look at ZNGA and then( Feb 6, 2013). So Mr. Fartz, . ZNGA when I left my reply for you to consider off on February 6th I posted “ ZNGA is up another 6% in after market trade( 11% total) , in 2 week since you sold your BA” Feb 6, Mr Fartz that was Feb 6( $2.99 close) today it is up another 20% at $3.61, in just 3 more trade days ! I have 6 Boeing fast response team haters on me( FBI), they hate me . Please follow me; on my user comments and get out of Boeing stock, you may get some great stock picks if you read me. You will have to go below the subject title to a follow up comment to find them. Mr Fartz, , you just missed a 31% gain since I made mention of ZNGA( do your own research ) and the stock is up 52% year to date. Do not read or accept the Boeing FBI team (six haters), spin cycle, cool aid and dog and pony show it is all BS. Any investor can make money following me or just buy and hold one of the major averages, please remember that Boeing, the stock, for one year now is up less than 2%. Boeing is not a buy or a sale it is a dead cat stock for a year flat. . No investor should own or support the Boeing Management team in Chicago which you do when you own any Boeing stock. Do not vote yes for the BOD or the Boeing CEO until they are replaced; Boeing should be a no buy stock Remember Boeing CEO pay is up 34% from last year and every year he has given himself a huge pay raise since he was hired by a guy with zero aerospace experience Lewis Platt the Boeing CEO has a fully funded pension of 22 million, in return the shareholder get less than 2% for the year. Do not support weak performance standards for the CEO and miss other better stock investment opportunities lost by staying with Boeing stock. Move on.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360604559804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:42:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360604675382-68</Id><Topic><Title>Questions about Boeing's new battery solution</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360602457029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:07:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about PETA, the stop cruelty to animals group? Won't they object? Will teh bunnies have their own oxygen masks?</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1360604675382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:44:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360604713389-69</Id><Topic><Title>Questions about Boeing's new battery solution</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360602457029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:07:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will the AFLAC duck insure them?</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1360604713389</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:45:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360604798594-70</Id><Topic><Title>787 Dreamliner : You can not fix what you do not understand</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581802613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:23:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you expect? They farmed this all out to TURD world countries with young punks over a solid, knowledgeable American work force!</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360604798594</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:46:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360604811932-71</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Rich Keep Getting Richer</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360600779362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blogoyovich was pretty cheap.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360604811932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:46:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360604840120-72</Id><Title>If you like BA at $76, you will love it at $46</Title><Msg>because this stock is building into a massive sell off when investors realize (maybe too late) that the 787 Dreamliner problems are long term serious, possibly unrepairable (under current configuration) and months away from being acknowledged and addressed in accordance to FAA standards. But the far bigger problems is BA now will show no profit on any 787 sold over the next two years due to shipment delays, huge (delayed) shipment penalty fees, out of pocket compensation to current airlines whose 787 are useless and massive back up orders due to plane grounding. And if that ain't bad enough in a month or two the Pentagon is going to kick BA between the legs with massive defense cuts that will cause company layoffs and more company turmoil.</Msg><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360604840120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:47:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360605078469-73</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Avoidance is Perfectly Legal</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599456629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ignorant people are very entertaining. The more you expose how ignorant they are the more names they'll call you, the more lies they'll resort to and the louder they get with name calling. The extent they'll go to in order to maintain denial of being totally duped, is hilarious.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360605078469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:51:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360605114003-74</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No one needs law enforcement to be in panic mode." That is true. There is an obvious bias on the part of the police when they think that they are under attack. LAPD Chief Beck was almost apologetic when he announced the "unprecedented" $1 million reward leading to capture/arrest of Dorner and he rationalized: "This is the largest local reward ever offered to our knowledge ... Some may ask, ‘Why so large’” he continued, adding, “This is an act — and make no mistake about it — of domestic terrorism." He went on to opine about the sacrifice of officers, which I totally agree. There is no fair way to put this: double standard, yet we understand and empathize. California had about 1000 police officers involved in search and protection. They need to get this guy and wipe him off the face of the planet ASAP. "Do you think the answer was for the paper delivery to respond with AK 47 fire?" Of course not, but the police did not follow procedure and the incident illustrated what I was trying to say is that the government can lose control of itself and overwhelm the citizens with their greater fire power. Whether that was by mistake or by design. The Second Amendment ot the Constitution was written to protect both the individual and the "free State": "A well regulated Militia, being necessary to the security of a free State, the right of the people to keep and bear Arms, shall not be infringed." Notice that it does not say anything about a "foreign" enemy. Is that to be "assumed" or did the founding fathers acknowledge that the threat can be from without and within?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1360605114003</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:51:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360605694103-75</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't bet of the government. It can't even control the south side of Chicago or the border between Juarez and El Paso much less a bunch of angry gun tote'n REAL AMERICANS.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360605694103</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:01:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360606712443-76</Id><Topic><Title>New CBO Report Shows Social Security Trust Fund Worse Than Thought</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360591261508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:01:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it still true that the only thing wrong with socialism or entitlement is that you eventually run out of other people's money to spend?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360606712443</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360606737394-77</Id><Topic><Title>If you like BA at $76, you will love it at $46</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360604840120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:47:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can Boeing stock surge (if 787 problems corrected) if the stock's 52 week high was $78 a share before the Dreamliner (battery) went up in smoke? Just curious how you see this stock jumping past $78 when it was trading at that level when the Dreamliner was thought to be the next best thing to sliced bread? Seems if BA (claims) they can fix things BA stock maybe goes back to $78 but we still have the defense cuts coming to all major defense companies.</Msg><Username>hold4triple</Username><Timestamp>1360606737394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:18:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360607232954-78</Id><Topic><Title>400,000 guns enter America illegally every year</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1360606647173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So lets just say #$%$ it and do nothing and sit back and watch Americans be slaughtered the Republicans agenda on everything. DO NOTHING</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360607232954</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:27:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360607691388-79</Id><Title>BA at 80.00 by the first of March</Title><Msg>Back in the air sooner than that...</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360607691388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:34:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360608715511-80</Id><Title>one of the greatest american companys still left...</Title><Msg>787 will be flying again soon..</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360608715511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:51:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360608791229-81</Id><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Msg>From: Davaz, Dennis D Sent: Friday, February 08, 2013 6:16 PM To: Rogers, Kyle R Subject: SPEEA: Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer? Hi Kyle, Good question! For others receiving this note, read Kyle’s question at the bottom, then pop back here for the answer. Most of this is my strike story from 2000, but there’s other good stuff in here, too. I’m Dennis Davaz, a Fabrication Division Core Quality investigator in the SPEEA Technical Bargaining Unit. I work at the Everett site, but report through Fab, and right now I’m supporting our FOD implementation across the Fab MBUs. I’m currently a SPEEA Area Rep in District E14 (bldgs 40-21 &amp; -22), but back during the 40-day strike in 2000 I was the SPEEA Council Rep for the Boeing facility in Spokane (which has since been sold to Triumph). I know SPEEA has recently put out several statements at how many “best and final offers” didn’t end up being best or final back then. The rule of thumb is no matter what the company says, it’s never a best or final offer until we accept it. Boeing executives and Mike Delaney have made a weird statement that they “didn’t leave anything on the table” – I’m sure they meant to say “we put everything we possibly can on the table” in their offer – meaning they aren’t still holding onto any improvements that they can make to this offer if we do reject it and go on strike. Of course that’s not true – it’s a bluff that all companies make. I think the metaphor they were trying for is similar to the football adage to “leave it all on the field” – don’t walk off the field with any reserve of effort you didn’t spend to win the game – but I think they got it wrong. I’m assuming you must be one of the folks who have hired into Boeing since 2000 and weren’t here yourself or weren’t in a SPEEA-represented position back then so may not have followed the play-by-play as closely as those of us who were hip-deep in it. People who did experience the strike in 2000 are supposed to have been telling their stories to the newer folks for just this purpose – to let them know that our contract offer got significantly better and a strike isn’t really as scary as it seems. Back then was the first time I had noticed that the company would cut benefits to the exempt and non-represented employees a year or two ahead of time in order to make the case that they’re just trying to make the benefits the same for all employees. They can get away with imposing cuts onto exempt or non-represented employees and there’s nothing those employees can do about it. But the company has to convince us to accept a contract offer with cuts in it. Back in 2000 the Boeing Negotiation Team tried to get concessions from the IAM, but they weren’t going to budge and started preparing for a strike. The company couldn’t afford one back then either, so Phil Condit intervened and gave the IAM a much better offer with a nice bonus as a carrot. They accepted. SPEEA members had bought into the narrative that we would usually get a fraction of whatever the IAM got – the crumbs left over – and the managers and non-represented employees would get whatever table scraps were left by us. That was just after the McDonald Douglas merger, and we heard that Harry Stonecipher berated Phil about giving in to labor, and he said he would handle the SPEEA negotiation and “show him how to deal with labor”. Our original offer was ugly (though not as bad as the original offer we got this time), but no one thought SPEEA had the balls to really go out on strike. It was rejected by a really high percentage then, too, but lots of people thought we were going to get railroaded into accepting that a bad deal anyway. The second offer we got just shifted the take aways from one thing to another. SPEEA had commissioned independent surveys, and most of our members were responding that they would only support a strike for a week or two before having to cross the picket line and come back to work. SPEEA leaders rightly feared that even a modest strike would end up breaking the union. But then a miracle happened: Harry opened his mouth and showed his contempt for the engineers. He said that “engineers would just have to realize that they weren’t the center of the universe anymore.” It was signaling a big shift in the company from what had been an aerospace engineering-centric, manufacturing-industrial powerhouse toward a MBA-centric, “bean-counters make all the rules” entity. It didn’t matter whether we were building airplanes or selling coffee – business is business, and it’s all about the Benjamins. Back then we had an open shop – you weren’t required to be a member (and thus pay dues) if you were in a SPEEA-represented job. There were lots of free-loaders who didn’t pay dues but got the benefits of the contract and union representation anyway. But when Stonecipher treated the engineering community with such contempt, a majority were so offended that they signed up in droves. The typical membership percentages in the Puget Sound region pre-foot-in-mouth was about 30-some percent – at Spokane it was closer to 50%. Shortly after Harry’s statement, membership in PS doubled to 60-70%, and in Spokane we had 100% of the SPEEA-represented employees signed up as dues-paying members. The negotiations issues had become about basic respect – or the lack of it that the company was demonstrating to the engineers. That’s why you still hear Ray Goforth and others still using that “it’s about Respect” phrase today – to hearken back to what worked in 2000. We were an untested and unproven group back then, and the company had the same data that only some of us would go out on strike, and those that did wouldn’t stay out for long, so they expected they would stomp us good. Our SPEEA Negotiation Team actually recommended to accept the offer! – I think that was a concession coerced by the company that in order to lift the offer from the table and take it to the membership for a vote, the SPEEA Negotiation Team at the time had to endorse the offer – slimy tactic by the company, I know. But by then the membership was just too pissed off. When we did go out it was a major event – people lined the aisle ways and cheered. Many of those that didn’t walk out the first day came out and joined us during that first week, even non-members walked out. Our movement grew stronger rather than weaker over time. Once people were out they discovered it wasn’t as bad as they feared. Then no one wanted to be the first to give in and cross the picket line. If people were hurting or had special needs, each of us pitched in to help out so they didn’t have to cross the line. And we got all kinds of support from the IAM, other unions, and the general public. Even though we were getting better exercise by walking the line, people gained weight because of all the donuts and pizza people dropped off. We had people showing up for picket duty when they weren’t even scheduled because it turned into such a party atmosphere. There were guys who would fire up the barbeque to make pancakes, eggs, &amp; bacon every morning. People would bring guitars or other instruments and sing around the burn barrel. It was awesome. Our mantra became “how long are we going to stay out? – one day longer than necessary to get a good offer.” When we passed the 30-day mark and people had already been missing out on pay days, we still didn’t break. Back then Boeing had delivery contracts with more airlines that had strike escape clauses in them: if Boeing had late deliveries there were steep penalties, unless it was due to a work stoppage lasting over 40 days, then the penalty was dropped. That meant that any strike that resulted in any late deliveries was likely to go at least 40 days so Boeing could at least not pay the penalties. Airlines have gotten wise to this ploy and that provision has been removed from most of the contracts – they knew Boeing was posturing for strikes as excuses to drop penalties on deliveries that would have been late anyway. The airlines don’t care what we do or don’t get in our contract, they just want Boeing to have happy employees getting out good quality airplanes on schedule. Boeing won’t reduce the list price of an airplane if the labor costs are reduced, so they don’t care how much we get out of the profit – they just want a good plane, and they know happy employees are more likely to get them one. That’s why Moral was on the QCDSM metrics scale. [That’s Quality, Cost, Delivery, Safety, and Morale.] What brought the 2000 strike to a head was pressure from the U.S. government because of the trade deficit, from the FAA in particular because Boeing was using unqualified managers to fulfill the Designated Engineering Representative (DER) role – which is equivalent to the AR role now for certifying planes as airworthy – and from the airlines themselves. We weren’t budging, and if anything we were growing more adamant with each day, and each day we were ratcheting up pressure on the company. We finally got a contract offer that was way better than any of us thought we could possibly get and which replaced all the take aways Boeing was trying to strong-arm from us. I believe the acceptance percentage of that offer was somewhere around 78% - higher than a union activist wants an accept percentage to be because that telegraphs to the company that they gave in too much. A company is always looking to provide a contract offer that will be approved by just barely over 50%, meaning they got a contract approved as inexpensively as they could. On the contrary, a union doesn’t want too high an acceptance percentage, because that just means they’ll have to fight that much harder next time to keep the same contract provisions. After we came back from the strike I even had managers from the inside pull me aside and congratulate me for a well-run strike. We got what we wanted, no one got hurt, we came back with no hard feelings so we could all get back to work productively, and we gained universal respect – just what we said we wanted. The IAM was proud of the stand we took, along with many other outside unions. It was only a short time later that we affiliated with the IFPTE, which gave us a connection to the AFL-CIO, which meant we were no longer just an association – we were a real union, on par with the IAM &amp; Teamsters. We also had a majority of us as dues paying members, so we had the ability to institute an Agency Fee, which meant everyone had to pay dues unless they were a Beck Objector – no more free loaders! I think most importantly we gained some self-respect – none of us thought it was possible, and even our union leadership was timid about it, but we surprised everyone, even ourselves. It was the biggest white-collar strike ever, and we had been successful. After we got settled, the company also was shamed into improving the salary increases and benefits for the exempt and non-represented employees – in fairness Boeing had to retract what they had originally imposed on them since both the IAM and SPEEA had avoided the same concessions. There were lots of those employees who thanked us for holding the line on benefit erosion. That was my experience and is my recollection of events – though I’m sure there was an entire range of experiences for various people. Back then Boeing was saying the same thing, that if we didn’t make drastic concessions we would not be competitive and Airbus would walk away with the market. Now it’s 12 years later and Boeing is stronger than ever. Boeing says that they’ll outsource to cheaper sources of labor if we don’t give in – but they’re doing that anyway everywhere they can and in some cases with work that they shouldn’t. In lots of cases they’re ending up paying more in the long run. Boeing is playing on our insecurities in order for us to willingly choose to work for less, no matter how successful our business is. They’re following the GE model of Management by Stress (see attached). Kyle, I remember other sharp but concerned guys saying the same thing back in 1999/2000: “what if we go out on strike and take the financial hit, only to come back and take the same offer?” This isn’t the first dance for our negotiation team. We’re not untested anymore. A strike authorization is a tool they need to get a better offer that they think they can get from the company without a strike! Boeing’s primary goal in this negotiation was to start the process for ridding itself of the pension for both unions (SPEEA &amp; IAM), just like lots of other corporations (GE, IBM, et. al.) are doing successfully. The PR campaign they’re waging is a significant investment to achieve that goal. But their primary responsibility as a company is to make the most money they can. The immediate savings on day one of the current contract offer is nothing – it’s only after years of hiring new employees under the 401(k) that they’ll see a difference at all, and that will only be the delta between what the pension would have cost them and what the 401(k) would end up costing them. It’s not a huge difference. Tangent: they keep talking about how they’ll use that money for R&amp;D – first off, don’t believe it; and second, what kind of company tells it’s employees “we’re buying back stock to make our own stock more valuable, we’re giving larger dividends to shareholders, we’re giving massive increases and bonuses to our executives, profits have never been better, and damn it, business is just so good we want bigger profit margins – but the only way we can pay for R&amp;D and future development programs is by taking money away from future engineers and techs – money that would have gone to a better pension for them will be our investment for future business. If people want a job bad enough in this sluggish job recovery, they’ll take it no matter how bad an offer it is!” If there was any chance that was true, it would be flat out evil. Even the lame excuses they’re giving us aren’t credible. But a work stoppage at a time when our 787 fleet is grounded and costing bazillions each day, not to mention the impact to our other priorities this year (new development programs, rate increases, etc.), would be HUGE. I mean even bigger than Donald Trump “huge”. The Board of Directors won’t allow it. Boeing will bring forward a better offer before a strike takes place. Also, when the IAM goes out on strike it’s a clean break: everything shuts down when they stop work and then it all fires right back up again when they come back to work. When SPEEA goes out on strike it unloads the production system – the IAM bleeds out as much work as they can out of the hopper and loads up a bunch of backlog for us. When we come back in, it take months to recover and get back to healthy equilibrium in the production system. We would lose productivity and effectiveness for a year at our current production levels, let alone having no progress on new programs and rate increases. A common metaphor is that if Boeing production is a car, the IAM is the gas: if there’s no gas you don’t go anywhere; add gas and you’re back on the road – and SPEEA is the oil: if you’re low on oil, you can keep driving, but you’re risking much greater damage. Boeing absolutely can’t afford to let us go out on strike – they would suffer many times over the extent we would. So I think if it really comes down to it and we force the issue, Boeing would have no choice but to keep the pension in place for now because they want to stay in business more than they want to get rid of the pension. Ray Conner and others keep saying “no one wins in a strike”, and they’re right – a strike is the utter break-down of the negotiations process. SPEEA wants to win a better contract offer without having to resort to a strike, but with the company playing hard-ball I can’t guarantee it won’t come down to a work stoppage. If union-represented employees want to avoid concessions when they’re not warranted, occasionally they have to strike and take the personal economic loss to prove to the company that they’re serious and willing to do so – it’s the cost of doing business in order to get the better pay and benefits that union-represented jobs can garner. We don’t ever earn that money back, but we keep our benefits from being eroded, which is worth money on into the future. My answer to “no one wins in a strike” is that you never get back what you give away by accepting a take away contract offer, either. We can win the privilege to keep our pay and benefits honestly market-leading by occasionally investing the cost of lost pay while we’re on strike. The Boeing Company wants you to think you’d be sacrificing your pay for someone else’s (the new hire’s) benefits – that’s how they’re dividing us in order to conquer all. If they’re successful in shifting new hires to 401(k), it’s a guarantee that they’ll end up freezing the pension for the rest of us in the not too distant future. This concession is targeted at the rest of us, too, just not yet – but it’ll be inevitable if we give in now. This might be fun: if you’re familiar with Texas Hold ‘Em, the negotiations process up to this point is like we’ve seen the Flop and we’ve got a good hand, but Boeing is the Big Stack and they’re bluffing - trying to intimidate us into folding before seeing the Turn. The price to see the River card would be us actually walking out on strike. For us to call we’ve got to reject the offer and authorize a strike in order to see the Turn card. Rejecting an offer and authorizing the strike to “see the card” costs us nothing – we’re not actually going out on strike yet, just saying we would in order to see the next offer. Of course there’s another offer available – the money is too good in aerospace for Boeing to fold and quit doing business. If we fold by accepting the offer or not authorizing a strike sanction, Boeing will rake in the pot and chuckle to itself that it successfully bullied us into giving up a winning hand. And they know that once they’ve detected weakness they don’t need to play to get the best cards in future hands – they just keep on psyching out the other player. I wouldn’t be surprised if others would come up with slightly different analogy descriptions on this, but hopefully it helps make the point. I must be Jonesing for a game. Here’s something else we need to consider: if Boeing does reinstate the pension for new hires but takes back some other provision in the current offer that costs us more than what the 401(k) option would have cost new hires, technically they’re giving in on what we said was important to us but giving us the back of their hand at the same time. Advantage Boeing. It’ll be harder for us to keep playing Whack-a-Take-Away from offer to offer and not lose the support we have now. Hopefully Boeing will realize that it only has so many chances before they run out of time, too. We want an offer with no take aways and protection from things getting worse for us through Congressional legislative action – just that simple. We reject the notion that we have to give in on anything and lose out in order to reach a compromise. There’s no reason for us to compromise anything – we’re not overcompensated. I know that’s way more than you asked for, but I hope it helps. I like sharing the strike story in that much detail because it really is a source of pride for all of us. Those of us from Spokane all mostly got along pretty well as coworkers in a small shop before the strike, but our bonds of friendship were well-forged by the burn barrel during those 40 days on the picket line and we’re all still close friends to this day. Hope you don’t mind if I share this question and answer with others, because I’ll wager others are wondering the same thing. Dennis Davaz Dist E14 SPEEA Area Rep 425-931-9316 From: Rogers, Kyle R Sent: Friday, February 08, 2013 5:51 AM To: Nowlin, Dan C Subject: RE: New videos explain contract offers and recommendations (and a personal appeal) Dan, The one thing she does not state in this appeal is whether or not in 2000 the “Best and Final Offers” got any better. The risk I see is going on a 40 day walk out and not garnering any more benefits that what we were already offered. If Boeing doesn’t want to pay a pension benefit they won’t, they will hire engineers in a non-union environment. I agree we need to show strength but I just want to be certain it is not a foolish display. If you could inform me about the progress made in 2000 it would make me and my colleagues feel much better about putting our families in this potential predicament. Thanks, Kyle R. Rogers</Msg><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360608847441-82</Id><Topic><Title>New CBO Report Shows Social Security Trust Fund Worse Than Thought</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360591261508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 09:01:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who`s money pays social security? and since when has Social Security been an entitlement?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360608847441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:54:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360609970889-83</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. Let's say everyone can have all the machine guns they want as long as the guns never leave the house. No packing them around on the off chance the government decides to oppress us. Anyone caught transporting one before Oppression has been declared is in violation of the law.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360609970889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:12:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360609989668-84</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Rich Keep Getting Richer</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360600779362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you are one ignorant UNAmerican</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1360609989668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:13:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360610349715-85</Id><Topic><Title>400,000 guns enter America illegally every year</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1360606647173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and most of those guns are attached to illegal immigrant mexicans</Msg><Username>goatshit28</Username><Timestamp>1360610349715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:19:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360610441685-86</Id><Topic><Title>Questions about Boeing's new battery solution</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360602457029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:07:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don;t know. Maybe?</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360610441685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360610482744-87</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Avoidance is Perfectly Legal</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599456629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent description of how the tax system is designed. The rich folks should thank the middle class for being such suckers......but they wouldn't understand anyway.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360610482744</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:21:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360610685891-88</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Rich Keep Getting Richer</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360600779362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Useless to you because it's too complicated for you to understand.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360610685891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360610892640-89</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Reagan ever own a business during a riot where hundreds of people trying to burn it to the ground? Reagan was a nice man from an era where people were civil. He could never have envisioned the rapid growth drug gangs, rape groups and Muslim domestic terrorists groups, etc that have proliferated today. Obama is a defective human being Hooz. He is a practitioner of absolute corruption, a liar who helped to develop and sustain the "killing fields" in Chicago. The fact that you find solace in his "tweet a twit dependent on government tit" musings makes you a disingenuous clown. Har Har Har.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360610892640</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:28:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360611074063-90</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Avoidance is Perfectly Legal</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599456629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Our tax system with over 50,000 pages of rules and regulations was designed by Democrats and RINO Republicans" Your 'logic' is laughable. Hey, where's rover?</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1360611074063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360611202021-91</Id><Title>This is Scary - Six/seven weeks after ground 787 BA has no clue</Title><Msg>and probably won't know the cause of multiple problems for several months. Say goodbye to $76 today and hello to upper $60's by Wednesday. If any doubt with that position hen read this.. In an annual filing on Monday, Boeing Co. said it is too soon to estimate how much the 787 problems will cost. The financial impact will depend on what the cause turns out to be, how long it takes to find it, and the fix required to get 787s flying commercially again, the company said. Not a clue after almost two months of head scratching. BA investor panic soon to kick in.</Msg><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1360611202021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:33:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360611712237-92</Id><Title>Obamacare is a Disaster</Title><Msg>Minimum insurance will soon cost the average family of four $20,000 a year and then after paying all that money you may still have to wait months to see a doctor. Somehow the brilliant minds that crafted Obamacare forgot to include doctors in the equations. Sure glad you liberals don't mind paying all that extra money for longer wait times and poorer accces to medical care. You really doner good with that'n.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360611712237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:41:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360612539785-93</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus getting a head start on looking at an alternatie battery and 787 stuff</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360530319433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:05:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McNerney (and most of the BOD) should resign (nobody ever gets fired for poor performance) and replaced with people who have airplane experience. Stock is going nowhere (except maybe down) until they get their act together.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360612539785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 14:55:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360613182318-94</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing solves battery problem! Hires Energizer Bunny!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360359667150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 16:41:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the drum is necessary to generating power.</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360613182318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:06:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360613763057-95</Id><Title>$20, 000 a year for Med. Insurance and you still can't see a Doctor</Title><Msg>......just brilliant Democrats......just brilliant. Oh yea.....maybe we should have talked to the people who are actually doing the doctoring.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360613763057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:16:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614032357-96</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Number 5 is flying now.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360614032357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:20:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360614502601-97</Id><Title>Obama: Job of debt reduction nearly done</Title><Msg>One thing you won’t hear when President Obama delivers his State of the Union address Tuesday: An ambitious new plan to rein in the debt. In recent days, the White House has pressed the message that, if policymakers can agree on a strategy for replacing across-the-board spending cuts set to hit next month, the president will pretty much have achieved his debt-reduction goals. “Over the last few years, Democrats and Republicans have come together and cut our deficit [over the next decade] by more than $2.5 trillion through a balanced mix of spending cuts and higher tax rates for the wealthiest Americans. That’s more than halfway towards the $4 trillion in deficit reduction that economists and elected officials from both parties say we need to stabilize our debt,” Obama said during his weekend radio address. By the administration’s math, Washington needs to enact only another $1.5 trillion in 10-year savings to hit the $4 trillion target, White House economic adviser Jason Furman told reporters last week. At $1.2 trillion, the automatic cuts, known as the sequester, quite nearly fit the bill. The problem with this scenario? It would indeed stabilize the national debt, compared with the broader economy, for the next 10 years. But the debt would fluctuate between 73 percent and 77 percent of gross domestic product, according to new projections by the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office — the highest level in U.S. history except for the period after World War II. It’s also much higher than the 62 percent target policymakers were aiming for just 3 years ago when Obama appointed the Bowles-Simpson debt-reduction commission. And because policymakers have avoided reforms to the big health and retirement programs, the debt would start rising again after 2023, as the baby boom generation retires.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360614502601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:28:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614513484-98</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You didn't answer the question. Did Reagan ever have to defend himself against 30 or 40 rioters that wanted to do him or his business harm? It's a simple question you dimwit. Yes or no?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360614513484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:28:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614742678-99</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus getting a head start on looking at an alternatie battery and 787 stuff</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360530319433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:05:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You talkin' about me? I'll have you know that I am a missus and not a mister. My portfolio is doing just fine thank you, as are my chart reading skills.</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1360614742678</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:32:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360614781715-100</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Avoidance is Perfectly Legal</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360599456629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you just love it when some brilliant liberal says people who avoid paying taxes aren't patriotic and aren't paying their "FAIR SHARE."</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360614781715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:33:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360615743085-101</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By a test pilot. Not allowed to fly over people or 50 miles from a runway. Wow I am so impressed I can not wait for you fly on one.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360615743085</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:49:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360615828828-102</Id><Title>Poll: Would you fly on a Drealiner 787 in 2013?</Title><Msg>Not me. If they have a clean record maybe 2015 but I think the plane will be scrapped.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360615828828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:50:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360615904065-103</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you d...right he did and his heavily armed bodyguards were unable to prevent him from getting shot you moerawn</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360615904065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:51:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360616005409-104</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just against a deranged kook with a gun who shot him in the lung. But, that nice man shut out the lights at a high school prom when he was governor because they were playing rock music.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360616005409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:53:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360616103661-105</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The southern legislators and representatives weren't concerned about the King that's just the ignorant #$%$ big lie- they were actually concerned about their SLAVE PATROLS and being able to keep them armed so they could suppress slave revolts- these were the precursors of the COOCLUCSCLAN if you didn't know</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360616103661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:55:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360616270390-106</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>........and neither can you and your ignorant rednecks</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360616270390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:57:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360616413629-107</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Would you fly on a Drealiner 787 in 2013?</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360615828828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 15:50:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey don't sweat it art they wont ever let you ride in a 787 - you are too skrewey</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360616413629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:00:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360616770866-108</Id><Title>DoD new ruling on military benifits</Title><Msg>Penetta's new ruling has same sex spouses and live withs now eligible for military benefits. Do heterosexual live withs get military benefits? Well do they???</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1360616770866</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:06:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360616810987-109</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You hit a new low ( or should I say high ) for stupidity." You got that right about Ali_Infestation.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1360616810987</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360617033924-110</Id><Title>Using Sandy Hook To Disarm The Public Was Conceived In 1991</Title><Msg>“The government encouraged the manufacture and importation of firearms for the criminals to use. This is intended to foster a feeling of insecurity, which would lead the American people to voluntarily disarm themselves by passing laws against firearms. Using drugs and hypnosis on mental patients in a process called Orion, the CIA inculcated the desire in these people to open fire on schoolyards and thus inflame the anti-gun lobby. This plan is well under way, and so far is working perfectly. The middle class is begging the government to do away with the 2nd Amendment.” (William Cooper 1991) You have to hand to the CIA they sure know the behavioral characteristics of monkey brained progressive and far left fanatics.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360617033924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:10:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360617544247-111</Id><Title>Pelosi: We Don't Have a Spending Problem</Title><Msg>The latest bit of fiscal denialism from a high priestess of the pro-science "reality based community".... “We have to make a judgment about what -- how do we get growth with jobs, that is where the real revenue comes from. You don’t get it by…cutting your education and cutting back on investments in science and National Institutes of Health, food safety, you name it. So, it isn’t as much a spending problem as it is a priorities -- and that is what the budget is, setting priorities...So it is almost a false argument to say we have a spending problem, we have a budget deficit problem.” On one side of the aisle, we have Republicans asserting that we have a spending problem. On the other, Democrats insist that we have a revenue problem -- and that the outlays side of the equation isn't really about excessive spending, per se. The facts unambiguously demonstrate that conservatives are correct, and that liberals are either projecting deliberate dishonesty or dangerous self-delusion. What's especially mystifying is some powerful liberals' propensity to repackage the nation's spending problem as some other malady. President Obama calls it a "healthcare problem." (Well, yes, Mr. President; and a driving component of that problem is that we spend too much on healthcare, and that problem is getting worse, not better -- despite your ritual promises during the Obamacare debate). In this interview, Pelosi labels the issue a "budget deficit problem." (Well, yes, madam leader; our budget deficits are projected to remain perilously and historically high because we spend much, much more than we take in every single year). Our healthcare expenditure and budget deficit crises are by definition spending problems, a basic fact that the Left cannot fully acknowledge without reinforcing a prime argument for scaling back the scope of our rapacious government. Conservatives have spelled out America's spending problem over and over and over and over again. It's math. Rather than recapitulate all of the facts and figures, let's focus on the nonpartisan CBO's recent projections for 2023 -- just ten years from now:</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360617544247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:19:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360617697695-112</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi: We Don't Have a Spending Problem</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360617544247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One would believe that Pelosi thinks all the Hooz sheep followers are stupid, and believe what she says is true. But I thinik she is just as stupid as they are.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360617697695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:21:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360618010663-113</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Rich Keep Getting Richer</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1360600779362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My advice: If anyone here is unsatified with their financial situation, tough! It's your life! If you want something better, don't ask me to pitch in. Only you can get up off the sofa and make it happen!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360618010663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:26:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360618352743-114</Id><Topic><Title>Using Sandy Hook To Disarm The Public Was Conceived In 1991</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360617033924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:10:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of your posts are incoherent and make no sense,but you outdid yourself this time.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1360618352743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:32:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360618687297-115</Id><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 test flights since they were useless in</Title><Msg>trying to find out why the Dreamliner has defective electrical system and major battery problems. In plain English - Boeing Management decided that flying hazardous material in the sky was to risky and offer no answer for a very bleak future.</Msg><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360618687297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360618896124-116</Id><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Msg>YA cant make this up Pelosi: "We Avow The First Amendment," "People Have A Right To Have A Gun" House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi (D-Cali.) confuses the first amendment and the second amendment in an interview with Chris Wallace on FOX News Sunday today. HOUSE MINORITY LEADER NANCY PELOSI: I think that you took one piece of it. We're talking about no further sales of assault weapons. What is the justification for an assault weapon? No further sales of those, no further sales of the increased capacity, 30 rounds in a gun. We're re talking about background checks which is very popular, even among gun owners, and, hunters. We avow the First Amendment. We stand with that and say that people have a right to have a gun to protect themselves in their homes and their jobs, where, and that they -- and the workplace and that they, for recreation and hunting and the rest. So we're not questioning their right to do that. (FOX News Sunday, February 10, 2013) ++ And to think she WAS 3rd in line to be POTUS. Must be the water or the math or ??? No doubt the 2nd amendment doesnt protect YOUR right to free speech or some such of her alternate reality "we have to pass it to find out whats in it !!! "</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360619073304-117</Id><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Msg>Boeing wraps up 787 test flights for now Boeing conducted a second test flight of its 787 on Monday as it looks for the cause of battery problems that have grounded the planes. It said no more tests are currently planned. By JOSHUA FREED AP Business Writer ++ Of course if you beleive the AP on such issues . . . maybe BA is trying to save money ? do not want to expose crew to dangers ?</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360619171958-118</Id><Title>Great Entertainment - Watch Benjamin Carson Humiliate Obama and his Policies</Title><Msg>Just go to you tube an find Benjamin Carson's speech at the National Day of Prayer Breakfast Keep your eye on Obama as well as Dr. Carson. It's not only entertaining, this man is very inspiring an extremely accomplished. Unlike Obama he's actually achieved something and unlike Obama he actually knows something.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360619171958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:46:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360619537346-119</Id><Title>The Graham Cracker</Title><Msg>Chuck Hagel is a decorated combat veteran who went to the sound of the guns in defense of his country. Lindsey Graham was an Air Force lawyer who never got near the sound of the guns. As a member of the South Carolina Air National Guard Lindsey was called up during the first Gulf War,. His duties “included briefing pilots on the law of armed conflict, preparing legal documents for deploying troops, and providing legal services for family members of the South Carolina Air National Guard. ” His service never took him out of South Carolina. Lindsey boastfully claims in his bio that he has been to war but the truth is he is a shyster phony.”</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360619537346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360619539502-120</Id><Topic><Title>Great Entertainment - Watch Benjamin Carson Humiliate Obama and his Policies</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360619171958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't give Carson too much credit. Most graduates of the 5th grade can make Obama, and his policies look like a fool.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360619539502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360619548998-121</Id><Topic><Title>The Ignorance Caucus</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360587890392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 08:04:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz_beef_ dude You might want to tell Paul Krugman that Norfolk was built on a swamp that is sinking. Think of quick sand. In Krugman's irrational mind, if he stepped into quick sand he would claim the world around him was rising and then blame it on climate change. That is exactly what he is doing in this screed by saying climate change is the reason that Norfolk VA. is seeing a rise in ocean level. When the land is sinking rapidly, which it is, the tidal gauges on that land are also sinking and are no longer giving an accurate reading of actual sea level rise. It was a nice attempt though to copy and paste the thoughts of a blithering idiot that thinks everyone else is the problem.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360619548998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360619874419-122</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you? Did anyone?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360619874419</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:57:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360619962913-123</Id><Topic><Title>Will BA Bounce? SEE OUR IN DEPTH BA BOUNCE REPORT</Title><Username>kyledurham521</Username><Timestamp>1360012053563</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:07:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report</Msg><Username>raymondcooks</Username><Timestamp>1360619962913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:59:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360620060261-124</Id><Topic><Title>The Graham Cracker</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360619537346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep - chicken Hawk. Bush had a ton of them. Guys who never were in the military but really enjoyed playing soldier when they were eight years old. That in a nut shell is one of the big problems with the Republican party. They want to spend trillions on defense, but cut the legs out from under senior citizens, those on social security, those who need cost of living increases to get by as gasoline prices head back to $4 a gallon. Chaney, Romney, Karl Rove, Rumsfeld, Rice, and Graham Cracker all chicken hawks and the real reason the United States has a 17 trillion dollar deficit.</Msg><Username>youbgone</Username><Timestamp>1360620060261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:01:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360620179772-125</Id><Title>Fox's Roger Ailes: 'Obama's Too Busy Getting Middle Class To Hate Rich People, Blacks To Hate Whites'</Title><Msg>Fox News CEO Roger Ailes had some harsh words about Barack Obama recently. In an interview published by the New Republic Monday, Ailes said, "The president likes to divide people into groups." “He’s too busy getting the middle class to hate rich people, blacks to hate whites," Ailes told TNR. "He is busy trying to get everybody to hate each other.” The Daily Beast's Howard Kurtz quickly came to Obama's defense asking, "What in Obama’s record casts him as a racially divisive leader?" Really, Howie? You think race relations are better in America today than they were before Obama took office? Maybe Kurtz should read his own publication. Here's what the Daily Beast reported last April: "Back in 2008, 52 percent of Americans told Pew Research Center that they expected race relations to get better as a result of Obama’s election; only 9 percent anticipated a decline. But today that 43-point gap has vanished. According to the Newsweek survey, only 32 percent of Americans now think that race relations have improved since the president’s inauguration; roughly the same number (30 percent) believe they have gotten worse. Factor in those who say nothing has changed and the result is staggering: nearly 60 percent of Americans are now convinced that race relations have either deteriorated or stagnated under Obama." You were saying, Howie?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360620179772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:02:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360620310478-126</Id><Title>Obama to mention Dreamliner at State of the Union</Title><Msg>He is going to ask Congress for another 500 billion to loan Boeing so they can 1) try to fix the never ending 787 electrical problems 2) remodel their corporate office in his home town - Chicago 3) give over any left over taxpayer money to overpaid BA engineers Its the American way</Msg><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360620310478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:05:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360620589504-127</Id><Topic><Title>Great Entertainment - Watch Benjamin Carson Humiliate Obama and his Policies</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360619171958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like how Michelle kept politely applauding for all the anti big government jabs he hurled at Obama. Now you know why Obama surrounds himself with idiots like Biden, Pelosi and Reid. Obama appears smarter relative to the three stooges but put him in a room with someone like Carson and it is evident that Obama is an intellectual poser. For a neuro scientist Carson presented himself with a great deal of humility which also juxtaposes the pompous #$%$ style of Lord Obama. You couldn't find two people more diametrically opposed in thought and action .</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360620589504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:09:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360620626852-128</Id><Title>Post of the Day</Title><Msg>from mir_roguns: "If you've ever got money back after filing your tax return, you've engaged in tax avoidance. If you've ever used itemized deductions, you've engaged in tax avoidance. It's perfectly legal as long as you obey they law. Our tax system with over 50,000 pages of rules and regulations was designed by Democrats and RINO Republicans to allow some classes of people to avoid taxes that other classes of people can't avoid in order to buy votes and campaign donations from the favored classes. They have done this from 1913 forward. The more complex they can make the system the more it favors rich guys like myself and big corporations like GE who can afford to take advantage of the complexity of the system's design. After giving huge donations to Obama and Democrats GE was able to pay ZERO taxes on over $ 5billion of profits. This happens with thousands of huge corporations and many wealthy individuals Less sophisticated people and small businesses are left to pay what they owe plus the taxes not paid by more successful tax avoiders. That's the way the system is designed to work. The Amazing thing is, their propaganda has absolutely convinced the ignorant and naive masses of people this is all in the interest of the preserving and growing the mediocre class. The system assuages their jealousy and envy by making the masses think the system is designed to hurt and punish high income achievers. Meanwhile we rich guys keep getting richer and the mediocre income achievers keep sinking lower on the food chain and the politicians can keep taking the votes of the ignorant and naive for granted. What a system?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360620626852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:10:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360620687309-129</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop listening to FOX and Limbaugh, perhaps then you will understnd the Earth is round and not flat. Legalise drugs and take the profits out and crime will reduce. Besides taxes could be collected.</Msg><Username>fountain123_45</Username><Timestamp>1360620687309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:11:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621409434-130</Id><Topic><Title>Great Entertainment - Watch Benjamin Carson Humiliate Obama and his Policies</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1360619171958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:46:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post ali_infesto. Another big difference is that even though bother men were raised in single parent homes Obama college educated white momma turned to welfare. Dr. Carson's black mother with her 3rd grade education had the character to look at people on welfare and know it was wrong and robbed people of dignity. She worked 3 jobs as a domestic to refused to even apply for welfare.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360621409434</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:23:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621441508-131</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad they played it safe and were only allowed to fly over unpopulated areas for these tests, even considering that these same flight test planes had never experienced any battery problems during certification. Since these same test flight planes never experience any issues during certification, it is understandable that there were no issues found with these flights(yet). They must now be looking for something that may not have been understood during certification. If not something new, it could be a long investigation to find the issue.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360621441508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:24:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621549277-132</Id><Topic><Title>Questions about Boeing's new battery solution</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360602457029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 12:07:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems that Boeing is still befuddled. They should have used "Bunny Batteries" made in the good ole USA to begin with rather than that TURD World junk!</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360621549277</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:25:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621665684-133</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did they fly these test flights with a full load of passengers? With passengers with their electronic devices? Their TV's and radios on? I don't think so!</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1360621665684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:27:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621836635-134</Id><Topic><Title>The Graham Cracker</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360619537346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya just gotta love the way liberals substitute name calling and insults for intellectual dialog. It's like a neon sigh flashing "I'm too stupid to come up with anything that makes sense so in my frustration I'll just call people names instead." Thanks imshockedshocked.....you're a monument to socialized government education.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360621836635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:30:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360621878283-135</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Boeing learning something on these test flights its unlikely that they would share it. Also the missing passengers and their activities aboard is that somehow factored in?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1360621878283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:31:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360622014812-136</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point. Power off in rest rooms, no hot coffee, no over head lights or air. No "fasten your seat belt signs" or "this is your captain announcements". Best to test on the ground where the FAA can make sure Boeing does not cut corners again and put millions of flying passengers at risk.</Msg><Username>youbgone</Username><Timestamp>1360622014812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:33:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360622230886-137</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360622230886</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:37:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360622500686-138</Id><Topic><Title>The Graham Cracker</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360619537346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lindsey Graham to President Bush - Yea its hard being in the military when all i do all day is move papers, play golf and think of my bright legal future when I get the far away from here. Bush to Lindsey - I know what you mean. My old man had to really work hard to get me in the Texas Air National Guard. They wanted to send my behind to Vietnam, but I say no way. I'd hide in Canada if that happened/ Lindsy to Bush - Yea I should of done that but if you do that in South Carolina they brand you a pinky Democrat. No way I could live with that. By the way President Bush, how many days did you serve in the Texas Air National Guard? Bush to Lindsey - Oh about 30 days. Most of my time was spent off base, drinking, chasing women and spending my old man's millions..Hey it paid off - I got to be president off my old man's coat tails and even was a partner of the Texas Rangers using my old man's oil money. Man those were the good old days. Fight for your country but never show up for duty.</Msg><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360622500686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360623846811-139</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lasertech, why did you use their full names?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1360623846811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:04:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360623954021-140</Id><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Msg>Remember AlQ AEDA..YOU KNOW...THOSE GUYS WHO supposedly GOT NORAD TO STAND DOWN AND DO IMPOSSIBLE SPIRAL DOWN FLIGHT MANUEVERS INTO THE PENTAGON ON 9-11.....TURNS OUT THAT THE WEST IS BACKING THEM...KIND OF LIKE SAYING LEX LUTHER IS REALLY SUPERMAN....THE BAD GUYS ARE THE GOOD GUYS NOW.....WE ARE THROUGH THE LOOKING GLASS PEOPLE...AND THE NEW WORLD ORDER THINKS YOU ARE TOO STUPID TO NOTICE Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda (THIS INFO IS BACKED BY MULTPLE SOURCES FROM MULTIPLE PEOPLE FROM MULTIPE WEB SITES AND MULTIPLE NEWS ACCOUNTS) Executive Intelligence Review February 11, 2013 In an article for the Feb. 5 Kölner Stadtanzeiger news daily, former Bundestag member for the Christian Democrats Jürgen Todenhöfer denounced the unholy pact among the West, the Saudis, and the I slamic terrorist groups. His analysis is flawed to the extent that the British aspect does not appear, but the piece otherwise, is a very useful exposé. “The S yrian rebels receive money and weapons predominantly from S audi A rabia and Qatar. S audi A rabia is mainly supplying Al Q aeda, with the U.S.A. knowing about it. The West is providing political cover for the entire rebellion, including al-Q aeda. It is de facto an ally of al-Q aeda. In M ali against, in Syria for al-Q aeda—it can’t be more cynical.” “Assad is a dictator. So is the King of S audi Arabia and the E mir of Q atar. The U.S. and the despots of S audi A rabia and Q atar don’t want to see democracy in S yria. Their objective is to knock out an important ally of Iran, which has become too powerful because of the I raq War for them. That this goes along with one of the most amiable multi-ethnic peoples of the A rab world, does not interest our ‘world strategists.’ Nor does the fact that if the extremists win, 2 million Christians will lose their home.” Todenhöfer writes that Assad will be able to hold out for some time, therefore it would be better to negotiate with him than to continue this tragic civil war. When Ronald Reagan once negotiated with the Soviet leaders, he never called on them to step down. What would be required is for the U.S. to force S audi A rabia and Q atar to stop supplying the weapons, with Russia doing the same on the other side. A ceasefire should be used for talks between Assad and the opposition, with the aim of forming a transitional government, of working out a democratic constitution that also protects minorities, and of preparing free elections under international monitoring. Assad is not that much interested in being a Presidential candidate in 2014, if there is a fair peace agreement, Todenhöfer writes. “It is time for a correction of the West’s course. It must end its cynical pact with al-Q aeda.”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360624230626-141</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at the moment -BA is forfbidden to share anything not of public record such as flight path and times</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360624230626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:10:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360624365195-142</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I posted in haste and should have thought to redact the name of the original questioner. However, this email is going viral as Mr Davaz had hoped, so I'm sure there was a no desire on his part to remain anonymous.</Msg><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360624365195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:12:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360625390901-143</Id><Title>So is BA losing 100 million a day, 200 million a day or $300 million</Title><Msg>everyday the dreamliner is shut down? At some point it will be impossible for the company CFO to hide such huge losses. Stock down in AH and thinking Executive Heads are going to roll in near future.</Msg><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360625390901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:29:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360625559546-144</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>99.999 PERCENT OF THE AK'S ARE NOT machine guns. A WASR 10 for example is Romanian made and is semi auto and in essence is no different then a hunting rifle with a higher mag capacity. You've been admonished to quit distorting the facts Brokedik</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360625559546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:32:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360625635109-145</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you're BETTING on the Government...then shouldnt Americans be BETTER arm'd not less ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360625635109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:33:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360625982701-146</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Word out now that had JAL incident occurred in flt. It would have result in tail/fuselage separation.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1360625982701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:39:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360626080006-147</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was more of an observation that people like you are not capable of providing opposition.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1360626080006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:41:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360626474574-148</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roger that</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1360626474574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:47:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360626555716-149</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uhh the battery involved in JAL japan was under the cockpit ! thats the pointy end with windows !! The JAL Boston battery was in the front part of the cargo hold . which one and where getting info ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360626555716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:49:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360627532117-150</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you are right again..... The Communists, like the raven, love to confuse the population and demonize the semi-auto.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360627532117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:05:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360627602475-151</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you think about thebigbamboozle?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360627602475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:06:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360629205151-152</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dimbecile Pecker only "thinks" he had a "thought" today! Poor Dim Pecker with just another moronic Dim copy / paste!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1360629205151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:33:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360629285534-153</Id><Topic><Title>has Obama cut drilling on gov.land again?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1360626574994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:49:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey dobas s don't you know about the summer gas blend scam yet- where you from Arkansas?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360629285534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:34:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360629787092-154</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of "coloring?...Poor Dim Pauline seems to be a little on the "red" side this time of month!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1360629787092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:43:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360629855978-155</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shooting...scoring.....yawn</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360629855978</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:44:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360630059311-156</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make us yawn, too.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1360630059311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 19:47:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360630878995-157</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all true but that the report. multiple news accounts.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1360630878995</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:01:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360631294166-158</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Revere: Are you saying Sparty's firm prediction that Obama would vacate the White House LAST AUGUST didn't exactly pan out?</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1360631294166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:08:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360631695832-159</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Genna alias trying to be humorous.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1360631695832</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:14:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360631786608-160</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I for one was mighty proud of how well SPEEA ran their strike. We had zero confidence they would stay out very long and boy were we wrong. We welcomed them back and quickly identified those ot their brethren who "forgot" to strike.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1360631786608</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:16:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360631952480-161</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they are big and they are bam Is it because of too much boozle?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1360631952480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:19:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360632180035-162</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing wraps up 787 flight test(s)</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360619073304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:44:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you know those Boeing engineers, maybe the same ones that ok'ed that battery. They may have the tail starting right behind the cockpit door.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1360632180035</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:23:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360632404011-163</Id><Topic><Title>The Graham Cracker</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360619537346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard Obama served by constantly being high and having #$%$, although one time he visited an Army surplus store and suffered PTSD from the experience. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360632404011</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:26:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360632597984-164</Id><Topic><Title>Fox's Roger Ailes: 'Obama's Too Busy Getting Middle Class To Hate Rich People, Blacks To Hate Whites'</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360620179772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:02:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big surprise there. Ailes is the mouthpiece of the unhinged right -- he even hires all the right-fringers the voters reject: Rove, Palin,. Huckabee, etc. etc. etc.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360632597984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:29:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360632982840-165</Id><Topic><Title>Using Sandy Hook To Disarm The Public Was Conceived In 1991</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360617033924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:10:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll try to write at #$%$ level next time just for you.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360632982840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:36:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360633055949-166</Id><Topic><Title>Fox's Roger Ailes: 'Obama's Too Busy Getting Middle Class To Hate Rich People, Blacks To Hate Whites'</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360620179772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:02:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's against the law for them to hire the ones the voters didn't reject. the other cable news channels to the same thing.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360633055949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:37:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360633350830-167</Id><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Msg>It's not like they had any moral compass when they were criticizing Bush for water boarding. Obama is worse than Bush because he has given himself authority to any american he wants. Who knew hope and change would come to this.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360633387786-168</Id><Title>Has anyone in the Obama administration served??????</Title><Msg>....heck.....has anyone in the Obama administration ever had a job where they actually had to work for a living.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360633387786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:43:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360633623178-169</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A sharp analysis by Mr Davaz of John Tracy's (CTO) message to SPEEA represented employees has been posted at the speea website .../Bargaining_Units/PS%202012/What_members_are_saying.html</Msg><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360633623178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:47:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360633953076-170</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Graaaate post- right on- I'll add a little bit to the pension issue - same as I posted on the Everett herald blog ' ray conner strike no one wins BA Released its annual report today - and with a little work it can be found on the boeing site corporate governance find 10K report , etc Anyhow this bit from said report regarding pensions should give lie to the BA PR About BA pension costs from the annual report released today ...At December 31, 2012 and 2011, our pension plans were $19.7 billion and $16.6 billion underfunded as measured under GAAP. ****On an ERISA basis our plans are more than 100% funded at December 31, 2012 with minimal required contributions in 2013. *****We expect to make discretionary contributions to our plans of approximately $1.5 billion in 2013. We may be required to make higher contributions to our pension plans in future years... ++ Under ERISA accounting there are some interesting goodies and baddies 1) maximum surplus ( over 100 percent ) is about 120 to 150 percent- after which NO tax deductions allowed 2) ERISA counted surplus - ON PAPER - can be directly transferred into OPERATING EARNINGS - BUT no real $$ are involved 3) Smoothing of ERISA minimums and maximums over bucu years is allowed to avoid direct relationship to market issues So why would BA - with 100 percent ERISA funding want to make discretionary deposits ?? Answer- read above about SURPLUS- its like a tax free piggy bank- allowing tax free money to go into earnings ! Increased earnings make for Bone-yous to top executives. So when the going gets tough - the execs get more !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360633953076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:52:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360634496103-171</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correction Obama is worse than Bush because he has given himself authority to kill any American he wants. Who knew hope and change would come to this.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360634496103</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:01:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360634599705-172</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... If Boeing got away with dropping the pension, the DOD's contributions would continue to flow into the companies pension coffers. Where would those funds end up actually? .. Actually - in such a case - BA has to pay back any excess from such a move. They tried that scam ( keeping the money Gubbermint paid for benefits on gubbermint programs ) and got hammered big time- although it took a few years. One little sideline - For decades, employees on such programs ( eg military or NASA or ) had a higher average wage than their counterparts in commercial . By 5 to 15 percent ( according to plots and figures I beat out of them a few decades ago ). So often when a person transferred from " military " to commercial, his/her wage v experience v age was higher than commercial ( cuz gubbermint was picking up the benefit costs ). Result was said person usually got levelled for a year or more till commercial scale caught up !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360634599705</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:03:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360634789512-173</Id><Topic><Title>End game is here already, Obama said no support for Syrians 30k dead, I expect no support for Isreal either</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1360632413244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:26:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem with Obama's foreign policy is he tells the enemy what he will be doing...NOTHING. There is no fear of a strong USA. HE gives the enemy confidence. Obama needs to go to a coin flip. He'd at least get things right half the time instead of never.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360634789512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:06:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360635045264-174</Id><Topic><Title>Has anyone in the Obama administration served??????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360633387786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:43:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Govt socialists call work skimming off of workin folks' labor. And serve? Who would want to serve next to a Van Jones, a self admitted communist?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360635045264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:10:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360636111666-175</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's a pension anyway? not familiar with that term.</Msg><Username>danspd</Username><Timestamp>1360636111666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:28:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360636913486-176</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna and Hooz alias's have a lot of allusions to Paul Macartney and the Beatles.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360636913486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:41:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360637133494-177</Id><Topic><Title>Has anyone in the Obama administration served??????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360633387786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:43:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes - they served ObUma</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360637133494</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:45:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360637528784-178</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saing that the Big Bamboozle is even more important then Crossing the Rubicon ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360637528784</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 21:52:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360638292327-179</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holy Jesus! I knew there was an unspoken alliance between Obama and Al Qaeda! Gunrunning weapons to Syrian Rebels with close ties to Al Qaeda. And the Lame Stream Media covers for this President at the same time. The American People are being BETRAYED! Benedict Arnold Obama and the Socialist Media!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360638292327</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:04:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360638499637-180</Id><Topic><Title>Has anyone in the Obama administration served??????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360633387786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:43:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, they all have "positions", now . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360638499637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:08:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360638690316-181</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The following is not the case I mentioned- but I'm sure everyone will enjoy the comments made a while ago by Hairy StonedCipher How Do Pensions Affect Corporate Capital Structure Decisions? Anil Shivdasani Kenan-Flagler Business School, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill Irina Stefanescu Kelley School of Business, Indiana University ... This article examines the capital structure implications of defined benefit corporate pension plans. The magnitude of the liabilities arising from these pension plans is substantial. We show that leverage ratios for firms with pension plans are about 35% higher when pension assets and liabilities are incorporated into the capital structure. We estimate that the tax shields from pension contributions are about a third of those from interest payments. Pension contributions have a modest effect in lowering firms’ marginal corporate tax rates. Once pensions are considered, firms are less conservative in their choice of leverage than has been previously thought.We show that firms incorporate the magnitude of their pension assets and liabilities into their capital structure decisions. (JEL G32, H20, J33) Investing in our pension as long as we get the tax deduction for it is a very good investment for us, Harry Stonecipher, president and chief executive officer of Boeing, told analysts in a third quarter conference call in October. Boeing’s $3.6 billion contribution in 2004 will result in a tax benefit that year of between $1.1 billion and $1.3 billion, assuming a tax rate of 30% to 35%, according to Boeing spokesman John Dern. —Wall Street Journal (2005), “How Companies Make the Most on Pensions”</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360638690316</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:11:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360638841367-182</Id><Topic><Title>End game is here already, Obama said no support for Syrians 30k dead, I expect no support for Isreal either</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1360632413244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:26:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad to see you have stopped posting gay porno . Your choice, or Yeahooz ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360638841367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:14:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639086270-183</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I knew it . Where's that idiot nowarrantneeded, now ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360639086270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:18:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639147796-184</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its a lot worse then you realise.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360639147796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:19:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639265597-185</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and for a sample of Boeing ethics ... and bookcooking go to site .contractormisconduct d o t o r g contractor id 13 The federal contractor misconduct database pogo 8. 777 Aircraft Program (Unallowed Costs) Boeing agreed to an administrative settlement of over $6 million for including costs from the 777 commercial airline program in governmental general and administrative accounts. "Contractors are not permitted to include costs of commercial contracts either directly or indirectly in accounts for which the Government is charged.” but that database does not go back quite far enough and only has about 46 entries of BA misconduct ..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360639265597</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:21:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639485670-186</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and a bit more in the same document quoting Hairy pension liabilities and record these contributions as a pension expense at the same time. In practice, such a strategy would create significant volatility in companies’ reported earnings as the value of pension assets and liabilities, and hence the required contributions, fluctuate over time. To avoid this variability, accounting rules allow companies to adopt several pension cost smoothing mechanisms. Because of these smoothing techniques, it is not uncommon for companies to report pension income as part of their operating income when, in fact, the funding status of their pension plan has deteriorated. As an example, in 2003, the Boeing Company reported pension liabilities of $39.9 billion and PA of $33.2 billion (a 17% underfunded plan) while reporting a pension income of $67 million on the income statement (i.e., a negative pension cost). Do not do this at home - unless you want room and board at club fed.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360639485670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360639529199-187</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nan heads up the ignorance caucus . Today Medved asked why the dims keep reelecting a "dotty demented old lady" to one of the most important public offices there is . I know why, she represents them perfectly . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360639529199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:25:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360640527470-188</Id><Title>When will the plastic planes fly again?</Title><Msg>I knew they should have made them out of styrofoam and rubber bands.</Msg><Username>cramerblows_a_s_s</Username><Timestamp>1360640527470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:42:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360640617951-189</Id><Topic><Title>Has anyone in the Obama administration served??????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360633387786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:43:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know as well as I do that nobody in Junior Bush's administration served. Junior was AWOL himself- thruout the war. John Kerry was an officer, was decorated and wounded but that really doesnt count with RWNJ draft dodging rampant like it was</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360640617951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:43:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360640715632-190</Id><Topic><Title>Has anyone in the Obama administration served??????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360633387786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:43:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaeces tell us where you served- and if you did eh or were you a draft dodger too. If you were in the serveice then I know why we lost the war</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360640715632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:45:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360641230111-191</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't believe this story. Not until WND posts it, that is. s/ Orly</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1360641230111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:53:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360641703270-192</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when are you going to tie this jaw-dropping, mind-blowing, truly stunning "development" to the Pope's resignation?</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1360641703270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:01:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360641734977-193</Id><Title>Ted Nugent going to the State of the Union</Title><Msg>PoopyPants is going to the State of the Union address as a guest of some Texas Turd. Hope he makes a stink - as the NRA and the gun nuts will never live down the bad publicity.</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1360641734977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:02:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360642077299-194</Id><Topic><Title>End game is here already, Obama said no support for Syrians 30k dead, I expect no support for Isreal either</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1360632413244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:26:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's this? Gregjanetommaxcheckn? Should you be worrying about GAY centrifuges?</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1360642077299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:07:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360643001289-195</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of ignorance//jumbo, here's a classic: Bin Ladenn is dead! 3-May-01:50 am "I don't know for sure, but it could have something to do with the facts: Fact 1.) Fish eat corpses . Fact 2.) J**s eat fish ." Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1360643001289</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:23:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360643530063-196</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Where's that idiot nowarrantneeded/Genna, now ?" May as well say where is that little Hypocrite now ? Endless posts about how Bush was a war criminal 5 years ago...crickets from the out of work reporter now.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360643530063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 23:32:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>