<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-10-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380773025441-1</Id><Title>China's attempt to break into the large airplane market</Title><Msg>SINGAPORE/BEIJING (Reuters) - China's largest domestically produced aircraft may not enter service until early next decade, a delay that gives dominant rivals Boeing Co and Airbus time to launch their upgraded single-aisle planes first. The Comac C919, which will compete with the Airbus A320 and Boeing 737 family of aircraft, was scheduled for its first flight next year, but that has now been delayed until 2015, which pushes the first delivery to around 2017 or 2018, local media have reported.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1380773025441</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 00:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380773731743-2</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, If you recall, Obama and Wash, DC security would not deploy anyone to shut down the illegal take-over of a Wash, DC park by the "Occupy Stupidity" folks - for FOUR MONTHS (McPherson Square) from October 2011 to Feb 2012, but they immediately try to deny veterans the ability to observe a moment of peace and remembrance for what the country used to stand for - that apparently cannot be understood or tolerated by the present Administration. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1380773731743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 00:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380773902635-3</Id><Topic><Title>Guess who just blinked?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380731536314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 12:32:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah. So THAT explains how he got elected a 2nd time. Hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380773902635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 00:18:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380773971939-4</Id><Topic><Title>Reading Hoozdik's Posts are Like Reading the Onion</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380753107116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 18:31:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In every presidential election, there are lots of people who don't vote for the winner. You can count them, but they don't ... well, count.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380773971939</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 00:19:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380774229264-5</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see any first-amendment consideration. Freedom to assemble? It's not exactly an assembly area, more like space for individual reflection. I don't think there HAS to be any Constitutional aspect to this -- it's just that there are no locks on the doors it doesn't have</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380774229264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 00:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380775374213-6</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The memorial was funded by private-public donations, including maintenace, etc. You it is the same as a public park open to all with no doors or locks, etc. No barriers whatsovever. So how does anyone have the right to put up barriers, restrict entrance, prevent speech, meditation or observation. True the forest servide. park service can shut down ranger stations and enterances to parks which require an entrance fee- but that does NOT apply to the memorials. Just who(m) is/are the twit(s) who has or claims to have the authority to block anyone who indivudually or peacefully assembles there. Where does the funds to pay for the workers and equipment to put up some barrier- including police tape do not enter? Why would it be called civil disobedience to enter, jump over or remove such barricades absent a safety of public issue. ? would not any of those actions( putting up barriers ) violate the first amendment ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380775374213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 00:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380777031616-7</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Don, I don't think so. I don't see any first-amendment rights involved in shutting the WW2 Memorial. But what would anyone have to make that case anyway? What DC cop is going to arrest an 89-year-old Battle of the Bulge veteran in a wheelchair for driving through that colossal assemblage of concrete? I think everyone's chapped hide about all the OTHER things is tuning them into all this caterwauling about a tyranny. But the rule I learned was, "Never attribute to malice what is adequately explained by stupidity." Why not spend tour time calculating how much yellow tape would be required to "close" the Vietnam Veterans Memorial -- and evaluating how effective that would be? About the only case the govt. could make is if those open-air monuments needed police patrols to prevent vandalism -- and none of them have had the kind or costly security up to now. Buildings like the Lincoln and Jefferson memorials might be a different story, but I don't know. I repeat my earlier question: With all the s*it this s*utdown is causing, aren't we overworking our tear ducts just a little on this matter. Ask yourself who you'd blame if there were to be a terrorist incident during this carnival?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380777031616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 01:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380780602883-8</Id><Topic><Title>Do as the Belgians Do? The Country that went 589 Days Without a Government</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380751119959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 17:58:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would much rather be in Belgium than where Obama was a community organizer. Starting to look like Obama's legacy of south Chicago is becoming going to be his legacy for all America.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1380780602883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 02:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380782808286-9</Id><Title>Proposed combined order of Etihad, Emriates, and Qatar for 777x to be 50-100 Billion dollar range---just 3 airlines</Title><Msg>This is just for these 3 sources and no speaking of options---everyones going of a qty break---they go smart with combining 3 airlines at the Dubai airshow in Nov. A lot of other airlines to add---this will be an amazing year---it will be recorded setting especially if the Rynair order for the 737 MAX comes in shortly.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380782808286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 02:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380783858761-10</Id><Topic><Title>Do as the Belgians Do? The Country that went 589 Days Without a Government</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380751119959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 17:58:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long live King Philippe !!</Msg><Username>wellsaid_1234</Username><Timestamp>1380783858761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 03:04:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380799560984-11</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do YOU want to keep WWII away from THEIR memorial???????????????????????????</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1380799560984</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 07:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380800477637-12</Id><Title>Another NSA Congressional Hearing</Title><Msg>It is plain frustrating watching on CSPAN the same old smoke and mirror presentations from General Alexander and Mr. Clapper explaining and not explaining the workings of the NSA. What we don't have is any collaborating testimony from an insider of the NSA who is willing to be candid with Congress and tell the American people the truth. Yes someone like an Eric Snowden. If only Congress would invite him to testify under immunity we could get to the bottom of what Congress and the American public needs to know. Lets end the charade games and stonewalling to Congress. Congress needs to know what it is funding. Its all about protecting our national security.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1380800477637</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 07:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380801535822-13</Id><Topic><Title>Proposed combined order of Etihad, Emriates, and Qatar for 777x to be 50-100 Billion dollar range---just 3 airlines</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380782808286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 02:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got a nice proven fuselage, a huge energy saving wing, and a pair of nice energy saving engines--should really be quite a seller for years. No true competition for years with all the advancements which the 777x seris will carry. Exciting time for any Boeing long</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380801535822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 07:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380802724580-14</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Freedom to assemble? It's not exactly an assembly area"...the freedom to assemble is a freedom to assemble ANYWHERE ...if..not it is not freedom to assemble...in ANY case..to deny WWII vets the right to assemble at THEIR MEMORIAL is just plain petulant and cruel by the Obama administration.....I cant think of one President other then the current one who would deny access...UNLESS...it the CURRENT ONE has an agenda ..TO REMIND THE SLAVES OF THEIR PLACE IN THE NEW ORDER !!!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380802724580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 08:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380802773697-15</Id><Title>The House is the Peoples House</Title><Msg>......and the House has the power of the purse......they were elected and re-elected too.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380802773697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 08:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380802907052-16</Id><Title>There is no constitutionally mandate to pass a CR.</Title><Msg>.....but there is one to submit a budget every year which Obama and the Democrats failed to do.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380802907052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 08:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380803420750-17</Id><Title>Evident Obam Fears 90 year old WWII vets more than hed Does Terrorists</Title><Msg>.....he has employed more guards to keep WWII vets out of their open air memorial than he did the Benghazi consulate. That's the way to reduce spending Mr. President but the as Hillary would say, What difference does it make.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380803420750</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 08:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380803723898-18</Id><Topic><Title>Proposed combined order of Etihad, Emriates, and Qatar for 777x to be 50-100 Billion dollar range---just 3 airlines</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380782808286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 02:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I share your enthusiasm for Boeing's superior products but remember, as a euro-phrench subsidized jobs program, airbutt can undercut Boeing on price. Certainly the 777x will out perform anything airbutt has or will have, but if airbutt lowers the purchase price enough to cover operational expenses, they could even sell one of those a-340 crates. I know the a-340 has been discontinued and for good reason but if they give them away, what airline wouldn't use them ?</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1380803723898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 08:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380805675757-19</Id><Topic><Title>787</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380725228949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 10:47:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two other 787;s were delivered on 10/1. L/N 123 delivered to Qantas, L/N 128 delivered to Royal Brunei Airlines.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380805675757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:07:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380805747610-20</Id><Title>The real crises is not the Government Shutdown</Title><Msg>The inability of the media and politicians to focus on the real issues never ceases to amaze. Image: US Dollar. The real crisis is not the “debt ceiling crisis.” The government shutdown is merely a result of the Republicans using the debt limit ceiling to attempt to block the implementation of Obamacare. If the shutdown persists and becomes a problem, Obama has enough power under the various “war on terror” rulings to declare a national emergency and raise the debt ceiling by executive order. An executive branch that has the power to inter citizens indefinitely and to murder them without due process of law, can certainly set aside a ceiling on debt that jeopardizes the government. The real crisis is that jobs offshoring by US corporations has permanently lowered US tax revenues by shifting what would have been consumer income, US GDP, and tax base to China, India, and other countries where wages and the cost of living are relatively low. On the spending side, twelve years of wars have inflated annual expenditures. The consequence is a wide deficit gap between revenues and expenditures. Under the present circumstances, the deficit is too large to be closed. The Federal Reserve covers the deficit by printing $1,000 billion annually with which to purchase Treasury debt and mortgage-backed financial instruments. The use of the printing press on such a large scale undermines the US dollar’s role as reserve currency, the basis for US power. Raising the debt limit simply allows the real crisis to continue. More money will be printed with which to purchase more new debt issues needed to close the gap between revenues and expenditures. The supply of dollars or dollar denominated assets in foreign hands is vast. (The Social Security system’s large surplus accumulated over a quarter century was borrowed by the Treasury and spent. In its place are non-marketable Treasury IOUs. Consequently, Social Security is one of the largest creditors to the US government.) If foreigners lose confidence in the dollar, the drop in the dollar’s exchange value would mean high inflation and the Federal Reserve’s loss of control over interest rates. It is possible that a drop in the dollar’s exchange value could initiate hyperinflation in the US. The real crisis is the absence of intelligence among economists and policymakers who told us for 20 years not to worry about the offshoring of US jobs, because we were going to have a “New Economy” with better jobs. As I report each month, not a single one of these “New Economy” jobs has appeared in the payroll jobs statistics or in the Labor Department’s projections of future jobs. Economists and policymakers simply gave away a good chunk of the US economy in order to enhance corporate profits. One result has been to create in the US the worst distribution of income of all developed countries and of many undeveloped ones. In the scheme of things, the enhanced profits are a short-run thing, because by halting the growth in consumer income, jobs offshoring has destroyed the US consumer market. As I noted in a recent column, on September 19 the New York Times reported what I have reported for years: that US median family income has not increased for a quarter of a century. The lack of consumer income growth is why 5 years of massive monetary and fiscal stimulus have not brought economic recovery. The real crisis cannot be addressed unless the jobs are brought back home and the wars are stopped. As powerful organized interests oppose any such measures, Congress will pass a new debt ceiling and the real crisis will continue. Do you hear any mention of the real crisis in the media? Today I was on an international TV program for 25 minutes with the chief financial editor of one of England’s major newspapers. Little doubt but that he was a good-hearted and intelligent fellow, but he had no capability of thinking outside the box. He was unable to comprehend my explanations, and resorted to regurgitations of the media’s ignorance or subservience to Washington’s propaganda. Among his regurgitations was the “solution” of cutting Social Security. The chief financial editor of a major UK newspaper did not know that for the past quarter of a century Social Security revenues exceeded Social Security payments, and that the Treasury spent the surplus to fund the annual operating expenses of the government, issuing non-marketable IOUs to the Social Security Trust Funds. The chief financial editor also did not comprehend that cutting Social Security payments also cuts consumer spending or aggregate demand, and sends the economy down further, thus magnifying the deficit/debt problem. Because of the serious decline in the US economy caused by jobs offshoring and financial deregulation, Social Security no longer adds to its surplus. Social Security payments need the supplement to the annual payroll revenues of repayments by the Treasury of the borrowed funds. The only reasons that Social Security is in trouble is that jobs offshoring and wars have constrained the US Treasury’s ability to make good on its debts except by having the Federal Reserve print money. Every job that is sent abroad does not contribute payroll taxes to Social Security and Medicare. Insouciant American economists say that manufacturing is an outmoded source of employment, but Chinese manufacturing employment is almost equal to the total US labor force in all occupations, including waitresses and bartenders and hospital orderlies. China’s economy is growing at a rate of 7.5% in real terms, while Western economies cannot move forward and some are regressing.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380805747610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380805785847-21</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna.....You sound like a communist.......is that what you fought for.....a more communistic government? Why have new immigration laws when you have a President who doesn't keep his oath of office and refuses to keep the immigration laws we already have?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1380805785847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380805806125-22</Id><Topic><Title>The real crises is not the Government Shutdown</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380805747610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In order to appease Wall Street, the most corrupt institution in human history, and to prevent Wall Street-financed takeovers of their corporations, executives destroyed the American consumer market by offshoring American incomes in order to enhance profits by substituting cheap foreign labor for US labor. In my opinion, the US economy is not salvageable in its present form. The economy is running out of water resources. The supply that remains is being decimated by fracking. The soil is depleted by glysophate, a requirement of GMO agriculture. The external costs of production are rising (the costs that the corporations impose on the environment and third parties) and possibly exceed the value of the increase in corporate output. Economists are incapable of independent thought, and elected representatives are dependent on the private interests that finance their campaigns. It is difficult to imagine a more discouraging situation. At this time, collapse seems the most likely forecast. Perhaps out of the ruins, a new, intelligent beginning might occur. If there are any leaders. Paul Craig Roberts was Assistant Secretary of the Treasury for Economic Policy and associate editor of the Wall Street Journal. He was columnist for Business Week, Scripps Howard News Service, and Creators Syndicate. He has had many university appointments. His internet columns have attracted a worldwide following. His latest book, The Failure of Laissez Faire Capitalism and Economic Dissolution of the West is now available.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380805806125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380806146476-23</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He might be Illegal .. and he might JUST be a criminal fraud (forging papers in the process to make the official narrative the reality)...doesn't matter for the point I am making. He is as Obama HIMSELF puts it..a "citizen of the world"...as he himself spent large parts of his time OUTSIDE of America and was indoctrinated in Globalist and communist philosophy by Frank Marshall Davis....(probably his real biological father) philosophy. To Obama there ARE no borders...no National Sovereignty...Can you imagine ANYONE being a more eager servant to the borderless globalist bankers for which he serves ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380806146476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:15:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380806842090-24</Id><Title>GOP still trying to create a scandle</Title><Msg>They should look at themselves for the scandal.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380806842090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:27:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380807068306-25</Id><Topic><Title>The real crises is not the Government Shutdown</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380805747610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post Spart.......Jealousy and Greed is self-defeating cannibalism. The left's desire to keep punishing the job creators with higher taxes and unnecessary regulations is driving them off-shore so we end up with less revenue, less jobs and more outlay to care for the jobless. Even when the revenue is a record levels, if it's all phoney money and no one wants to buy our debt except the phoney Federal Reserve. We are in an economic death spiral.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1380807068306</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380807311860-26</Id><Topic><Title>GOP still trying to create a scandle</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380806842090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rocks4brains would defend Obama and the Democrats if they suddenly got struck by honesty and said, "Yes, we are communists and we do want to fundamentally transform America into the Socialist Republic of America."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1380807311860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380807471194-27</Id><Title>Obama Quote of the Day</Title><Msg>• "The only freedom which deserves the name, is that of pursuing our own good in our own way, so long as we do not attempt to deprive others of theirs, or impede their efforts to obtain it." --John Stuart Mill</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1380807471194</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380807802932-28</Id><Topic><Title>Evident Obam Fears 90 year old WWII vets more than hed Does Terrorists</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380803420750</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 08:30:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The way Obama and the Democrats treat our vets is despicable.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380807802932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380808188445-29</Id><Title>This Government Shut Down is Wonderful</Title><Msg>If we could stay shut down for a few years we might actually balance the budget like we did the last time the government was shut down but we might also have to get another Monica Lewinsky to keep the president occupied while we righted this sinking ship.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380808188445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380808802624-30</Id><Topic><Title>This Government Shut Down is Wonderful</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380808188445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's put Americans back to work</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380808802624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380808838264-31</Id><Title>IRS AUDITED BEN CARSON AFTER PRAYER B'FAST SPEECH</Title><Msg>Dr. Ben Carson was targeted by IRS agents who requested to review his real estate holdings and then conducted a full audit without finding any wrongdoing. “I guess it could be a coincidence, but I never had been audited before and never really had any encounters with the IRS,” Dr. Carson said in an interview Thursday with The Washington Times. “But it certainly would make one suspicious because we know now the IRS has been used for political purposes and therefore actions like this come under suspicion.” Dr. Carson is a world-renown neurosurgeon whose rise from poverty and a single family home , and his medical work with pediatric patients was celebrated in a movie called “Gifted Hands.” He has electrified the conservative world with speeches and columns since his February National Prayer Breakfast speech in front of Mr. Obama, in which he decried the “moral decay and fiscal irresponsibility” of America in recent years. He writes a weekly column for The Times. Dr. Carson first hinted at the problem earlier this week during a speech in Alabama when he made a vague reference to having his first “encounter with the IRS” earlier this year. Dr. Carson told The Times that IRS agents contacted him in June — less than four months after the speech — and requested to review his real estate holdings. After finding nothing that concerned them, the agents then informed him they were conducting a full audit of his finances , and then asked to go back an additional year to review his records, he said. They finally ended the review in August after finding no problems, Dr. Carson said. “They told me everything was in good standing and left,” he said. Asked whether he thought the audit was a retaliation for his speech, Dr. Carson quipped: “I guess I’m surprised it took them that long.” He said the more serious issue is that the IRS has been politicized — “something that should never have happened” — and that leaves all of its activities open to suspicion.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380808838264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380808888376-32</Id><Topic><Title>The House is the Peoples House</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380802773697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 08:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's put Americans back to work and you watch the deficit decrease</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380808888376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380808909180-33</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For all you who put your thumbs down PLEASE stop drinking the KOOL AID! My bet is that when this shutdown is all over that all will get their pay retro active to the layoff! What is the point then to shut down any of it except for the Dems and Obama to try to keep control of their failure to destroy America and the Constitution. Passing a law (TAX) and then exempting yourself and buddies from this tax is wrong and they know it!</Msg><Username>dafarmer9460</Username><Timestamp>1380808909180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380808995354-34</Id><Topic><Title>Reading Hoozdik's Posts are Like Reading the Onion</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380753107116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 18:31:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's put Americans back to work and you watch the deficit decrease....a Jobs bill, please</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380808995354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380809351366-35</Id><Title>Why not make Obamacare voluntary?</Title><Msg>Eliminate all penalties for non participation and make it totally self supporting. Put the medicare money back they stole so they could lie about the cost of this monstrosity. Why do Democrats hate freedom so much?</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380809351366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380809364201-36</Id><Title>Scuzzbuckets Pose with Veterans at WWII Memorial</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- Rep. Michele Bachmann (R-Minn.) on Tuesday promised that she and other members of Congress would personally keep the World War II Memorial open during a government shutdown, in defiance of the U.S. National Park Service. "Every day there's a shutdown, we're going to be here to make sure the veterans get in," Bachmann said. "There'll be some members of Congress here to make sure they get in." Bachmann and several other members of Congress were on hand to visit the World War II Memorial with a group of Mississippi veterans. The group was part of the Mississippi Gulf Coast Honor Flight's trip to Washington, which arrived in town Tuesday morning for a long-anticipated visit to the memorial. The government shutdown complicated their plans. Because of Congress' failure to agree on a continuing resolution to fund the federal government, national parks and monuments are closed nationwide. "Regardless of the shutdown, it makes no sense," said Rep. Steven Palazzo (R-Miss.). "Why close an open air monument?" Palazzo sent a letter Monday to President Barack Obama requesting that veterans be allowed to visit the monument in spite of the government shutdown. National Park Service officials stood by while veterans and Congress members from Mississippi and elsewhere brushed past the barricades. Bagpipes welcomed the veterans as they made their way to the Mississippi section of the memorial.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380809364201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380809577968-37</Id><Title>Barrycades: Try to Close Privately Owned Mount Vernon...</Title><Msg>The National Park Service erected barricades to shut down parking lots surrounding Mount Vernon despite the fact that the tourist destination is privately owned, another example of how the feds are deliberately worsening the government shut down. Mount Vernon is the former plantation of George Washington and is owned by the Mount Vernon Ladies’ Association, which doesn’t receive any government funding. The attraction’s official website reads, “NO SHUTDOWN HERE – The Federal government may be shut down, but Washington’s home remains open. Mount Vernon has remained a private non-profit for more than 150 years.” However, a dispute began when the National Park Service began putting up barricades to block off the facility’s car park, blockading the entrance as well as a spot where tour buses turn around. The parking lots are co-owned by Mount Vernon and the NPS, but require no immediate maintenance at all, meaning the decision to close them down was completely unnecessary.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380809577968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380809808882-38</Id><Title>Monuments and memorials remained open during previous shutdown</Title><Msg>Although President Obama claims that he can’t avoid shutting down public sites and monuments, war memorials were in fact kept open during the 1995/1996 government shutdowns. The administration’s decision to barricade the Lincoln Memorial marks the first time in its history the memorial has been totally off limits to visitors during a shutdown.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380809808882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380810067302-39</Id><Title>Grocery stores on Army bases closed, Obama's golf course open...</Title><Msg>Grocery stores on Army bases in the U.S. are closed. The golf course at Andrews Air Force base is open. All 128 employees of the Saint Lawrence Seaway Development Corp. are working, while 3,000 safety inspectors employed by the Federal Aviation Administration are off the job. The Food and Drug Administration is reviewing new pharmaceuticals. The National Institutes of Health is turning away new patients for clinical trials. The seeming randomness of the U.S. government’s first shutdown in 17 years can be explained in part by anomalies in the spending Congress does and doesn’t control. Activities funded by fees from drug, financial-services and other companies are insulated from year-to-year budget dysfunction. The ones that get a budget from Congress get hit. “What’s really happening in America is that the appropriations process has completely failed,” said Elaine Kamarck, a senior fellow in governance at the Brookings Institution in Washington who worked in the White House during the last shutdown in 1995-96. This isn’t government according to U.S. civics textbooks. Government is supposed to collect taxes, the president is supposed to propose each year how to spend the money, and Congress has the final say with the constitutional power of the purse.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380810067302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380810282147-40</Id><Topic><Title>Scuzzbuckets Pose with Veterans at WWII Memorial</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380809364201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shutting down Obama's big bloated govt, and his leftist Administration has about as much impact as putting a lock on an outhouse door out in the middle of nowhere during sub-zero weather...only the moose, and the Buffalo give a schit.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1380810282147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380811262274-41</Id><Title>Democrats Resort to Favorite Fall-back Tactic - Name Calling and Insults</Title><Msg>When you're out of Ideas just do what any 8 year old would do.......scream, holler stomp your feet and hold your breath. It's entertaining to watch but embarrassing for our country to show the world what infantile and uncivilized leaders our country has under the Obama administration. Democrats, who have long posed as the party of peaceniks and doves, have been anything but during the great rhetorical war of 2013. In fact, the party of George McGovern and Jimmy Carter has been mad as hell as of late, leading an offensive of bombastic insults and rhetorical bullying that has dominated the government shutdown. It’s a perfect storm, with Democrats leading the pace. President Obama called Republicans “reckless and irresponsible,” casting the Grand Old Party in the role of villain. Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid, Nevada Democrat, referred to Republicans as “anarchists,” and House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi, California Democrat, deemed Republicans “legislative arsonists.” “Public attacks make it personal. The response, the entire conversation, goes to the attack, not the problem at hand. The moment there’s an audience, posturing takes over,” said Peter Post, director of the Emily Post Institute and author of five etiquette books. Insults have hidden risks because people don’t always equate aggressive behavior with authority. Roger L. Simon, founder of Pajamas Media, has suggested that Republicans counter Democratic acrimony with a Ronald Reagan-style “charm offensive” to win over disaffected voters. “Democrats have hurled every insult imaginable, such as ‘terrorist,’ ‘arsonist’ and ‘murderers’ against Americans who differ with President Obama. Despite their threats and childish behavior, the speaker has been steadfast in his vision to reduce the size and scope of government and treat everyone fairly,”</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380811262274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380811336069-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why not make Obamacare voluntary?</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380809351366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are communists AT THE TOP who just want POWER FOR THE SAKE OF POWER...its not America any more. ..the rank and file Democrats are just useful idiots ...for that matter some of the Republicans are too</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380811336069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380811338569-43</Id><Topic><Title>Reading Hoozdik's Posts are Like Reading the Onion</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380753107116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 18:31:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did our Pinko hooz have anything to do with establishing Aljazerra News Station here in the states? Does he ride in on his lefty humped camel, and direct the show?</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1380811338569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380811866743-44</Id><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Msg>Who would've known that when Reagan closed all the mental health facilities the patients would get together and form the tea party.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380811866743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380812074422-45</Id><Topic><Title>Why not make Obamacare voluntary?</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380809351366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly right spart.......the GOP establishment is just like the Democrats......it's amazing to watch them fight each other over the same power to control the freedom and lives of Americans. No wonder they both hate and demonize the TEA Party when all it wants is Lower Taxes and a smaller more constitutional government. TEA Part People are the REAL Freedom Fighters.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380812074422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380812123906-46</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Resort to Favorite Fall-back Tactic - Name Calling and Insults</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380811262274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually that comes after the Democrats run out of other people to blame for their incompetency and failures. As for the name calling it now seems that Republicans are racists because they don't want Obama to turns us into a socialist country. Just ask Kooky Roberts or hooz or genna.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1380812123906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380812376296-47</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380811866743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoodz displays multiple personality disorder (he thinks he's Paul McCartney and about 15 other IDs) and also demonstrates his mental disabilities on the BA board on a daily basis and yet the concept of irony constantly escapes him.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380812376296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380812410602-48</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Resort to Favorite Fall-back Tactic - Name Calling and Insults</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380811262274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's all they have as an option. All of their policies are very destructive to the health and welfare of Americans.....so they attempt to character assassinate anyone that doesn't join their destruction campaign. Listen to these libs on this thread. It's the same with libs everywhere.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1380812410602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380812491774-49</Id><Title>Obama Voter Says Barack Obama is A Divider, Not a Uniter</Title><Msg>Mr. President, We thought you were different, but you turned out to be like all the others. You promised hope and change, but we trust government even less than before. You offered a new brand of post-partisan governing, but the red states and blue states are farther apart than ever. Washington was a mess when you arrived in January of 2009, but by breaking your promises and, frankly, our hearts, you made it worse. You vowed to ban lobbyists from the White House only to sneak them in through loopholes. Advertisement You barred corporate donations to the first inauguration but let the special interest money rain down the second time around. You even learned to love super PACs. How could you? Signed, Hopeless and Changed (for the worse)</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380812491774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380812944583-50</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Resort to Favorite Fall-back Tactic - Name Calling and Insults</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380811262274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Listening to Democrats bray one might believe The TEA Party is a bunch of mental deficient terrorist and anarchists......unless you just happen to believe that lower taxes, a smaller government and political leaders that obeys the constitution is a good idea.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380812944583</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380813163164-51</Id><Title>Uh Oh: 36 Percent of Uninsured Americans "Do Not Plan" to Seek Coverage Through Obamacare</Title><Msg>We already knew that in spite of its astronomical costs, Obamacare will leave 30 million Americans uninsured, but a new nationwide Gallup survey suggests that millions of uninsured Americans have no intention of signing up for coverage through the law's exchanges. This is potentially a huge miscalculation by Democrats.</Msg><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380813163164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380813643389-52</Id><Topic><Title>Uh Oh: 36 Percent of Uninsured Americans "Do Not Plan" to Seek Coverage Through Obamacare</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380813163164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:12:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone that thinks a bunch of libtard democrats can run a healthcare plan as large as the economy of France is dumber than a hooz. They couldn't manage a kool-aid stand. ObamaCare depends on a high percentage of 21 yr. olds to sign up for it to even come close to solvency, and that ain't gonna happen. This is democrap policy expecting the general public to be way more stupid than the liberal elites expect them to be.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1380813643389</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380814211412-53</Id><Topic><Title>Uh Oh: 36 Percent of Uninsured Americans "Do Not Plan" to Seek Coverage Through Obamacare</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380813163164</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:12:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree but with one correction. Instead of, "dumber than a hooz", it should be as dumb as a hooz. No one is dumber than a hooz.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1380814211412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380814777719-54</Id><Topic><Title>Scuzzbuckets Pose with Veterans at WWII Memorial</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380809364201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>speaking of moose - Palin wasted no time with her photo ops</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380814777719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380815066128-55</Id><Topic><Title>GOP still trying to create a scandle</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380806842090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>such drama queens</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380815066128</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380815438984-56</Id><Title>Boeing posts delivery info</Title><Msg>Q3 = 170 planes 112 737's, 4 747's, 5 767's, 26 777's, 23 787's. year to date = 476 planes.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380815438984</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380815496865-57</Id><Topic><Title>GOP still trying to create a scandle</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380806842090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems like a wasted effort to me given the many scandals already that should impeach BO. put them on the #$%$ end of a donkey target, and throw darts.....take your pick.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1380815496865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380815580592-58</Id><Topic><Title>GOP still trying to create a scandle</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380806842090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP doesn't need to create any scandals......the Democrats are doing an outstanding job of creating their own.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1380815580592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380815631639-59</Id><Topic><Title>Reading Hoozdik's Posts are Like Reading the Onion</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380753107116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 18:31:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Does he ride in on his lefty humped camel" Well, yes... I do. But hey, I am very careful when considering a vessel of choice. Sorry he scored twice what you did on the qualifying exam.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380815631639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380815720398-60</Id><Topic><Title>GOP still trying to create a scandle</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380806842090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 09:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rockstar, they have never been able to make one stick... and they never will.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380815720398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380815823632-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Voter Says Barack Obama is A Divider, Not a Uniter</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380812491774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:01:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reality suddenly looks a lot different when you snap out of that hypnotic trance and stop shouting "HOPE &amp; CHANGE.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1380815823632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380816210142-62</Id><Topic><Title>The House is the Peoples House</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1380802773697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 08:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The House sort of gave up the power of the purse when they shut down the government.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380816210142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380816285661-63</Id><Title>CA says 5M hits; actual number 645K.....</Title><Msg>California's health insurance exchange vastly overstated the number of online hits it received Tuesday during the rollout of Obamacare. State officials said the Covered California website got 645,000 hits during the first day of enrollment, far fewer than the 5 million it reported Tuesday. The state exchange had cited the 5 million figure as a sign of strong consumer interest and a major reason people had so much difficulty using its $313-million online enrollment system. Dana Howard, a spokesman for Covered California, said the error was the result of internal miscommunication.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1380816285661</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:04:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380816409630-64</Id><Title>Some state websites see less than 1% signup rates...</Title><Msg>California's program registered an estimated 0.58 per cent of website visitors in its first day A Connecticut congressman boasted that his state took 167 applications for Obamacare services on day one, a rate of 0.59 per cent Obama administration won't say how many Americans signed up on the central website that covered insurance exchanges for 36 states Kentucky's 5.3 per cent application rate seems to be the nation's highest Other states wouldn't provide statistics, or tracked only the creation of new online accounts, not numbers of completed applications</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1380816409630</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380816528429-65</Id><Title>Louisiana: Zero Enroll?</Title><Msg>Louisiana’s top health-insurance provider said that not a single person enrolled in a new health-care plan offered through the Affordable Care Act on its first day. An executive with Blue Cross Blue Shield of Louisiana told the Times-Picayune that the agency was unable to sell the plan because customers were unable to access the HealthCare.gov website due to its website’s sluggishness. “It was not as intense as we had anticipated,” the company’s vice president of communication said of the company’s sales. He urged supporters and critics, however, to “take a deep breath and relax” and assured them that the website would eventually allow consumers to enroll in a plan. According to the newspaper, the company spent $60 million in preparation of the October 1 rollout, but the website continued to stall on the day of its rollout. One interested applicant spent five hours trying to get onto the site, but eventually resorted to calling a customer-service representative and was told she would receive plan options via e-mail.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1380816528429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:08:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380816730594-66</Id><Title>Liberal TV Station Can't Find Anyone Who Has Successfully Signed Up for Obamacare</Title><Msg>WSMV in Tennessee was unable to find a single person who successfully signed up for Obamacare: "We're hearing not a single person locally has been successful getting through to the new health insurance exchange," said a local reporter. "It seems to be a problem especially in states like Tennessee, where the state opted out and left it up to the federal government to run what is essentially an online shopping site." The other reporter comes on screen and adds, "Again, as you just said, no one in Tennessee that I know of, according to the counselors I've talked to, has been able to successfully negotiate that federal website."</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1380816730594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:12:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380816978510-67</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think Barack Obama went out his back door to the mall and put up those barricades, Don.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380816978510</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380817532555-68</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380811866743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's first and foremost members are the Mad Hatter and the March Hare.</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1380817532555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380817603572-69</Id><Topic><Title>Why not make Obamacare voluntary?</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380809351366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with Spart-man... The Dems want everyone to do what they want, therefore freedom to choose doesn't work.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1380817603572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380817770297-70</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter how much you stir, Spart, there isn't going to be a tempest in this teacup. When I was in DC, the national archives was closed. Does that mean my first amendment rights were infringed? If closing the WW2 memorial is a 1st amendment infringement, why isn't the closure of the air &amp; space museum?? Anyway, who has suffered from by this closure? We could put up a sign at the WW2 memorial like they put in a movie's screen credits: "No veteran was harmed in the making of this shutdown," Oh, except for the veterans who are NOT getting VA health care during it. Or the ones whose disability compensation MAY be delayed. It is much like the Michele Bachmanns of the world, and their supporters, to wail and moan about denying them the photo op of a visiting a memorial site, but letting them quietly expire out of the way someplace -- maybe a freeway underpass.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380817770297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380818029501-71</Id><Topic><Title>Only a Free Healthcare Market can Make Healthcare Cheaper and Better</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380734357609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 13:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your elected representation has had years to alter or eliminate those institutions. Instead, they chose to protect them even more. Now your elected officials are trying to prevent the rest of us from utilizing them in the best remaining manner possible.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380818029501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380818072489-72</Id><Topic><Title>Why not make Obamacare voluntary?</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380809351366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dems want a bill that was passed by congress, signed into law by the pres, and upheld by the supreme court to be implemented. Is that what you mean by "doing what they want" ?????</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380818072489</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380818175222-73</Id><Topic><Title>Only a Free Healthcare Market can Make Healthcare Cheaper and Better</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380734357609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 13:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380818175222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380818857639-74</Id><Topic><Title>House Republicans ‘Self-Righteous, Orwellian Zebra Queefs’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380817882070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:31:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50% of Stewarts audience are on drugs and the other 50% are bums and government sponges.....he has to bash sensible ideas like living within your financial means and quit spending money you don't have because if he told his audience, "Get sober, get a job and pay your own way", it would be the end of his career.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380818857639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380819291565-75</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is a bunch of Freedom Loving People</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1380743154369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 15:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are trying to prevent me and millions of others from participating in a large pool of health insurance that has already been legislated. And their methods of prevention are keeping me from visiting my National Parks and Memorial. And pretty soon they are going to make me lose face by not paying bills I have already agreed to pay. And soon much of production will stop for lack of government inspectors, which will affect my friends in food processing and manufacturing. And my friends who work in the federal government have already had to apply for unemployment, while this subcult within the House still collects their paychecks.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380819291565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380819428784-76</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"No matter how much you stir, Spart, there isn't going to be a tempest in this teacup." Well said. Oh, and paste that into a file. Seems it's appropriate to use at least once per week</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380819428784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380819526249-77</Id><Topic><Title>House Republicans ‘Self-Righteous, Orwellian Zebra Queefs’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380817882070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:31:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"50% of Stewarts audience are on drugs and the other 50% are bums and government sponges" Could you provide a reputable source for that claim ( keeping in mind you are not one ).</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380819526249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380819689054-78</Id><Title>Tesla Goes Up in Flames, Tesla Stock Tanks, Wayne (aka elonmusk909 &amp; fred.james48) on Suicide Watch</Title><Msg>- Tesla Motors confirmed yesterday that the car was destroyed by a battery fire. - It is believed that the car struck some kind of small object in the road, which then impacted the battery, causing the battery to break out the charcoal briquettes and start an old fashioned, Texas-style barbecue. Apparently, one cannot drive one of these things down the road without the risk of it spontaneously launching itself into “self-imolation” mode and burning you alive. Some have referred to the vehicle as a “crematorium on wheels”. - Concerned that Tesla’s cars may have a chronic battery problem, Tesla’s stock dropped $12 a share in a single day and Wayne lost his shirt. - Homeless, dirty, disheveled and wearing urine-stained pants, Wayne was recently seen “panhandling” on a local street corner in an attempt to make up for his losses. It is rumored that he was heard mumbling, “Brother can you spare a dime?”</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1380819689054</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380820378193-79</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing posts delivery info</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380815438984</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With 16 787's in some form of preflight or test flight and 3 ready for delivery, Boeing should be able to hit the target of 60 787 deliveries for the year. And with 476 planes delivered so far, they should be able to easily exceed 600 planes this year with just the 737.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380820378193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380821188490-80</Id><Title>Thanks Tea Party for my losses today and this past week</Title><Msg>how much more are you going to make me lose until you get your heads out of your butts?</Msg><Username>toby8989</Username><Timestamp>1380821188490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380821992427-81</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal TV Station Can't Find Anyone Who Has Successfully Signed Up for Obamacare</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1380816730594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:12:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many tried?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380821992427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380822125473-82</Id><Topic><Title>Some state websites see less than 1% signup rates...</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1380816409630</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. 167 = 0.59% It must be a pretty popular website.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380822125473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380822219711-83</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re first amendment this from the seattle times socialist daily via mcclatchy McClatchy Washington Bureau WASHINGTON — The tourists from China didn’t know what to make of it as they contemplated the sign posted in front of one of Washington’s grand memorials. “Because of the federal government shutdown, this National Park Service area is closed except for First Amendment activities,” the sign declared. Did that mean they weren’t supposed to walk up to the memorial, a giant bronze flaming sword commemorating those who died in the 2nd Division of the U.S. Army? They weren’t sure. Neither was their escort from Pennsylvania, John Li, who didn’t know if looking at a memorial is covered by the First Amendment, which among other things grants freedom of speech and the right to peaceably assemble. “That’s hard to tell,” he said. ++ So just what does that mean- can one person assemble ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380822219711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380822263725-84</Id><Topic><Title>House Republicans ‘Self-Righteous, Orwellian Zebra Queefs’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380817882070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 12:31:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably from the same folks who supply Chemical Ali Infested's climate data.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1380822263725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380822704700-85</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And apparently- the Normandy beaches in france and the U.S Cemetary is SHUT DOWN !! Be sure to thank OBAMA administraton for their support of veterans- and refusing to allow fubnding for thebn ' park service " but be polite- no threats or obscene language !! Didn;t know the normandy beaches were ceded to the U.S as was the cemetary ???</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380822704700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380823025029-86</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Voter Says Barack Obama is A Divider, Not a Uniter</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380812491774</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 11:01:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopium--feels real good until it wears off.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380823025029</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380823249923-87</Id><Topic><Title>More Security cops deployed to defending closure of WW memorials</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380755202469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 19:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US government shutdown on Tuesday affected military cemeteries worldwide. In France, the famous Omaha Beach cemetery, where thousands of US troops who died in key battles during the First and Second World Wars are buried, was temporarily shut. By FRANCE 24 (text) Iconic military cemeteries around the world where thousands of American soldiers who died in the First and Second World Wars lay to rest were temporarily closed from Tuesday due to the US government shutdown. A sign outside the Suresnes American Cemetery and Memorial, west of Paris, informed visitors of its closure. “Due to the United States government shutdown, this site is closed to the public” But Suresnes isn’t the only one. The move affects some 20 cemeteries in France, Belgium, Britain, Italy, Tunisia and Mexico which serve as the final resting place for troops who died in landmark campaigns such as the Normandy D-Day landings, the American Battle Monuments Commission (ABMC) said on its website.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380823249923</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380823915743-88</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is a bunch of Freedom Loving People</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1380743154369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-02 15:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So. the TEA Party is not doing anything illegal.......you just don't like it when they do the same things Democrats do to their opponents.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380823915743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:11:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380824621243-89</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing spin and complete nonsense. There is no way the far right Republicans are going to come out of this one with out damaging themselves and the Country with this childish actions.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380824621243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380824924502-90</Id><Title>104,000 Strong: Tea Party Patriots Have Record Turnout for Cruz on Tele-Townhall</Title><Msg>The Tea Party Patriots blew away expectations at last night's tele-townhall on the Continuing Resolution with 104,000 participants for Senator Ted Cruz (R-TX) and Rep. Jim Bridenstine (R-OK). The previous record for an event was three weeks ago when 67,000 participants attended. TPP Co-founder Jenny Beth Martin stated, "no special measures were taken to draw the crowd—only the standard Facebook post for two hours and a robocall earlier in the day." The pupose of the tele-townhall was to get TPP members up to date on the latest developments in the ongoing battle to defund Obamacare. It was the TPP's rallies during the congressional recess in August that drove interest in the current hard-line strategy. Senator Cruz laid out a series of action items that grassroots activists could take on a daily basis to stop Obamacare. These measures included everything from signing petitions to doing blog and Facebook posts. Cruz emphasized the importance of citizens talking to their neighbors about Obamacare and enlisting more people around the country to join the movement to stop its implementation. Of particular note was his call for TPP members to get the word out on the special Obamcare exemption for Congress. Calls were taken from the participants, and several veterans expressed the importance of getting veterans to join the group. Rep. Bridenstine , a former fighter pilot, expressed his frustration with House Democrats in clocking a rule change that would allow funding of the Department of Veterans Affairs. Tea Party Patriot officials believe the intensity of emotions to continue the fight against Obamacare will carry through the upcoming debt ceiling negotiations. Martin noted that the tele-townhall four weeks ago drew over 50,000 participants, and active engagement by grassroots is building with each passing day.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824924502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380824929036-91</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama hates older people especially older white people except the older White men who are willing to perform non-reciprocating fellatio on him. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380824929036</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380825080144-92</Id><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Msg>.....by demanding our politicians follow the constitution and fighting for lower taxes and a smaller less intrusive Federal government.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380825264938-93</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then there is no hope, because the tea party is finished.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380825264938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380825297743-94</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America will be Much Stronger When out Politicians fight back at those who want to take away our freedoms. Healthcare is a personal responsibility not a right.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825297743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380825340182-95</Id><Title>Republicans are failing Americans</Title><Msg>AMERICANS’ RESPECT for their Congress has, sad to say, diminished in recent years. But citizens still expect a minimal level of competence and responsibility: Pay the bills and try not to embarrass us in front of the world. By those minimal standards, this Congress is failing. More specifically, the Republican leaders of the House of Representatives are failing. They should fulfill their basic duties to the American people or make way for legislators who will. We don’t come to that view as rabid partisans. On many of the issues stalemating Washington, we find plenty of blame to go around. We’ve criticized President Obama’s reluctance to pursue entitlement reform. The last time the country reached the debt ceiling, we urged both sides to compromise on revenue and spending in the interest of long-term fiscal soundness. This time, fiscal responsibility isn’t even a topic. Instead, Republicans have shut much of the government in what they had to know was a doomed effort to derail the Affordable Care Act. That law, in case you've forgotten in the torrent of propaganda, is hardly revolutionary. It is an effort to extend health insurance to some of the 40 million or so people in this country who have none. It acts through the existing private-insurance market. Republicans tried to block its passage and failed; they hoped to have it declared unconstitutional and failed; and they did their best to toss Mr. Obama out of the White House after one term in order to strangle it in its cradle, and they failed again. They’re entitled to keep trying, of course — though it would be nice if someday they remembered their promise to come up with an alternative proposal. But their methods now are beyond the pale. After months of refusing to confer with the Senate on a budget proposal, they have demanded a conference committee to keep the government funded for six weeks. They are rejecting a budget extension that includes limits on federal spending — the so-called sequester — that they insisted on and that Democrats oppose. In a particularly shabby piece of faux populism, their final proposal Monday night included a measure to deprive congressional aides, many of whom earn considerably less than the esteemed members, of the subsidy to purchase health insurance that employers routinely provide. That measure was emblematic of Republicans’ heedlessness of the impact of their actions on ordinary Americans and their government. Incoming FBI Director James B. Comey was stunned to discover that his agency has had to stop training recruits, close criminal cases and even deny gasoline money to agents because of budget cutbacks, as The Post’s Sari Horwitz reported. Now, with the shutdown, 800,000 workers are being furloughed, and thousands of others are being ordered to work but may not get paid. And these effects pale beside the economic havoc that would be caused by a failure to honor the government’s financial obligations, a prospect that looms just a couple of weeks ahead. Speaker John Boehner, Majority Leader Eric Cantor, Budget Committee chairman and former vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan and their colleagues may be in a difficult political position. Honestly, we don’t much care. They need to reopen the government and let it pay its bills.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380825340182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:35:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380825371640-96</Id><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Msg>by creating policies that enslave the people and transferring wealth to the few.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380825469673-97</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The TEA Party will never be finished as long as there are REAL AMERICANS willing to stand up for the cause of liberty.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825469673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380825620288-98</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You obviously don't have a clue what Capitalism and Free Markets are.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825620288</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380825847089-99</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380811866743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you are a pathogical LIAR who welches on bets</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380825847089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826009288-100</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380811866743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Reagan closed those facilities, all those patients were relabeled 'criminals' and are now housed in the jail and prison system, where the personnel are little prepared to handle the mentally ill and deficient.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826009288</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826192862-101</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are failing Americans</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380825340182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can vote the republicans out of office if you want just like the American public voted the Democrats out of office. Our constitution creates checks and balances against abusive political tyrants like the Democrats. We elected people we want fighting for our freedom not to have our personal responsibilities controlled by an over reaching and intrusive government. The TEA Party members are doing exactly what we want them to do. If that changes, we'll vote against them ourselves. Ain't freedom great!</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826192862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826332141-102</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in your opinion what is a Free Market ?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380826332141</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826405070-103</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tea party will pretty much be finish after this latest screw up by them. and you`re either an American or not, you`re just fantasizing again with the term Real Americans. A Real American don`t hide out on some fantasy island not even in America.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380826405070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380826416338-104</Id><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Msg>When history is strewn with calamities and disastrous wreckage where it's been tried?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826446767-105</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where exactly in the constitution does it say that a legitimate way to repeal a law is NOT through the legislative process, but through holding a budget hostage? The tea party is all about the Constitution, except when it doesn't like the results. They are nothing like they think they are, they are spoiled brats.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1380826446767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380826469061-106</Id><Title>I don't see any Repube legislation passed</Title><Msg>turning down their gov't pay while they shut down the gov't \or demanding they not be exemot from Obamacare why because they are a bunch of two-faced lying hypocrites feeding their low-information and low IQ constituents as they take them to the slaughter house</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380826469061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826472763-107</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A personal responsibility that has been made unachievable for millions by colluding doctors, hospitals and insurance companies. Congress has had years to enact remedies to this problem, but chose not to. When a solution was produced, they passed it. Now a handful are holding it and us hostage.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826472763</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380826540893-108</Id><Title>Boehner: "The President is stubbornly refusing to end this crisis I created."</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (The Borowitz Report)—Speaker of the House John Boehner (R-Ohio) said that he was disappointed after meeting with President Obama at the White House on Wednesday afternoon, telling reporters, “The President is stubbornly refusing to end the crisis I created.” “Government is about teamwork,” Mr. Boehner continued. “I’ve done my part by putting together an entirely optional crisis that has shut down the government and will throw thousands out of work. Now it’s up to the President to do his part by ending it.” Mr. Boehner said that he was “flabbergasted” that the President was looking to him to bring the current government shutdown to an end: “So after doing all of the hard work to push the country to the brink, I’m supposed to pull it back, too? How about you pitching in a little, Mr. President?” The House Speaker said that he hoped he did not have to manufacture another entirely avoidable crisis over the debt ceiling in order to stir the President to action. “Quite frankly, orchestrating these unnecessary stalemates takes a lot of energy and I could really use a rest,” he said. But Mr. Boehner seemed pessimistic that the President “got the message.” “Because of my actions, thousands of federal workers have already been furloughed,” he said. “How many more people do I have to throw out on the street before the President wakes up?”</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380826540893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:55:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380826618982-109</Id><Title>Republicans will trade Obamacare for your Social Security</Title><Msg>yes - America may keep ACA but Republicans will gut Social Security, SNAP, Medicare, Medicaid in trade....!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380826618982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826663542-110</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They overplayed their hand. It was amusing for awhile to watch them play house. Now they've done damage to the country, and mainstream Republicans are tired of them and would like them to go away.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380826663542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826791429-111</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really ? next time you plan on driving thru I-5 - Dont - buy your own Highway !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380826791429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380826945767-112</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner: "The President is stubbornly refusing to end this crisis I created."</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380826540893</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:55:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does the Boehner still find the time to make his average of seven stock trades per day during the crisis which he created and demands the president to end according to terms/condtions of 30 tbaggers...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380826945767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380826946461-113</Id><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Msg>Not much known.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380827461582-114</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are failing Americans</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380825340182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What nonsense the tea party is just a front the far right hides behined there is nothing patriotic about them at all. their goal is to get their way through programed propaganda and getting a lot of fools to repeat them word for word everyday.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380827461582</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380827464451-115</Id><Title>Republicans Attempt Coup d'état on Capitol Hill</Title><Msg>Witnesses reported hearing gunshots outside the Capitol after 2 p.m. Thursday, setting off a huge police response and heightened security inside the Capitol, which was already tense during shutdown negotiations. “Gunshots have been reported on Capitol Hill requiring staff in all Senate office buildings to immediately shelter in place,” read an e-mail sent out by the Capitol Police. “Close, lock and stay away from external doors and windows. Take annunciators, emergency supply kits and escape hoods; and move to your office’s assigned shelter in place location or the innermost part of the office away from external doors or windows.” Members not near their own offices were asked to go to the nearest office, and shelter there. Capitol police officers could be seen with semiautomatic rifles drawn as they scrambled for position on the Capitol grounds. Several senators were outside the Capitol when they reported between four and six shots fired. Police officers in a high-speed chase pulled over a black car in front of one of the Senate office buildings, but witnesses said a man fled on foot with a gun visible. “I heard a pop-pop-pop, and we were told to get down,” said Senator Bob Casey, Democrat of Pennsylvania.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380827464451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380827801231-116</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have my own private highway.....many others do too and they are better than and were built and maintained for far less then government roads. I've built several bridges too - always better and cheaper than the government could - that's why I could always sell them to the government for huge profits.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380827801231</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380828372353-117</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where exactly in the Constitution does it say the President can unilaterally change, modify and exempt political cronies and supporter from a law?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380828372353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380828450552-118</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>quite a few tea party members are crazy and have hallucinations too, I see you fit right in.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380828450552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380828523186-119</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are failing Americans</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380825340182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you mean repeat foolish slogans like "Hope and Change" and "Yes we can?"</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380828523186</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380828664964-120</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@ Constitution and 2nd must be a bagger bigot</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380828664964</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:31:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380828868205-121</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you have proof of colluding doctors, you can file charges and have them put in jail. Same for hospitals and insurance companies. But not so for politicians and government agencies who can dictate prices below cost then shift the balance of the real cost to doctors, hospitals and insurance companies.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380828868205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:34:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380829144396-122</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know....you're probably right rockstar.....you almost have to be a little crazy and hallucinating to expect or even hope that a libtard will see any value in individual liberty.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380829144396</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380829455122-123</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually I did help build part of I-5 - the part between Wolf creek and Quines creek Oregon.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380829455122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380829647975-124</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean individual liberty like abortion, birth control, legal marihuana? lol nice try</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380829647975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380829731285-125</Id><Title>ROUHANI BOASTS: I REJECTED OBAMA 5 TIMES...</Title><Msg>Iran's President Hassan Rouhani told reporters on Wednesday that he turned down five requests from U.S. President Barack Obama to meet at the United Nations, according to Iran's semi-official Fars News Agency. Rouhani said: "Before my trip (to New York), the Americans had sent 5 messages to arrange a meeting between me and Obama, but I turned them down."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380829731285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380830003379-126</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be specific, who is exempt? What was changed and modified to benefit cronies? Facts only please, not the usual lies running around out there.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1380830003379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380830031845-127</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One dead female suspect who tried to drive car through White House fence.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380830031845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380830117983-128</Id><Title>This is a Test</Title><Msg>.....to see which GOPers are real patriots like the TEA Party members and which ones need to be replaced. This is a hostile takeover of the GOP because the establishments Republicans refused to do their job and counter the Democrat's move to the left and toward socialism.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380831629331-129</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has been treating the Obamacare “Law” as a malleable bill for three years?” There are many examples of administrative actions taken that contradict the wording of the Affordable Care Act, but here are a few: over 1200 ObamaCare waivers have been granted since the law’s passage, primarily to labor unions. The administration has also abandoned the CLASS Act part of ObamaCare, and the administration has delayed the law’s date of implementation for the employer mandate for two years. None of these actions have any basis in the wording of the law as passed by Congress.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380831629331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380831828903-130</Id><Topic><Title>Why not make Obamacare voluntary?</Title><Username>ireadhistory2</Username><Timestamp>1380809351366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You DO realize Obamacare is a tax..(the Supreme Court said so) but a tax that does not go to the Government..but Big Insurance corporations. ... It is a Transfer of wealth from the middle class right into the hands of the Power Elite...but that is all part of the NEW Freedom...its all trendy and liberal...Obama loves you</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380831828903</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380831934501-131</Id><Title>Too bad poor kids in Chicago are forced to attend public schools</Title><Msg>The private school I attended spends $3,000/year/student less than a public school for education and has just released their 2013 graduating class results. -97% are university or college bound -249 college scholarships were EARNED -$9,400,000 in scholarship money EARNED -Average scholarship EARNED was $71,212/student I would give my school an A+ whereas Chicago public schools get a solid F for being one of the worst school systems in the country while being one of the most expensive.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380831934501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380832361896-132</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380811866743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bapsycho - I'm sure you miss the white jacket they used to give you before Reagan closed the mental health facility that you called home. I see you're still delusional. How many times must you be told not to skip taking your meds?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380832361896</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380833271374-133</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have enslaved yourself by being dependent on others for your happiness, as you are obviously not happy. It is people like you destroying America as you demand that everyone to be as unhappy, pathetic, dependent and as much of an underachiever as you. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380833271374</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380833465344-134</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A free market is when I have something you want and you have something I want and we both think it will be to our advantage to exchange those things without any interference.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380833465344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380834046593-135</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exactly what Obamacare does....Transfers wealth from Middle Class small business flks...and transfers it in the form of a tax to the Elite Insurance companies ...not very egalitarian and not very liberal is it ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380834046593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380834901995-136</Id><Title>Obama Sued for Changing Obamacare Law</Title><Msg>It was last July when Obama announced he was delaying the requirement for employers to provide adequate and affordable health insurance starting Jan. 1, 2014, or pay huge fines. Obama, responding to complaints from businesses, changed the effective date to Jan. 1, 2015, strategically after the 2014 elections. The suit was filed in the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of Florida on behalf of Boca Raton-based employer Kawa Orthodontics LLP. It argues that the delay of the employer mandate “exceeded [the Obama administration's] statutory authority, is arbitrary, capricious, and contrary to law, and is otherwise unlawful.” The employer mandate, which subjects certain large employers to tax penalties if they do not offer “affordable,” “minimum essential” health insurance coverage to their employees, is “one of the pillars” of Obamacare, according to Judicial Watch. But Obama’s decision to suddenly announce a change in the law caused Kawa Orthodontics “to lose the value of its substantial efforts to prepare for the controversial provision taking effect beginning next year.” “[Kawa Orthodontics] expended substantial time and resources, including money spent on legal fees and other costs, in preparation for the ‘employer mandate’ taking effect on January 1, 2014….[The company] would not have expended its time and resources and incurred these anticipatory costs in 2013 if the mandate had not been scheduled to take effect until 2015, but instead would have spent its time, resources, and money on other priorities,” the action explains. The action is being brought on behalf of Larry Kawa of Kawa Orthodontics against the U.S. Department of Treasury, Secretary of Treasury Jack Lew, the Internal Revenue Service and IRS Acting Director Daniel Werfel. Kawa is a longtime Florida resident and business leader with a company that employs about 70. The complaint alleges that the decision to delay the employer mandate violates the Administrative Procedure Act, which forbids “agency action” that exceeds an agency’s statutory authority, is arbitrary, capricious, an abuse of discretion, or otherwise not in accordance with the law. The complaint asks the court to enter a judgment declaring the delay to be unlawful and an injunction prohibiting the delay. “We obviously object to the employer mandate and the entire Obamacare law, but we understand that, under the U.S. Constitution, the law can only be changed by legislation passed by Congress and signed by the president. President Obama would delay the damage of his health care scheme until after the 2014 congressional elections. But politics do not trump the Constitution or the rule of law,” said Judicial Watch President Tom Fitton. “And to paraphrase Ulysses S. Grant, the best way to ensure the repeal of a bad law is to enforce it vigorously.” Kawa added: “I am tired of Washington, D.C., picking winners and losers and giving preferential treatment to those inside the Beltway. This is just more of D.C. career politicians protecting their own.” The legal challenge was filed on the same day Obamacare websites intended to recruit millions of Americans to sign up for Obamacare policies opened.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380834901995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380835433283-137</Id><Title>Obama Administration Forces Hundreds of Privately Funded Parks to Close Amid Shutdown</Title><Msg>The Obama Administration is ordering hundreds of parks that sit on federal land to close amid the government shutdown -- even though they don't use any government funding. Operators of Claude Moore Colonial Farm in Virginia, for example, say they were shocked when the National Park Service ordered their park be shut. That's because it's been 80% funded by a local non-profit for years, which agreed to take over 100% of the costs of the facility as of October 1. Still, the National Park Service spent taxpayer money to erect barricades around the park and evict everyone from the farm this week. “We do not know why CMCF was barricaded from public access or why NPS police escorted staff and volunteers off the property right before a fundraising event on Monday. The National Park Service does not pay CMCFs employees, for its operations, maintenance, events or programs,” Claude Moore Colonial Farm Operations Manager Heather Bodin wrote in an email to FOX Business. "In our 32-year history of running the farm, through other government shutdowns, we have never had to close our doors before.” The same is true for the more than 100 U.S. Forest Service campgrounds and day-use areas run by the Arizona-based company Recreation Resource Management. In a letter to his congressman, RRM's owner and president Warren Meyer writes that his parks haven't been affected by past government shutdowns because "our operations are self-sufficient (we are fully funded by user fees at the gate), we get no federal funds, we employ no government workers on these sites, and we actually pay rent into the Treasury." However, Meyer says he too got orders yesterday, directly from the White House, to close up shop. "I can only assume their intention is to artificially increase the cost of the shutdown as some sort of political ploy," Meyer said in his letter. "The point of the shutdown is to close non-essential operations that require Federal money and manpower to stay open. So why is the White House closing private operations that require no government money to keep open and actually pay a percentage of their gate revenues back to the Treasury? We are a tenant of the U.S. Forest Service, and a tenant does not have to close his business just because his landlord goes on a vacation."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380835433283</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380835626239-138</Id><Topic><Title>The TEA Party is America's Last Great Hope to Preserve Freedom.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380825080144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said specific, which labor unions, the only thing I've seen on that was the rejection. On Politico "W.H. rejects labor’s bid for Obamacare exemption" go look. So far your one example is BS. As usual, you make up stuff because you have nothing. Show me something specific that can be verified.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1380835626239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:27:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380835826914-139</Id><Topic><Title>104,000 Strong: Tea Party Patriots Have Record Turnout for Cruz on Tele-Townhall</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824924502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:28:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i have this mental picture now of 104,000 mostly far Righties at a Tele Tubby convention all rubbing each others belly's singing Laaa Laaa Laaa.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380835826914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380835956385-140</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America is doing just fine and in time will weed out all you new generation tech savy "pan handlers". One day the free money wont be there for all you takers and you will "eat your young" or you will be "Darwined" off the planet because you raided the pantry of a fellow liberal and he used his illegally gotten gun on you.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1380835956385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:32:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380836224163-141</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are failing Americans</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380825340182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every President has a slogan they run on since that election the only people I hear repeating it are folks you can do nothing but remain negative and only look for the bad side of things. take a look at some Presidential slogans from the past this is a good laugh. Campaign Candidate Slogan 1840 William Henry Harrison Tippecanoe and Tyler Too 1844 James K. Polk 54-40 or fight 1844 James K. Polk Reannexation of Texas and reoccupation of Oregon 1844 Henry Clay Who is James K. Polk? 1848 Zachary Taylor For President of the People 1856 John C. Fremont Free Soil, Free Labor, Free Speech, Free Men, and Fremont 1860 Abraham Lincoln Vote Yourself a Farm 1864 Abraham Lincoln Don't swap horses in the middle of the stream 1884 Grover Cleveland Blaine, Blaine, James G. Blaine, The Continental Liar from the State of Maine 1884 James Blaine Ma, Ma, Where’s my Pa, Gone to the White House, Ha, Ha, Ha 1888 Benjamin Harrison Rejuvenated Republicanism 1896 William McKinley Patriotism, Protection, and Prosperity 1896 William McKinley Good money never made times hard 1900 William McKinley A Full Dinner Pail 1916 Woodrow Wilson He kept us out of war 1920 Warren G. Harding Return to normalcy 1920 Warren G. Harding Cox and Cocktails 1924 Calvin Coolidge Keep cool with Coolidge 1928 Herbert Hoover A chicken in every pot and a car in every garage 1952 Dwight Eisenhower I Like Ike 1956 Dwight Eisenhower Peace and Prosperity 1960 Richard Nixon For the future 1964 Lyndon B. Johnson The stakes are too high for you to stay at home 1964 Barry Goldwater In your heart you know he’s right 1968 Richard Nixon Nixon's the One 1976 Gerald Ford He’s making us proud again 1976 Jimmy Carter Not Just Peanuts 1976 Jimmy Carter A Leader, For a Change 1980 Ronald Reagan Are you better off than you were four years ago? 1984 Ronald Reagan It’s morning again in America 1984 Walter Mondale America Needs a Change 1988 George Bush Kinder, Gentler Nation 1992 Bill Clinton Don’t stop thinking about tomorrow 1992 Bill Clinton Putting People First 1992 Ross Perot Ross for Boss 1996 Bill Clinton Building a bridge to the 21st century 1996 Bob Dole The Better Man for a Better America 2000 Al Gore Prosperity and progress 2000 Al Gore Prosperity for America's families 2000 George W. Bush Compassionate conservatism 2000 George W. Bush Leave no child behind 2000 George W. Bush Real plans for real people 2000 George W. Bush Reformer with results 2000 Ralph Nader Government of, by, and for the people...not the monied interests 2004 John Kerry Let America be America Again 2004 George W. Bush Yes, America Can! 2008 John McCain Country First 2008 Barack Obama Change We Can Believe In 2008 Barack Obama Change We Need 2008 Barack Obama Hope 2008 Barack Obama Yes We Can! 2012 Barack Obama Forward 2012 Mitt Romney Believe in America</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380836224163</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380836537287-142</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"that's why I could always sell them to the government for huge profits" Then why do you want less government spending, you idiot? Dude, you're embarrassing yourself.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1380836537287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380836662095-143</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are failing Americans</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380825340182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see one the local ediot tea party gofer wannabes is spouting his normal warped opinions against basic healthcare for Americans. We stick our Troops into the middle of religious wars, that your teaparty and republican mentors championed, expending American treasure and blood, but youall cant find a way to open hearts here in America and help fellow Americans. Wrong from a strictly business/economic level and wrong from an American Christian basic value and principle</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1380836662095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380836749945-144</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla Goes Up in Flames, Tesla Stock Tanks, Wayne (aka elonmusk909 &amp; fred.james48) on Suicide Watch</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1380819689054</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 13:01:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it for Wayne Dickley.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1380836749945</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380836809241-145</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Parents make all the decision for a child once it`s born up to about 18 yrs of age. Parents should have the only decision that matters not some politician and or religions people. It is their individual liberty at stake. I forgot to mention gay marriage, there is another individual liberty I hear the people who are screaming about having their liberty's taken away can`t accept.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380836809241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380836927052-146</Id><Topic><Title>startling claims about the objectionable practices The ACA will sanction -- most of them totally false.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380831761008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:22:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The propaganda campaign surrounding Obamacare may be the most widespread onslaught of misinformation since the McCarthy inquisitions of the 1950s." Man, that's the truth.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1380836927052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:48:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380837286548-147</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The average liberal SOB on the street doesn't understand that America no longer has a democrat party. Socialist and Communist lawmakers now control the extinction of the democratic party for the new Anarchist Party.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1380837286548</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380837598056-148</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe, but not likely. The child that was carried away by police after the shooting is clearly African-American. Too early to draw concrete conclusions - except by "block heads".</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1380837598056</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380837620748-149</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Communism will bury what's left of America in the end for the more brutalTotalitarianism.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1380837620748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:00:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380837913960-150</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also seems a suspect in custody, no one deceased.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380837913960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380837928597-151</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike Democrats, I love my country and the concept of individual liberty far more than I love profits. The less the government spends, the more the same capital the government would have spent/wasted/used to buy votes will be used to create wealth in the private sector. I like the way the private sector distributes that wealth much better than I do the villainous way the government distributes it. And I don't mind competing with others to get a fair share of it. That's why I'm rich and you mediocre class guys are whining for the government to provide something you aren't willing to pay for yourselves.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380837928597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380838095158-152</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post BB......that's the usual and typical post full of hope......most time it turns out to be an Obama voter.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380838095158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380838297698-153</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I see. You didn't draw any conclusion whatsoever after learning the child is African-American. The correct spelling is hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380838297698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380838422800-154</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The average knee-kerk right-fringer on the street doesn't know the difference beween Socialist, Communist, Anarchist or Democrat. All he knows is that they are "not like him." Harharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380838422800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380838496770-155</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: "knee-jerk right-fringer". Like sdmiller.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380838496770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380839490318-156</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent (Himmler) Raven likes that..........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1380839490318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380839533016-157</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: sdmiller is so despicable they kicked him out of the right wing.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1380839533016</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380839609672-158</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Kent (Himmler) Raven alias flapping his gums.................</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1380839609672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380839666655-159</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"most time it turns out to be an Obama voter." Are you sure about that?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380839666655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380839799632-160</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great question. I know why it is for those who make big money off of govt expansionism, but the ave. Joes that support it I have no idea. It screws them even if they are in a private sector union, and now ObamaCare really screws them.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1380839799632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380839860675-161</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris, There goes that apparent "hate thing" again. I know that you didn't really read or comprehend my post because, perhaps, you seethe with anger and frustration. But I will cull for you, from the post the "key words": "maybe", "not likely", "too early to draw concrete conclusions". We know that greater than 90% of African-Americans vote Democrat. That fact is what I used to simply point out the lack of probability of baps' assertion regarding "bagger bigot" - which, as we know, does not normally describe a person of African-American heritage.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1380839860675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380840049257-162</Id><Topic><Title>startling claims about the objectionable practices The ACA will sanction -- most of them totally false.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380831761008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:22:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And still put mildly.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380840049257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380840093230-163</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an idiot that has to be on drugs. Workers move up the economic ladder daily. It isn't a static number. Many CEO's started out at the bottom of the ladder. In the 80's Bill Gates created 4,000 millionaires in the Seattle area alone. Many were software workers with below ave salaries for the industry. Was your point that you are a lazy libtard that doesn't like to work?</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1380840093230</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380840384157-164</Id><Topic><Title>House GOP is failing Americans in their effort to kill ObamaCare</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380838238672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great editorial.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380840384157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380841132912-165</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380811866743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chemical Ali Infested forget the teenage-girl-speak this time: "lol." Must be an imposter.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1380841132912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380842252830-166</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'll never have anything I'll want at any price. That may be free but it's no market.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380842252830</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380842297365-167</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like you saw the movie "Inequality for All"</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380842297365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:18:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380842385890-168</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380811866743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 10:51:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But they can make a lot of money mishandling them.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380842385890</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380842474169-169</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://news.yahoo.com/capitol-hill-on-lockdown-after-reports-of-shots-fired-183834445.html</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380842474169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380842641634-170</Id><Topic><Title>Too bad poor kids in Chicago are forced to attend public schools</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380831934501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you're so poorly educated you expect people to believe the unsupported claims of an anonymous internet poster--'cause you think that we're as dumb as you are.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380842641634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380843174249-171</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@Constitution and 2nd, after trying to 'ram' the WH oh, the irony it would be maenwhile, "We know that greater than 90% of African-Americans vote Democrat" because according to the bagger bigots Democrats are the party of the KKK, right Miriam Carey, from CT sounds Irish to me, but could be African_American Irish</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380843174249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380843912968-172</Id><Topic><Title>What more proof do you need that the TP/GOP is crazy than this......</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380842981500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like they are going to form a committee to pick and chose which part of the government they shut down shall be re-opened "All animals are equal". Snowball teaches the animals reading and writing while Napoleon educates young puppies on the principles of Animalism. The pigs elevate themselves to positions of leadership and set aside special food items, ostensibly for their personal health. Napoleon and Snowball struggle for preeminence. When Snowball announces his plans to build a windmill, Napoleon has his dogs chase Snowball away and subsequently declares himself leader of Animal Farm. Napoleon enacts changes to the governance structure of the farm, replacing meetings with a committee of pigs who will run the farm. Through a young pig named Squealer, Napoleon claims credit for the windmill idea. The animals work harder with the promise of easier lives with the windmill. When the animals find the windmill collapsed after a violent storm, Napoleon and Squealer convince the animals that Snowball is trying to sabotage their project. Once Snowball becomes a scapegoat, Napoleon begins purging the farm with his dogs, killing animals he accuses of consorting with his old rival. 'Beasts of England' is replaced by an anthem glorifying Napoleon, who appears to be adopting the lifestyle of a man. -- ...some are more equal than others</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380843912968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380844274951-173</Id><Topic><Title>Too bad poor kids in Chicago are forced to attend public schools</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380831934501</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 16:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ali -infested Squealer - The pig who spreads Napoleon’s propaganda among the other animals. Squealer justifies the pigs’ monopolization of resources and spreads false statistics pointing to the farm’s success. Orwell uses Squealer to explore the ways in which those in power often use rhetoric and language to twist the truth and gain and maintain social and political control. Republican presidential candidate Rick Santorum lit into President Obama at a Americans for Prosperity Tea Party event in Troy, Michigan over his advocacy for higher learning. “President Obama once said he wants everybody in America to go to college,” Santorum sniped. “What a snob!”</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380844274951</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380844418376-174</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have plenty of things you want. Oil, gas, Beef, Sugar.....just try to do with out them. You may not buy these things from me directly but you will still end up buying them them and I will still end up with money paid for them. Why are liberals so hateful and angry.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380844418376</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380844707697-175</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sound full of oil, beef, and sugar resulting in gas try some Beano</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380844707697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 19:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380844924802-176</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul: Putz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380840338002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's more confirmation that revelation about Pauly Rand.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380844924802</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845028066-177</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm only trying top help you get right with God, Bob. If I can't do that, I'll just shake the dirt from my sandals and move on.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380845028066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845064071-178</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, toddlers don't vote.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380845064071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845129691-179</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't want your sulfurous oil, your watery gas, your hormone-laden beef, or your tainted sugar.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380845129691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845159086-180</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm only trying top help you get right with God, Bob." How is that working for YOU?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1380845159086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845231573-181</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does anybody else remember that scene in "Food, Inc" where they jabbed a downer cow with a forklift to make it get up so they could slaughter it? Mir runs a downer cow ranch.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380845231573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845265165-182</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul: Putz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380840338002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: That's more confirmation than revelation about Randy Paul.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380845265165</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845300160-183</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it's time for another Mir(de) screed including converting C to F like that time he stated thrice that -50 is the same on both scales, then flaccidly tried to say all 3 were typos. Private schools on display! Mir(de) was funny that day.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1380845300160</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845310111-184</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess YOU don't like being preached to -- either.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380845310111</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845515727-185</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think mir realized he was presenting one of the more compelling cases for capitalism when he showed than non-producers like him can attach themselves (like lamprey) to our food chain and profit from that.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380845515727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:11:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845549464-186</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Years ago mir and his sidekick bumper were trying to claim they were both vietnam vets. I looked at mir's profile and saw that his claimed birthdate was not consistent with service in vietnam. He tried to laugh it off, claiming the birthdate was his high school graduation date or some such rot. Mir's been bs from the start, but he's so dumb he doesn't know people are wise to him.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380845549464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380845647453-187</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mir has never been unsure about anything--not even when he knows it's a lie.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380845647453</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380846010535-188</Id><Topic><Title>Why Has Socialism and Communism Become so Attractive to Democrats?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380826416338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:53:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you ask them. "Hey, little one. Do you want to come into the world with a mother who doesn't want you, can't afford you, and is going to resent you? Do you want to share the home with a string of Uncles who will slap you around and maybe do you worse? Or would you rather sit this one out?"</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380846010535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:20:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380846179110-189</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Administration Forces Hundreds of Privately Funded Parks to Close Amid Shutdown</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380835433283</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 17:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the FS guys are closing them because the FS doesn't have the people to supervise them and don't trust them to supervise themselves?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380846179110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380846218782-190</Id><Topic><Title>This is a Test</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you're flunking it.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380846218782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380846894680-191</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your #$%$ Moment of the Day!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380846680220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:31:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder what all these people that sell hate for a living would do if selling hate didn't pay so well.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380846894680</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380846969865-192</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I guess YOU don't like being preached to -- either." You are in rare form today. Actually, and you should have already figured this out by now, I LOVE to be "preached at" - from someone that actually knows something about God's word. Otherwise, I am also happy to have discussions of the Bible with less knowledgeable individuals - for which all can benefit. God's Word has many attributes: 1) it cannot be voided or made of no effect (Isaiah 55:11); 2) it is powerful (Hebrews 4:12); and it is God Himself (John 1:1). But you have chided me severely in the past for bringing up His Word. Are you having a change of heart? I hope so. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1380846969865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380847083567-193</Id><Topic><Title>This is a Test</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Real patriots respect the Constitutional process. Like it or not Obamacare was passed and was judged constitutional by the Supreme Court. You do not try to destroy the government because the democratic process didn't go your way.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380847083567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380847305147-194</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla up 411% this year VN-rants BA stock down 5 days ina row to 52% Airbus better 67% ytd</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380837894620</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 18:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" BA stock down 5 days ina row" BA was up Tuesday and Wednesday. Was that another typo? P.S. Avoiding cnn money on the 3 year numbers til you figure out how they can be off by 100%, 200%, 300%, or MORE? LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380847305147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:41:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380848250518-195</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody held a gun to their head a forced them to be doctors. If they don't like the way it goes in a democracy, they can move to a Banana Republic--or join you on your fantasy island.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1380848250518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 20:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380848803358-196</Id><Topic><Title>Proposed combined order of Etihad, Emriates, and Qatar for 777x to be 50-100 Billion dollar range---just 3 airlines</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380782808286</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 02:46:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 20 year or so life cycle of the plane with its efficiencies should make the plane a better value in the long run by far. Also, at that time period there will be no real advanced widebody able to match it as it will be more advanced than any Airbus plane out there due to timing. A350 design will be a few years old as Boeing adds the lessons learned parts to the new 777x. Gotta remember fuel cost is what has started this revolution of replacing the old planes, so the A340----not worth it.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380848803358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380848956471-197</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can we all, at least, acknowledge that Obama hates Americans almost as much as he hates America?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1380848956471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380849469805-198</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she is from somalia, surprise surprise</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1380849469805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380849553750-199</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too late, he is taking america down, and you dumb fools voted for this puppet........</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1380849553750</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380849633380-200</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Tightens Screws - Wants to Make Sure Americans Feel Pain.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380824398498</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>enjoy your part time job.........</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1380849633380</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380849634423-201</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bapsycho, how about this, if Michelle Obama had a 3rd daughter the maniac would have looked just like her! Looks like she couldn't log in to receive free healthcare and then found out it was going to cost money..that was the straw!</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1380849634423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380849841736-202</Id><Topic><Title>This is a Test</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not quite true re current Obamacare. Over a thousand modifications have been made - some needed to implement- bur mostly waivers or friends, and made OUTSIDE the process ( approval by congress ) - but simply by the UN constitutional process of executive order or by unelected bcrats. And NOT all of Obuma care was found constitutional by SCOTUS- but that seems to be ignored. How about simply implementing Obuma care without all the waivers, the changes in implementation times for companies, etc. AS WAS PASSED BY CONGRESS - ( BY mostly lame duck congresscritters )</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1380849841736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380850378358-203</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In addition to loving to bear false witness . . . .</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1380850378358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380850804313-204</Id><Title>The Iranian Nuclear Threat</Title><Msg>Bibi Netanyahu, PM of Israel appeared on Charlie Rose and discussed the real threat of Iran seeking nuclear bombs. The PM made it clear that Israel does not have an issue with Iran having nuclear energy power plants for electricity and other civil needs. 17 other nations have nuclear energy power plants and do not have the capacity to make nuclear weapons. What Bibi Netanyahu is trying to get across is that Iran wants more than nuclear power for civilian needs. Iran wants nuclear centerfuges with the capacity to make nuclear weapons. Thats one reason its nuclear program takes place under ground. Also, Iran has been testing long range missiles capable of deliverying nuclear weapons that could eventually reach the US. We all know of Iran role in committing mass murder on the population of Syria. We should not be sweet talked into giving Iran more time to complete their nuclear weapons program.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1380850804313</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380851884871-205</Id><Topic><Title>Shots Fired Near Capitol</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380826946461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Looks like she couldn't log in to receive free healthcare and then found out it was going to cost money" ...driving an Infinity. ...only to a bagger bigot</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1380851884871</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 21:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380853029175-206</Id><Topic><Title>This is a Test</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BULL PUCKY! NONE</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380853029175</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 22:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380853113822-207</Id><Topic><Title>This is a Test</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of the modifications effect the intent or the constitutionality of the law. The intent of the radicals in Congress is to destroy the law in its entirely.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380853113822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 22:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380853892306-208</Id><Topic><Title>This is a Test</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B.O. care passed by dims against overwelming public disapproval, what's so democratic about that ? The last offer by the House only asked that the law be implemented as originally passed . Hairy Weed: NO VOTE . B.O.: I will veto . You parrots are truely hilarious . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1380853892306</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 22:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380854064902-209</Id><Title>Big Inflated Dimbulb Claims</Title><Msg>"Exchange agencies walk back high-traffic hype Other exchanges have had to pare down their initial statistics. Covered California, that state’s subsidized insurance exchange, initially claimed that its website had received 5 million hits on October 1. They later had to revise that number down 87 percent, to 645,000. KUSI-TV in San Diego is reporting that not one policy has yet been sold on the California exchange. Double Down: Obamacare Will Increase Avg. Individual-Market Insurance Premiums By 99% For Men, 62% For Women . Interactive Map: In 13 States Plus D.C., Obamacare Will Increase Health Premiums By 24%, On Average The War On Bros: Exchange Subsidies Won't Protect Young People From Obamacare's Higher Insurance Premiums . According to Megan McArdle, high traffic alone doesn’t explain why the federal healthcare.gov website is having so many issues. For example, the drop-down boxes for security questions aren’t working, which shouldn’t be a traffic-related problem. “The drop-down thing is mystifying,” a programmer source told McArdle. It “could very easily be because deadline pressure caused them to take some shortcuts that impacted their ability to scale.” Glitches around traffic and web server loads will be relatively easy to fix. The real question is this: will healthier and younger individuals, who stand to face steep premium hikes under Obamacare, pay up? A Manhattan Institute study I helped conduct suggests that average to younger-than-average men will face underlying rate hikes of 97 to 99 percent, with women facing increases of 55 to 62 percent. AAF: 30-year-old men face average premium hikes of 260% A new study from the American Action Forum that looks at healthy 30-year-old men finds that underlying premiums for those individuals will ." Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1380854064902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 22:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380855423110-210</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism is Destroying America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380825371640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It never ceases to amaze me how liberals can come up with profound logic that is as distorted as it can possibly be! Enslave in what way? All societies require that you work to get paid, even communist societies. If you have a complaint with work (as enslavement) then you should complain about the introduction of money in the world. The introduction of money and how to acquire more of it may be the clue to your dissatisfaction.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1380855423110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 22:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380856465673-211</Id><Topic><Title>Big Inflated Dimbulb Claims</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1380854064902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 22:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's one jumbosca*ski tried to walk back: "I see Chrissy has some new ids, but no new ideas . P.S. every time I see chrisgenna2 my brain says chisgenetal, ...... isn't that wierd ?" Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1380856465673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 23:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380857662602-212</Id><Topic><Title>This is a Test</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans "bravely" helped take down the barriers so the WWII veterans could get to the memorial (on camera) but somehow they forgot the 500,000 veterans who are partially supported by Meals on Wheels. Brave folks.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1380857662602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 23:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380858125937-213</Id><Topic><Title>This is a Test</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1380830117983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reall: Senate Democrats and Obama said the House must send them a measure that would restart all of government with no strings attached. ‘‘Take a vote,’’ Obama urged Boehner in his speech. ‘‘Stop this farce and end this shutdown right now.’’ It might not be so simple, however. Moderate Republicans have said they think they could provide enough votes to join with minority Democrats and push a bill through the House reopening the government with no restrictions on the health care law. But under pressure from House GOP leaders, they failed to join Democratic efforts on Wednesday aimed at forcing the chamber to consider such legislation.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380858125937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-10-03 23:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>