<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371355451085-1</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gillette still airborne at Boeing The new Boeing 7E7 jet, if launched as planned, will be the 25th commercial airplane model unveiled by the Western world, and the 11th jet from Boeing or McDonnell Douglas. It also will be the last for Boeing Commercial Airplanes Vice President Walt Gillette, who in a 37-year engineering career has worked on nearly all of Boeing's commercial jets, from the 707 to the 777. Walt Gillette"I'm older than dirt," 61-year-old Gillette told the Associated Press in the story that ran in newspapers including the Houston Chronicle. He joked that his very first plane project was the one the Wright Brothers flew. Gillette, who's in charge of Engineering, Manufacturing and Partner Alignment for the 7E7 program, is now leading the design and development of the super-efficient airplane that Boeing hopes will enter into service in 2008—one year after Gillette expects to retire. The company's board of directors is expected to decide whether to go ahead with the program by early next year. ++++ That was in 2003</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371355451085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371355667913-2</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and a bit more He went to the University of Texas at Austin, where he earned his bachelor of science and master's degrees in aerospace engineering while also spending three summers working on the Apollo space program with NASA. He joined Boeing in 1966 as a research engineer in the Aerodynamics Research unit of the company's commercial airplane division. In the 1970s, Gillette worked on the 707, 727 and 737 jets. He was part of the original team on the 757, 737-300 and 777. In the 1990s Boeing assigned him to work on the 747 and 767 jets. He also led the initial development of the 747X and the Sonic Cruiser—projects that Boeing abandoned in the past three years—before being assigned to lead development and design of the 7E7. But he has little sentimentality for what might have been. ++ Note there is no mention of his efforts on b-2 program !!! but I was there and after 1991 approx it was no secret- nor in 1997 when the B-2 spirit was at Boeing field So was another of my buds named shellhorn !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371355667913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:07:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371355943271-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If you question him about the money, he will attack you for questioning his honesty." reminds me of a certain forged birth certificate</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371355943271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371356287945-4</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mcdummy aero types had heads up posterior evidenced by the 737 NG wing fiasco, spending bucu bucks to get less than 2 percent gain- and pushed the mcdummy dc-11 trailing edge wedge- which was an butt patch for the poor aero of the dc-11 wing. They were adamant that the aero-partners winglet was a nonissue- would wreckm the wing, etc. So a few BA types managed to convince the BBJ people to try it out as it would diffeerentiate the BBJ from the plebian 737. The aero data showed 3 to 7 percent improvement- but still they said no - eventually a german charter outifit agreed to buy a few planes with the winglet --- and the rest is history !! It is mostly mcdummy managers /executives and butt kissers that are responsible for the 7 late 7. Suggest you read a book called turbulence about Boeing. . . its a factual of a book as you will find on the events and people and morale leading up to the 7 late 7..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371356287945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371358617756-5</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing Commercial Aero were adament that the winglets would not work. BBJ bypassed them and convinced senior management to try them out because they looked good (no kidding). The rest is history but there are still BCA aero types than insist the winglets are useless.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371358617756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371358776897-6</Id><Title>spartacus9991 and his claim about other stocks that pay dividends, now its utility stocks dividends lets examine that one</Title><Msg>spartacus9991 you only said , in a sarcastic reply, to the specific comparison between Airbus bettering Boeing in stock price gain over 1 and 5 years, after I stated a fact , Airbus is up 80 % for 1 year , Boeing is up 40% and for 5 years Airbus is up 162%, or 107% better than Boeing as of that user comment. Then, once you suggested dividends would be a factor, I shot you down big time . I demonstrated that you know nothing about dividends and showed you how to compute and pointed out there is a .6% difference between Airbus and Boeing dividend payout. that is insignificant since Airbus is better than Boeing by 40%for a year and over 100% better for 5 years . Spartacus9991 then you attempted to substitute utility stocks for the original Airbus to Boeing comparison and dividend statement. . , . . So Spartacus9991 , lets go with your latest hack attempt to misguide the readers about Boeing stock. Spartacus9991, you once more demonstrate your foolish and ignorant argument and a hack approach and total lack of stock market skill, knowledge or ability. Utility stocks do not go up 80% in one year like Airbus or 40% like Boeing for that matter so they would have to pay about 80% dividend to be able to compete with Airbus so once more Spartacus 9991 your a hack for Boeing and a evil troll and not very good at both. You accuse me of acting like a certified financial planner. I have told you I have 30 years of street smart investing experience , backed up with a MBA and have leaned by consistently, every day studying how the financial markets and learning how to read a stock charting work. I can suggest ACAD, up 13.5% this week and say that Boeing is not good down .6% this week without , being a financial planner</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371358776897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371359437851-7</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BC aero at that time ( 2002- 2003 ) was essentially run by a few mcdummy refugees who insisted that their magical trailing edge ' wedge" was THE major aero breakthru of the century ( or millenium ). What few people knew was that since it did not work well, many transpolar flights with the dc-10-11 flew with on to three empty seats to meet load range limits- and McDummy ( Boeing ) had to pay for those seats for NOT meeting load range guarantees. In about 2002 or 3 I had a long chat with a few people who had the facts- data- and curves from the BBJ " fight test results . The agreement was that as long as the winglets were NOT detrimental, they could be used on the BBJ as the equivalent o/f the " chrome spinner hubcaps " suitable for VIP personal jet travel ... Speaking of Chrome wheels - how many know that about that same time- the wheels for Boffos Durango were stolen when he left it parked at Tukwilla while on a typical boondoggle trip. ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371359437851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371360275375-8</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 and his claim about other stocks that pay dividends, now its utility stocks dividends lets examine that one</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371358776897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:59:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw spartacus9991, I do not like people like you who refuse to look and listen, now ACAD is up 1195% for one year remember, spartacus9991 when I told you I was up 25% for a week and then 60 % several months ago , Spartacus9991, you tell me your not in Boeing stock well good for you, But too bad your argumentative and miss all these stocks to look at and decide for yourself, if they are good. you know like TSLA on May 3 I said get in and 16 days later at 100% gain I stated the short squeeze was done and that mans get out. . since then I said if you know how to day trade you can trade it , as it is a traders paradise now with the stock market bouncing around 100point in a day that is great for me I can read a stock chart, and you can wait until TSLA breaks above the Bollinger band or fails . I doubt spartacus9991 that you are you learning yet</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371360275375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 01:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371365203112-9</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 and his claim about other stocks that pay dividends, now its utility stocks dividends lets examine that one</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371358776897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:59:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it to keep his manic musings near the top for all to read. Sad.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371365203112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 02:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371366279692-10</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus 350 first flight and burns 25% less fuel than a 787, no lithium batteries and TSLA up as I said,BA not so good</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371216663708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One last bit of trivia. The 777 is the only aircraft that has never had a crash that resulted in loss of life. Impressive track record for an aircraft that has been around this long. Yes I am a engineer at Boeing and helped design the 777. The 777 design team is rock solid in all aspects of aircraft design. The 777X is going to be one great aircraft!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1371366279692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 03:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371377322968-11</Id><Title>bump spartacus9991, who said" he agree's with everything said , what musings ?who cares what you agree with</Title><Msg>spartacus99991 • I don't care that you agree with about everything I said, ""Spartacus9991 who cares if you agree about Airbus being better than Boeing. or if your a lawyer or not, or what your family thinks , why are you here, how made you a critic , you don't know about dividends, you don't know about stocks you want to talk about land values.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371377322968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371378281135-12</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 and his claim about other stocks that pay dividends, now its utility stocks dividends lets examine that one</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371358776897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 00:59:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who reads his BS anyway?</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1371378281135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371378310735-13</Id><Title>Battle of the Paris Airshow Airbus compared to Boeing what is up now</Title><Msg>The much-anticipated Airbus A350 flew for the first time on Friday, launching a new air race between the European plane maker and Boeing for long-haul wide-body aircraft. Boeing has dominated the market so far, but troubles with the lithium ion batteries in its 787 Dreamliner are giving customers a reason to give a close look at Airbus' first all-new plane in eight years. The CEO of Airbus parent EADS, Tom Enders, has said he expects a "few hundred" new orders. Boeing executives, meanwhile, downplayed the air show's importance for orders, noting that the two companies have historically split the commercial aircraft market. The race for the title of biggest plane maker is as tight as ever. Over the whole of 2012, Airbus delivered 588 planes. That was a record, but one Boeing beat with 601 deliveries, the first time since 2003 it came out on top. Considering that is the only time since 2001 Boeing slightly beat Airbus and my only 2.21% Airbus has dominated Boeing for 11 years and the stock price reflects this . Airbus stock over time has bettered Boeing shareholder returns As a striking example , for 3 years to date Airbus shareholders have gained 165% while Boeing shareholders have only made 35% return on their investment. Airbus has bettered Boeing for years on return on investment. They have a great business strategy, wait for Boeing to go first, study the new plane and come up with a better plane to take away market share, like the new 350. The new Airbus 350 will eat away at both the 787 and the 777 and cost of only one new plane , very smart for Airbus to wait and study Boeing first . Next Boeing management is not good, the company is not trusted, the management does not come close to delivery date promises, so the Boeing company credibility is hurting Boeing shareholders. A lithium battery failure and false starts on the 787 has damaged the once good Boeing names, while Airbus A380 problems are behind them. The Boeing 747 is slowing production</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371378310735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371378446895-14</Id><Title>As dell continues to rant</Title><Msg>BA continues to go up,maybe the longs should send him a check,,,,LMAO</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1371378446895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371378965414-15</Id><Topic><Title>Battle of the Paris Airshow Airbus compared to Boeing what is up now</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371378310735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:25:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why unposter , you said , "who reads my comments" , well you spend most of your time reading my comments, based on your posting history, as a Boeing hack and troll you stay very busy monitoring me , I wonder why? does the truth about Boeing hurt you unposter? unposter 6 times in the past few days of May and more in June how about that you care very much about what I have to say unposter ha ha Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371378965414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371379402576-16</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus 350 first flight and burns 25% less fuel than a 787, no lithium batteries and TSLA up as I said,BA not so good</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371216663708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>since when di you ever play fair ha ha I ignore you as much as possible, but your so wrong most of the time , like with you call on a stock that does not exist to show me up remember ? maybe you should stick to California land value if you know anything about that . Spartacus9991, as a MD engineer that would mean you were part of the bankruptcy of MD, so as an engineer that is not much of a credential to toss around . Spartacus9991, you were in a group that failed at MD and you own no Boeing stock, run by a management team that follows the same MD failure business model, but you champion Boeing all the time. Spartacus9991, what a phony you are spartacus99991</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371379402576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371379809189-17</Id><Topic><Title>Battle of the Paris Airshow Airbus compared to Boeing what is up now</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371378310735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:25:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let me post startacus9991 on the real facts(about Boeing management- added by wayne)| and show he just hates me| but understands everything I say is right "Spartacus9991 on boeing leadership and Airbus stock price betters boeing "If Condit, Stonecipher, and now McNerney had heeded them and Hart-Smith's2001 paper thngs( spelling things) would be a lot better today. A big if ( comma added ,)and now( comma added,) the company and shareholders have to live with their bad decisions.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371379809189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:50:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371380057095-18</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep Boeing management, rewards rubber stamping by QA , until there is a problem, then cams(corrective action memo )to the persons HRM file, the motto for Boeing QA is, " sit down, shut up and don't move", from your QA chair or the supervisor will be watching if your doing your job, and hassle you abut it too.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371380057095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371380444464-19</Id><Topic><Title>Battle of the Paris Airshow Airbus compared to Boeing what is up now</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371378310735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 06:25:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the 25% story as told by the CEO of Airbus not my quote there are the facts "Airbus CEO Fabrice Bregier likes how his planes stack up against Boeing. The prototype of the A350 – a composite, fuel-efficient plane that will compete against Boeing's 787 Dreamliner – will fly at mid-year, Bregier says. The first A350 deliveries are expected in 2014. As the plane gets certified, Airbus decided in February to stick with a nickel-cadmium battery rather than try a lithium-ion battery like the ones that have left the Dreamliner grounded since mid-January. Bregier says lithium-ion batteries are still attractive, but that putting them on Airbus planes He says he there are too many uncertainties surrounding the new batteries. "I'm on the safe side. I'm not saying Boeing is not on the safe side – this is not up to me. This is (up) to FAA and other agencies," Bregier says. Translation, they are unsafe and he knows better than to put passenger lives at risk when the NiCad batteries work with good safety record. The Federal Aviation Administration grounded the Dreamliner on Jan. 16, after an All Nippon Airways flight made an emergency landing in Japan with a smoldering battery. The incident came after a Jan. 7 battery fire in a Japan Airlines plane parked in Boston. "It's not to make Boeing's life more difficult," Bregier said of the battery decision. "Their life is difficult enough right now." Asked how Airbus would compete with a potential Boeing 777X, Bregier said the A350-1000 already slated for delivery in 2017 will carry just as many passengers but at 25% greater fuel efficiency. "To my knowledge, this is Boeing's response to the very successful A350-1000 that we have launched and started to market more aggressively," Bregier said. "It is not easy to match and beat. The ball now is in Boeing's camp." Bregier broke ground Monday on a manufacturing plant in Mobile, Ala., which will build the A320 family. Airbus already has plants in Germany and China,</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371380444464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371380790923-20</Id><Title>Obama is the sociopath?</Title><Msg>The racism of that thread is appalling. Would you clowns please google the term "eefing" and then click on "Hee Haw's Jimmie Riddle and Jackie Phelps Eefing and Hambone act". Once you master the fine art of eefing you can entertain Southerners and at least accomplish something rather than sit back and spread vicious and unfounded rumors.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371380790923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371380913803-21</Id><Title>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox</Title><Msg>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox He loves her, he loves her not. Fox News CEO Roger Ailes says he’s bringing Sarah Palin back as an on-air contributor. Will the second time be a charm? By David Freedlander Refudiate that! Former Alaska governor and professional maverick Sarah Palin will be returning to Fox News as on-air contributor, the network announced today. Sarah Palin returns to Fox AP (2) “I’ve had several conversations with Governor Palin in the past few weeks about her rejoining FOX News as a contributor,” said Fox News CEO Roger Ailes in a statement. “I have great confidence in her and am pleased that she will once again add her commentary to our programming. I hope she continues to speak her mind.” Ailes’s confidence in Palin’s TV talent has proven to be a tad misplaced in the past. She was a contributor to the network for three years after her surprise resignation as governor of Alaska in 2009, but was by many accounts an unsteady television presence. Her reality show, Sarah Palin’s Alaska, on TLC, was a critical and commercial flop, and her Fox series, Real American Stories, was panned by critics, with a Los Angeles Times reviewer writing that "As a host, Palin brings little besides her name and all that it has come to mean. Despite her time on the campaign trail and in front of often-unfriendly cameras, Palin still has an eyes-locked-on-the-teleprompter stiffness." Joe Muto, a former Fox News employee who was fired after he anonymously blogged on Gawker about what it was like to work at the network, and who dished about the inner workings of the network in his new book, Atheist in the Foxhole, described mounting frustration at Fox with the former governor—this, despite Palin being treated as a rock star when she first arrived at company headquarters. Can't wait for Sarah Palin's return to Fox News? Check out these highlights from her first stint as on-air contributor. Ailes’s confidence in Palin’s TV talent has proven to be a tad misplaced in the past. “It started going awry for Sarah Palin at Fox almost immediately. She wasn’t willing to do the work. And they made it easy for her. They built a studio for her in house in Alaska, so all she had to do was slap on some makeup and go sit in front of the camera,” Muto told The Daily Beast. “She would still show up late, unprepared, hadn’t even bothered to study what the topic was and would completely whiff it on the air.” At times, Ailes has acknowledged her shortcomings, telling an Associated Press reporter in 2011, “I hired Sarah Palin because she was hot and got ratings.” Conservatives 2016 Carolyn Kaster/AP Palin responded in kind. When she decided not to run for president in 2012, she did not make the announcement on Fox but instead read a letter aloud on conservative radio host Mark Levin’s program. She took to Facebook to vent when Fox News cancelled her interview of John McCain during the 2012 convention. Although Palin has a devoted following in some conservative corners of the country—witness the loud cheers she received when she slurped from a Big Gulp on stage at the Conservative Political Action Committee annual meeting this year, in a rebuke to Mayor Mike Bloomberg’s large-soda ban—others in the Republican Party have been urging the faithful to move away from Palin’s brand of emotional, scorched-earth politics. She is not considered a likely contender for the 2016 presidential nomination, even though she continues to be a key endorser in GOP primaries. Palin will appear on Fox’s daytime and primetime programming, according to the network, starting with an appearance on FOX &amp; Friends on Monday, June 17. She will also contribute to FOX Business Network. In a statement, Palin gushed about the network and her new role: "The power of FOX News is unparalleled. The role of FOX News in the important debates in our world is indispensable,” she said. “I am pleased and proud to be rejoining Roger Ailes and the great people at FOX."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371380913803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371383168561-22</Id><Title>Boeings Answer To A350-----Bigger 787!! Great idea----now Airbus has more risks ahead</Title><Msg>Boeing’s expansion of the Dreamliner seating capacity would give the company an answer to the Airbus A350 while giving airlines a way to haul more passengers per flight, increasing profits on every run. Sources told Reuters Boeing is saving its announcement for the upcoming Paris Air Show, but word started traveling just as Airbus celebrated the maiden voyage of the A350. An increased passenger capacity in what is called the 787-10 would give airlines an opportunity to run flights more economically. Increased range, which Boeing’s customers may not want or need, is not part of the package</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371383168561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371383371585-23</Id><Topic><Title>Boeings Answer To A350-----Bigger 787!! Great idea----now Airbus has more risks ahead</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371383168561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a great response by Boeing to the A350----just making a longer, higher capacity, flying now plane. May take a little thunder from the A350 as Boeing already beat it at its own game and can do more upgrades for the 787-10. Love it.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371383371585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:49:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371384186856-24</Id><Topic><Title>Marines land Osprey aircraft on Japanese ship</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371264851057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:54:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the Marines would care!</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371384186856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371384998123-25</Id><Title>Boeing to Streamline Royal Netherlands Chinook and Apache Support</Title><Msg>Boeing and the Royal Netherlands Air Force have signed the first-ever integrated contract for maintenance and spare parts for Chinook and Apache helicopters. The $60 Million contract will result in more affordable support solutions and enhanced flight hour readiness of Royal Netherlands Air Force CH-47 Chinook and AH-64D Apache helicopters</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371384998123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371385219675-26</Id><Title>Airbus listens to their sharholders, result Airbus sharholders better than boeing shareholder.Airbus up 164% -3 years</Title><Msg>The chief executive of European aerospace firm EADS Airbus ,has ruled out another attempt to merge with Britain's BAE Systems , saying "This window is closed," he told the newspaper. " Investors in EADS also had largely opposed the deal because it would have diluted their exposure to strong demand from airlines in emerging markets. Result a 3 year gain in stock price of over Boeing . Airbus has bettered Boeing shareholders for 3 years by 116% Dividends for the two is about equal Boeing pays 1.9% dividend yield , and Airbus pays 1.3% for a year , so only .6 of a percent difference in dividend. the only real significant difference is stock price ,and the reason is the poor management skills of Condit, Stonecipher and McNerney for Boeing. These Boeing leaders , do not care about shareholders or the customers flight safety of the 787 , they could have gone with the lighter safe, NiCad battery over a combined heavier dangerous lithium battery in a heavy box which total now weighs more than the safe NiCad Airbus system and more than a total NiCad system in a 787 without the fire box a dangerous idea . Remember the Boeing company reason for a fire box, "We don't know , what we don't know about why the lithium batteries' catch fire" Boeing Shareholder's understand that is not a good reason to continue the insanity. No other passenger airliner except the 787 is going with lithium batteries. Cessna tried it and switched to NiCad after their fires , Airbus listened and switched to NiCad , only the Boeing executives think , apparently it flies in the corporate board room just fine, too bad the rest of the world does not appreciate being a test dummy for a fire in a box . Airbus will watch this experiment if it does work they will copy it, if not, they will stay with NiCad . Smart management, the Boeing CEO says Airbus lacks guts but the shareholder just take the 116% stock price gain and laugh at McNerney guts or stupid way to run a company .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371385219675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371385662390-27</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, Don your right, every body got out of McDummy as soon as they could, same with the rank and file we all saw what was going on to the good Boeing company once MD got their bankrupt hands on Boeing , failure is assured , Boeing was absorbed by the borg MD collective failure machine . its a done deal now destruction is assured</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371385662390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:27:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371386037609-28</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets see, A350 now 90 days behind schedule- soon in typical Airbus fashion just as they did with their vaunted military transport the A400M, (20-30 billion euros over budget and 5 years behind schedule) Airbus will begin to screw up on the A350. They have done it with every airplane they ever attempted to build. The A320 with its fatal fly by wire problems, the A330 with its inadequate flight instrumentation, the A380 with its failed schedules and engine problems etc etc etc-oh and last but not least the A350 is several percentage points BEHIND the 787 on fuel efficiency</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371386037609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:33:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371386392330-29</Id><Topic><Title>Marines land Osprey aircraft on Japanese ship</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371264851057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:54:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Japanese Navy would care and since they don't have their vaunted carrier fleet of 75 years ago and need to provide a world wide military presence as they have been doing- they may need a fleet of V-22 aircraft for the next time they have to deploy to the Arabian gulf of the Balkans. Don't forget they have participated in a small scale in the Middle East for the past 20 years</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371386392330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371386420670-30</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whstleffanms and yet Airbus stock is better than Boeing by 116% net, in 3 years , it must be because the 787 is 4 years late and 30 billion dollars over cost while you talk about 90 days wow you really need to confer with Paul Allen on this one remember"whsteffanms on his posts and MSFT, eh! 18-Jun-11 01:42 pm whsteffanms... I was wondering your IP address shows as Everett and you have 4528 update(6039)posts, with almost all of them containing slams and HAR HAR HAR and nothing of any value to anyone, how is it that you get along so well with Paul Allen? eh! Re: Microsoft Shows First Look at Windows 8 Interface VIDEO Whsteffanms said” dell george my address may be Everett, but my mansion is actually located over on Widbey Island( sure it is) and I get back and forth with my yacht( the full size scale model?)- I tie up next to Paul Allen a lot( a lot like never !) down in Elliott bay and confer( wow) with him quite a lot-- how do you like that eh ( just like all your other emails,, har, har , har ) Rating : (No ratings) Rate it: 1 whsteffanms... Male Everett WA ________________________________________ View Messages Ignore User Report Abuse</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371386420670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371386855571-31</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Wayne Paul and I are meeting for late breakfast at Elliotts later this morning- if you hadn't lost your Boeing job and could afford transportation over to the bay we might ask you to join in if you aren't too grubby looking these days might even get you a ride on Pauls submarine</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371386855571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371387204747-32</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing wings have been bendy since the B-47 and B-52 days-- the flex is designed in and Boeing has been getting away with it for 70 years- In fact the feature has been important to the structural durability of the airplane and comfort of the passengers and if you don't believe it ask any Boeing airplane pilot</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371387204747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371387383899-33</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus listens to their sharholders, result Airbus sharholders better than boeing shareholder.Airbus up 164% -3 years</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371385219675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:20:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump this for the BHT crowd, it makes them angry, the truth hurts them . Airbus CEO said he does what the shareholders told him , no we airbus shareholders do not want our stock price diluted with military problems and he hears them on the military , so Airbus CEO said ok ,Airbus stock owners your the boss , unlike the Boeing CEO who says the customer will have to wait for the 737 max and immediately two past all Boeing customers airlines switched to Airbus and Airbus got over 1000 plane orders on that one stupid CEO Boeing statement,! Mcnerney, refused to listen to the customer and bragged about it. . Like now, he is calling the Airbus CEO out for having no guts to do a all new composite plane first . Well wow Mcnerney if a runner can get a kicker to lead out first then that is good, I thought McNerney played baseball , he should understand street wise smarts, he is like Marie Antoinette, so removed from common sense she said, no bread, well let them eat cake, there was no cake, so off with her head, mcnerney has not head now stupid the things that come out of his mouth , this Boeing CEO is less than mediocre and that is why jack Welch at GE passed him over and said you have to leave now for some other sucker company , and whoops there it is Boeing got the sucker</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371387383899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371387434771-34</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you too cheap to pay for my breakfast then ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371387434771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371387675230-35</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus listens to their sharholders, result Airbus sharholders better than boeing shareholder.Airbus up 164% -3 years</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371385219675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:20:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump this for my free breakfast on Paul Allen and his best friend father z aka whstleffanms he is now having breakfast with Paul allen at a greasy spoon eatery yuck</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371387675230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371387987664-36</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus listens to their sharholders, result Airbus sharholders better than boeing shareholder.Airbus up 164% -3 years</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371385219675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:20:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well I suppose you cant pull yourself away from that boyfriend that got you fired from Boeing as a urinal cleanup tech---I certainly wouldn't want to create any jealousy there HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1371387987664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371389061992-37</Id><Title>British Airways set to confirm an order for 10 787-10 Dreamliner --- $2.5 billion value approx</Title><Msg>Hence, here off at the races!</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371389061992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371389292086-38</Id><Title>Boeing Seeks KC-46A Tanker Exports Customers ---- this could be good</Title><Msg>Boeing going for the quantity break again in talks with several potential buyers for its KC-46A aerial refueling tanker as it aims to make the aircraft available for export one year ahead of its 2018 target.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371389292086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:28:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371389430567-39</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Seeks KC-46A Tanker Exports Customers ---- this could be good</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371389292086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:28:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forgot, Boeing said they are discussing export orders for about 20 tankers, with more in the pipeline, he said. Jeff Kohler, Boeing’s vice president for military international business development, told reporters in Paris today</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371389430567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371389535555-40</Id><Title>osprey the rest of the story</Title><Msg>The V-22's development process has been long and controversial, partly due to its large cost increases The V-22's development budget was first planned for $2.5 billion in 1986, then increased to a projected $30 billion in 1988. As of 2008, $27 billion had been spent on the Osprey program and another $27.2 billion will be required to complete planned production numbers by the end of the program. the V-22 was so bad that even defense secretary #$%$ Cheney wanted to cancel it. V-22 has suffered half a dozen major mishaps during development claiming 30 lives. some of the original engineers who worked on the V-22, and they’ve expressed some concern as well about the V-22. Its [The V-22's] production costs are considerably greater than for helicopters with equivalent capability—specifically, about twice as great as for the CH-53E, which has a greater payload and an ability to carry heavy equipment the V-22 cannot... an Osprey unit would cost around $60 million to produce, and $35 million for the helicopter equivalent. —Michael E. O'Hanlon, 2002. The V-22 squadron's former commander at Marine Corps Air Station New River, Lieutenant Colonel Odin Lieberman, was relieved of duty in 2001 after allegations that he instructed his unit that they needed to falsify maintenance records to make the aircraft appear more reliable. Three officers were later implicated in the falsification scandal.[49] The aircraft is incapable of autorotation to make a safe landing in helicopter mode if both engines fail. A director of the Pentagon's testing office in 2005 said that if the Osprey loses power while flying like a helicopter below 1,600 feet (490 m), emergency landings "...are not likely to be survivable In August 2012, the USAF found that "CV-22 wake modeling is inadequate for a trailing aircraft to make accurate estimations of safe separation from the preceding aircraft They are primarily used in Iraq's western Anbar province for routine cargo and troop movements, so a helicopter would work just as good at less pork barrel military industrial complex prices . A taxpayer pig out deal . the military would rather have had something else for the money The USMC states that the cost per flight hour January 2012, averaging $10,000 that is high cost to the taxpayer. Better planes faster and better helos safer. Japanese government leaders and Okinawa residents opposed the planned V-22 deployment in Japan due to the April and June 2012 accidents the V-22 is a morphidite, like most not as good as a helo or as fast as a fast jet, and yes the marines are brave men and women and will go in whatever the USA gives them . Too bad they gave them a CV-22.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371389535555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371390050635-41</Id><Title>ANA and JAL may l switch from All Boeing to Airbus at paris Airshow more Boeing market share gone to Airbus</Title><Msg>Among the most closely watched competitions are those held by ANA and JAL, which are considering orders for A350s. That could mark a seismic shift in the airline world as JAL operates only Boeing aircraft and ANA, which has Airbus A320 narrowbody aircraft, operates only Boeing jets on its medium and long-haul services. Amid tough competition, analysts say Japanese airlines could pick up the Airbus aircraft.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371390050635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371391586250-42</Id><Title>Obonzo happy to give guns to terrorists while trying to take them away from US citizens</Title><Msg>Obonzo lied to OSU grads.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371391586250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371394090570-43</Id><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Msg>Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda so says USA TODAY (google it.....Once again I am right) So if Obama supplies arms to Alqaeda/Syrian backed Rebels...doesn't that make Barry in violation of his own unconstitutional NDAA (giving aide and comfort to the enemy) ...as a Nation we have to ask which side we are on ...AlQaeda or the Bill of Rights</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371394126877-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obonzo happy to give guns to terrorists while trying to take them away from US citizens</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371391586250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394126877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371394260927-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371380790923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does Obama continue to Arm AlQaeda in Syria Doesn't that violate the NDAA...giving Aide and comfort to the Enemy ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394260927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371395261456-46</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371380790923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 07:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz is just a Ho working for race card pimps. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371395261456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371395710853-47</Id><Title>The Obonzo Doctrine = Provide arm and support enemies of the USA.</Title><Msg>while trampling the constitutional rights of US citizens. No wonder Bush's approval ratings are edging out Obonzo's.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371395710853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371396000438-48</Id><Topic><Title>The Obonzo Doctrine = Provide arm and support enemies of the USA.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371395710853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:15:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that makes Barry Soetoro guilty of supplying aide and comfort to the enemy ...under his OWN NDAA</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371396000438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371396212281-49</Id><Title>Is the Obonzo supporter with 22 kids via 14 unwed moms enjoying Father's Day?</Title><Msg>I wonder if any of the 22 #$%$ are named Barack or Michelle? lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371396212281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371396764665-50</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who? All the managers at the Aero group up through the director level have been homegrown BCA up to the present day (Wayne Tigert, good man).</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371396764665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371397763754-51</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brilliant plan really...liberate (har har) Syria (like Libya) and put the Bin Laden Brigade in charge...and THEN the US can RE-invade in a few years...saying "We must stamp out AlQaeda".....guaranteed a permanent opponent ....The war is not MEANT to end..."Oceana has ALWAYS been at war with Eurasia"</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1371397763754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371398998653-52</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget I ran is as serious a threat to the US as al Qaeda. The Aytollah wants to hurt the US with a nuke. I ran has been a key supplier of arms to the Taliban and to insurgents like al Sadah in the Iraq restoration, I ran is responsible for the killings of thousands of US soldiers. The plan in Syria is to remove Assad from power, and for the US to develop allies in Syria we can trust to lead the next government something akin to what we did in Iraq and what we are achieving in Afghanistan.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1371398998653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371400389889-53</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you on the side of Alqaeda ? Why do you love Americas enemies ? As for I ran wanting to Nuke the US ? do you have a credible source where he actually SAID that ?</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1371400389889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371400583424-54</Id><Title>Wait and See: on Changes in I ran</Title><Msg>For eight years the former government in I ran waged a war against the US using surrogates like the Taliban and #$%$ insurgents in I raq. Iran has been the key ally aiding the Syrian dictator in the use of Chemical weapons, displacing millions of civilians, the destruction of towns and cities in Syrian and the murder of some 60 thousand civilians in Syria. Achmedijad's anti-American rhetoric to put it mildly made clear I rans intent against the US. The alliance with Russia and North Korea to provide Iran nuclear weapons capablities is a present danger. But now the hard line government is out and the majority of the I ranian people elected a reform candidate. What changes he proposes to make to end the civil war in Syria, stop the nuclear weapons program and stop arming the Taliban we should wait and see and give him a change. Therefore I will hold off for now calling for the bombing of I ran.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1371400583424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371400713730-55</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the large swept wings have flex wings, ridged wings are for smaller aircraft. These 787 wings have way too much flex. After the test flight Boeing PR pitch said it was to give comfort to the passenger by the soft bounces. (something like an inner tube on the ocean). Remember these were the same designers and company that built the wings that would break off of the AP and they were going to fly it that way until some refused. They also were the ones that designed and built the center section front spar too weak (the part that the airplane is built around). How did they find out it was to weak? Maybe because the morning aft installing engines, they were resting on the floor? Come on fool quit making excuses for the hacks at the flying public's expense.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371400713730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371400899716-56</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus listens to their sharholders, result Airbus sharholders better than boeing shareholder.Airbus up 164% -3 years</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371385219675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:20:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I realize the dividend based on the dollar amount is small, but percentage wise, Airbus would need to raise their dividend by 46% to get to 1.9%.. Which EADS stock symbol do you look up to get any dividend at all. EADS.NV, EADS.MU etc.? They all indicate no dividend. Not being a troll, just want to know where the 1.3% comes from</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371400899716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371400948932-57</Id><Title>June delivery status</Title><Msg>So far I have found 26 deliveries. 18 737's. 1 747. 1 767. 3 777's. 3 787's.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1371400948932</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 12:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404167417-58</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What your hardline I ranian eyes miss in reading the news events is that the US in aiding Syrian freedom fighters is making an all out effort to prevent US arms getting into the hands of al qaeda rebels. Don't tell me I am on the side of al qaeda. I have been here a continuous hawk against al qaeda since 9/11/01. I put the mark on al qaeda for the terrorist attack of 9/11 from the beginning while your ilk denied al qaeda were responsible for 9/11. The winds have shifted I ranian now see al qaeda as an enemy. have not only been against al qaeda I am against all I slamic terrorists and their sponsors like the I ranian extremists in power. Hopefully not for long.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1371404167417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:36:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371404931944-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd put your hair out, but A) I just went No.1 and B) it's so much fun watching you run around screaming in dread about preposterous things you have made up.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371404931944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371405304759-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when Michelle made the statement, "I live a single mothers life". I bet it came pretty close.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371405304759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371405594388-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when you consider the killing of Ben Laden as it played out on the tv. Americans learned later a Hollywood producer where there in the White House. Penata said I am not responsible for the clearance of those in the White House, then you have to think a stranger can get there. This past week the WSJ carried an article that thru the investigation of emails that Penata had invited this guy. So its in facts lies covering up lies, like where does this end. Sociopath the correct term for these people, Penata also. No shame.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371405594388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 13:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408559137-62</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets be real, with all of the misques that Airbus has had, they are about 3 years behind schedule on the A350 program also. I don't know what you read or smoke, but remember this, Airbus was so sure of themselves, they felt that they could compete with the 787 with a slightly modified A330 until 500 orders or so, they realied that they made a bad assumption. You are aware that the 787 is lighter then the A350, and except for the A350-1000 the A350-800 and A350-900 virtually use the same engines as the 787s. You are aware that the airlines that have 787s have report that the 787 have exceeded expectations and are getting better fuel economy then advertised.</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1371408559137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371409695489-63</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The difference between the position of a B-52's wingtip on the ground, and a B-52's wingtip in flight was 15 feet. That was in the 1950s. So what's new and dangerous ? Care to speculate (more)?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371409695489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371410879391-64</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for me its all about stock appreciation and Airbus wins hands down. Also talk to world travelers, Airbus a more comfortable plane. That's right, my last job at Boeing Flight Controls Project Manager for the 737 and 777. Taking my lunches at Plant II and the Executive dinning room. These managers are just too busy chasing after skirts, Stonecyher and Condit not sure about it now but the move to Chicago probably a good one, Cronie capitalism can't hurt, I could write a book on how many women running around promoted way beyond their skills. Guys like me always running around trying to fix these people screw ups. Keep those pension checks coming.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371410879391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371411921670-65</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some how I knew CG would weigh in here. there is quite a lot of difference. Military plane, all metal, and you are talking static to fullly loaded in flight. Further you are talking about a bend that considers the full lenght of a long wing. In the 787 almost all occurs in the outbd 1/3. and how many ft was that? The 787 bends so far that they begin a considerable arc. Did they ever get those flutter issues resolved? Yes its a design flaw.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371411921670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371411977279-66</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus listens to their sharholders, result Airbus sharholders better than boeing shareholder.Airbus up 164% -3 years</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371385219675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 08:20:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EADSY</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371411977279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371412231074-67</Id><Title>So how do you fix a weak plastic center section main spar</Title><Msg>Copied from a previous post. All the large swept wings have flex wings, ridged wings are for smaller aircraft. These 787 wings have way too much flex. After the test flight Boeing PR pitch said it was to give comfort to the passenger by the soft bounces. (something like an inner tube on the ocean). Remember these were the same designers and company that built the wings that would break off of the AP and they were going to fly it that way until some refused. They also were the ones that designed and built the center section front spar too weak (the part that the airplane is built around). How did they find out it was to weak? Maybe because the morning after installing engines, they were resting on the floor? Come on fool quit making excuses for the hacks at the flying public's expense.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371412231074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371412529661-68</Id><Topic><Title>So how do you fix a weak plastic center section main spar</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371412231074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well one can only imagine. It is all plastic. I suspect they build a containment form around the weak front spar section, same as a form is built to make concrete house foundations. Then bucket in the pails of hot liquid composite material (plastic) and fill it up. A little rebar if you have it.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371412529661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371412857161-69</Id><Title>BA WILL JUMP 15 POINTS in the next 30 days!</Title><Msg>Just laoding up on backlog of all kinds of planes, copters, services, parts, re-fuelers, jets, drones, etc. This is a $200 stock in 10 months.</Msg><Username>helloagain19777</Username><Timestamp>1371412857161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371413785229-70</Id><Topic><Title>So how do you fix a weak plastic center section main spar</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371412231074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Engines did not touch the floor. Flaw was found during proof testing of the wing. Suffice it to say that the fix was an elegant piece of engineering using a very sophisticated analysis model.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371413785229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371414635090-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just keep reminding him that Obama has about 1,250 days in the White House... that's 1,250 days. And I'll keep reminding him. :-)</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371414635090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:30:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371415535113-72</Id><Topic><Title>So how do you fix a weak plastic center section main spar</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371412231074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so I see yu don't know what you are talking about. This defect was not found during the bend test. If its that elegant there must be pictures? Really a hack job to fix a hack mfg job.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371415535113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:45:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371415587416-73</Id><Title>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox</Title><Msg>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox He loves her, he loves her not. Fox News CEO Roger Ailes says he’s bringing Sarah Palin back as an on-air contributor. Will the second time be a charm? By David Freedlander Refudiate that! Former Alaska governor and professional maverick Sarah Palin will be returning to Fox News as on-air contributor, the network announced today. Sarah Palin returns to Fox AP (2) “I’ve had several conversations with Governor Palin in the past few weeks about her rejoining FOX News as a contributor,” said Fox News CEO Roger Ailes in a statement. “I have great confidence in her and am pleased that she will once again add her commentary to our programming. I hope she continues to speak her mind.” Ailes’s confidence in Palin’s TV talent has proven to be a tad misplaced in the past. She was a contributor to the network for three years after her surprise resignation as governor of Alaska in 2009, but was by many accounts an unsteady television presence. Her reality show, Sarah Palin’s Alaska, on TLC, was a critical and commercial flop, and her Fox series, Real American Stories, was panned by critics, with a Los Angeles Times reviewer writing that "As a host, Palin brings little besides her name and all that it has come to mean. Despite her time on the campaign trail and in front of often-unfriendly cameras, Palin still has an eyes-locked-on-the-teleprompter stiffness." Joe Muto, a former Fox News employee who was fired after he anonymously blogged on Gawker about what it was like to work at the network, and who dished about the inner workings of the network in his new book, Atheist in the Foxhole, described mounting frustration at Fox with the former governor—this, despite Palin being treated as a rock star when she first arrived at company headquarters. Ailes’s confidence in Palin’s TV talent has proven to be a tad misplaced in the past. “It started going awry for Sarah Palin at Fox almost immediately. She wasn’t</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371415587416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371415655508-74</Id><Topic><Title>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371415587416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>willing to do the work. And they made it easy for her. They built a studio for her in house in Alaska, so all she had to do was slap on some makeup and go sit in front of the camera,” Muto told The Daily Beast. “She would still show up late, unprepared, hadn’t even bothered to study what the topic was and would completely whiff it on the air.” At times, Ailes has acknowledged her shortcomings, telling an Associated Press reporter in 2011, “I hired Sarah Palin because she was hot and got ratings.” Palin responded in kind. When she decided not to run for president in 2012, she did not make the announcement on Fox but instead read a letter aloud on conservative radio host Mark Levin’s program. She took to Facebook to vent when Fox News cancelled her interview of John McCain during the 2012 convention. Although Palin has a devoted following in some conservative corners of the country—witness the loud cheers she received when she slurped from a Big Gulp on stage at the Conservative Political Action Committee annual meeting this year, in a rebuke to Mayor Mike Bloomberg’s large-soda ban—others in the Republican Party have been urging the faithful to move away from Palin’s brand of emotional, scorched-earth politics. She is not considered a likely contender for the 2016 presidential nomination, even though she continues to be a key endorser in GOP primaries. Palin will appear on Fox’s daytime and primetime programming, according to the network, starting with an appearance on FOX &amp; Friends on Monday, June 17. She will also contribute to FOX Business Network. In a statement, Palin gushed about the network and her new role: "The power of FOX News is unparalleled. The role of FOX News in the important debates in our world is indispensable,” she said. “I am pleased and proud to be rejoining Roger Ailes and the great people at FOX."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371415655508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371415698878-75</Id><Topic><Title>British Airways set to confirm an order for 10 787-10 Dreamliner --- $2.5 billion value approx</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371389061992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 09:24:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how much will Boeing lose on that order -- like $0.5 billion?</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1371415698878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371416744907-76</Id><Title>From Fox News to Rush: Secrets of the right’s lie machine</Title><Msg>One key factor that has altered campaign coverage comes from the corporate right in the form of “conservative” media. If there has been a vacuum created by the downsizing of newsrooms, conservative media have filled it with an insistent partisanship unseen in commercial news media for nearly a century. The conservative media program has been a cornerstone of the Dollarocracy’s — the big money and corporate media election complex — political program since at least Lewis Powell’s 1971 memo. Initially, the work was largely about criticizing the news media for being unfair to conservative Republicans and having a liberal Democratic bias. Although the actual research to support these claims was, to be generous, thin—one major book edited by Brent Bozell actually claimed corporations such as General Electric were “liberal” companies with an interest in anti-business journalism because they had made small donations to groups like the NAACP and the Audubon Society—the point was not to win academic arguments. The point of bashing the “liberal media,” as Republican National Committee chairman Rich Bond conceded in 1992, was to “work the refs” like a basketball coach does so that “maybe the ref will cut you a little slack” on the next play. The ultimate aim of Dollarocracy was, as James Brian McPherson put it, “to destroy the professionalism that has defined journalism since the mid-twentieth century.” The core problem was that professional journalism, to the extent it allowed editors and reporters some autonomy from the political and commercial values of owners, opened space for the legitimate presentation of news and perspectives beyond the range preferred by conservatives. That professional journalism basically conveyed the debates and consensus of official sources and remained steadfastly within the ideological range of the leadership of the two main political parties—it never was sympathetic to the political left—was of no concern. It still gave coverage to policy positions on issues such as unions, public education, civil rights, progressive taxation, social security, and the environment that were thoroughly mainstream but anathema to the right. Key to moving the political center of gravity to the right was getting the news media on the train, and that meant getting them to have a worldview more decidedly sympathetic to the needs of society’s owners. Newt Gingrich was blunt when he told media owners in 1995 that they needed to crack the whip on their newsrooms and have the news support the corporation’s politics. “Get your children to behave,” he demanded in a private meeting with media CEOs. In the late 1980s, conservatives moved from criticism to participation with the aggressive creation of right-wing partisan media. The first decisive move came with AM talk radio. The elimination of the Fairness Doctrine (which required that a broadcaster provide two sides to controversial political issues) and the relaxation of ownership rules such that a handful of companies established vast empires opened the door to a tidal wave of hard-core right-wing talk-show hosts. By the first decade of the century, the 257 talk stations owned by the five largest companies were airing over 2,500 hours of political talk weekly and well over 90 percent was decidedly right wing. This isn’t your grandfather’s conservatism either. Although some conservative hosts, such as Michael Medved, can be quite thoughtful, just as conservative writers such as William Kristol will sometimes acknowledge when the movement has gone off the rails, the realists are in the minority. For a huge portion of contemporary conservative media, the broadcast begins and ends with the fear card, and it is often played in extraordinarily incendiary ways. Sure, some of the radio ranting comes from lightweights who are only trying to fill the three hours on the all-talk affiliate in St. Louis or Minneapolis. But the most effective purveyors of the venom are gifted and charismatic figures, such as Glenn Beck and Michael Levin, whose fire-and-brimstone moralizing is matched only by their willingness to bend the truth to support whatever argument they’ve decided to make that day. Across large swatches of America, and most rural areas where little journalism remains, right-wing talk radio is arguably the leading source of political information. The undisputed heavyweight champion was and is Rush Limbaugh, who emerged as a national radio force by 1990 and who by 1993 was already recognized by the bible of modern conservatism, William F. Buckley Jr.’s National Review magazine, as an unmatched political power in Republican circles; the Review dubbed him the “Leader of the Opposition.” Limbaugh and his cohorts have the power to make or break Republican politicians, and all who wish successful national careers have to pray at his far-right altar or suffer the consequences. As Kathleen Hall Jamieson and Joseph Cappella put it, in many respects Limbaugh came to play the role party leaders had played in earlier times. In the late 1990s, Rupert Murdoch launched the Fox News cable channel, and because television is such a ubiquitous and powerful medium, that put right-wing news media in the center of the mainstream. Michael Wolff characterized Fox News as “the ultimate Murdoch product,” because it brought tabloid journalism to American television. What has been missed in the analysis of Fox News is the business model of tabloid journalism: dispense with actual reporting, which costs a lot of money to do well, and replace it with far less expensive pontificating that will attract audiences. For a tabloid news channel, that means the value added is a colorful partisan take on the news; otherwise the channel has no reason to attract viewers. Former CNN head Rick Kaplan told the story of how he was confronted by Time Warner executives in 1999 or 2000 who were dissatisfied with CNN’s profits despite what had been record revenues and a solid return. “But Fox News made just as much profit,” Kaplan was informed, “and did so with just half the revenues of CNN, because it does not carry so many reporters on its staff.” The message to Kaplan was clear: close bureaus and fire reporters, lots of them. In short, Fox News is the logical business product for an era where corporations deem journalism an unprofitable undertaking. Fox News and the conservative media sector (including the conservative blogosphere) provide a “self-protective enclave” for conservatives to cocoon themselves. Research demonstrates that the more a person consumes conservative media, the more likely she is to dismiss any news or arguments that contradict the conservative position as liberal propaganda and lies. Tom Frank argued that the point of conservative media is to facilitate a “deliberate cognitive withdrawal from the shared world” by their adherents. Conservative media also, to a remarkable extent, stay on message, and the message is largely that of the Republican Party; these media, at least Fox News and Limbaugh, seem to march in lockstep with the same talking points, the same issues, and even the same terminology deployed across the board. They apply the core principles of advertising and propaganda. Although Fox News and today’s conservative media might look at first glance like descendants of the partisan media of the nineteenth century, there are crucial differences. The old partisan media were far smaller in scale, and they operated in very competitive markets where it was not difficult for newcomers to effectively enter the field, hence giving readers/voters/citizens considerable leverage and a greater diversity of views. A partisan newspaper had difficulty avoiding periodic serious engagement with contrary policy positions in its pages if it wished to remain credible. Chains and corporate empires did not exist. In partisan systems, everyone is partisan and behavior is thus understood. Moreover, nineteenth-century newspapers, while often aligned with parties, tended also to be ideologically driven, which meant that they frequently fought inside parties and in the broader political landscape for a set of ideals. In the twenty-first century, ideals are invariably sacrificed by corporate right-wing media outlets that are, first and foremost, profit machines owned by some of the largest multinational conglomerates on the planet. They make their profits by selling advertising to other large corporations. They have considerable monopoly power and receive valuable licenses and privileges from the government, which they are adamant to protect. They are at the pinnacle of the corporate establishment as much as the political establishment. The single most important difference, however, is the shell-game premise of the entire conservative media shtick: that the mainstream news media have a distinct liberal bias that is deeply hostile to the right and big business and therefore that conservatives are simply offering either straight unbiased news by contrast or, more to the point, are justifiably bending the stick in the conservative direction to balance the liberal propaganda. In the current system, mainstream journalism works formally to not favor either major party and to prove at every turn its lack of bias toward either party. Reporters have to answer for such a bias if it is exposed. Conservative media do not have to play by those rules. The irony, of course, is that Fox News insists that it is “Fair and Balanced” and that “We Report, You Decide,” so it assumes the mantle and prerogatives of professional journalism while going about its partisan business. Being a partisan player in the world of professional journalism has provided the right with considerable power to set the news agenda. Traditional journalists get their cues about what to cover from official sources and can dismiss some as ludicrous if they fail to meet an evidentiary standard and are opposed by other official sources. Fox and the conservative media, on the other hand, can reduce complex issues to one-word battle cries—“ACORN!” “Solyndra!” “Benghazi!”—which Republican politicians gleefully echo. Then those same politicians and right-wing media “watchdogs” badger traditional media for having a “liberal bias” if they do not cover the stories as well. By the time a hyperpartisan congressman like House Oversight and Government Reform Committee chairman Darrell Issa, a Republican from California, is gaveling hearings into session, the Washington press corps is not about to say, “Hold it! This is ridiculous.” So it is that the nonstories that come to dominate news cycles invariably benefit the right. But the right is never satisfied. Because they believe they are in an uphill battle with liberal propagandists, conservative media can have an unabashed and breathtaking double standard: they have very different evidentiary standards for stories that support, rather than damage, their politics. If facts prove inconvenient for the preferred narrative, ignore them. Republican officials are treated entirely differently from Democrats, even when the facts of a story are virtually identical. It is this opportunistic and unprincipled nature of conservative “journalism” that draws widespread analysis and consternation from outside the political right and from those remaining thoughtful conservatives willing to brave the wrath of Limbaugh. Between the cocoon effect and the shameless disregard for consistency and intellectual honesty, it is not surprising that professional surveys tend to find regular viewers of Fox News to be more ignorant about what is actually happening in the world compared to those who watch other networks. In November 2011, Fairleigh Dickinson University’s PublicMind Poll examined how New Jerseyans watched television news, and the poll concluded that “some outlets, especially Fox News, lead people to be even less informed than those who say they don’t watch any news at all.” In some surveys, to be accurate, Fox News does not rank at rock bottom in terms of audience knowledge. But on balance, it is the clown dunce of TV news. No other network ever comes close to getting the sort of assessment Fox News received from World Public Opinion, a project managed by the Program on International Policy Attitudes (PIPA) at the University of Maryland, in 2010. As one reporter summarized it, PIPA conducted a “survey of American voters that shows that Fox News viewers are significantly more misinformed than consumers of news from other sources. What’s more, the study shows that greater exposure to Fox News increases misinformation. So the more you watch, the less you know. Or to be precise, the more you think you know that is actually false.” As Theda Skocpol and Vanessa Williamson concluded in their study of the Tea Party, “Fox News makes viewers both more conservative and less informed.” What may be most revealing is that there is no evidence that this finding bothers the management of Fox News in the least. In private moments, conservatives concede they have won the battle to control the news, though to justify their modus operandi, they have to maintain and ceaselessly hype the shtick of being the abused outsiders battling entrenched liberal dominance. The mainstream of journalism has indeed moved to the right, in part because it has followed official sources to the right. Also the corporate news media owners, as Newt Gingrich understood, were certainly open to the idea of more probusiness journalism. The news media have made concerted efforts to appear welcoming to the right, unlike any similar welcome to the left. As Jeff Cohen, who has spent time in all the major cable TV newsrooms, observed, the greatest fear of working journalists is to be accused of being a liberal. “Nearly all of the Clinton scandals,” McPherson noted, “were set in motion by right-wing groups, floated through conservative media organs.” Rick Kaplan acknowledged as much and said he sometimes covered stories at CNN for fear of right-wing attack, not because they were legitimate stories. If professional journalism was resolute in splitting the difference between the two parties, there has been a greater price to pay for antagonizing Republicans in recent years. The unraveling of media over the past two decades has driven many liberals, not to mention those to their left, to the brink of madness. Many are frustrated that traditional journalism has proven so incapable of resisting the right. With the success of Keith Olbermann’s on-air commentaries condemning the Bush-Cheney administration, MSNBC began to recognize that a lucrative market for low-expense, high-revenue programming was being underserved; it gradually put a few explicitly liberal programs on its schedule, which now includes boundary-breaking shows hosted by Rachel Maddow, Lawrence O’Donnell, Chris Hayes, and Ed Schultz. Some have equated these programs with Fox News in style, imagining MSNBC as just a left-wing variant on Rupert Murdoch’s network, but the comparison fails upon inspection. Although these programs are expressly liberal, they are more independent of the Democratic Party than Fox has been of the Republican—as was amply evident when MSNBC hosts were quick to decry Obama’s weak performance in the first of 2012’s three presidential debates. They also have a commitment to factual accuracy and intellectual consistency that is rare on the right. At the same time, as Olbermann and Cenk Uygur learned as they were shown the door, the corporate management has little sympathy with the politics of these shows if it veers too often outside the mainstream Democratic Party, even when the shows are profitable. There is an implicit pressure to rein in the politics. Most striking is this: the explicitly liberal programs tend to spend considerable time fact-checking, debunking, and ridiculing the material on Fox and conservative talk radio. Right-wing media seem far less interested in what the liberals are saying. Why should they be? In the overall calculus, they are still calling the shots, and the liberals spend inordinate amounts of their time responding to the right. This call and response is a logical commercial manifestation of the post-journalism moment. Neither Fox News nor MSNBC has its own teams of reporters to send out to break news stories. Slogans like “We Report, You Decide” are rooted in fantasy. Cable channels have program hosts, producers, and guest bookers. They look at what others are reporting, and then they invite people to talk about the politics of the day. At their best, they invite interesting and diverse guests who might even disagree with one another—as happened on Ed Schultz’s MSNBC show during the debate about whether to include a public option in the Affordable Care Act. At their worst, they feature Sean Hannity and Karl Rove abandoning all the touchstones of realism and engaging in extended preelection discussions about how all the polls are wrong and Mitt Romney will win by a landslide. VOTE THIS WAY If the rise of conservative media aggressively pushing Dollarocracy policies has strongly shaped political journalism, it has had a similar effect on election coverage. Conservative media are obsessed with elections and with winning power. They aggressively promote Republican candidates, push their issues, and amplify the charges made in TV political ads. They can provide a launching pad for charges against Democrats or progressive organizations and use their influence to demand mainstream coverage. Consider how the group ACORN, which was instrumental in registering poor people to vote, was destroyed in 2009–2010, based on a largely bogus video hatchet job. The stalwarts of conservative media are by their own admission expressly committed to Republican electoral success—as anyone who has heard the whistle of Sean Hannity’s “Stop Obama Express” well understands—by any means necessary. During the 2012 presidential campaign, Fox News steadfastly refused to address any significant Romney campaign falsehoods that had been exposed in the balance of the media. It routinely announced that the “mainstream” media were “in the bag” for Obama, all the while giving the Romney campaign an enormous advantage on the amount and tenor of coverage. In the final week before the election, Fox News gave coverage of Romney’s campaign speeches eighty-four minutes of airtime, compared to eighteen minutes for Obama. In contrast, the coverage elsewhere was only slightly greater timewise for Obama: forty-nine minutes to forty-two at MSNBC and fifty-three minutes to forty-two at CNN. Fox News is now a singular force in Republican politics. “The introduction of Fox News into the cable roster has been shown to have coincided with an uptick in voting for Republican presidential candidates,” Skocpol and Williamson noted. “The capacity to shift U.S. voting patterns suggests that Fox News has a very real persuasive power.” Fox News almost singlehandedly made the Tea Party a powerful force in American politics in 2009–2010, as Tom Frank put it, by presenting “the emerging protest campaign as if it was the network’s own reality show.” Skocpol and Williamson’s comprehensive analysis of the media coverage of the Tea Party concluded that Fox News’ “assiduous promotional and informational efforts surely made a big difference.” They argued that “Tea Partiers’ factually inaccurate beliefs about many policy matters are particularly striking given their relatively high levels of education and overall savvy about the political process. It is hard to escape the conclusion that deliberate propagation of falsehoods by Fox and other powerful media outlets is responsible for mis-arming otherwise adept Tea Partiers, feeding them inaccurate facts and falsely hyped fears.” By 2011, observers noted that traditional presidential “retail” campaigning had all but disappeared on the Republican side. “The contenders,” the New York Times observed, “are far more likely to make their visits on television than to ever drop by in person.” “Everything has changed,” Kansas Republican governor Sam Brownback stated. “It’s like a town hall every day on Fox News. You hear people talking back to you what you saw yesterday on Fox. I like Fox, and I’m glad we have an outlet, but it is having a major, major effect on what happens.” Fox’s first great achievement came in 2000 when it played a foundational role in getting George W. Bush in the White House despite the fact that he lost the vote. At a critical point in the early morning hours of the day after the November 7, 2000, election, Fox analysts—led by a cousin of Bush, John Prescott Ellis (who would later admit to having been in contact with the Bush campaign in the fateful night)—declared that Bush had won Florida. Thinking Fox had simply crunched the numbers more quickly, the other networks quickly followed Fox in making the call and, with it, identifying Bush as the winner of the Electoral College competition that would identify the next president. But Fox had the same numbers that the other networks had, and its analysts could not by any reasonable estimate have found a win for Bush in the available data. The Florida race, as the ensuing weeks of wrangling over recounts would confirm, was too close to call on election night. Indeed, there is an argument to be made that it was still too close to call when, thirty-six days later, a U.S. Supreme Court majority, made up of justices appointed by administrations in which Bush’s father had served, called the contest for the Republican nominee. To our view, there is a better argument to be made that Democrat Al Gore had a more credible claim to victory. That Gore was never able to effectively stake that claim, that he was in fact portrayed throughout the recount fight as a sore loser, was a media construct. By making a seemingly impossible election night call for Bush, Fox positioned the Republican as the inevitable winner. Twelve years later, the mastermind of Bush’s campaign, Karl Rove, melted down on Fox’s election night broadcast, openly arguing with the network after it called the key swing state of Ohio for Obama. In 2012, however, it wasn’t too close to call. A grudging Rove had to accept the will of the people, a circumstance with which he did not seem to be entirely familiar. But only the most naïve commentators presumed that Rove’s embarrassment was anything but transitory. The next day, he was on a conference call, explaining how he was recalculating for the next election. And Fox was featuring him once more, as if nothing had happened. For conservatives, Fox means never having to say you’re sorry—even when you are massively, publicly wrong. That’s because, like most of the right-wing echo chamber, Fox is not journalism. It’s what fills the void when journalism disappears. The political right is perfectly comfortable with the false construct of a “news” network that has, in the words of Eric Boehlert, “altered the game by unchaining itself from the moral groundings of U.S. journalism.” For partisans who do not want to be held to account, the conservative media landscape of the twenty-first century looks like a future in which they could reside quite comfortably. A world with little journalism, where the affairs of the wealthy and corporations receive little scrutiny, especially their dalliances with politicians, and where the political news agenda is dominated by their partisan news media and pundits, is jim-dandy. The conservative media can continue their migration and colonization of the news so that they are indeed the mainstream. It is a world where their ability to win elections is greatly enhanced, even when they are pushing policies opposed by the majority of the population. Even if they lose an election, as happened with the 2012 presidential race, conservative media are there the next day to tell conservatives that they need not accept the will of the people. “Conservatism did not lose last night,” shouted Rush Limbaugh on November 7, 2012. Actually, it had lost. Rather badly. But if there is a basic premise that unites Limbaugh, the folks on Fox, and the vast infrastructure of regional right-wing talkers, it is this: conservatives should never bend to the demands of the voters; voters should be made to bend to the demands of conservatives. To that end, conservative media actively campaign against any proposal that might renew actual journalism. The conservative media and dollarcrats oppose all policy measures to address the journalism crisis, from increasing postal subsidies, enhancing public media, or breaking up monopoly media firms to create more competition. To the conservatives and to Dollarocracy, the status quo is just fine, thank you.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371416744907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371418083816-77</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus 350 first flight and burns 25% less fuel than a 787, no lithium batteries and TSLA up as I said,BA not so good</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371216663708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The original story on Friday in the LATimes and others had the below sentences near the end of the report. Airbus CEO Bregier (or EADS CEO Enders) has never and would never say 25 percent better than the 787 because he is knowledgable about airplanes and comparisons. Wayne likes to see something in reports that isn't there and modifies it (by adding 787 after Boeing). That's called plagarism or worse. You've been corrected again. Compare Wayne's modified sentence to the original article. Wayne's sentence: A350 burns 25 percent less fuel than the Boeing 787 due to its lighter weight, redesigned Rolls Royce engines and new aerodynamics. From LATimes Business on Friday morning:</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371418083816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371418691290-78</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many delusions and hallucinations in there courtesy gregjametommaxweirdo.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1371418691290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371419024376-79</Id><Topic><Title>So how do you fix a weak plastic center section main spar</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371412231074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's quite an imagination you've got. Anybody besides you know about this alleged defect?</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371419024376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:43:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420248664-80</Id><Topic><Title>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371415587416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you DFC's hate successful women? Are you a fearful little cowardly pansy?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371420248664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371420319694-81</Id><Title>Boeing to launch 787-10 with $30 billion order haul approx</Title><Msg>Paris Airshow is a great week. Nice award noted above--total I am sure to increase after BA announced the 787-10. This plane will eliminate the A350 as it can hold about 80 more passangers and have a greater range</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371420319694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420385847-82</Id><Topic><Title>From Fox News to Rush: Secrets of the right’s lie machine</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371416744907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you DFC's need propaganda instead of facts for your very survival and existence?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371420385847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420503518-83</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you drunk or just trying to be a funny little DFC?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371420503518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371420586624-84</Id><Title>777x max 415 passengers while A350-1000 only holds 350 passengers</Title><Msg>A350, even in its stretch version, can't match capacity. Wait till the 777x comes out with their planned stretch 777x which may eliminate the hard to park A380</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371420586624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420632605-85</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven, a DFC, is all for as long as he doesn't have to go.............</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371420632605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371420712805-86</Id><Topic><Title>Obonzo happy to give guns to terrorists while trying to take them away from US citizens</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371391586250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it trendy?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1371420712805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371420952557-87</Id><Title>Hi, I'm Carlos Slim</Title><Msg>Compared to me Paul McCartney is a poor excuse for value. People pay him for the value they think he produces and people pay me for the same reason. It just so happens people think I produce a lot more value than does the dwarf sized limey.</Msg><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371420952557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371421203629-88</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nonsense, floyd. But that's about all you ever have, so why would I be surprised? In the first place, I'm 67 years old. Would you want me watching your back in a fight? In the second place, I've been there, done that, and bought the T-shirt. 44 years ago. I wouldn't want to get in the way of you finally getting your chance. Come home with medals, son. Put your actions where your bragging is.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371421203629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371421451972-89</Id><Topic><Title>So how do you fix a weak plastic center section main spar</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371412231074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 15:50:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's your duty to every future airline passenger to e-mail the Wall Street Journal right this minute. Hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371421451972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371422010898-90</Id><Title>Fascist State attacks Conservative News Sites....</Title><Msg>I did a search after horrendously slow results on drudge, hotair, ....state apparachiks, goggles n yahoos, seemingly immune from Washington Times... "The Washington Free Beacon yesterday became the latest victim in a wave of cyber attacks targeting conservative news outlets. The Beacon, in what appears to be a coordinated assault, joined National Journal and radio station WTOP as a target after certain articles were featured on the Drudge Report, one of the most heavily trafficked and influential sites in the world...." I expect they're actively jamming sites that make reference to attacks</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371422010898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:33:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371422604689-91</Id><Topic><Title>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371415587416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She's successful only if your definition of successful includes her losing to Obama, and then deciding NOT to run anymore because she knows she will continue to lose.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371422604689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371422687829-92</Id><Topic><Title>From Fox News to Rush: Secrets of the right’s lie machine</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371416744907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell me, floyd... what color is the sky in your world?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371422687829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371422717801-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent Post Gregjanetommax! Obama is married to his Muslim Religion. Everything else takes a second seat. Michelle's comment is an admission of her roll in the union between the President and herself. I heard the Obama marriage was an arrangement conceived by Rev. Jessie Jackson and Rev. Wright.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1371422717801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423286731-94</Id><Topic><Title>Fascist State attacks Conservative News Sites....</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371422010898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably not. More likely the NSA, SEC, FBI, XYZ, USAF, USAID, KKK, and BFD are all targeting you specifically.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1371423286731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423367435-95</Id><Topic><Title>Fascist State attacks Conservative News Sites....</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371422010898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>could be the fascist's use our schools, the IRS, EPA, and every other gov't agency to work their will</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371423367435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423590644-96</Id><Topic><Title>Fascist State attacks Conservative News Sites....</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371422010898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably not. Maybe you're simply a goofus doofus zoofus. On your best day. Ever.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1371423590644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371423728794-97</Id><Topic><Title>Fascist State attacks Conservative News Sites....</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371422010898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty, you able to track down your daddy today?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371423728794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371426719997-98</Id><Topic><Title>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371415587416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumbos hate sarah, she gives em sissy/hissy fits</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371426719997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371427289082-99</Id><Topic><Title>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371415587416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't hate her... just think she's a #$%$. And that's being very generous.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371427289082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371427803207-100</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Don't tell me I am on the side of al Qaeda" You seem to be Pro Obama...he supports the Syrian Rebels and some of the Syrian Rebels ARE Alqaeda OR give loyalty to that organization.....so what else ARE we to believe as to where your loyalties are</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371427803207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371428764680-101</Id><Topic><Title>Don’t Misunderestimate Her! Sarah Palin Returns to Fox</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371415587416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's great news that She is back on Fox. Fox and the country are better for it. Although the dim witted, damocrates can't figure it out.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371428764680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371428908188-102</Id><Title>$$$$ BUY PREFERREDS $$$$ 6-7% dividends..sleep at night !!..</Title><Msg>dittO again</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1371428908188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371433237443-103</Id><Topic><Title>Fascist State attacks Conservative News Sites....</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371422010898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:33:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our government's intolerance of Christians and Jews and TeaParty and Conservatives is a reflection of this President's policies within government. My favorite word of the day: intolerance. Can a democrat recognize tyranny when it's knocking at the door or will they continue to drink the kool- aid that's being put out by the lamestream government media? They don't believe it? They do believe it but aren't being honest with themselves? They don't believe it now but did believe it when Bush was president? As a independent voter I see and except that both parties are horribly corrupted. I've voted republican, democrat, and independent. I have never been this disappointed or frightened by what I am witnessing today by our unresponsive government. Corruption is eating away at the heart of this government. A great Cancer has taken hold of this nation.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1371433237443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 21:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371433805537-104</Id><Topic><Title>USA TODAY: "Syrian rebels pledge loyalty to al-Qaeda" (The guys Obama Arms)</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371394090570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 10:48:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All those who are still having cognitive dissonance over a Sitting President giving aide and comfort to the enemy of 9-11...there IS an explanation...and that is that AlQaeda is on the payroll in Syria and Libya...they were on the payroll against the Russians in Afganistan in the 80s, they were on the payroll in Kosovo...AND MOST IMPORTATNLY FOR YOU TO UNDERSTAND ALQAEDA WAS ON THE PAYROLL on 9-11-2001 Sibel Edmonds of Able Danger fame verifies it....the CIA was visiting Bin Ladin 6 weeks before 9-11...the Bushs were doing business with the Bin Ladin group for years...Bin Ladin could have been killed dozens of times and patriots like Col Schaefer were told to stand down dozens of times...oh ..and don't forget the Anwar Al Alaki being invited to the Pentagon AFTER 9-11.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371433805537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 21:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371438070215-105</Id><Topic><Title>From Fox News to Rush: Secrets of the right’s lie machine</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371416744907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 17:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Floyds has to open his mouth first in order to see it.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1371438070215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 23:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371438767452-106</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well the A380 didn't have enough flex or bending. That is why the brackets inside the A380 had cracks and had to be replaced. The more you say the more stupid you sound.</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1371438767452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 23:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371439343321-107</Id><Title>Boeing Defends 777X Aluminum Hull----the 777’s fuselag proven</Title><Msg>The 777X will burn 20 percent less fuel and have a 15 percent operating improvement over the current 777-300ER. Customers are very excited about the potential of the aircraft. The 777X will have a maximum capacity of about 415 people in a three-class setup. Boeing plans to modify the fuselage to make more space in the 777X.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371439343321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 23:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371439502731-108</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Defends 777X Aluminum Hull----the 777’s fuselag proven</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371439343321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 23:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part of Boeing overall plan to reduce development costs. The risk mitagation folks are very happy to go with a modified proven product. Now the monster size wing</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371439502731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 23:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371439622311-109</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go watch the 787 static test video of the wing ultimate test. The wings are as high as the top of the tail and never broke. I don't think they pushed to to the breaking level, but the flex was within predictions with no failures.(except maybe the side of body joint which they corrected)</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371439622311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 23:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371439920945-110</Id><Topic><Title>777x max 415 passengers while A350-1000 only holds 350 passengers</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371420586624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 18:09:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That fact alone will sway alot of awards in this envirnoment of the ever increasing capacity and route length competition. If done right, the 777x could be much bigger than projected. Middle East and Indonesia/china region is really expanding. Can't make airports fast enough</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371439920945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 23:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>