<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368506605424-1</Id><Title>This just in .. .</Title><Msg>explorers have found another level of the ruins of TROY. After deciphering the ancient writings and glyphs, it became evident that the destruction of TROY was the direct result of a GW Bush appointee forgetting to lock the main gate. The Obama administration is using this an an example of the attempts to politicize the issue by blaming it on a so called Trojan horse- which was actually paid for by Mitt Rommney to discredit BaracK Hussein Homer Harry reid has promised to bring the GOP to justice</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368506605424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 00:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368508611058-2</Id><Topic><Title>This just in .. .</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368506605424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 00:43:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And this was foretold in 2500 BC by #$%$ Cheney the Oracle of Halliburton, who caused the extinction of the dinosaurs that young Harry Reid raised on his T Rex ranch.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1368508611058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 01:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368509124207-3</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush taps terrorists phone calls and the press screams civil rights infringement. Obama taps reporters phones and its all OK, maybe the ACLU has lockjaw.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1368509124207</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 01:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368509563166-4</Id><Topic><Title>Is it jet lag or does Barry believe his own lies?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368486284805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 19:04:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you know he is lying - his teleprompter is on</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1368509563166</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 01:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368515978374-5</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly report Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368221271918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DDD up 7.53% today , and after market analyst just raised earnings expectations and this is not a stock I am doing this week it does not make enough for me too bad the gibberish out of Boeing trolls who dwell in isolated rocks, mountains, or caves, live together in small family units, and are rarely helpful to human beings. As time allows I will be posting my better than DDD and other stocks at the end of the week after I make my money, trolls you can pick up my scraps after I get the body of the dog you can have the tail. This iss fun I like the stoogies of Boeing and trills they make my life fun and rewarding . i just wanted to add the DDD analyst upgrade to arnings tonight and happy trading unless you own boeing then your a sucker for a loser Hart-Smith said it all MD to BA its a failure idea</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368515978374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 03:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368516253855-6</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tesla up 14.17% today Monday 5-13 -2013 and up 159% year to date and I told you on march 3 to look into it they use lithium batteries too , remember Boeing trolls, Boeing is up laugh now 425 in 5 years not as good as 159% in 3 month then is it. remember I told you to get inot apple for 15 years until Seve jobs died, too back Boeing hacks and trolls listen now or stay in boeing they need yoru money trolls-trolls dwell in isolated rocks, mountains, or caves, live together in small family units, and are rarely helpful to human beings.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368516253855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 03:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368523921404-7</Id><Topic><Title>Is Obama Clueless about What Going on in his Administration?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368477773046</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What he has effectively done is convince the board that you are a complete putz who knows nothing about what's going on..</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368523921404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 05:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368524090329-8</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reprises ’90s scandal playbook</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368487248868</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 19:20:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What difference does it make" is about the same as "who cares", you DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368524090329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 05:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368524176865-9</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FatherZosima Himmler, yet another Kent Raven alias and DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368524176865</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 05:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368524438838-10</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly report Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368221271918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever read the articles of impeachment for RMN?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368524438838</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 05:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368528854985-11</Id><Title>WHAT NO ONE WANTS TO DISCUSS ABOUT BENGHAZI</Title><Msg>The Islamic radicals who attacked Benghazi were the same people let loose by the US-led attack on Libya. They were the rebels on whose behalf the US overthrew the Libyan government. Ambassador Stevens was slain by the same Islamic radicals he personally assisted just over one year earlier.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368528854985</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 06:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368531437535-12</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Brother</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368531437535</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368532649488-13</Id><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Msg>Senator Rand Paul responded to the barrage of scandals to hit the Obama administration, from Benghazi, to the IRS targeting conservatives, to the Justice Department spying on Associated Press reporters, by accusing President Obama of being “drunk on power.”</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368534178433-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dem elites, commie n mobro, didn't get where they are, respecting boundaries, or anything else for that matter.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368534178433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368534718991-15</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big brother wanted to know who dem reporters were talking to, before it became news, huh spart i don't expect your financiers were targeted by the IRS, but i'll bet axelrod knows what's on your blackberry, huh jackripper, i mean sparty</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368534718991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368535249197-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dem elites are ruthless, it's no wonder maobowa doesn't have any friends (cept for reggie love, it's rumored his other luv interests met untimely end prior to the last election)</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368535249197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368535481884-17</Id><Title>CommieCare Expected to Increase Premiums between 100 &amp; 400%</Title><Msg>whoops, they lied...AGAIN</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368535481884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368535700633-18</Id><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Msg>Robert Gates: Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack By Brad Knickerbocker | 05/13/13. The Obama administration got some backing Sunday for the way in which it responded as terrorists attacked the US diplomatic facility in Benghazi, Libya, last September – a night of violence and confusion during which Ambassador Christopher Stevens and three other Americans were killed. Former Defense Secretary Robert Gates, a Republican who served in both the Bush and Obama administrations, said if he had been at the Pentagon at that time, "Frankly … I think my decisions would have been just as theirs were.” Republican critics have said a Special Forces team or overflights by fighter aircraft based in Italymight have prevented the US losses or at least frightened off the attackers. Mr. Gates disagrees. Such actions, he said on CBS’s “Face the Nation” Sunday, “without knowing what the environment is, without knowing what the threat is, without having any intelligence in terms of what is actually going on the ground, would have been very dangerous." "It's sort of a cartoonish impression of military capabilities and military forces," Gates said, referring to morning-after analysis. "The one thing that our forces are noted for is planning and preparation before we send people in harm's way, and there just wasn't time to do that." Meanwhile, the veteran diplomat who co-chaired the special board which investigated the US situation at Benghazi before and after the attack said he stands by the panel’s decision not to question then-Secretary of State Hillary Clinton, focusing instead on officials who had direct roles regarding the attack. "We knew where the responsibility rested," said Pickering, who headed the Accountability and Review Board that investigated the attack, along with retired Adm. Mike Mullen, the former chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff. Speaking of Secretary Clinton’s critics, Pickering said, "They've tried to point a finger at people more senior than where we found the decisions were made.” The former ambassador, who served under Republican and Democratic administrations for some 40 years, appeared on three TV news shows Sunday. The politics behind attacking or defending Clinton – one of the most popular politicians in the country today – are palpable. "This has been caught up in the 2016 presidential campaign, this effort to go after Hillary Clinton," said Sen. #$%$ Durbin, a Democrat, on CBS. "They want to bring her in because they think it's a good political show and I think that's unfortunate." Even without the Clinton factor, the Pickering-Mullen review – it found "systematic failures and leadership and management deficiencies at senior levels" of the State Department, concluding that security at Benghazi was "grossly inadequate to deal with the attack that took place" – remains controversial. The top Republican on the House Oversight and Government Reform Committee, Rep. Darrell Issa ofCalifornia, said he wants sworn depositions with Pickering and Mullen. Issa said his panel has not been provided sufficient details on the State Department review, such as a list of everyone the investigators interviewed or a full transcript of those conversations. "We want the facts. We're entitled to the facts,” Issa said on NBC’s “Meet the Press” Sunday. “The American people were effectively lied to for a period of about a month.” Meanwhile, the debate over the “talking points” used to explain Benghazi in the days after the attack remain just as controversial. ABC News – followed by other news sources – reported Friday on State Department e-mails showing that official talking points were “extensively edited as they evolved from the drafts first written entirely by the CIA to the final version distributed to Congress and to US Ambassador to the United Nations Susan Rice before she appeared on five talk shows the Sunday after that attack.” “Summaries of White House and State Department emails … show that the State Department had extensive input into the editing of the talking points,” ABC reported. Republicans describe this as a “cover-up” at the time Obama was running for reelection. US Sen. John McCain (R) of Arizona says he wants Clinton to testify before a select committee on Benghazi. "She had to have been in the loop some way,” McCain told ABC's Martha Raddatz Sunday. "We need a select committee that interviews everybody," he said. "I don’t know what level of scandal this rises to, but I know it rises to the level where it requires a full and complete ventilation of these facts."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536051597-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he turn himself in? I know he was in hiding. Where?, only the Obamanator knows where he hid out.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368536051597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536095917-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's only fault is he is black and this is an ignorant racist readneck country</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368536095917</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:54:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536198588-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey mobro you still think there are commies around?? why don't you let us in on it- who are they and where are they</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368536198588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:56:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536283976-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can actually see the hate ooze out of Rand Paul's pores when he appears on TV</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368536283976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536581755-23</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly report Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368221271918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well this morning, tesla , remember I suggested you follow me on march 3 is up 5.8% in pre market trading that's more than Boeing makes on any day trade !, acad, for those who follow me, was suggested a long time ago for another Boeing troll instead of Boeing. Attention Boeing trolls, ACAD Monday up 5.66%, 3 months up 109% and for one year ACAD is up 735%. Boeing trolls, that is a lot better than 42% in five eyars for Boeing eh ! I am off to get set for my trading today trolls are you going to post gibberish instead of make money , sure that is all you know how to do ha ha .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368536581755</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536598705-24</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whats going on at the IRS is there are going tyo be prosecutions of TAX Cheaters soon. Especially the Koch bros front organizations like the Americans for Prosperity- they have had non profit tax status and they have been campaigning for candidates, and other illegal things for non profits. IRS personnel red flagged them to catch them</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368536598705</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536715399-25</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tsla up 5.5% in premarket !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368536715399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536750407-26</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly report Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368221271918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ddd got a analyst upgrade last night in stock price</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368536750407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536903867-27</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>moebro you wouldn't know big brother if he bit you in the sas-- the mega rich like the Kochs, Olins, Mellons etc etc have been driving this country to a world where Big Brother would truly be watching- not just crooks but everybody. Fox Newspeak would have their TV's everywhere and you wouldn't just watch their TVs their TV's would be watching you- and the radical right, RWNJ's and Tdouchebaggers would be their lieutenants</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368536903867</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368536971272-28</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Floyd the board #$%$ speaks</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368536971272</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368537095497-29</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>moebro you had better make certain you weren't involved in any tax cheating yourself you could be getting a jailhouse suntan in the near future</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368537095497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368537223497-30</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if they were audited and were subject to penalty, i guess they didn't do anything wrong...ahkmed, how did maobowas economic commieczar austin ghoulsby know about the koch brothers taxes? ahkmed, i mean chrissie, err spart, whens the last time you were audited, does the IRS ever audit double n triple dipping welfare queens/kings/msg board disinformation peddlers? is your funding org tax exempt?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368537223497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368537742917-31</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for The Boeing Company Read Now!</Title><Username>dunnmichael487</Username><Timestamp>1368536050121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:54:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that would be the overall direction</Msg><Username>pikejohn797</Username><Timestamp>1368537742917</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368537875966-32</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tesla is being talked up right now on cnbc upgraded( attention for Boeing trolls ) I bet you would like to be up 5.8% before the market opens and ready to take profits at the open or hold on and see if you were in March 3 like I suggested you would be deep into profits now and able to hold and watch. , boeing stock is flat as a pancake on premarket only 400 shares traded not the 1.2 million like tesla tsla so Boeing trolls how si that Boeing stock working for you now ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368537875966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368537946403-33</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong with Americans for Prosperity? Don't you want spending cuts, less regulations on job creators and more freedom for workers? Or are you a collectivists like Obama?</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1368537946403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368538083459-34</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup 100 787's now built and 750 to go- too bad you cant take part in it dell George- maybe if you and your boyfriend had gone to a motel instead of the urinal at renton for your shenanigans you would be able to participate and you would still be employed at Boeing</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368538083459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368538302709-35</Id><Title>Americans for Prosperity is a Great Organization</Title><Msg>Radical Marxists like Obama have never worked in, much less built, a business. All they know is how to take from them so they can give to people who don't. If we want this country to prosper and jobs to be created, we leaders who have know the value of freedom and how it plays a vital part in building a prosperous country.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1368538302709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368538311124-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i expect zosima, i mean chrissie/spart, and maobowa have a lot in common in terms of friends / luvers...no friends and ....</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368538311124</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368538686432-37</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>farter_zemafag While Barry wants to be Django Unchained he has ended up coming across as Jagbag Unhinged. He is contradicting his previous statements on issues, which is not a sign of intelligence the last time I checked. The calm leader facade that Barry created is nothing but an unsustainable PR stunt, and is now eroding in Nixonian fashion with everyone beginning to actually observe Barry's true nature which is that of paranoid liar and power hungry control freak. Barry can fool some of the people some of the time but he can only fool morons time after time. I told the alias IDs long ago that Barry had deep psychological issues and he is prone to addiction. Such a man can only pretend to be in control of himself which requires reliance on a human defensive mechanism of lying to himself. As an example, people who lie to themselves like Barry, can't understand why others don't believe him when he says that he sat in a Black separatist church for 20 years and never realized that Reverend Wright (a father figure to Barry) was an anti-American and a hater of White people. Intelligent people don't miss things that are blatantly obvious. Only a damaged person who lies to himself could miss the obvious as Barry did.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368538686432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:38:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368538873557-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As the article mentioned: "Former Defense Secretary Robert Gates, a Republican who served in both the Bush and Obama administrations, said if he had been at the Pentagon at that time, "Frankly … I think my decisions would have been just as theirs were.” That's huge.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368538873557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368538974694-39</Id><Topic><Title>Gigantic Update for The Boeing Company Read Now!</Title><Username>dunnmichael487</Username><Timestamp>1368536050121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:54:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cool</Msg><Username>howardpeter628</Username><Timestamp>1368538974694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368539072038-40</Id><Topic><Title>BREAKING: Obama Justice Department Secretly Monitored AP Reporters' Phone Records</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368481433698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you have done nothing wrong- you have nothing to fear l . Beria</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368539072038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368539166084-41</Id><Title>George Soros is Anti American</Title><Msg>George Soros' Open Society is actually the brain child of Marxist devotees to Karl Popper. Soros is openly anti-capitalist. Although he is a convicted felon who has made billions as a capitalists he still advocates for Marxist ideology when it comes to to government.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1368539166084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:46:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368539574085-42</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tesla blew pas the 52 week high this morning at $95.39 going to $97.12 it closed at $87 yesterday FYI on March 3 , just 7 trade days ago I posted here about tsla it closed at $54.55 today this moring it hit $97.12 that is a gain of 78% a lot more than Boeing shareholders can do in 5 years or year to date in just 7 days get it now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368539574085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368540036670-43</Id><Topic><Title>Americans for Prosperity is a Great Organization</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1368538302709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 09:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree but Marxists and other anti-freedom collectivists sure do hate them. That makes me admire them all the more.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368540036670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368540057319-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gates is irrelevant. He will not be testifying and there are many others who refute what Gates is saying that will be testifying to a select committee in the near future.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368540057319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368540320315-45</Id><Topic><Title>CommieCare Expected to Increase Premiums between 100 &amp; 400%</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368535481884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:44:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who do you think barry will try to blame when the Obamacare house of cards caves?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368540320315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368540516210-46</Id><Title>Barry doesn't know much</Title><Msg>◾He doesn’t know that he was running assault rifles to Mexican drug lords ◾He doesn’t know that he was using the IRS to attack political opponents ◾He doesn’t know that he has been wiretapping the press ◾He doesn’t know that he let Ambassador Stevens die, and then lied about it the families of the victims ◾He doesn’t know that he has tripled the deficit ◾He doesn’t know that he is the most divisive president in US history ◾He doesn’t know that his pastor of 20 years in an America hating racist</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368540516210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368540622744-47</Id><Title>IRS Officials in Washington DC Helped Target Tea Party Groups</Title><Msg>When news broke last week just ahead of an IRS inspector general report detailing the specific and inappropriate targeting of conservative tea party groups, IRS officials claimed the targeting was the result of a few low-level IRS agents in Cincinnati. It turns out, that isn't true. Not only did senior IRS officials know about the targeting as early as 2011, but officials in California and more importantly, Washington D.C., helped carry it out. Internal Revenue Service officials in Washington and at least two other offices were involved with investigating conservative groups seeking tax-exempt status, making clear that the effort reached well beyond the branch in Cincinnati that was initially blamed, according to documents obtained by The Washington Post. IRS officials at the agency’s Washington headquarters sent queries to conservative groups asking about their donors and other aspects of their operations, while officials in the El Monte and Laguna Niguel offices in California sent similar questionnaires to tea-party-affiliated groups, the documents show. The IRS has been caught in three lies up to this point. The first: IRS official Lois Lerner admitted to the inappropriate targeting of tea party groups but said the targeting in no way was politically motivated. That is a lie. The IRS targeted conservative groups and flagged words and phrases like "constitution," "patriot," "government spending," "limiting government," "9/12," "making America a better place to live," etc. The entire thing was political. The second: Initially IRS officials said the targeting was conducted by a few "low-level" agents working in Cincinnati. It turns out, the Cincinnati IRS office is anything but "low-level" and is the place to go when applying for tax-exempt status. Upon a review of the IRS bureaucracy, though, the Cincinnati office is not a random backwater outpost for "low-level" IRS rogues. In fact, the Cincinnati office is where determinations on tax-exempt organizations' eligibility are made and is the only physical office in the complex IRS bureaucracy dedicated to tax-exempt determinations. On the IRS's website, in the "How to Contact the Tax Exempt and Government Entities Division" section, the Cincinnati office is the only one listed for people to contact if they have questions about "Charities &amp; Non-Profits."</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368540622744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368540784657-48</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Officials in Washington DC Helped Target Tea Party Groups</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368540622744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:10:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The third: IRS officials claimed nobody in Washington D.C. was a part of ongoing targeting and that senior IRS officials knew nothing about this when in fact, as noted above, senior officials knew as early as 2011. Senior officials at the Internal Revenue Service were aware that its agents were targeting Tea Party groups as early as 2011, according to an Inspector General's draft report obtained by Fox News. Lois Lerner, who runs the IRS division that oversees tax-exempt organizations, knew about the targeting of Tea Party groups since June 29, 2011. Yesterday President Obama said if conservative groups were being targeted by the IRS, which we know they in fact were being targeted, that he's "got no patience for it."</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368540784657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368540880626-49</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DDD up 8.5% so far this morning , should have read and followed my suggestions made on march 3 and followed up on my march 10. The " weekly reports"! nice to get out of tsla in 7 days at a 78% profit if you pulled the trigger this morning on the pop! get back in and ride the rocket if you know how to read a stock chart! Attention Boeing trolls and hacks , if not you have to be a Boeing troll and make nothing on see the 787 fly its 4 years late and 30 billion over cost and this is our future the outsource failure as demonstrated by MD bankruptcy and now being verified by Boeing on the 787 way to go cheap and lowest price plane ever and it flies just like the cheap outsourcing too Hart-smith was right on ha ha lol</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368540880626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368541024533-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the government takeover of general motors, fast n furious, and "man made disaster" whitewash, shoulda been enough to identity the true colors of our occupiers</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368541024533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368541029194-51</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have to look far......there's a bunch of them right there in the White House</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368541029194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368541032740-52</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>forgot to point out I just sold the ddd for this morning wanted to post that for the boeing trolls to give them an exact time of my profit have fun with that trolls ha ha over 8% today again lol for Boeing is the 787 flying yet ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368541032740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368541126797-53</Id><Topic><Title>IRS Officials in Washington DC Helped Target Tea Party Groups</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368540622744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:10:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IRS = Internal RevenGe Service Do you have any relatives still living. ? NO ? Use our online service to register them to vote for our dear leader OR ELSE !!!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368541126797</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368541138131-54</Id><Title>TSLA.....WAYNEDICK'S NEW TOY</Title><Msg>Lol new toy vs boeing 52 week high and a triple digits for ba..soon</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1368541138131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368541460563-55</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>must be hungover after the fundraisers in the big apple...good day to hunker down in front of the tv with valerie and do more scheming 12:30 am Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jay Carney 10:20 am The President and the Vice President receive the Presidential Daily Briefing Oval Office Closed Press 4:45 pm The President and the Vice Presdent meet with Secretary Hagel Oval Office Closed Press</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368541460563</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:24:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368541873269-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: I Have no Idea Why my pants are on Fire</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1368482818739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 18:06:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry doesn't seem to have a clue of anything. Maybe he should quit spending so much time campaigning, raising money and playing golf and try to find out what's going on in his administration.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368541873269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368542192160-57</Id><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Msg>With all eyes now on the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) for its selective targeting and harassment of conservative tax-exempt organizations before the 2012 elections, IRS officials and President Barack Obama are scrambling to paint the scandal as the handiwork of a few bumbling, nonpartisan IRS underlings. Obama White House Press Secretary Jay Carney said the president thinks the government should hire “the very best public servants with the highest levels of integrity.” He claimed that “based on recent media reports, [Obama] is concerned that the conduct of a small number of Internal Revenue Service employees may have fallen short of that standard.” But a review of political campaign contributions during the 2012 election cycle paints a slightly different picture, one that deviates from patterns of support found in the rest of the country. According to figures compiled by the Center for Responsive Politics, IRS employees donated over two-and-a-half times more to Barack Obama than to Republican challenger Mitt Romney.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368542205008-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, ali, everything written on this board is irrelevant. Gates said the above on network television... because he was the Secretary of Defense at one time.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368542205008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368542485612-59</Id><Title>IRS Revelations 'Just The Beginning'</Title><Msg>On Monday, Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-KY) fired back on assertions by the IRS that its efforts to target conservative groups were relegated to low-level employees. “Of course not,” he told Breitbart News. McConnell noted that he had raised the issue of IRS targeting of conservatives in 2012, and further noted that the Washington Post “dismissed it as a bunch of red herrings.” The scandal, McConnell said, extends up the chain. “The Obama effort to shut up opponents isn’t limited to the IRS,” he stated. “It applies to the FCC [Federal Communications Commission], SEC [Securities and Exchange Commission], FEC [Federal Elections Commission], HHS [Department of Health and Human Services] …. And you remember, the Obama campaign last year published a list of eight businessmen who it believed were enemies.” McConnell further noted reports that the Department of Health and Human Services had been contacting businesses “skeptical about the implementation of Obamacare and asking them to contribute money to sell the program to the American people. That’s absolutely improper if not illegal. This administration will stop at nothing to get its way. It will do anything it can to silence its critics.” McConnell said would not trust any Democrat-led investigation into the IRS scandal. He added with regard to a House investigation of the IRS’ activities, “I’m confident they will do it in the way in which it ought to be conducted, with a high level of skepticism about an agency trying to silence the critics of the Obama administration.” He also added that the recent IRS revelations were “just the beginning of the story. This is no little thing. This is a big thing. The good news about it is they finally got caught. They finally messed with an agency everybody fully understands. When they try to quiet the critics through other agencies, it doesn’t get attention. This does. Everybody understands the IRS and how powerful they are. This is just one example of an administration-wide effort to silence critics.”</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542485612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:41:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368543050080-60</Id><Title>You need to start your research on MISM right away!</Title><Msg>You NEED to check out MISM. Huge assets on their books + gold mines that are tested and confirmed to have gold and silver. It wotn last long once investors take notice</Msg><Username>hwyatt954</Username><Timestamp>1368543050080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368543222520-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maobowa stood down the night of the attacks, huh spart and hillary dropped the phone callS</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368543222520</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368543566655-62</Id><Title>Stern Agee target 120.</Title><Msg>EOM</Msg><Username>tmurphy227</Username><Timestamp>1368543566655</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368543664395-63</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"According to figures compiled by the Center for Responsive Politics, IRS employees donated over two-and-a-half times more to Barack Obama than to Republican challenger Mitt Romney." One could assign a reason to this as a function of demographics. Simply, that the employees any part of the government are more likely to support a "big government" candidate. The IRS would not be any different. Or, on a more sinister note, and as demonstrated by the scandal within the IIRS being aired today, the "tools" available to the IRS allow managment to determine who is supporting the "correct" candidate and who is not. And the employees of the IRS know that. Perhaps, donating to Obama was a requisite for promotion. If the IRS was compromised in its external dealings (i.e., the illegal and unethical audits), the reasonable expectation is that its internal dealings merit review for ethical and legal violations.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1368543664395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:01:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368543729995-64</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Drunk on Power</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368532649488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 07:57:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He may want to move back to Indonesia, at least he would be a legal citizen there. Being black isn't his only fault by a long shot.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1368543729995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368544050483-65</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>both ddd and tsla reached 52 week highs today, Per my weekly report of march 3 and reviewed on March 10, your a loser if your in boeing stock, tsla up 61% for 5 days more for 7 days all new high today and out and same for DDD up 18% for 5 days and 7.3% today and out that is 80% in 7 trade days on just two stocks and gibberish comes from Boeing trolls as usual</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368544050483</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368544172572-66</Id><Title>What would it take for Obama to lose the support of Zosima, rocks4brain. hoozprick and</Title><Msg>.....and the 95% of black voter? Would it be that he's an ideological Marxist......naw.... that would only make make him more of an idol to them. How about if he admitted he was working for the downfall of America, capitalism and freedom.......naw, that would would only make him more popular with them. Here's what it would take.......he would have to admit he loved America, freedom, free markets, our constitution, was for lower taxes, less government regulations and control over our lives and a smaller more restrained and accountable federal government.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368544172572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368544322076-67</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly report Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368221271918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe you're posting to the wrong "sparty". I don't do politics.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1368544322076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368544408702-68</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But.you always come boeing boards puking your jealousy and u mr waynedick are a fired employee of boeing.. What else it could be? Lol yeah ba on the way to triple digits take it to the bank!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1368544408702</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368544674959-69</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome Improvement for BA. Read Now!</Title><Username>zayaswarren</Username><Timestamp>1368544467356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice find here.</Msg><Username>lancedonaldson744</Username><Timestamp>1368544674959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368544844274-70</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome Improvement for BA. Read Now!</Title><Username>zayaswarren</Username><Timestamp>1368544467356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I count it as 0.71%</Msg><Username>ortizhenry136</Username><Timestamp>1368544844274</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:20:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368544955716-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who do you think people will listen to... you, with zero military experience, or a former Defense Secretary?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368544955716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545065626-72</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no protection for the Ambassador, no contingency only those hundered if not a thousand miles away. For two weeks even at the UN the world heard the movie caused it, even the Lybian president had it right, so where do we find the truth in this world. Obviously not with this Obama. Sending out his minions for over two weeks with lies. Now Americans are suppose to believe these excuses. Its a crazy world, these liberals follow down the yellow brick road. Hicks testimony means nothing to these liberals when the world find more truth in him then our Obama and Hillery and the UN Ambassador</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368545065626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:24:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368545113817-73</Id><Title>We now Have Another Good Example for Why the IRS should be Abolished</Title><Msg>A flat income tax, a consumption tax like the "Fair Tax" would take way the tools of government to persecute the opponents of those in power. The 72,000 page IRS code we now have is the result of politicians granting favors to special interests while punishing their competition. It gives the government far more power than our founder ever intended the government to have. Get rid of the IRS and let the free market work.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368545113817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368545164842-74</Id><Title>now Americans are suppose to believe that the two weeks of lies did not occur?</Title><Msg>finding truth every where else. How can we believe any thing from this administration</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368545164842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545244128-75</Id><Topic><Title>We now Have Another Good Example for Why the IRS should be Abolished</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368545113817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:25:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a liberal strategy policy to me. Favor one over the toher, and eliminate competition.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368545244128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368545340559-76</Id><Title>787 deliveries coming</Title><Msg>From NYC787 site; Sunday, May 12, 2013 Upcoming 787 deliveries Now that the battery modifications are underway Boeing is gearing up to re-start deliveries to customers. First up will be deliveries to ANA and LOT Polish Airlines. ANA (ZA512, LN 83, JA818A) should deliver tomorrow 5/13/2013 (flyaway the next day) while LOT Polish (ZA272, LN 86, SP-LRC) should deliver the following day on 5/14/2013 (flyaway the next day). Thomson Airways is expecting their first 787 (ZA317, LN 92, G-TUIA) on 5/30/2013 with the second (ZA318, LN 94, G-TUIB) to follow on 6/2/2013. JAL can also take delivery this week of ZA184 (LN 89, JA830J) though I haven't heard about a delivery date. Hainan and China Southern could take their first 787s as early as the end of this month but that could easily slip into June since the delivery is waiting on Chinese aviation authorities certifying the 787 for use by Chinese carriers. British Airways is looking to take delivery within the next few weeks but it does look like that they'll pick up their first 787s next month.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1368545340559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545402281-77</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly report Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368221271918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one. Laughing with you at the Wayneker. Wayneker also claims that McDonnell Douglas went bankrupt which they never did.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1368545402281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545437902-78</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you miss my acad up that past 4 days? read a stock chart, Boeing trolls. ACAD ( yes I discussed it the last time it was moving up after I made most of the gain, like now too) up 183% year to date and 4% today and 10% for a week that is an ok one for me. It's nothing to complain about, but not much only 183%year to date that is just about 4 months and change, So Airbus made about the same 185% but in in 5 years and Boeing has made 42% gain in 5 years . So one more time , attention trolls of Boeing, can you see the 787 flying yet ? Hacks for Boeing , how is that cheap outsourcing going as cheap as your gibberish</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368545437902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545569032-79</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trolls I can do this all day while I move in and out of good stocks and you can do gibberish all day too, fair trade for me , pun intended lol</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368545569032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545636897-80</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I'm sorry... apparently Gates was supposed to go on national television and say "Bongo 52, this is Sabre 6". Then we would all know he has expertise.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368545636897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368545673385-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz You already posted the same nonsense on Gates' meaningless TV appearance and speculations, why did you feel the need to post it twice? Gates is unaware of whistleblowers yet to be heard and he wasn't in the loop when the Benghazi attack occurred. Whistleblowers that were in the loop certainly know more than Gates does about this specific attack, and they are not talking to Gates. It will all come out when a select committee is chosen and the investigation begins. The public deserves to know why Hillary lied to them.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368545673385</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546046239-82</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you did not hear what the military in the field say, Hicks had more balls then the military. the defense secretary nor the un secretary have any credibility but to twist the facts. Obama of which you have posted has turned on his minions to speak and write of facts they had no knowledge at the time of the attack. no protection no contingency to protect the embassy, there is a cover up, we all know it.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368546046239</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546051800-83</Id><Topic><Title>Awesome Improvement for BA. Read Now!</Title><Username>zayaswarren</Username><Timestamp>1368544467356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ws it up before that?</Msg><Username>foley.mitchell</Username><Timestamp>1368546051800</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546194327-84</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as Americans listened to the lie for over two weeks. Obama trying to make it stick. does not make sense hooz</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368546194327</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546391091-85</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA up 225 percent in 50+ months. That's better than Airbus 185 percent in 60 months. Don't you like math? Many current Boeing employees (some your former co-workers?) got those low prices then in the savings plan and are dollar cost averaging and doing quite well (especially with the company match). Are they hacks too?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1368546391091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546410499-86</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gates wants to be invited to the next sing-a-long with Sir Paul at the White House.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1368546410499</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546412717-87</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly report Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368221271918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Boeing gibberish is starting now , is the 787 flying yet blaa, blaaa, blaa, just out of a day trade SSYS up 9% not bad for 2 hours and the Boeing hacks and trolls keep on doing nothing for mankind, stay away from Boeing stock it a MD failure and being verified by the 787, the 747 and will continue with the 777X out source Hart_ Smith was right</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368546412717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368546446316-88</Id><Title>Former General sal Benghazi was the Result of Obama’s dereliction of duty</Title><Msg>U.S. Air Force Lt. Gen. Tom McInerney.served at the highest levels in the Air Force, including time as assistant vice chief of staff and vice commander in chief of the U.S. Air Forces in Europe. He believes the Obama administration deliberately misled the American people on the motivation for the attack and is now covering its tracks on decisions to prevent a military rescue in Benghazi. He told WND that is more clear than ever following Wednesday’s testimony of former Deputy Chief of Mission Gregory Hicks and two others before the House Oversight and Government Reform Committee. “This is going to be the biggest scandal. It is going to make Watergate look like kindergarten because Watergate was primarily limited to the Oval Office. This cuts across the whole national security apparatus, where people were lying and covering up,” McInerney said. “It is a dereliction of duty that this nation has never seen before.” So what consequences could that mean for the highest levels of the administration? “Well, just see what the consequences were in Watergate. If it’s far worse than Watergate, the consequences will go right into the Oval Office,” he said. McInerney said the tell-tale sign of Obama’s dereliction of duty can be determined in the admitted White House narrative of the president’s actions as the terrorist attack played out the night of Sept. 11, 2012. “When is the exact minute he knew? We don’t have the timeline, and it was well before the secretary of defense and the chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff went over there. He only talked to the secretary of defense one time, so it’s obvious he knew that he had given the stand-down order and did not need to talk to the secretary of defense or anybody else after that,” McInerney said. “Then he goes the next day out on a fundraising campaign to Las Vegas. That is a low for the commander in chief of this great nation.” He also insists the stand-down order could only come from one source: the president himself. “The only person who could have given it was the president, and he had to give it through the secretary of defense, secretary of state. The word came out so it came from the combatant commands and other unites below, but nobody could have given that except the president of the United States, and that is very clear,” said McInerney, who noted that the State Department’s own Accountability Review Board likely reached a similar conclusion in its report, which is why so few have seen it and the leaders of that study refuse to appear before Congress. McInerney believes they should be subpoenaed.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368546446316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546505003-89</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there's no limit to #$%$ dumbos n mobros willingly swallow if it emanates from their dear leaders they're trained.... Yu_ri Bez_men_ov (YAHOOs don’t like this guy) is a former KGB agent and an expert on ideological subversion. He discusses the slow process of demoralization that transformed America from a conservative and mostly homogeneous country into a socially-marxist and egalitarian one.- 1984 “It's a great brainwashing process which goes very slow and is divided into four basic stages. The first one being "demoralization". It takes from 15 to 20 years to demoralize a nation. Why that many years? Because this is the minimum number of years required to educate one generation of students in the country of your enemy exposed to the ideology of [their] enemy. In other words, Marxism-Leninism ideology is being pumped into the soft heads of at least three generation of American students without being challenged or counterbalanced by the basic values of Americanism; American patriotism.... The result? The result you can see ... the people who graduated in the 60's, dropouts or half-baked intellectuals, are now occupying the positions of power in the government, civil service, business, mass media, and educational systems. You are stuck with them. You can't get through to them. They are contaminated. They are programmed to think and react to certain stimuli in a certain pattern [alluding to Pavlov]. You cannot change their mind even if you expose them to authentic information. Even if you prove that white is white and black is black, you still can not change the basic perception and the logic of behavior...</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368546505003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368546514806-90</Id><Title>when the media came out with doubt in Obama's response to Bengazzi Obama got his minions to bring</Title><Msg>more misinformation to the table. Unless you were in the field, when the military said Hicks had more balls then the military and then being demoted for not playing the party line tells America this President is a liar. Retallitation cause Hicks has balls, he was there.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368546514806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546710388-91</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With all due respect to you, ali ( and I have never found a reason to give you any ), I interpreted Gates' move as a Republican giving advice to his fellow teammates to think long and hard about this, as it could backfire. When a guy like Gates speaks, there is always a reason for his doing so. This wouldn't happen without it being advice to others. If you are old enough to remember O.J.'s murder trial, it looked like a slam dunk for a guilty verdict. It didn't turn out that way. That's what Gates is saying.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368546710388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368546770070-92</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you can really drift....</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368546770070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547282015-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The right decision was to let people die? I see.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1368547282015</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547720463-94</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great post</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368547720463</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547739501-95</Id><Topic><Title>Robert Gates: I would have handled Benghazi the same way</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368457388706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:03:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Informative post, shupe.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1368547739501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368547817796-96</Id><Title>Boeing up 1% today Airbus up 2.4% as usual anything that MD er I man BA can do Airbus does better</Title><Msg>today, as I pointed out on march 3 in my weekly report, you shoulda been in tsla up 80% in just 10 days and up huge for the ytd 160% plus - and it had a new high and you sell, same for DDD it had increased earnings rating and new high , so you sell into strength and move on. I am already in my next weekly report stocks now, and making a lot more just banked 9% on SSYS in a day trade. .Or you can be a Boeing Hack and troll with gibberish is the 787 flying yet ? A troll is a In Internet slang, a troll (pron.: /ˈtroʊl/, /ˈtrɒl/) is someone who posts inflammatory,[1] extraneous, or off-topic messages in an online community, such as a forum, chat room, or blog, with the primary intent of provoking readers into an emotional response[2] or of otherwise disrupting normal on-topic discussion.[And a troll is in history, is A Boeing MESSAGE BOARD USER bent on mischief and wickedness</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368547817796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368547962416-97</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Troll on in the mean time is the stock for airbus up 2.5% today compared to boeing up 15 yep that is the pattern boeing up 42% in 5 years, air bus now up 192% in five years and the trolls gibberish continues for newbies ha ha like anyone is going to respond to trolls</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368547962416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368548182127-98</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT NO ONE WANTS TO DISCUSS ABOUT BENGHAZI</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368528854985</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 06:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama screwed up from the get go. This is what happens when you put an inexperienced amateur in a management position.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368548182127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368548262824-99</Id><Title>Airbus rolled out the first A350 the 787 beater with nicad batteries for safety of flight too!</Title><Msg>Airbus rolled out the first A350 from the paint shop, perhaps positioning the European aircraft maker to take advantage of Boeing's (BA_) long series of 787 problems. lol 4 years late and 30 billion 787 over cost now ! The A350 is scheduled to fly for Qatar Airways which operates the world largest Airbus fleet, and gibberish from the Boeing trolls as usual</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368548262824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368548318138-100</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing up 1% today Airbus up 2.4% as usual anything that MD er I man BA can do Airbus does better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368547817796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about that new 787 beater from Airbus rolled out today !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368548318138</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368548378902-101</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok outsource 787, your late by 4 years, and now Airbus has rolled out their 787 beater with nicad safe batteries too !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368548378902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368548392615-102</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT NO ONE WANTS TO DISCUSS ABOUT BENGHAZI</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368528854985</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 06:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're a #$%$ lying as GOP toad !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368548392615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368548597363-103</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT NO ONE WANTS TO DISCUSS ABOUT BENGHAZI</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368528854985</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 06:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now Obama has his minions speaking misinformation to confuse the weak minded and ignorant. Thinking this is just a GOP attack. When ABC came out with questions, the minion button was pushed again to keep spinning the info for the weak minded.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368548597363</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368550439430-104</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT NO ONE WANTS TO DISCUSS ABOUT BENGHAZI</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368528854985</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 06:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many management jobs Obama couldn't even get clearance to get the job with his shady background. But he was placed in the highest level position in the land....and it never should have happened.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368550439430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368550450996-105</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus rolled out the first A350 the 787 beater with nicad batteries for safety of flight too!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368548262824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:17:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just banked day trade of 5% on RDN, probably going higher for a day trade, but moving on to the next day trade so Boeing trolls, gibberish as usual eh ! a Internet troll is someone who posts inflammatory, extraneous, or off-topic messages in an online community, such as a forum, chat room, or blog, with the primary intent of provoking readers into an emotional response or of otherwise disrupting normal on-topic discussion. A message board user who is bent on mischief and wickedness like attempting to put any investor into Boeing a dead cat bounce stock is a troll worthless human . Ba up 42% in 5 years is pathetic read hart-smith learn to trade stocks and make money trolls</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368550450996</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368550707475-106</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368550707475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368550718001-107</Id><Title>Another day</Title><Msg>and the GOP fails to do anything about creating jobs or reducing the deficit as they promised to do if they were elected. Instead they use their time trying to create some kind of controversy by tossing as much poo at a wall as fast as they can . nothing ever sticks though.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1368550718001</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368550845738-108</Id><Title>Obama made wrong decision to lie to Americans for two weeks movie over the facts</Title><Msg>that every body else had. Two weeks of trying to deceive Americans. No protection for the Ambassador and no contingency protection, according to Hillary NONE. Obama's freindly to terrorists policy gone to far.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368550845738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:00:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368550997337-109</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this board is any guage, "all eyes" are not focused on the IRS. Two -thirds of the loons here are still yakking about Benghazi.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368550997337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368551260967-110</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hopydopy The Prince of poop slingers.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1368551260967</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368551878555-111</Id><Title>remember the days when Obama claimed to be Bipartisan and voted not to increase the Debt ceiling?</Title><Msg>what we found, a president that likes to joist with the Congress and the Supreme Court even making threats. Debt ceiling ha selling out the next two generations. Claims of a presidency of ransparancy to more hiding behid Executive Orders then ever before to Bengazzi, IRS, Foreign Policy gone wrong. After the Boston bombing insite of how terrorists have used Obama's immigration to infultrate America. Now its waiting in fear for the next bombing. Thank you Obama</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368551878555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368552290206-112</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"great post" Yeah right... illiterate minds think alike, eh?</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1368552290206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:24:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553149849-113</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>our midnight cowboy, i mean sparty, is at one with the ONE, dependent on collective theft of OPM</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368553149849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:39:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553533234-114</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus rolled out the first A350 the 787 beater with nicad batteries for safety of flight too!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368548262824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:17:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would you want to post a definition that slams yourself?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1368553533234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368553648782-115</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big surprise there, huh spart dumbos are attracted to non-competitive gov't jobs like flies to s***, i mean bees to honey bonus, fed employment make close to double (in terms of pay and benefits) private sector employees, state n local, make close to 160% their private sector equivalent. dem dumbos hate those that have more, less they're dumbos, teachers, lawyers, etc... Millionaire Household Occupations 17% Manager 12% Educator 07% Sr. Corporate Executive 06% Business Owner 04% Accountant 04% Sales Person 02% Attorney 02% Doctor/Dentist</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1368553648782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368554140830-116</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gates is right. It's clear that is was a crisis. But to over react or to react in the wrong way could have increased the disaster exponentially. It is only in movies and novels that a fighter jet or Rainbow Six leaves Italy, arrives on time, kills the bad guy and the bad guy only and gets to a safe haven before morning. And it happens without us having to declare war on someone or having someone declare it on us. It's tragic those people died, but the wrong reaction could have led to hundreds dying, or to a conflict of nations. That could be what the puppet masters on the other side actually hoped for.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1368554140830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:55:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368554448211-117</Id><Topic><Title>Another day</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1368550718001</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:58:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's true. Do they have to be President to do it? Can't the many Senators, Representatives, Governors and State Legislators who happen to be Republican contribute to job creation? Waiting to be President is a sorry excuse for failing to do what you were elected to do.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1368554448211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368554492555-118</Id><Title>How many A350's will crash during certification??</Title><Msg>Oh I guess only one A320 crashed during certification killing the entire crew- seems those Frenchies have a little trouble with fly by wire Then there was the inadequately instrumented A330 that proved to be unflyable in a big South Atlantic thunderstorm- hard to believe but pitot tube heat would have saved the crew and 250 passengers on that flight from Brazil to Europe</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368554492555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368554868008-119</Id><Title>Hey moebro</Title><Msg>Are you completely satisfied with the loss of 4500 Americans in the unecessary Iraq war?? If the Iraq war was uneccessary then the guy that started it is still running loose and has escaped prosecution for his war crime dont you think</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368554868008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368555068925-120</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How else could we identify and prosecute the Tdouchebagger front organizations for Tax evasion who were illegally posing as nonprofit organizations when in reality they were illegally conducting massive political campaigns to defeat Democrats</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368555068925</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368555121371-121</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing up 1% today Airbus up 2.4% as usual anything that MD er I man BA can do Airbus does better</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368547817796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 12:10:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about that Boeing is up 1% today wow but wait , bark and ouch Airbus as usua,l is up 2.5%. Airbus has learned from Boeing so no lithium batteries for them and they have a pool of buy back money in case of any delivery problems too 18% buy pack so the Airbus stock will fly if they need it to. but doubtful the 787 killer will need any fixes they make good planes not like the 787 a sourced plane built by the cheapest contractors in the world and gibberish from the Boeing trolls as usual BA for five years up 42% Airbus up 192% and climbing so have fun trolls not making any money gibberish is what you know making money is what we are here for</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368555121371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368555350059-122</Id><Topic><Title>Weekly report Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368221271918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 17:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about those Boeing trolls, gibberish as usual Boeing up 1% Airbus up 2.5% today same story, on trend. Airbus up 192% in five years Boeing up 42 % well ouch, and bark for Boeing trolls and Boeing hackereliski's is the 787 flying yet ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368555350059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368555476206-123</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so BA trolls ready to call it a loss yet my stock rule your stock suck, har lol how about that Airbus up 2.5% BA up 1% ha ha today and the 787 Airbus killer just rolled out on time, and on budget, not 4 years late</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368555476206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368555802850-124</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err deluded err sparty err spaz err opm err pmo err omp err mpo err mop err welfare bum fascist err spazlamo bumper</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1368555802850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368555839321-125</Id><Title>It's Tuesday, May 15, 2013</Title><Msg>and at Boeing alls well.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1368555839321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368556167871-126</Id><Topic><Title>How many A350's will crash during certification??</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368554492555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy I guess Im being ignored by Dell George/Waynedickensen HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368556167871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368556315756-127</Id><Topic><Title>How many A350's will crash during certification??</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368554492555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell George/Wayne Id say you havent got yourself on the ball yet on these Boeing airplanes- that hunkajunk A350 will compet with the 777 not the 787 and it will have to compete with the new upgraded 777 which will have new wings(composite) and engines to say the least. Looks like the A350 will go the way of the A310---NOWHERE</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368556315756</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:31:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368556433548-128</Id><Topic><Title>Hey moebro</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368554868008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>moebro- where you hidin?????????????? eh????????</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368556433548</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368556452227-129</Id><Topic><Title>It's Tuesday, May 15, 2013</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1368555839321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good for you, Jack! Its May 14.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1368556452227</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368556869174-130</Id><Topic><Title>Hey moebro</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368554868008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We don't talk like that in Aerospace. We don't hope other people planes crash any more than our own.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1368556869174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368557273479-131</Id><Topic><Title>Hey moebro</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368554868008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who said anything about planes??? care to tell us what you are babbeling about?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368557273479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368557553087-132</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They don't think. They simply mindlessly repeat whatever is in the Faux News echo chamber.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1368557553087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368558325085-133</Id><Title>Republicans Voting to Repeal Obamacare for the 40th Time !</Title><Msg>House speaker John Boehner (R-OH) made a statement in defense of this impending vote to deny affordable healthcare to millions of Americans who otherwise wouldn't have it in an interview last week. His bizarre statement was: "We have 70 new members of the House who have not had a chance to vote on repealing Obamacare and we're going to give them a chance to vote on it."</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368558325085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368558364105-134</Id><Topic><Title>It's Tuesday, May 15, 2013</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1368555839321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 14:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's 5 o'clock (May 15, 2013) somewhere and the hooz is sitting next to the Raven with his toes in the water and a beer in one hand.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1368558364105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368558687547-135</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Voting to Repeal Obamacare for the 40th Time !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368558325085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:05:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamacare referred to as affordable healthcare is an oxymoron.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1368558687547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368559407346-136</Id><Title>The Plot Thickens</Title><Msg>The progressive-leaning investigative journalism group ProPublica admitted the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) office that targeted and harassed conservative tax-exempt groups during the 2012 election cycle gave the progressive group nine confidential applications of conservative groups whose tax-exempt status was pending. The commendable admission lends further evidence to the lengths the IRS went during an election cycle to silence tea party and limited government voices. ProPublica says the documents the IRS gave them were “not supposed to be made public”:</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368559407346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368559622088-137</Id><Title>ana 787 delivered</Title><Msg>Boeing delivered a 787 to ANA today. Hopefully the beginning of a lot more deliveries.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1368559622088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368559696878-138</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I`m an entertainer what percentage do i fit in?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1368559696878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368559825594-139</Id><Topic><Title>The Plot Thickens</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368559407346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup.......the IRS illegally collected info it had no right to collect from applicants of conservative groups. They would then illegally turn this info over to a left-wing George Soros funded media group who would then use the info to slime the conservative groups. Fits the Obama MO perfectly. This one looks like it could go to the top if a few people want to save their hide by rolling on Obama.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1368559825594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368560352939-140</Id><Topic><Title>What would it take for Obama to lose the support of Zosima, rocks4brain. hoozprick and</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368544172572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:09:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.....maybe that he wanted to leave people alone and let them make their own choices and suffer the consequences of their choices?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1368560352939</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368560611095-141</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're reading a bit more between the lines than latitude allows.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1368560611095</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368561083890-142</Id><Title>Markets Continue Solid Climb Into Record Territory</Title><Msg>The AFU radicalized extremist followers of RubeRadio political propaganda have been predicting financial armageddon ever since Americans booted the pious baloney spouting repubs out of power. Their predictions, like their cockamamie ideology, continues to be AFU..</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1368561083890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368561384155-143</Id><Topic><Title>Robert Gates: I would have handled Benghazi the same way</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368457388706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:03:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone with a brain not saturated by RubeRadio radicalized extremism would agree with Secretary of Defense Gates, and the head of the CIA, Petraeus..</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1368561384155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:56:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368561565655-144</Id><Topic><Title>120$.. No seller remorse, no more.</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365695094586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:44:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are we there yet?</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1368561565655</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368561667897-145</Id><Title>Obama.....son of Watergate</Title><Msg>40 years to the week......Obama far worse than Nixon.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368561667897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368561973057-146</Id><Topic><Title>What would it take for Obama to lose the support of Zosima, rocks4brain. hoozprick and</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368544172572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:09:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" What would it take for Obama to lose the support of Zosima, rocks4brain. hoozprick and .....and the 95% of black voter?" Brain cells......obviously can't happen.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1368561973057</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368562020742-147</Id><Topic><Title>The Plot Thickens</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368559407346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It sounds like they need to put a few people in jail to put the fear of the law into the creepy leftist #$%$ that make a habit of breaking the law. Right now they operate under the assumption that no one will attempt to enforce the law, and so far they have been right.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1368562020742</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368562223509-148</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing ,787 built from the cheapest sources in the world.tesla hit a new 52 week high today posted march 3!</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1368476732714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"on time, and on budget" What are you smoking? First offered/sold in 2004, revamped in 2006, finally rolls out in 2013. Maybe you mean the budget and schedule from last month? HarHarHar</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1368562223509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368563010814-149</Id><Topic><Title>The Plot Thickens</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368559407346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So where are the masses of people protesting to have the IRS shut down? Are there any marches on Washington being planned? I guess Barry just expects conservatives to clutch their bibles and guns and take it in the pooper and so far it looks like conservatives are going to oblige Barry. Any Progressives and liberals who still think that Barry is a unifier, a good leader and a president who serves all Americans, needs to be slapped or doused with a bucket of cold water.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368563010814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:23:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368564370498-150</Id><Topic><Title>Obama made right decisions night of Benghazi attack</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368535700633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 08:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>albucucuforcocopoofs my reading is fine and my logic is spot on and latitude is in the eye of the beholder.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368564370498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368564953288-151</Id><Topic><Title>What would it take for Obama to lose the support of Zosima, rocks4brain. hoozprick and</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368544172572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:09:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The alias IDs are like abused spouses that continue to love their mate beating after beating. They are not rational human beings but fanatic ideologues. A better question is when are conservatives going to march on the White House and call Barry out for his secret war on conservatives?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1368564953288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368565310367-152</Id><Topic><Title>What would it take for Obama to lose the support of Zosima, rocks4brain. hoozprick and</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368544172572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:09:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>organize the march.....I'll be there. maybe freedom works will get something going.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1368565310367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368565932765-153</Id><Title>In scandal-plagued Washington, lawmaker struggles to keep track of issues</Title><Msg>With the rumbling of so much scandal ripping through Washington this week—woeful stories about Benghazi, the DOJ subpoena of journalists' phone records and the IRS unfairly targeting conservative groups—it's hard to keep track of all the terrible. Even lawmakers sometimes struggle. At Rep. Steny Hoyer's weekly meeting with reporters on Tuesday, the Maryland Democrat was asked if he was concerned about the DOJ seizing phone records from Associated Press journalists working in the House press gallery in the Capitol building. Hoyer's answer was well-delivered: Articulate, clear, firm and precise. One problem: He responded to the wrong scandal. "The IRS activity was inappropriate, inconsistent with our policies and practices as a country, very concerning, needs to be reviewed carefully," Hoyer, one of the top-ranking House Democrats, said in response to a question from Fox News' Chad Pergram about the DOJ. "We need to ensure that this does not happen again, and we need to find out how long it continued, when it was stopped. It is my understanding—there was a front-page story on this at the [Washington] Post—it's my understanding that [IRS official] Lois Lerner, who was apparently overseeing this, at some point in time found out about this and said ..." When Hoyer named Lerner, Pergram interrupted. "We're talking about two things," Pergram, who apparently had not heard the first mention of the IRS, said from across the table, "You said Lois Lerner and the IRS." Another reporter sitting closer to Hoyer, Public Radio International's Todd Zwillich, learned over and said softly, "He's talking about the AP story." "Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, excuse me," Hoyer said, pausing briefly. "Whatever happened, we need to find out why it happened. But clearly it should not have happened. I don't know enough about whether there was a warrant sought." Boom. He nailed it! But Hoyer wasn't finished. "I don't know fully the rationalization or justification that was being used, but the president's statement that it was outrageous, that there was no place for it and that they have to be held fully accountable is a statement in which I agree," Hoyer went on to say. The only problem is that President Barack Obama didn't comment about the DOJ story. And he certainly didn't call it "outrageous." In fact, the White House has declined to say much of anything about the DOJ investigation. Was he talking about the IRS story again? Yup. Hoyer continued: "He then points out in another statement with which I agree: 'I can tell you that if you've got the IRS operating in anything less ...'" Hoyer's voice trailed off. "Oh I keep going IRS. I'm really fired up on the IRS."</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1368565932765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368566234065-154</Id><Title>Benghazi Poll !</Title><Msg>Voters trust Hillary Clinton more than GOP lawmakers on Benghazi !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368566234065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:17:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368566654522-155</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Poll !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368566234065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trusting Hillary, or Obama on ANYTHING is like trusting Attila the Hun..both are corrupt liberals, and I repeat myself I know.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368566654522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368566757168-156</Id><Title>GOP push for Special Benghazi Committee !</Title><Msg>they want to know what color underwear Hillary Clinton wore the day of the attack...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368566757168</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368567379900-157</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% Kent Bath House.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368567379900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368567970771-158</Id><Topic><Title>GOP push for Special Benghazi Committee !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368566757168</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or how wet her panties were when she escaped to South America to avoid questioning.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368567970771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368570526125-159</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Poll !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368566234065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dopey if you really want to insult somebody dont use Attila the Hun- use the Tdouchebaggers and their boosters- such as yourself</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368570526125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368570627265-160</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When will IRS prosecutions of Tdouchebagger organizations Tax evasion get under way the sooner the better I say</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368570627265</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368570764655-161</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bulky what you are really going to enjoy is the IRS prosecution of these RWNJ front organizations -prosecution and conviction of tax evasion</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368570764655</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368570925082-162</Id><Topic><Title>What would it take for Obama to lose the support of Zosima, rocks4brain. hoozprick and</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368544172572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:09:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Jesus Christ almighty came down from heaven and walked among us a reassured us that the GOP, RWNJs and Tdouchebaggers werent the most criminal element in the ranks of humanity and that we can stop prosecuting and jailing them</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368570925082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368571006668-163</Id><Topic><Title>What would it take for Obama to lose the support of Zosima, rocks4brain. hoozprick and</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368544172572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 11:09:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet you figure you are a bright upstanding Tdouchebagger- when in reality infestid you are an ignorant racist wredgneck</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368571006668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368571432915-164</Id><Title>Piracy War Crimes, Pish Posh, They don't care</Title><Msg>What a waste, everyone knows Isreal is Above the International Criminal Court war crimes court in The Hague, Netherlands. AMSTERDAM (AP) — The prosecutor of the International Criminal Court — the permanent war crimes court in The Hague, Netherlands — says she has received a complaint about Israel's 2010 raid on a humanitarian aid flotilla bound for Gaza, and she will open a preliminary investigation. The complaint comes from the tiny African state of Comoros, a member of the court, though Israel is not. Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said she met Tuesday with lawyers from a Turkish law firm that is representing Comoros. Israel is not a member of the court and has no respect for its decisions unless they benefit Isreal..</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1368571432915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368571592314-165</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What cartoon did you rob this garbage from, thief?</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1368571592314</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368571874395-166</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Poll !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368566234065</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I repeat myself I know", I suspected for you to know a corrupt liberal that you are a corrupt liberal. Well at least corrupt. Everyone knows a corrupt NeoCon. Corrupt NeoCon make up the entire Republican Party! No guessing there.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1368571874395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 18:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368572470156-167</Id><Title>OH YEAH AGAIN !!!! 96 !!! 97 tomorrow ;-)</Title><Msg>LOVING IT !!!!</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1368572470156</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368572787628-168</Id><Topic><Title>IRS EMPLOYEES DONATED TWICE AS MUCH TO OBAMA IN 2012...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1368542192160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima - dream on.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1368572787628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368574063490-169</Id><Topic><Title>Markets Continue Solid Climb Into Record Territory</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1368561083890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RubeRadio propagandists proven wrong, health care costs shown to be trending down, the stock market is at record highs and the deficit is now shrinking. No wonder bаggers are foаmіng at the mouth over Benzoggie.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1368574063490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368574107955-170</Id><Topic><Title>Obama.....son of Watergate</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368561667897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least a dozem impeachable offenses</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1368574107955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368574431414-171</Id><Topic><Title>Robert Gates: I would have handled Benghazi the same way</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368457388706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:03:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congressional repubs should go directly to Benzoggie to conduct an investigation. They can interview anyone they meet on the streets. They can stay at a slightly rundown building that used to belong to the CIA.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1368574431414</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368574822626-172</Id><Title>When the IRS targeted liberals</Title><Msg>When the IRS targeted liberals Under George W. Bush, it went after the NAACP, Greenpeace and even a liberal church By Alex Seitz-Wald While few are defending the Internal Revenue Service for targeting some 300 conservative groups, there are two critical pieces of context missing from the conventional wisdom on the “scandal.” First, at least from what we know so far, the groups were not targeted in a political vendetta — but rather were executing a makeshift enforcement test (an ugly one, mind you) for IRS employees tasked with separating political groups not allowed to claim tax-exempt status, from bona fide social welfare organizations. Employees are given almost zero official guidance on how to do that, so they went after Tea Party groups because those seemed like they might be political. Keep in mind, the commissioner of the IRS at the time was a Bush appointee. The second is that while this is the first time this kind of thing has become a national scandal, it’s not the first time such activity has occurred. “I wish there was more GOP interest when I raised the same issue during the Bush administration, where they audited a progressive church in my district in what look liked a very selective way,” California Democratic Rep. Adam Schiff said on MSNBC Monday. “I found only one Republican, [North Carolina Rep. Walter Jones], that would join me in calling for an investigation during the Bush administration. I’m glad now that the GOP has found interest in this issue and it ought to be a bipartisan concern.” The well-known church, All Saints Episcopal in Pasadena, became a bit of a cause célèbre on the left after the IRS threatened to revoke the church’s tax-exempt status over an anti-Iraq War sermon the Sunday before the 2004 election. “Jesus [would say], ‘Mr. President, your doctrine of preemptive war is a failed doctrine,’” rector George Regas said from the dais. The church, which said progressive activism was in its “DNA,” hired a powerful Washington lawyer and enlisted the help of Schiff, who met with the commissioner of the IRS twice and called for a Government Accountability Office investigation, saying the IRS audit violated the First Amendment and was unduly targeting a political opponent of the Bush administration. “My client is very concerned that the close coordination undertaken by the IRS allowed partisan political concerns to direct the course of the All Saints examination,” church attorney Marcus Owens, who is widely considered one of the country’s leading experts on this area of the law, said at the time. In 2007, the IRS closed the case, decreeing that the church violated rules preventing political intervention, but it did not revoke its nonprofit status. And while All Saints came under the gun, conservative churches across the country were helping to mobilize voters for Bush with little oversight. In 2006, citing the precedent of All Saints, “a group of religious leaders accused the Internal Revenue Service yesterday of playing politics by ignoring its complaint that two large churches in Ohio are engaging in what it says are political activities, in violation of the tax code,” the New York Times reported at the time. The churches essentially campaigned for a Republican gubernatorial candidate, they alleged, and even flew him on one of their planes. Meanwhile, Citizens for Ethics in Washington filed two ethics complaints against a church in Minnesota. “You know we can’t publicly endorse as a church and would not for any candidate, but I can tell you personally that I’m going to vote for Michele Bachmann,” pastor Mac Hammond of the Living Word Christian Center in Minnesota said in 2006 before welcoming her to the church. The IRS opened an audit into the church, but it went nowhere after the church appealed the audit on a technicality. And it wasn’t just churches. In 2004, the IRS went after the NAACP, auditing the nation’s oldest civil rights group after its chairman criticized President Bush for being the first sitting president since Herbert Hoover not to address the organization. “They are saying if you criticize the president we are going to take your tax exemption away from you,” then-chairman Julian Bond said. “It’s pretty obvious that the complainant was someone who doesn’t believe George Bush should be criticized, and it’s obvious of their response that the IRS believes this, too.” In a letter to the IRS, Democratic Reps. Charles Rangel, Pete Stark and John Conyers wrote: “It is obvious that the timing of this IRS examination is nothing more than an effort to intimidate the members of the NAACP, and the communities the organization represents, in their get-out-the-vote effort nationwide.” Then, in 2006, the Wall Street Journal broke the story of a how a little-known pressure group called Public Interest Watch — which received 97 percent of its funds from Exxon Mobile one year — managed to get the IRS to open an investigation into Greenpeace. Greenpeace had labeled Exxon Mobil the “No. 1 climate criminal.” The IRS acknowledged its audit was initiated by Public Interest Watch and threatened to revoke Greenpeace’s tax-exempt status, but closed the investigation three months later. As the Journal reporter, Steve Stecklow, later said in an interview, “This comes against a backdrop where a number of conservative groups have been attacking nonprofits and NGOs over their tax-exempt status. There have been hearings on Capitol Hill. There have been a number of conservative groups in Washington who have been quite critical.” Indeed, the year before that, the Senate held a hearing on nonprofits’ political activity. Republican Sen. Charles Grassley, the then-chairman of the Senate Finance Committee, said the IRS needed better enforcement, but also “legislative changes” to better define the lines between politics and social welfare, since they had not been updated in “a generation.” Unfortunately, neither Congress nor the IRS has defined 501(c)4′s sufficiently to this day, leaving the door open for IRS auditors to make up their own, discriminatory rules. Those cases mostly involved 501(c)3 organizations, which live in a different section of the tax code for real charities like hospitals and schools. The rules are much stronger and better developed for (c)3′s, in part because they’ve been around longer. But with “social welfare” (c)4 groups, the kind of political activity we saw in 2010 and 2012 is so unprecedented that you get cases like Emerge America, a progressive nonprofit that trains Democratic female candidates for public office. The group has chapters across the country, but in 2011, chapters in Massachusetts, Maine and Nevada were denied 501(c)4 tax-exempt status. Leaders called the situation “bizarre” because in the five years Nevada had waited for approval, the Kentucky chapter was approved, only for the other three to be denied. A former IRS official told the New York Times that probably meant the applications were sent to different offices, which use slightly different standards. Different offices within the same organization that are supposed to impose the exact same rules in a consistent manner have such uneven conceptions of where to draw the line at a political group, that they can approve one organization and then deny its twin in a different state. All of these stories suggest that while concern with the IRS posture toward conservative groups now may be merited, to fully understand the situation requires a bit of context and history.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368574822626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368575036472-173</Id><Title>Some voters outraged by Benghazi don’t know where Benghazi is</Title><Msg>Poll: Some voters outraged by Benghazi don’t know where Benghazi is A new poll finds 39 percent who say Benghazi is "the biggest political scandal in American history" can't locate it By Jillian Rayfield A new poll from the Democratic-learning Public Policy Polling finds that among those who describe the Benghazi controversy as ”the biggest political scandal in American history,” 39 percent don’t actually know where Benghazi is located. From PPP: One interesting thing about the voters who think Benghazi is the biggest political scandal in American history is that 39% of them don’t actually know where it is. 10% think it’s in Egypt, 9% in Iran, 6% in Cuba, 5% in Syria, 4% in Iraq, and 1% each in North Korea and Liberia with 4% not willing to venture a guess.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368575036472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368575204064-174</Id><Topic><Title>When the IRS targeted liberals</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368574822626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz Chi Minh, a DFC and Kent Raven alias, attempts to deflect the current issue and blame it on past events.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368575204064</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:46:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368575284579-175</Id><Title>How the Republican Party could go extinct</Title><Msg>How the Republican Party could go extinct The party has a golden chance to make inroads with Latinos and gays with one immigration move. And it's blowing it By Kerry Eleveld From a pure political perspective, supporting inclusion of same-sex couples in the immigration reform bill should be a slam dunk for both Democrats and Republicans. Scuttling the package over this provision would alienate the growing Latino constituency by blocking a pathway to citizenship — and denying rights to LGBT Americans would be ignoring the direction of the country on civil rights. And yet, according to a flurry of news stories from the past couple of weeks, the die is apparently cast on the matter: Allowing some 30,000 same-sex couples the same access to green cards that opposite-sex couples enjoy will halt the bill for 11 million immigrants. Even before the provision has been debated or a vote count begun, Republicans are holding firm to a position that’s literally killing their party. Meanwhile, Democrats run scared, to the detriment of the overall bill. In plain English: The Republicans need this bill because their party doesn’t have a future if they can’t appeal to Latino voters. On the flip side, Democrats shouldn’t be sacrificing any progressive priorities before the horse-trading even begins because the more they start with, the more they will be able to keep in the end. Now it may not seem like news that the GOP’s most reliable antigay senator, Lindsey Graham, is threatening to kill the 844-page bill he helped craft over the issue, but it is mind boggling that his three Republican counterparts in the gang of eight (Sens. Flake, McCain, and Rubio) have doubled down on the position that the LGBT provision will sink the bill. Think of it this way, the GOP – the party that has lost the popular vote in five out of the last six presidential elections – has the chance at this very moment to begin transitioning from the party of yesteryear to the party of tomorrow. From the party of declining margins to the party of expansion. And instead of opting for life, they are angling for extinction by threatening to walk away from the bill. Must we really revisit the fact that the ever-growing tidal wave of Latino voters chose President Obama over Mitt Romney by a margin of 71 to 27 percentage points? Meanwhile, white Evangelicals – the voting bloc that sustained the GOP for almost 20 years – accounted for 26 percent of 2012 voters (a very solid turnout that exceeded their 2004 showing by 3 percent) yet they still didn’t have the juice to push Romney over the top. Simply put, Republicans need the new lifeline that Latino voters represent and, therefore, they need the bill worse than the Democrats. And if the GOP really thinks it can walk away from this bill and justify it to Latinos by saying the gays killed the bill, think again. That rationale may play on the Hill — where most lawmakers live in an insular world of their own making — but it isn’t going to work at the polls. The next election won’t be a referendum on LGBT people, it will be a referendum on lawmakers. Plus, in a bilingual poll that was commissioned by the LGBT immigration group for which I consult, 64% of Latino voters said they support including same-sex couples in immigration reform. The even sadder truth is, Republicans have political cover if they want it. Instead of siding with the social conservatives who have become a millstone around their electoral neck, they could choose to side with Corporate America, which has been lobbying for inclusion of LGBT families in the bill. While Richard Land of the Southern Baptist Convention is piously promising that his organization will pull its support from the legislation if it brings any relief to same-sex couples, a coalition of nearly 30 Fortune 500 companies – including the likes of Goldman Sachs, eBay, Google and Nike – have been urging the gang of eight to equalize immigration treatment for same-sex couples. “We have lost productivity when those families are separated; we have borne the costs of transferring and retraining talented employees so they may live abroad with their loved ones; and we have missed opportunities to bring the best and the brightest to the United States when their sexual orientation means they cannot bring their family with them,” the companies wrote to the gang of eight in March. The GOP has the chance to choose between two constituencies, one of which has nowhere else to go and happens to be in decline (antigay social conservatives) and one of which could choose to turn more of their resources toward Democrats (the business community). By siding with the former, they cut themselves off from generations of Latino voters rather than broadening their appeal. As the Log Cabin Republicans recently noted in this blunt ad, “Reagan’s big tent isn’t what it used to be.” But even as Republicans doom themselves electorally, one has to wonder about the tactical decision of the Democrats to cede ground on same-sex couples from the get-go. First, gays are getting more popular by the day. Second, the constituency has proven rather fearless and effective over the past several years in advocating for equality. If there’s one thing LGBT activists and donors have demonstrated, it’s that they are not afraid to go after Democrats when necessary. That brings us to Sen. Charles Schumer, who spearheaded the gang of eight on the Democratic side and has a sizeable LGBT constituency in New York including a number of vocal same-sex binational couples. Schumer and the other three Democrats in “the gang” bowed to Graham’s wishes from the start by allowing LGBT families to be excluded from the base bill. But Schumer has now distinguished himself further as the sole Democrat on the Judiciary Committee who has not committed to voting for an amendment that Senate Judiciary Chairman Patrick Leahy is expected to offer. Why Schumer, who is always keen to cut a deal, hasn’t at least feigned enthusiasm for including the LGBT provision is a mystery. If he would fight for the measure, it would not only earn him points with a vital part of his electorate but it would gain Democrats bargaining room down the road. The Dems will almost certainly have to make some concessions in the final bill and that means that the more progressive priorities it includes on the front end, the more will remain intact on the back end. Think of it this way, every column inch of space the LGBT measure has occupied over the past couple weeks represents a column inch that wasn’t dedicated to other progressive ideals like a pathway to citizenship or that favorite GOP talking point, amnesty. As Greg Sargent of The Washington Post notes, if it turns out that the LGBT provision really does threaten to sink the bill, it could be “spiked later if necessary to salvage reform.” So what’s next? More than three hundred amendments have been filed and Senator Leahy has slated his committee to consider them over the next couple weeks. Leahy has also signaled his enthusiasm for offering at least one of two amendments that would allow LGBT Americans to sponsor their foreign-born partners. “You can’t go into a state like mine or — it will be now 11 or 12 states and the District of Columbia — where same-sex marriage is legal, and say to this couple, ‘OK, we can help you with the immigration matter.’ Turn to another couple equally legally married and say, ‘Oh, we have to discriminate against you,’” he told Politico. But it remains to be seen whether Senator Leahy will offer that amendment in committee or wait until the bill reaches the Senate floor for debate. If it is offered in committee and Democrats all vote for it, it will pass. But if Schumer (or any other Democrat) votes against it, the measure will fail. The alternative is trying to add LGBT families in a floor vote that would require 60 votes to pass – that’s a much higher bar. Schumer himself noted this chicken-and-egg dilemma on Thursday when speaking about the LGBT measure known as the Uniting American Families Act (UAFA). “I would like very much to see it in the bill, but we have to have a bill that has support to get UAFA passed,” Schumer said.“That’s the conundrum, because if there’s no bill, then there’s no UAFA either.” But it’s a dilemma he helped create. Inclusion of same-sex couples has come down to a game of chicken between Democrats and Republicans. Democrats blinked first. And if UAFA fails, Republicans will set their sites on something else.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368575284579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:48:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368575410349-176</Id><Topic><Title>Some voters outraged by Benghazi don’t know where Benghazi is</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368575036472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:43:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz Chi Minh, the BA board DFC and Kent Raven alias and blowhard, attempts to create false confusion about the issue by using fake stats.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1368575410349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368576076071-177</Id><Topic><Title>Some voters outraged by Benghazi don’t know where Benghazi is</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368575036472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:43:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This group includes rubes who believe that Saddam caused 9/11, we found his WMDs, the President is from Kenya, the President is Jewish, Death Panels, climate change is a hoax thought up by somebody, W's administration actually saw the creation of jobs, the President is gay, etc. ad nauseam.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1368576076071</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368576251592-178</Id><Topic><Title>remember the days when Obama claimed to be Bipartisan and voted not to increase the Debt ceiling?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368551878555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:17:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have been shown that the President's Executive Orders trail the others. Why do you insist on incessant, unending, nonstop, bald-faced, transparently made-up prevarications?</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1368576251592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368576272160-179</Id><Title>He said- she said -they said ???</Title><Msg>Thimk 4 urself wheter or not the White House is interfering Mr. Pickering’s appearances on CBS and NBC put the spotlight on him. He acknowledged that he was initially disinclined to testify before Congress because it seemed like a political circus but said he changed his mind and volunteered, only to be put off. That produced a quarrel on the set of the NBC studio, where he and Mr. Issa sat side by side. “Ambassador Pickering, his people and he, refused to come before our committee,” Mr. Issa said. Mr. Pickering interrupted. “That is not true,” he said. “We have it in writing,” Mr. Issa countered, suggesting perhaps it was the White House that refused to let him appear. “I said the day before the hearings I was willing to appear, to come to the very hearings he excluded me from,” Mr. Pickering said. “Don’t tell me I excluded you,” Mr. Issa interjected. “We were told the majority said I was not welcome at that hearing,” Mr. Pickering said. “I could come at some other time.” Mr. Issa said he wanted to explore whether the panel interviewed enough witnesses and focused high enough in assigning responsibility. “Ultimately, if that got it right, then we can put this to a rest,” he said. “We believe it was insufficient.” On the CBS News program “Face the Nation,” Mr. Pickering said there was no need. “I don’t see yet any reason why what we did at the accountability review board should be reopened,” he said. ***** So WHO from the white house said NO re Pickering and ISSA ? The Janitor ???</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1368576272160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368576390775-180</Id><Title>RNC FL Hispanic Director is Now a Democrat</Title><Msg>In his own words (shared with permission): From: Pablo Pantoja Subject: From Republican to Democrat Date: May 13, 2013 5:57:11 PM EDT Friend, Yes, I have changed my political affiliation to the Democratic Party. It doesn’t take much to see the culture of intolerance surrounding the Republican Party today. I have wondered before about the seemingly harsh undertones about immigrants and others. Look no further; a well-known organization recently confirms the intolerance of that which seems different or strange to them. Studies geared towards making – human beings – viewed as less because of their immigrant status to outright unacceptable claims, are at the center of the immigration debate. Without going too deep on everything surrounding immigration today, the more resounding example this past week was reported by several media outlets. A researcher included as part of a past dissertation his theory that “the totality of the evidence suggests a genetic component to group differences in IQ.” The researcher reinforces these views by saying “No one knows whether Hispanics will ever reach IQ parity with whites, but the prediction that new Hispanic immigrants will have low-IQ children and grandchildren is difficult to argue against.” Although the organization distanced themselves from those assertions, other immigration-related research is still padded with the same racist and eugenics-based innuendo. Some Republican leaders have blandly (if at all) denied and distanced themselves from this but it doesn’t take away from the culture within the ranks of intolerance. The pseudo-apologies appear to be a quick fix to deep-rooted issues in the Republican Party in hopes that it will soon pass and be forgotten. The complete disregard of those who are in disadvantage is also palpable. We are not looking at an isolated incident of rhetoric or research. Others subscribe to motivating people to action by stating, “In California, a majority of all Hispanic births are illegitimate. That’s a lot of Democratic voters coming.” The discourse that moves the Republican Party is filled with this anti-immigrant movement and overall radicalization that is far removed from reality. Another quick example beyond the immigration debate happened during CPAC this year when a supporter shouted ““For giving him shelter and food for all those years?” while a moderator explained how Frederick Douglass had written a letter to his slave master saying that he forgave him for “all the things you did to me.” I think you get the idea. When the political discourse resorts to intolerance and hate, we all lose in what makes America great and the progress made in society. Although I was born an American citizen, I feel that my experience, and that of many from Puerto Rico, is intertwined with those who are referred to as illegal. My grandfather served in an all-Puerto Rican segregated Army unit, the 65th Infantry Regiment. He then helped, along my grandmother, shatter glass ceilings for Puerto Rican women raising my aunt to become the first Puerto Rican woman astronomer with a PhD in astrophysics (an IQ of a genius as far as I’m concerned). Puerto Ricans, as many other Americans still today have to face issues of discrimination in voting and civil rights. Regardless of what political affiliation people choose, my respect for some remains. I don’t expect all Hispanics to do the same (although I would hope so) but I’m taking a stand against this culture of intolerance.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368576390775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368576757034-181</Id><Topic><Title>OH YEAH AGAIN !!!! 96 !!! 97 tomorrow ;-)</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1368572470156</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..AND TRIPLE DIGITS SOON...!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1368576757034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368576927914-182</Id><Topic><Title>ana 787 delivered</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1368559622088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:27:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now why in the heck would waynedick would put 2 thumbs down to the above post? Fired from boeing ?</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1368576927914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368577856377-183</Id><Topic><Title>Obama.....son of Watergate</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368561667897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you posting as gen.ripper? did sparty103,768 get turned in to Yahoo! ??</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368577856377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368578012173-184</Id><Topic><Title>GOP push for Special Benghazi Committee !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368566757168</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 17:25:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368578012173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368578257774-185</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Voting to Repeal Obamacare for the 40th Time !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1368558325085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 15:05:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't expect House Reps. to waste their time on anything meaningful, do you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368578257774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368578265448-186</Id><Title>the GOP is looking for a black conservetive who lies like crazy</Title><Msg>to run against Hillary.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368578265448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368578405434-187</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is looking for a black conservetive who lies like crazy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368578265448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you don't have to look far. I hear Herman Cain is available.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368578405434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368578537115-188</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is looking for a black conservetive who lies like crazy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368578265448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hard to find that lie. But that is the problem in the GOP camp. You get slimy liberals that will run as a conservative feeling they have a better chance to win. Once they get in they become corrupt, lyin liberals. We conservatives need to do a better job of weeding out the bad smell.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368578537115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368578614819-189</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is looking for a black conservetive who lies like crazy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368578265448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may find the conservatives are the bad smell.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1368578614819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368578679131-190</Id><Topic><Title>Obama.....son of Watergate</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368561667897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember what Watergate was all about....sneaking in to Dem headquarters, and stealing their secrets...childs play compared to what Obama has been involved in. Like a Boy Scout breaking the code vs. Jesse James leaving a bank guns blazing.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1368578679131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368578945723-191</Id><Topic><Title>Obama.....son of Watergate</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368561667897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Remember what Watergate was all about" You don't seem to.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368578945723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368579226422-192</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is looking for a black conservetive who lies like crazy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368578265448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Herman had only one misstep. GOP needs a guy who is so low so disgusting promise any thing to get elected. Then so selfish to drown the next two generations in debt.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368579226422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368579411074-193</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is looking for a black conservetive who lies like crazy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368578265448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah they want to balance the budget, how despicable is that. #$%$ got their hands for some mapo, bouncing checks, maxed out credit cards</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368579411074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368579633547-194</Id><Title>Obama ignores Fast and Furious subpoena, refuses to comply with Congressional investigation</Title><Msg>people were killed. and Obama hides behind Executive Order. Corruption at the top.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368579633547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 21:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368579979008-195</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is looking for a black conservetive who lies like crazy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368578265448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Herman had only one misstep." That's not what I heard.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368579979008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 21:06:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368583219288-196</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is looking for a black conservetive who lies like crazy</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368578265448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 20:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>balance the budget? you mean like Raygun, GHWBush and W??? only 10 trillion dollars in the red HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HNAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368583219288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368583920049-197</Id><Topic><Title>Obama.....son of Watergate</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368561667897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sez you skummbagg</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368583920049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368584130947-198</Id><Topic><Title>Obama.....son of Watergate</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1368561667897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 16:01:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How soon will the IRS take these GOP crooks(like Americans for Prosperity) to court and convict them?? Thats going to be a barrel of fun when the supposed skandals all backfire in the faces of the RWNJs and Tdouchebaqggers- the right wing looonies on this board are likely to go find some cyanide capsules and..........................</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368584130947</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368584434194-199</Id><Topic><Title>How the Republican Party could go extinct</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368575284579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:48:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP ignorance and racism will never let them go to the trouble to attract the minorities in this country especially the Latinos--never forget what former representative Jim DeMint said about the Latinos- that they were ok for menial work but when it came to demanding work like scientist or proffessional they werent equipped intellectually to handle the work- nuther words they were genetically impaired just like the blacks are suppose to be</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1368584434194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368585128438-200</Id><Topic><Title>remember the days when Obama claimed to be Bipartisan and voted not to increase the Debt ceiling?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368551878555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:17:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it exceeds all others, stop lying, but the point is this guy hides behind them. Even his back ground.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368585128438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368585215621-201</Id><Topic><Title>remember the days when Obama claimed to be Bipartisan and voted not to increase the Debt ceiling?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368551878555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:17:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush let the cards fall where they may, so his avoiding Vietnam was right out there for every one to see, bu not Obama, he hides.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368585215621</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368585747689-202</Id><Topic><Title>remember the days when Obama claimed to be Bipartisan and voted not to increase the Debt ceiling?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368551878555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:17:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess your definition "exceeds all others" is one unknown to the literate world. Your illiteracy impedes your understanding of "exceeds" as you must think this means LESS THAN. Obama's number of executive orders is LESS than Bush, Clinton, Bush, Reagan, Carter, Ford, Nixon, Johnson, Kennedy, Eisenhower, Truman, FDR, Hoover, Coolidge, Harding, Taft, T. Roosevelt, and McKinley.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1368585747689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:42:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368586370608-203</Id><Title>How about something Boeing Related!!</Title><Msg>Boeing target raised $20 to $120 by Sterne Agee Google it! Bill</Msg><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1368586370608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 22:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368587397938-204</Id><Title>GAP OPEN ON THE UPSIDE ANY DAY...</Title><Msg>......indeed any day a gap open on the upside and into triple digit territory the next double digit trade will be after 2 for 1 split!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1368587397938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368587828191-205</Id><Topic><Title>When the IRS targeted liberals</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368574822626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 19:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember when present presidents didn't blame things on the prior Presidents? Thought not Dimwit!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1368587828191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368588078602-206</Id><Topic><Title>remember the days when Obama claimed to be Bipartisan and voted not to increase the Debt ceiling?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368551878555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 13:17:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember the W_O_N promising Hope and Change?...lol...</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1368588078602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-14 23:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>