<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376200790952-1</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on WD not mentioning that apple would not be good after jos died,</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376085062526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 17:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne loses another challenge when he can't post any reference to an October 2011 post wherin he (Wayne) claimed he had gotten out of Apple. 2013 posts are not proof.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376200790952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 01:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376203126122-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party’s paranoid aesthetic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376140769507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama lies...That's what he is paid to do....he is paid to read a script off a teleprompter by his handlers...its all lies....that's what he does...that's ALL he does</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376203126122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 02:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376203326206-3</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden’s Email Provider Shuts Down</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049374862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:56:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can have freedom or security ...but not both. Absolute Freedom is being a prisoner.....that is what Americans are now....or at least fast becoming....CHOOSE....Ive always chosen freedom and that's what ALL Americans should want</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376203326206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 02:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376203370919-4</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden’s Email Provider Shuts Down</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049374862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:56:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That last should be "absolute security" would be someone in Prison</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376203370919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 02:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376203530329-5</Id><Topic><Title>SEAL Team Six Murdered: Family Speaks Out</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376174087089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 18:34:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn/t even pass the vaguely humorous test...You're babbling</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376203530329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 02:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376204193954-6</Id><Topic><Title>SEAL Team Six Murdered: Family Speaks Out</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376174087089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 18:34:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhhhhh...but our side hasn't MADE it to court yet ...with a jury trial where the evidence is presented..now have WE ? Hmmmmmm ? ...where the NSA knows everything about key legislators and Judges ....and where the righteous die mysteriously and the less righteous are bought off and the whistle-blowers have to go to a foreign country (like Snowden) or are breitbarted, (Like Seal Team Six or Michael Hastings) ... or the best amonst us go to prison (Ltc Lakin) then we live under fascism.....and the WORST amongst us (represented by you and Raven and others) ...gloat at the loss of freedom and call it Hope and Change ... and say "I'm on the winning team"...where in the end you TOO, will have your pension funds stolen and your freedom taken away and suffer egregiously along with the rest of us....you're just too stupid to realize it !!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376204193954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 02:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376207666503-7</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If I could have gotten the votes I would have said, "America, turn em all in" Diane Feinstein</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376207666503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 03:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376209366236-8</Id><Topic><Title>How Obama turned Obamacare into a weapon</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376180736075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 20:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How Obama turned Obamacare into a weapon" Yes...lots of Americans will likely die from Obamas weapon... and Obama care well cause a lot of collateral damage.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376209366236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 04:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376214588482-9</Id><Title>USAA Massive Insurance Con. If your house burns you get nothing up front (no full payment option),</Title><Msg>USAA will low bid you and drabble your money to you over time with their unfriendly people. They denied this--- THEN admitted this was true.</Msg><Username>consumercon101</Username><Timestamp>1376214588482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 05:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376216303286-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party’s paranoid aesthetic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376140769507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your jetjockenvy is surfacing again!!!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1376216303286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 06:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376216500021-11</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party’s paranoid aesthetic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376140769507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Projecting again?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1376216500021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 06:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376225925531-12</Id><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Msg>Selling Madame War Horse Kurt Nimmo August 11, 2013 general-hillaryDan Balz, writing for the former crown jewel of the CIA’s Operation Mockingbird, the Washington Post – a onetime media giant now a midget worth the fire sale price of a paltry $250 million – has come out swinging for Hillary in 2016. “At this point, Hillary Rodham Clinton has been awarded the Democratic nomination virtually by default and declared the clear favorite to win the general election against her as yet unknown Republican opponent,” writes Balz a full three years plus before the election. Presagious? Hardly. It’s not difficult to predict the establishment’s choices, especially when the competition out on the Republican fringe will consist of Rand Paul and Ted Cruz. Between now and the Iowa caucuses the Democrats will do a lot of Hillary Clinton wheedling and peddling along with a copious amount of Paul and Cruz bashing – expect a hearty playing of the race card – and the establishment media will do its part to gussy up Hillary as Madame President. Maureen Dowd, the liberal polemicist for another newspaper drawing near the chopping block, the New York Times, writes that we can’t hear summer cicadas or ourselves “over the roar of the Clinton machine — and the buzzing back to life of old Clinton enemies” already preparing to do battle early this time around. Dowd reminds us that Team Hillary ran a “shadow campaign” after she was appointed secretary of state under Barry. “Obama granted his former rival special privileges and allowed her to move Hillaryland, with all her loyal image-buffers and political aides, into the State Department intact,” Dowd writes.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376226017238-13</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2016 will be a watershed. The Republican establishment will attempt to counter Hillary with Condoleezza Rice, Jeb Bush, Marco Rubio or Paul Ryan, but all of these will play out as sure losers against Hillary. The only saving grace will be a Paul-Cruz ticket, but Republicans will certainly move to sabotage this, even if it results in a wholesale disaffection of the tea party wing previously cleaved of its libertarian trappings but remaining mistrustful of GOP stalwarts. If a Paul-Cruz ticket is undermined, we can expect a third party to become a reality in 2020. In the meantime, Democrats will work overtime to sell Hillary Clinton as the only palatable choice. It should be noted that the Democrat party was long ago sanitized of its antiwar contingent and is fully vested in the establishment’s agenda of total police state surveillance, forever war and the long distance drone offensive against imaginary enemies, and the full-tilt expansion of corporate-bankster financial shakedown across the board, from the third world to Europe and back home in the United States. Perpetually blindsided and bushwhacked, Democrats will champion the old war horse Hillary the same way they championed Obama, the CIA-groomed newcomer out of nowhere, although possibly with a bit less religious fervor (may we be spared fainting acolytes).</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376226017238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 09:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376227149907-14</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party’s paranoid aesthetic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376140769507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You bombard the public enough with lies, and even the uninformed start to get it. Did you catch the one Obama told them about terrorist attacks, and trying to convey the notion his foreign policy is working? Said more folks are dying in car wrecks than from terror attacks. Really Mr. bullschitter? In the worst of years, 9-11 year, 14 times more folks died in car wrecks. Does the Messiah think his followers are stupid, or what?</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376227149907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 09:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376227556109-15</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of them should lose given the GOP will go on the attack. Hillary has enough corruption, Mafioso connections behind her to fill a movie theatre for a week. And I am not even talking about her very weak Sec. of State job performance...total ineptitude. Her connection to Anthony Weiner, her direct connection to Benghazi that will continue to expose her involvement. And when times were tough she ran off, and hid!</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376227556109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 09:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376227879712-16</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'll get establishment War Mongers from the GOP...and you'll get establishment warmongers from the Democrats...NONE of whom will have served in Uniform....Both will believe in the NSA surveillance state and forever wars and both will be getting Gobs of money from Wallstreet/insider/Federal Reserve banking committees.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376227879712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 09:31:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376232199106-17</Id><Topic><Title>How Obama turned Obamacare into a weapon</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376180736075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 20:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real ineptitude pf liberal policy is yet to really surface. Now the rubber meets the road, and liberal policy always fails when it is taken off the chalk board, and put into practice. The fed exchange agencies aren't, and won't be setup, and working. Liberalism doesn't work! hahaha. So folks can't get insurance. Will the IRS fine them because they don't have insurance? haha And now those that Obama told their insurance will be free find out they have to pay a premium for it! Talk about another liberal fukup! All the while it continues to kill the economy.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376232199106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 10:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376232817049-18</Id><Topic><Title>How Obama turned Obamacare into a weapon</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376180736075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 20:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you realize how many Doctors will leave the profession...and how many Insurance companies will bleed middle class Americans (middle class is fast becoming an anachronism)...and how many phonies like the Diklicker and the Raven will post cut and paste jobs saying how great this all is ? Disgusting what is happening to America</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376232817049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 10:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376237815386-19</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Marxists tell NFL NO celebrating TD's.......</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1375997102053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 17:25:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My point is is that Obama did not win by a landslide as Hooz has said he did nor does he have a mandate as hooz,, in his feeble reasoning, thinks Obama has. My question to you is why your question isn't directed to hooz?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376237815386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 12:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376239535114-20</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hitler's party was the National Socialist Party. Sounds a lot more like Progressive Democrat than Republican, wouldn't you say?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376239535114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 12:45:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376239910339-21</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Evil is evil no matter WHAT party is in power...Democrat OR Republican....and the operative word IS P.O.W.E.R. POWER in all its evil manifistations...POWER to control, power to manipulate and abuse...because at the top of the world elite, the so called POWERFUL are FILLED with perverts and perverted minds that LOVE abuse for the SAKE of abuse....and the final step is to get the guns of the American people...THEN they can REALLY start having their way with us.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376239910339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 12:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376241178666-22</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Marxists tell NFL NO celebrating TD's.......</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1375997102053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 17:25:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Landslide" refers to the electoral vote, not the popular vote. Even FDR, who won in "landslides" several times, only won 57.41 percent of the popular vote in 1932, though his landslide electoral tally was 472-59. Hooz may have used the term relatively, since Obama's 365-173 and 332-206 looks pretty definitive when compared to Bush's 271-266 and 286-251. And as for "mandate," I don't think you want to go there, since it was George "Boxarox" Bush who talked about all the political capital he would spend that was given to him by his 2004 "mandate" of 50.73%, Conclusion: Both words are subjective, their correctness determined by the user of the words. And so my question to you remains.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376241178666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 13:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376243920150-23</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be SO MUCH EASIER if the PEOPLE were disarmed before being HERDED into FEMA CAMPS! Obama plans on doing a End Around to take America's arms away. He's a busy little BARNEY FIFE!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376243920150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 13:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376245418977-24</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's Mentor, Bill Ayers said this: In 1969 undercover FBI agent Larry Grathwohl infiltrated the Weather Underground. Bill Ayers said when he took over America he would send Patriots to re-education camps and murder those who would not accept the New World Order. He estimated he would have to murder 25 million American Patriots. THIS CAN EASILY BE SEEN ON YOU TUBE ...DESPITE THE USUAL PROPAGANDA THAT SAYS I AM A LOON MAKING THIS UP...YOU CANNOT MAKE THIS STUFF UP...this is Barry Soetoro's MENTOR...</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376245418977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 14:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376247880179-25</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of us need to worry, Sparty. We know you are on guard to protect from every evil you can imagine. And that's quite a lot of evil. Loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376247880179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376247938281-26</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh boy. Not the old "FEMA camps" cap again. (Oops. Forgot the "r.")</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376247938281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376248010375-27</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, if all you need is "sounds like," you can see libruls everywhere. It sounds like the monsters under your bed. Putz.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376248010375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376248086212-28</Id><Topic><Title>How Obama turned Obamacare into a weapon</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376180736075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 20:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least I'm a SANE American, Loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376248086212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376248159524-29</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patriots like you can always vote for off-the-wall wierdos like Pauly Rand.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376248159524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376248195499-30</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love to see you campaigning for Democrats.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376248195499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376248267212-31</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party’s paranoid aesthetic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376140769507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I caught the one about WMDs in Iraq and the threat of mushroom clouds. I heard those again and again a couple years ago. All that resulted was 4,000 American deaths and record profits for Halliburton.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376248267212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376248317035-32</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry me a river.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376248317035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376248881052-33</Id><Title>weekly review boeing</Title><Msg>Aug 9, Boeing minus 2.4%, TSLA + 10.9% July 26, Boeing minus 1.3% TSLA + 8.1% July 12 Boeing minus 2.2%, TSLA +8.2 Same pattern Airbus conclusion both Airbus and TSLA are better stock than Boeing verification for 2013 year to date from January to today Aug 11, 2013 the best stock gain is TESLA stock price investor gain is 352% each dollar invested you got $3.52 cents return Airbus has returned every stock investor 55% that is for each dollar you got 55 cents return Boeing 39% so a dollar got every investor .39 cents Both Airbus and Boeing pay essentially, the same dividend 1.6% after tax Airbus and 1.81 pre tax BA so no advantage on that issue. the Boeing management is flawed by the outsourcing business plan . John Hart-Smith details that key mistake and why Boeing will fail like the bankrupt McDonnell Douglas</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376248881052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376249299702-34</Id><Title>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Next Missed Deadline Be the Last?</Title><Msg>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Seventh Missed Deadline Be the Last? by Peter Cohan Jul 15th 2010 4:08PM Updated Jul 16th 2010 6:27AM Update nothing has changed the continued missed deadlines are still the fact. It has been just over three years since July 8, 2007 -- the day that the former head of Boeing's (BA) 787 Dreamliner program first paraded the shell of the aircraft in front of the media. The Dreamliner is a $166 million, 250- to 330-seat passenger aircraft with 865 orders and an estimated $150.6 billion backlog. As I've written many times on DailyFinance, Boeing has missed deadline after deadline with the 787 program -- six times over the last two-and-a-half years -- and it now looks poised to do so for a seventh time. But will this be its last delay? The sixth deadline for the first delivery of the 787 to Japan's All Nippon Airways was November 2009. But Bloomberg reports that Boeing is likely to miss its next deadline of late 2010 as well. As Bloomberg wrote, delivery "may be pushed back until the first weeks of 2011 instead of later this year as flight-test delays accumulate." Scott Fancher, Boeing's third 787 program chief, tells Bloomberg that Boeing has found it needs still more time to change instruments needed for testing the 787 as it waits for Federal Aviation Administration tification.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376249299702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376250516485-35</Id><Topic><Title>weekly review boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376248881052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. Boeing 3 month volume average is going down 28.49% from 5700000 to now 4,076,300 that is exit information, as it is significant volume change per Tom O:brien Boeing stock price is dead on the vine . . TSLA and Airbus are better investments than Boeing have been for half a decade or as long as the company has been publically traded in TSLA case. get over it Boeing Barkers investors are exiting Boeing stock and going to other stocks like TSLA and Airbus , attention bump this for veir nachten, spartacus99991,foulmouthharbor,and company, who take up space on the Boeing message board with anger at the truth , get over it , grow up, learn to read a stock chart, a clue, dirty tricks do not change financial and stock price facts</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376250516485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376251604563-36</Id><Topic><Title>slow start to August</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376066160790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny, seems like only the Charleston produced planes are going to problem customers.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1376251604563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376251798684-37</Id><Title>Boeing volume shows that investors are leaving Boeing stock</Title><Msg>Boeing was trading an average daily volume of over 7 million for this year for 3 months now it is trading a little over 4 million , that is a drop of 28.49% . (the time period is from the yahoo Boeing financial page and is their break down, a standard financial analyst procedure, not mine)that means a significant exit of investors. Verify it , use the yahoo Boeing information page here , mouse to " technical statistics" and look under "share statistics" at average volume for 3 months and compared to the most current weeks and do the math. I did its a decrease of over 28%, that is a very significant indicator of exit of shareholders only the rocks are staying now. an analyst who simply said that Boeing peaked at or around 107 and would retrace to 71, but he did not tell you how he figured that out other than previous stock price high recently was 107, this is one of the read a stock chart suggestions that I give to he Boeing investors, and then the Boeing barkers who make anger statements and derogatory comments about me attempt in effort to divert this factual information away from the loss any Boeing investor is going to get going forward in the last month Boeing has lost 1.45% while Airbus gained 13.4% and TSLA on a buy and hold is up 22% very clear if you are in Boeing now your not making , your losing money</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376251798684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376251977443-38</Id><Topic><Title>weekly review boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376248881052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>foulmouther you should start to read a stock chart, you comment other than taking up space means nothing , slow starts mean nothing it is the outsourcing business model, Wayne said so years ago get it now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376251977443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376253094912-39</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you should check your dipstick, you sound like you're a quart low.................</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1376253094912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376253648877-40</Id><Topic><Title>weekly review boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376248881052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45 you should start to read a stock chart and stop taking up space on the boeing message board</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376253648877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376253705285-41</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing volume shows that investors are leaving Boeing stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376251798684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:09:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VN domer and sparti you should stop taking up space on the BA message board this thumbs for you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376253705285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:41:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376253741522-42</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Next Missed Deadline Be the Last?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376249299702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:28:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>vn this long thumb is for you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376253741522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 16:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376258632721-43</Id><Title>The new Boeing!</Title><Msg>Boeing is going where no aircraft manufacturer has gone since the beginning of the aircraft industry. Boeing flat out builds the best aircraft in the world!. AirBus Who?</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376258632721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376258837525-44</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't say that ...the article did...(where have I heard that before...Hmmmmmm ?)</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376258837525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376258941075-45</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary is one ugly witch...I mean NOT just on the outside...I mean UGLY to the bone...coupled with that Demonic grin...gives you the shivers</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376258941075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376259187972-46</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party’s paranoid aesthetic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376140769507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll tell ya what PinDikHertz....For every lie that you can post that Jones has stated I'll give ya 2 for the Bamster...deal ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376259187972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:13:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376260165784-47</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's degenerate friends endorse genocide. Ayers and Dorn are as about as sociopathic as they come any where in the world. I feel that total isolation from society should be their sentence.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376260165784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376261664688-48</Id><Title>God Help America If the Next President is A Democrat</Title><Msg>The country can't take another 4 years of Republican Stonewalling. Somebody needs to hit the doomsday button and end this maddess. Gods creation of humanity has become nothing but a big, end stage, cancerous tumor on the planet Earth. I feel for those with a loving family that have little more than a pot-to#$%$-in and hope in a dream. The top 0.001% of the human population are those with the most worldly possessions to lose. Thermonuke the planet and let God sort'em out.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1376261664688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 18:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376265020959-49</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It must tear you up to be on the wrong side of an argument time after time</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376265020959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376267161172-50</Id><Title>DFC's like littledikhertz and the raven</Title><Msg>are what makes this board a funny place! (even though they are the same DFC) Whenever someone asks how can a libtard/socialist be so dumb I refer them to this board..........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1376267161172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 20:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376267247870-51</Id><Topic><Title>I saw a movie once where only the police and military had guns.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1375908734506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-07 16:52:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>littledikhertz is not only on the wrong side of every argument, he's on the wrong side of America.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1376267247870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 20:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376267364230-52</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>littledikhertz likes that............as long as he DOESN'T have to go..........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1376267364230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 20:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376267424759-53</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party’s paranoid aesthetic</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376140769507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>littledikhertz only cares about his welfare check...........and a case load of Twinkies.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1376267424759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 20:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376269181329-54</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a good little Bill Ayers Stalinist</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376269181329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 20:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376269412606-55</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear Hillary uses bug spray as a moisturizer.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376269412606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 21:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376270267351-56</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She is hair raisingly UGLY</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376270267351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 21:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376272005079-57</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your usual pithy insights, loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376272005079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 21:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376272063447-58</Id><Topic><Title>Someone needs to tell Rand Paul that Milton Friedman isn't... well, alive</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376257847560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 17:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The spartaloon would pick Thomas Jefferson.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376272063447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 21:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376273053066-59</Id><Title>Boeing All-Electric Satellite Passes Critical Design Review</Title><Msg>EL SEGUNDO, Calif., Aug. 6, 2013 – The first Boeing [NYSE: BA] electric-powered satellite, the 702 Small Platform (702SP), has passed its Critical Design Review, allowing the new program to move two satellites into assembly, integration and testing. Boeing introduced the 3- to 8-kilowatt 702SP to its 702 product line in March 2012 as a simpler design that can be built more quickly while costing and weighing less than traditional satellites. Its all-electric propulsion minimizes the spacecraft’s mass and maximizes available payload</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376273053066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376273275382-60</Id><Title>Boeing All-Electric Satellite Passes Critical Design Review ---good news</Title><Msg>This will bring forth a whole new era of more reliable, more robust satellites. Will be interesting to see markets response</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376273275382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:07:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376273350925-61</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary stood by her man against Republican lies that her Willy was getting BJ's in the White House...standing on piano legs.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376273350925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:09:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376274068976-62</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing All-Electric Satellite Passes Critical Design Review</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376273053066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376274068976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376274162837-63</Id><Title>6th Boeing-built Wideband Satellite Expands Tactical Communications</Title><Msg>EL SEGUNDO, Calif., Aug. 7, 2013 – With today’s launch of the sixth Wideband Global SATCOM satellite, Boeing [NYSE: BA] and the U.S. Air Force continue to expand the advanced WGS communications network that serves the U.S. Department of Defense and its international partners, including the Australian Defence Force. “The demand for wideband satellite communications continues to increase,” said Craig Cooning, vice president and general manager of Boeing Space &amp; Intelligence Systems. “WGS-6 and the additional WGS spacecraft yet to be launched will help to meet that need.”</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376274162837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376274277548-64</Id><Topic><Title>6th Boeing-built Wideband Satellite Expands Tactical Communications</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376274162837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The need for expansion is getting critical really. Getting to be new abilities must constantly be added to stay ahead----which we are.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376274277548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376275234568-65</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Next Missed Deadline Be the Last?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376249299702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:28:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's over 3 years old? Is that the best you can do? You are such tool.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376275234568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376275293393-66</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News bombshell about Hillary could cost her the White House:</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376262264448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 19:04:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary and Bill have no redeeming qualities! So how does Chelsea fit in to that mess?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376275293393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376275719142-67</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Madame War Horse</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376225925531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>s'ok...we all have issues..Hilllary is as fugly as they come and you're a fat slob...no ones perfect there Parrot.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376275719142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376275765278-68</Id><Title>d_proch on boeing and his credibility BIOL is his other pcik down 45% -1 month -60%-3month up 10%-5 years ?</Title><Msg>d_proch, yuu said," One thing I do know, technology! by d_proch • 8 hours ago Flag . Been working in the biz for the last 30 years for some of the biggest companies in the industry. I don't buy a companies stock unless I've visited the company and talked to the dudes that run the company. This company has some serious dudes that are about to take computers to the next level. Don't believe, we shall see!"Less dproch, who dd you visit with Boeing wow your approach to BIOL is not working cnn money stock chart shows you opinion on BIOL has netted you a one month loss of 45% a 3 month loss of 60% in fact over five years you made 10% that is worse than Boeing are you another angry opinionated,no stock chart barker boy ! If you studied Boeing why did you not compare it to Airbus hummm- here you go droch, for year to date Airbus stock has gained 55% Boeing only 39% a better stock is TSLA +over 350% dproche I will put my tsla up agains you boeing and your boil much better to make over 21% in tsla in one month or 100% in 3 months in tsla than to lose 45% in your other pick boil in 1 month or 60% in 3 months and no I do nto agree the time to buy is when blood is in the streets the time to buyis when the stock charts show tsla is going up not some op that means nothing but your have lost over half you money in just 3 months Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376275765278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376275891004-69</Id><Topic><Title>d_proch on boeing and his credibility BIOL is his other pcik down 45% -1 month -60%-3month up 10%-5 years ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376275765278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dproch you sound like a dude,look it up a dude is not a good thing it is a inexperienced rookie to put it nicely</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376275891004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:51:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376276086505-70</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 Delays: Will the Next Missed Deadline Be the Last?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376249299702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:28:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing has changed ,that is the first question you asked me without huge anger good job ierzig+nachten, now if I am wrong about any recent quarterly reports being on target for the 787 there is your argument now do some research for a change. Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376276086505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376276165950-71</Id><Topic><Title>How Obama turned Obamacare into a weapon</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376180736075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 20:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a hypocritical brainwashed parrot ...RAVEN !!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376276165950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376276369864-72</Id><Topic><Title>weekly review boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376248881052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 15:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trading stocks is simple, but no amount of anger or false attack on me will change the facts. it may make you Boeing supporters feel better but I still make the money and any reader will still look at Airbus charts tesla charts and Boeing charts . anger is good fun at some point in time as I have pointed out for years you will need to learn how to trade and invest in the stock market</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376276369864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376277815002-73</Id><Topic><Title>How Obama turned Obamacare into a weapon</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376180736075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-10 20:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I checked around. 12 doctors are leaving the profession due to Obama Care. I also checked the medical schools in the United States and they are still packed with pre-med students and turning away thousands of applicants each year.</Msg><Username>slope661</Username><Timestamp>1376277815002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 23:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376279002334-74</Id><Topic><Title>d_proch on boeing and his credibility BIOL is his other pcik down 45% -1 month -60%-3month up 10%-5 years ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376275765278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 22:49:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you didn't ask when I bought BIOL. I bought Biol after the the Q report. Point is that BIOL is going to kick some serious butt in the ENT market.</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1376279002334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-11 23:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>