<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369716219752-1</Id><Topic><Title>BA is firing on all lithium battery in a fire box cylinders do you know the sound of kaboom and Paul Allen</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369586074544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:34:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpity</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369716219752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 00:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369716679227-2</Id><Topic><Title>BA is firing on all lithium battery in a fire box cylinders do you know the sound of kaboom and Paul Allen</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369586074544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:34:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>, Boeing is run by an embarrassing blood sucking sit around and do nothing leadership who thinks that buying a bankrupt MD company and then following the same business plan will work. Transfer of made in america and engineered in America to the lowest possible bidder reslut is a is a 4 year late and 30 billion dollar excessive costly and 3 month grounded all hope on the 787 going forward a failure. Failure from day one read Hart-Smith , this is i the plane that will bring Boeing down battery in a fire proof box instead of a safe nicad what are they thinking</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369716679227</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 00:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369716943367-3</Id><Topic><Title>defense -junkie Elon Must of Tesla ? wow that is my stock read my user recommendation May 3 buy Tesla up 90%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369587427790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:57:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>facts tesla Friday price gain 4.93% one month 92%, three months 170% one year 221%, Boeing? forget it your in the wrong stock this week tesla will ring the bell at 100 and make another great gain</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369716943367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 00:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369718103078-4</Id><Topic><Title>TO THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369581575195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But how many can exercise them without paying dire consequences? Look at #$%$ Riot, for instance.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369718103078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 01:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369718582214-5</Id><Topic><Title>TO THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369581575195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Russia was one of the 8 countries that did not ratify the UN Declaration on Human Rights. All the other countries did. Soldiers dying in Afghanistan and Iraq have done NOTHING to protect my rights. In fact, their doing so has reduced my rights because its given jingoists like you an opportunity to claim that I owe them something. I owe them nothing. I didn't ask them to go there, I tried to bring them home.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369718582214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 01:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369727614822-6</Id><Topic><Title>TO THOSE WHO SERVED</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369581575195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Russia was one of the 8 countries that did not ratify the UN Declaration on Human Rights. All the other countries did. Soldiers dying in Afghanistan and Iraq have done NOTHING to protect my rights. In fact, their doing so has reduced my rights because its given jingoists like you an opportunity to claim that I owe them something. I owe them nothing. I didn't ask them to go there, I tried to bring them home.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369727614822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 03:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369731822376-7</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a funny one! You stupid DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369731822376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369731868221-8</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, you are just a mentally #$%$ old man.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369731868221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 05:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369736577585-9</Id><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Msg>acts tesla Friday price gain 4.93% one month 92%, three months 170% one year 221%, Boeing? forget it your in the wrong stock this week tesla will ring the bell at 100 and make another great gain! Boeing is run like a Bankrupt Company that was purchased by the past CEO , a proven failure business plan. The idea is to become a blood sucking sit back and do nothing company and hire outsourced engineering and parts makers who bid on your work. read hart-smith it will not work proof 4 years late,30 billion over cost grounded and now battery in a firebox means the battery system is heavier than a nicad battery how much pump are you going to absorb from the same old Boeing pimps that hang out on this message board? Move to better stocks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369740725751-10</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good morning Boeing pimp, I see you woke up and yep, here I am showing all the Boeing investors and potential investors a much better stock TSLA how does that work for you today then, eh ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369740725751</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 07:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369741459154-11</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This morning news, tesla surges above 100 dollars based on German headlines and the fact that it is a great stock, unlike Boeing pumped small gain by comparison, no way to make money , on Boeing's self stock buyback. This stock TSLA, is a medium to medium high shorted stock , that means that over the last 101 days while the over all stock market has set an all time long running move up all the TESLA shorts have been getting slaughtered, so it was a slam dunk that from last week at mid 90 stock price TSLA would ring the bell at 100 dollars this week. Now depending on any more good news on TSLA like this morning, that may #$%$ the shorts to sell their short positions That is called a short squeeze or panic selling to get out of shorts and theat makes the stock go much higher. I told you to get in May 3 read my user comments then it was $54.55 today at 100 that is a 85% gain you missed boeing pimps maybe start listening to me I also told you to be in Apple for 15 years until Steve Jobs died . Get it now ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369741459154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 07:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369742540846-12</Id><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Msg>....and see what you get</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369742646273-13</Id><Title>High-End Health Plans Scale Back to Avoid ‘Cadillac Tax’</Title><Msg>http://www.cnbc.com/id/100768749</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1369742646273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369743163336-14</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so pre market tesla is up 5%! so from Friday up at almost 10% you could have made 90% before the market opened this morning if you had listened to me on May 3 when I posted tesla was the stock to be in here on the Boeing message board and the 787 a review of the facts it is a failed airplane. 4 years late 30 billion excessive cost, 7 major delays and a 3 month grounding and now a battery in a fire box means the 787 is a failed airplane and with that Boeing is now a failed company.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369743163336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369744349430-15</Id><Title>#$%$ WAYNE#$%$-FEB IS AT IT AGAIN...</Title><Msg>Typical useless messages appearing....folks,for sure boeing to rock again this week! Txs wdick-feb!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369744349430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369745733075-16</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tesla leader,Elon Musk, is like watching a healthy Steve Jobs, "Tesla shares have soared more than 180% this year, with the firm reporting its first-ever quarterly profit earlier this month. Also note that SolarCity shares debuted on the Nasdaq in December at an IPO price of $8 and are now worth six times that, closing Friday at $48.78. Boeing Hacks are we learning yet? attention Boeing hacks , one thing you always look at is the CEO record! Jim for Boeing, was let go at GE, passed over was told to leave, and MMM did much better after he left and Boeing sucks too now , a comparison Boeing CEO to the</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369745733075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369746235792-17</Id><Title>Back short Friday, more today, timing is now right</Title><Msg>As I look at the flood of nothing but bullish posts here on the BA message board it tells me short is now the right side. Besides being priced for perfection and being bloated compared to peers, nothing stops a stock like the $100 price barrier. Yeah, round number resistance exists at many increments on the way up or down, but none hold the security like 100, or even 1000 like what's going on in the rut2k now. It just never, ever, never, ever cruises right through the number and keep moving up. Yeah it may cross the line but it comes right back under, then cross again a few times before either tanking or finally busting through. So I shorted 300 shares on Friday as we passed over the century mark and will double it today as we prolly open over a buck. Then I plan on holding til we pull back to the mid 90's and then covering, again waiting for it to assault 100 again then shorting again. After that round I will evaluate because the third attempt is usually the succesful attempt if its gonna do it. Either way ark my words the first attempt is never a success.</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1369746235792</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369746693121-18</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is the founder of Tesla accomplishments what has Jim Mcnerdey done other than take excessive pay from boeing shareholders for failure on the 787 and be booted from GE by Jack Welch ? Elon is the Chairman of SolarCity, the leading residential solar provider in the U.S. In addition to his role at SolarCity, Elon is also the co-founder, chairman and CEO of Tesla Motors, an all-electric American car company. As Chairman at Tesla Motors, Elon helped design the ground-breaking Tesla Roadster, for which he won an Index and a Global Green award, the latter presented by Mikhail Gorbachev. Elon is also the founder and CEO of SpaceX - a space launch vehicle company. Prior to SpaceX, he co-founded PayPal, the world's leading electronic payment system, and served as the company's chairman and CEO. PayPal went public in early 2002 and was sold to eBay later that year for $1.5 billion.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369746693121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369747685345-19</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so lets do a fact check, on solar city ,founded by the tesla founder , one week stock price SCTY gain 8%, one month stock price gain SCTY 94%, 3 month stock price gain SCTY 182% year to date stock price gain SCTY 308% are we learning yet? Boeing pimps! which is better a 5 year Boeing gain of 22% or a ytd gain of 308%for SCTY, solar city a company that the founder of tesla founded too ! you really need to stop feeding Boeing crapola, get it right it is not orders or flying 787s it has 1005 to do with the cost and the delay and the failure of the 787, which is a failed airplane! the 787 is a 4 years late, 30 billion over budget airplane with a 3 month grounding and 7 major delays that the CEO missed reporting or giving a heads up on, becasue he does nto knwo what he is doing, zero experience in air frame making well no wonder , he is a rookie and no history of success at GE engines or MMM a life time failure , and the fix come on boys a battery in a fire box failure, that will cripple Boeing. Attention Boeing pimps , the only reason Boeing stock is up for the last 3 months is Boeing investors are buying their own shares back on the company buyback fail program get it now think about it Boeing goes up on a 3 month 787 grounding and the stock moves up for the first time in a marginal way in five years use your heads. It is a stock buy back fail Now Obama today is pushing for adding a 14% tax on passenger tickets so that is going to hurt airlines and then airplane manufacturers get it now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369747685345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369747933911-20</Id><Title>101 OH YEAH !!!!</Title><Msg>SHOW ME THE MONEY BA !!! ;-)</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1369747933911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369747939787-21</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, I believe that you are confused. In this topic with several posts you have promulgated two things: 1) lauded Islam as a “religion of peace”, while 2) condemning all of Christianity as evil. To wit, your words, “Let's assume that 86.73% of Christians are murderous thugs. Now assume that the other 13.27% are too cowardly to turn them in.” I have told you before that the Koran is the antithesis of Christianity because it directly contradicts, with specific Koranic verses, the Person of Jesus as God and the premise of His mission on earth, to provide salvation. It is not a trivial and unimportant contradiction or a “matter of opinion”, it is an attack on the foundation of Christianity. Enough of that debate, we will concentrate on your words. You claim that all Christians are evil – either directly or indirectly. Then, by definition, you are saying that the Creator of everything, Jesus, is a failure, because He could not muster up even one person, as a Christian, to believe and ascribe to His admonition of love and service. Yet, you praise the followers of Islam in this post. You are clearly under the delusion predicted in 2 Thess 2:10-12: “They perish because they refused to love the truth and so be saved. For this reason God sends them a powerful delusion so that they will believe the lie and so that all will be condemned who have not believed the truth but have delighted in wickedness.” It is not too late to get it right. You are still breathing. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1369747939787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369748073732-22</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tesla reached a new 52 week high this morning and boeing is still a suck it stock</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369748073732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369748986194-23</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tesla now up 6.55% this morning after closing up 5% last Friday. attention Boeing hacks , i bet you wished you followed my suggestion to get in on May 3 at 55 dollars for tesla now! don't you Boeing hacks up 100% in less than a month , hows that Boeing stock price now looking to you up 100% this month like tsla ? nope</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369748986194</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369749050679-24</Id><Title>Come on 102 ;-)</Title><Msg>LOVE IT !!!!!</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1369749050679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369750053468-25</Id><Title>Baggers WRONG Five Years in a Row</Title><Msg>Market opens up triple digits again setting more record highs. You would think that after being wrong every day for more than five years gloom&amp;doom baggers would wake from their stupor.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369750053468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369750244927-26</Id><Topic><Title>Back short Friday, more today, timing is now right</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1369746235792</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:03:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moron! How is that strategy working for you! LMFAO</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1369750244927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369752628315-27</Id><Title>USAA INSURANCE IS A SCAM....NO FULL PAY OPTION UP FRONT IF YOUR HOUSE BURNS...... You fight their cheap bids and they nickel and dime you.....check it out!!!!!! you must re-build!!!!! No open door with robles ceo either!!! he is in hiding!! SWITCH TO CHUBB OR OTHER NOT THE SAME USAA--20YEARS AGO! MANY MORE HONEST COMPANIES NOW</Title><Msg>ROBLES CEO HAS TRASHED USAA</Msg><Username>eagle81752</Username><Timestamp>1369752628315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:50:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369752944125-28</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mus lims are committing genocide all over Africa. Can you name one instance where Christians are committing genocide? I keep asking Hooz and insane clown posse to provide a current example of Christian genocide but they have no example whereas Mus lims are committing genocide in numerous countries. Saying Islame is a religion of peace is an oxymoron perpetuated by morons.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369752944125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369753289694-29</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You get a bunch of BS from nutty green activists and NGOs that don't want to see drought resistant and insect resistant crops providing more food to poor countries, in hopes of killing off more of the world's poor via starvation. The ant-GMO movement is an anti-science movement created by green religious nuts.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369753289694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369753528787-30</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Syria and Alabama, for example</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1369753528787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369753962389-31</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers WRONG Five Years in a Row</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369750053468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>liberalism preys on ignorance and you are a winner in that regard. As long a Bernanke sells Treasurys to the Chineese and Japan the market will soar for the time being and that is what Obama wants. Fiscal responsibilty will fall under another President. When paying off the debt becomes a priorirty then we will see 20% mortgage rates and credit card interest rates. As we see in Greece liberal politicians promised any thing to stay in power but once the money ran out debt became overwhelming thier market crashed. The rise in the market is due to the fact Obama is selling out tomorrows future, your kids and grandkids.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369753962389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369753980924-32</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GFY - I was asked what my accomplishments were and I responded with the truth. You can go back to licking Hooz' balls and lapping up his baloney about Obonzo.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369753980924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369754801509-33</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369754801509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369754831347-34</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers WRONG Five Years in a Row</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369750053468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>somehow most of us think Bernanke knows one helluva lot more about macro economics than any clown named gregjanetommax--</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369754831347</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369755044031-35</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, TSLA and SCTY are better stocks than BA the last month for making money for traders. Happy now? McNerney - "or MMM a life time failure" So, how do you define failure? You seem to worship at the altar of making a buck (you've posted that you don't care about your former Boeing co-workers making money). I dare say McNerney has accumulated way more money in his lifetime than you, so how can he be a failure and not you? I bet he even has friends.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1369755044031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369755250615-36</Id><Topic><Title>Fighting Radical Muslim Preachers</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369573292696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"..When Jesus came along, He revoked the death and destruction judgment (for sin).." Jesus did no such thing !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369755250615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:34:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369755494525-37</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, BA up over 240 percent in last 4+ years for those long term investors who bought in March 2009 (like maybe some of your co-workers in the Savings Plan). I personally haven't owned BA in several years or any individual stocks. Pulled most of my funds out and invested in Orange County real estate over the last 40+ years and have done very nicely, thank you.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1369755494525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369755798515-38</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing buisness jet</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369623164141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 22:52:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't BBJ interiors provided by third-party (after-market) vendors? I thought every BBJ was sold WITHOUT any interior fixtures at all.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369755798515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:43:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369756178033-39</Id><Topic><Title>Fighting Radical Muslim Preachers</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369573292696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 09:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, Stick, Perhaps I did not make myself clear. Give a contemporary example of God judging the world for sin and imposing punishment, on earth. In fact, consider all two thousand years since Jesus birth. Then, go back to the Old Testament and there are multiple examples of God's direct intervention in the affairs of men wherein He was clearly imposing punishment for sin. Now, that being said, after one dies, that is another case, but that is AFTER death. And, God will once again directly judge man living on the earth. But that will come, apparently not too far away now, but that will be during the Tribulation. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1369756178033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369757493512-40</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus 99991, er I mean father z, er i mean joe dokes 25 er I mean wstlefansms , troll on ha ha your comment puts my top user comment back on top, so I can use you! spartacus been picking any more non existing stocks lately to try to put me in my place ha ha , say hello to your close personal friend,( laugh here), Paul Allen. Now if you are concerned that I have no friends then please take some action, and go out and get me some friends then, don't just complain about it! ha ha ha. My Boeing friends the ones who took me sailing a couple of weeks ago for the retirement of one of my other Boeing friends was posted i got about 12 thumbs up on that one. Several of us were real glad a certain worthless Renton Boeing employee was fired too. he has the same name as a company that hauls money and starts with B. Why didn't you bring your really big boat and your close personal friend paul Allen, and show off for us? we sailed out of Clinton departed from the ocean view house. we Boeing friends had a good time for three days . many of my Boeing friends especially like my stock tips and we visit on a daily basis on the internet or phone and they constantly ask me to move back to Seattle but I like Spokane no traffic and Idaho and Canada and Montana are very close . Went hydro racing saturday and was in Canada friday looking at a company to buy stock in , my friends are waiting for my report after talking to the CEO. spartacus99991 you keep trolling that is your strong suit . suite</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369757493512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369757752478-41</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama Is A Winner</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1369520943386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he promised handouts and free medical for the poor. Finance, budget nor did any thing else matter, getting someting for nothing did. Of course selling out the next two generations, but who cares about that, certainly not Obama or Liberals. Remember the $1T debt Carter handed to Reagan, that caused 20% mortgage and credit card interest rates. Obama is setting up the next Presidency to a failure for the next two generations with high interest and mortgage rates. Liberals are howling in approval today, but under a new president who decides to pay off debt they will howl dissaproval when this thug today caused tomorrows debt payment problem.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369757752478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369757967768-42</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an anti-science buffoon. GMOs have increased yield dramatically in drought ridden countries and has reduced the need for insecticides and fertilizers that wash into rivers causing contamination of drinking water. Growing organic foods require much more watering and insecticides and cause more harm to ecosystems than GMO crops. If you would read the scientific literature instead of being brainwashed by green religionists who ignore science, you would know this. You can also calculate the death toll in poor countries that have arisen since the US has started and expanded ethanol fuel production. Doing so has had a direct impact on food prices world wide and has led to increases in starvation in poor countries.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369757967768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369758078523-43</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The other half pay no income tax and live on food stamps and welfare checks. They are good with the Prez.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1369758078523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369758409390-44</Id><Topic><Title>Some thoughts on religion</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369584007954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 12:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Islame ists are persecuting Christians in Syria. Were you trying to be funny or just letting the message board know how ignorant you are?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369758409390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369758912034-45</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers WRONG Five Years in a Row</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369750053468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fascist, obviously your education at the RubeRadio Glenn Beck home skool Econ 101 for Ignorant Baggers has prepared you for a lifetime of continued employment at Fast Food Heaven. Have you graduated to Rest Room Cleaner 1st Class yet?</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369758912034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369759797877-46</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This reminds me of what Morgan Stanley (MS) analyst, Heidi Wood, told me about Boeing CEO Jim McNerney when he took over in 2005" Has Heidi called you lately? So are you a failure if you have less money than McNerney? You're so easy to tweek.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1369759797877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369759879674-47</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers WRONG Five Years in a Row</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369750053468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Greg but a brainwashed propaganda repeater such as yourself is in no position to call anybody ignorant.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369759879674</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369760909808-48</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By drought resistant, Monsanto offers Roundup Ready seed. That means the seed has been modified to withstand late applications of the toxin Roundup. That is more dangerous to field, stream and consumer.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369760909808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369761422485-49</Id><Title>787-9 production starts this week</Title><Msg>Production of the first 787-9 is scheduled to start on Thursday according to the nyc787 site.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369761422485</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369762277354-50</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't forget about deaths from DDT, Agent Orange, PCB - and the side-effects of rBGH, Aspartame !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762277354</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:31:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369762512740-51</Id><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Msg>SYRIA (The Borowitz Report)—During a meeting yesterday with Sen. John McCain (R-Arizona), Syrian rebels told the senator that he still seemed “really bitter” about losing the 2008 election to President Obama and advised him to “get over it.” After meeting with the Arizona senator in the border region near Turkey, a spokesman for the Syrian rebels told reporters that while they appreciated Sen. McCain’s support, “We were kind of uncomfortable with the place it was coming from.” “It was pretty obvious to me and the other rebels that everything McCain was doing was just to get back at Obama,” the rebel spokesman said. “And we were like, look, that election was five years ago. It’s time to move on.” Sen. McCain denied that his support of the Syrian rebels had anything to do with a personal vendetta against President Obama, but according to the rebel, “Every time he said ‘Obama,’ a vein in his head kind of bulged out.”</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369762574620-52</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that is about 50 thumbs up for me and yes Wayne is making several great points about how to make money on stocks. I am already loading up on the next big stock money maker. I have over 4000 shares now and keep buying the dips, it is a a mediim high number of shorts on this stock and working its way down or close to a bottom now. this is a stock that is going to make me a ton of money in a very short time . If you knew how to read a stock chart and could actually use the data that is supplied by nas on shorts then you could read the chart and know the shorts are on the wrong side of the trade and are going to get crushed . You could also read the news, if you knew what was important and what is just fluff like all the Boeing guys here talking about things that don't matter What does matter Boeing leadership that matters, it is leadership and cost to build the plane that matters and delivery on time being met, BTW Boeing is not a short candidate and has very few shorts it is and has been a dead cat stock not worth trading . any plane that cost an extra 30 billion to build and is not controlled by the company and is 4 years late with many unknowns to come up is a company bankruptcy deal for the shareholders , don't believe me just watch !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369762574620</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369762914108-53</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is seldom far from my mind. Aside from those catastrophes, there is the fact that there has been little data gathered on the long term effects or lack of effects genetically modified foods can have on consumers. By consumer, we need to consider livestock and wildlife as well as people. There could be an increase in consumption of toxin as well as certain building blocks of food that could be integral to digestion and growth that could be missing entirely. There just hasn't been much testing yet.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369762914108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369763121876-54</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>update on TSLA, from the pre market open. with todays gain , TSLA is up 7.52% today,( that is 12.5% gain from Friday and shorts are getting squeezed now ) for one month TSLA is up 103.87%, for three months, TSLA is up 203% and for one year TSLA is up 250%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369763121876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369763329394-55</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So your point is...Syrian Rebels are pro Obama. First bit of truth you've ever posted. So are the Muslim Brotherhood who Obama has provided guns to. So is Cezar Chavez. Most terrorist leaders are happy to support Obama, and be called "lone wolves ", rather than Muslim Radical terrorists when they attack Americans.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369763329394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369763554997-56</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So do you have more money than McNerney or are you a failure too?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1369763554997</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369766382880-57</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course McCain has a thing about Obama. He was set up to fail because Karl Rove wanted Obama in the WH to serve the 1% while putting the blame for all the pain on "socialism".</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369766382880</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369766747329-58</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The subject is not McCain, the subject is rebels getting arms, and Obama is keeping the Syrian murderer/tyrrant in power by not providing the rebels guns. McCain is the Rebels hope, and they expressed that hope that McCain will help them overthrow the Syrian mass murderer. Why does Obama continue to allow the slaughter of Syrian citizens by this tyrrant?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369766747329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369767161282-59</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers WRONG Five Years in a Row</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369750053468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since this has nothing to do with BA, everyone should just add you to their ignore list.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1369767161282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369767997079-60</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers WRONG Five Years in a Row</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369750053468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You overlooked the connection between Obama, and the left trashing the economy, and the rising stock markert. Stand out on the sidewalk after school, and stop a 5th grader headed home. He'll make the connection for you.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369767997079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369768492285-61</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama HAS armed the rebels, thus supporting al-Qaeda-affiliated Islamists.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369768492285</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369769596895-62</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This isnt some Liberal vrs conservative issue. Monsanto was responsible for Agent Orange and Round up....They are the first company to patent Life Forms.....Seeds cannot be resused any more by farmers....that is ANTI LIBERTY. Anti Human and anti common sense and anti last 10000 years of agricultural history. You have never been more wrong</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1369769596895</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369770271923-63</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aniti-obama wing-nuts know not the depth of their shalowness nor the depth of their vendetta in the namne of money not god, country, or love</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1369770271923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369770881753-64</Id><Title>No matter who won - the econmoy was set to improve</Title><Msg>that it why I chose to stay with the status quo and good team Obama rather than the religious-cultist Raw-money and lyin' Ryan and their uber right-wing backers end of story</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1369770881753</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369770922543-65</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so today TSLA is up 12%, short squeeze, and if you were in when I pointed it out as a buy on May 3 at $55.45 today you would have made 96.5% gain way better in 3 weeks than BA has done in 5 years up 22% . you would be so up now you could take a hit tomorrow if the stock comes down on this high open and fail down market. attention , you could buy more tomorrow at a lower price, it would not matter now get it now ? that is in just 15 days, unless your a troll and laying down smack then you make nothing , start learning to read a stock chart. I am the trader who told you for 15 years to be in Apple right up until $700 and then Steve Job's died . I got out at $650 and am not looking back at apple it is done bad leadership learn that now just like BA. we have a new leader great TSLA CEO and he has a great history . remember that is what makes a company, not hillbilly guys posting junk abut Boeing that does not matter. What matters is the 787 is late by 4 years , does not work so far and is like the comet a failure maybe like the comet they will solve the problems but the customers will not accept it going forward as more failures occur. What matters is the 787 is way over budget at 30 billion extra cost. The ," all composite passenger planes" haves never worked, there are smaller companies out of business that tried this idea but then you have proven failure the MD business plan to supercharge the failure of BA a do nothing and rely on contractors to do your work for you that is what bankrupted MD next up Boeing wait you will see.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369770922543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369771298930-66</Id><Title>Liberals hate the poor and especially Black people</Title><Msg>....that's why they work to make sure they're dependent on them.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369771298930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369771439495-67</Id><Title>Washington launches four different investigations into IRS mess...</Title><Msg>Capitol Hill aides spent their Memorial Day weekend scanning hundreds of pages of documents related to the IRS scandal in order to prepare their bosses for what will inevitably be a frantic month of June involving multiple simultaneous investigations into government wrongdoing. By the time lawmakers return to session next week, at least four different investigations will be underway. As The Daily Caller has reported, at least five different IRS offices including Cincinnati, Ohio; Baltimore, Maryland; Chicago, Illinois and El Monte and Laguna Niguel, California improperly targeted conservative nonprofit groups for extra scrutiny between 2010 and 2012. The IRS’ shenanigans, chronicled in a damning report by Treasury Inspector General J. Russell George, started when a “team of [IRS] specialists” came together in April 2010 to process the tax-exempt nonprofit status of conservative groups that might be “potential political operations” (page 13 of the IG report). The IRS added “additional specialists” to this effort in December 2011.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369771439495</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369771612704-68</Id><Title>30% of college professors believe Obama belongs on Mt. Rushmore</Title><Msg>why so low a percentage... when President Obama's visage 100% belongs there</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1369771612704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369771848781-69</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>armed with non-lethal aid</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369771848781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369772198649-70</Id><Title>CEO of BA and the CEO of TSLA which is better ?</Title><Msg>• FACT check, Here is the founder of Tesla accomplishments, Elon is the Chairman of SolarCity, the leading residential solar provider in the U.S. In addition to his role at SolarCity, Elon is also the co-founder, chairman and CEO of Tesla Motors, an all-electric American car company. As Chairman at Tesla Motors, Elon helped design the ground-breaking Tesla Roadster, for which he won an Index and a Global Green award, the latter presented by Mikhail Gorbachev. Elon is also the founder and CEO of SpaceX - a space launch vehicle company. Prior to SpaceX, he co-founded PayPal, the world's leading electronic payment system, and served as the company's chairman and CEO. PayPal went public in early 2002 and was sold to eBay later that year for $1.5 billion., so like Steve jobs of Apple then a money maker for his shareholders . SCTY ,, one month stock price gain SCTY 86%, 3 month stock price gain SCTY 168% year to date stock price gain SCTY 296%. I would stick with TSLA but he is the man making a lot of money for his shareholders Today TSLA is up 12%, short squeeze, and if you were in when I pointed it out as a buy on May 3 at $55.45 today at $110, you would have made 97% what has the CEO of Boeing Jim McNerdey done other than take excessive pay from Boeing shareholders for failure on the 787 and be booted from GE by Jack Welch ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369772198649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369772280998-71</Id><Title>Issa subpoenas State Dept. documents on Benghazi...</Title><Msg>House Oversight Committee Chairman Darrell Issa (R-Calif.) has subpoenaed State Department documents related to the Benghazi talking points, according to a letter sent to Secretary of State John Kerry obtained by The Hill. In the letter, Issa states that the department's release of 100 emails earlier this month was "incomplete." Issa demands that Kerry produce "relevant documents through subpoena. The enclosed subpoena covers documents and the communications related to talking points prepared for members of the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence and used by Ambassador Susan Rice during her September 16th, 2012, appearances on CBS, NBC, ABC, Fox, and CNN." Issa said that the documents released on May 20 did not answer "critical" questions posed by the committee as it investigates what happened during the attack on the U.S. consulate in Benghazi, Libya, and the aftermath of that terror attack that killed former U.S. Ambassador to Libya Chris Stephens and three other Americans.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369772280998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:18:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369772495161-72</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They don't really know who all the rebels are: probably not even all Syrian. What would be the good of arming them to oust Assad, only to replace him with the same or worse?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369772495161</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369772631643-73</Id><Title>REPORT: HOLDER WENT JUDGE SHOPPING TO OBTAIN FOXNEWS SUBPOENA...</Title><Msg>The New Yorker's Ryan Lizza, a bulldog on the DOJ/Fox News secret subpoena story, reports that the effort by the Justice Department to obtain the controversial court order was arduous, contentious and unsuccessful until finally a third judge acquiesced. The new documents show that two judges separately declared that the Justice Department was required to notify Rosen of the search warrant, even if the notification came after a delay. Otherwise: “The subscriber therefore will never know, by being provided a copy of the warrant, for example, that the government secured a warrant and searched the contents of her e-mail account,” Judge John M. Facciola wrote in an opinion rejecting the Obama Administration’s argument. Machen appealed that decision, and in September, 2010, Royce C. Lamberth, the chief judge in the Federal District Court for the District of Columbia, granted Machen’s request to overturn the order of the two judges. Lizza goes on to explain that Holder's Justice Department argued to the court that reporter James Rosen was a co-conspirator in a conspiracy to commit espionage and lists the detailed information they wished to explore: —“Records or information related to Stephen Kim’s or the Author’s knowledge of laws, regulations, rules and/or procedures prohibiting the unauthorized disclosure of national defense or classified information.” —“Any classified document, image, record, or information, and any communications concerning such documents, images, records, or information.” —“Any document, image, record, or information concerning the national defense, including but not limited to documents, maps, plans, diagrams, guides, manuals, and other Department of Defense, U.S. military, and/or weapons material, as well as sources and methods of intelligence gathering, and any communications concerning such documents, images, records, or information.” —“Records or information related to the state of mind of any individuals seeking the disclosure or receipt of classified, intelligence and/or national defense information.” The revelation that two courts denied the secret subpoena before Lamberth finally agreed will damage the narrative that there was nothing extraordinary or out-of-bounds about Holder's attempt to delve into the private communications of Rosen and his employer.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369772631643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369773044447-74</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian Rebels Urge McCain to Get Over Losing to Obama !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369762512740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like another Obama score making your rwnj head-spin which side are you on...anyways the south will rise again/ dixie ?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1369773044447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369773133229-75</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dow Chemical had a hand in Agent Orange also, but in all fairness, the worst of the Agent Orange had been contaminated with a very toxic dioxin. Not all agent orange had it in there. This is not to even mention agent blue, which was used to kill food crops, not just jungle.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1369773133229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369773872282-76</Id><Title>Obama Voter charged with murder after he 'shot dead six-month-old girl</Title><Msg>A 33-year-old documented gang member with 38 prior arrests has been charged in the devastating March shooting of a six-month-old Chicago girl - and police claim the alleged murder was in retaliation for a stolen video game system. Koman Willis is facing first degree murder and aggravated battery with a firearm charges after he allegedly shot dead baby Jonylah Watkins while aiming for her father, Jonathan Watkins. Police Superintendent Garry McCarthy said at a Monday press conference that Mr Watkins had earlier robbed Willis, prompting the spray of bullets.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369773872282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369773906346-77</Id><Title>While you're busy blaming in Benghazi !!</Title><Msg>... The vultures on capitol hill and wall street are gutting Dodd-Frank !! H.R. 992 would "repeal most of Dodd-Frank Section 716" of the Dodd-Frank Act. This section, also known as the "Lincoln Rule," was one of the hottest of hot potatoes during the negotiations for the Dodd-Frank bill H.R. 1062, the "SEC Regulatory Accountability Act," is the same bill as H.R. 2308 from last year, requiring the SEC to undertake a cost-benefit analysis of any new rule before it is adopted. These "cost-benefit analysis" bills are pure stalling tactics. They have absolutely no purpose other than to force the government to spend valuable time, effort and money engaging in pointless reviews of rules that already in some cases take years to craft, incidentally with the constant input of bank lobbyists H.R. 1256, the "Swap Jurisdiction Certainty Act," which is yet another leprechaun trick. What it basically means is that if you're Goldman or Chase and you have an office in some place like Mexico or Turkey or Russia or Saudi Arabia, you can do all the swaps business you want from there</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369773906346</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369774281284-78</Id><Title>The Ailes Manifesto: America Rallies Around Roger Ailes and Fox News</Title><Msg>Fox News CEO Roger Ailes’ May 23 stirring letter to Fox employees will be remembered as a turning point in the battle for freedom of the press in the age of Obama. The Ailes letter, denouncing the Obama administration’s trampling on the First Amendment, should be seen, of course, as a strong defense of Fox correspondent James Rosen. In addition, the Ailes letter--in truth, a manifesto--is a staunch vindication of Fox News and its “speak-truth-to-power” approach to journalism. Finally, the Ailes Manifesto should be seen as a clarion call for freedom--for freedom of the press, and also for the right of all Americans to think freely, liberated from the MSM thought-monopoly. As Patrick Caddell has pointed out here at Breitbart News, the Obama Administration has never truly been worried about leaks, because the Administration itself has been the main source of leaks. Why? For political advantage, of course. That is, to make the Administration look good, especially in regard to the war on terror in the run-up to the 2012 election. The Obamans wanted to maintain their exclusive “franchise” on leaks, rewarding friendly reporters, such as The New York Times’ David Sanger, with information on highly-classified programs, including the Stuxnet virus used against Iran. In fact, Chairman of the Senate Intelligence Committee, Senator Dianne Feinstein, upon reading Sanger’s book Confront and Conceal: Obama’s Secret Wars and Surprising Use of American Power, said, "You learn more from the book than I did as Chairman of the Intelligence Committee, and that's very disturbing to me." In other words, US national security was a distant second, well behind the primary goal, which was the President’s re-election. To be sure, the Obama Administration leaked for other reasons, as well. As Breitbart News’ Matthew Boyle reported, the Obama Justice Department was happy to leak documents to advance its own interests in the “Fast and Furious” scandal. It is obvious that the Obama Administration will leak any information regardless of its sensitivity to national security or to individuals' reputations when it is expedient for political gain. The facts are incontrovertible, over a broad range of issues, over a long period of time. While the Obama administration has been playing this dangerous game, Roger Ailes has been clear and straightforward. The Ailes Manifesto is, indeed, fierce in its defense of freedom. As the Fox News founder--at the helm, now, for 17 years--wrote: The administration’s attempt to intimidate Fox News and its employees will not succeed and their excuses will stand neither the test of law, the test of decency, nor the test of time. We will not allow a climate of press intimidation, unseen since the McCarthy era, to frighten any of us away from the truth. Even amidst the greatest threat to press freedom in six decades, neither Fox, nor its friends and allies, are going to back away, or back down. The fight for freedom is a fight for all of us.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369774281284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369774758131-79</Id><Title>Study: Republicans are “the less credible party”</Title><Msg>PolitiFact rules GOP "false" far more often than Democrats, with Bachmann one of the worst, a new report reveals Many politicians stretch the truth or obfuscate to some degree or another — but does one party do it more than the other? According to a new study from the Center for Media and Public Affairs at George Mason University the answer is an unequivocal yes. Parsing 100 statements evaluated by the fact-checking website PolitiFact between Obama’s second inauguration and this month, the researchers found that claims from Republican officials were labeled as “false” or “pants on fire” by a 3-to-1 margin, compared to claims from Democratic officials. Conversely, half as many Republican claims were labeled “entirely true.” “While Republicans see a credibility gap in the Obama administration, PolitiFact rates Republicans as the less credible party,” said CMPA President Dr Robert Lichter in a press release. An earlier study from the CMPA found the website rated the Romney campaign worse than the Obama campaign during the 2012 election. Not surprisingly, Michele Bachmann is one of the most poorly rated politicians on PolitiFact. Undoubtably, Republicans would blame this on “bias,” accusing the fact checkers of operating as little more than Democratic party shills. “We’re not going to let our campaign be dictated by fact-checkers,” Romney pollster Neil Newhouse famously declared last summer after the campaign got whacked for running nakedly false ads.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369774758131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369774940811-80</Id><Title>State Department Served With Subpoenas Over Benghazi</Title><Msg>For months the State Department and the White House have refused to issue requested information about the 9/11 terrorist attack in Benghazi to Congressional investigators. More specifically, the administration has refused to release documentation and communications surrounding the talking points used to explain Benghazi to the American people. As a result, Chairman of the House Oversight Committee Darrell Issa sent a letter to Secretary of State John Kerry Tuesday informing him about subpoenas being issued to State Department employees. "The use of compulsory process is necessary to obtain documents from the State Department. I prefer to advance the Committee's investigation without having to use the compulsory process to obtain the entire universe of documents that the Department has withheld from Congress," the letter states. "In light of your continuing refusal to provide documents in response to my requests, however, I have found it necessary to issue a subpoena to compel documents related to the Benghazi talking points. This subpoena creates a legal requirement that you produce the specified documents to room 2157 of the Rayburn House Office Building no later than 12:00 noon on Friday June 7, 2013. The subpoena covers all documents and communications referring or relating to the Benghazi talking points, to or from the following current and former State Department personnel."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369774940811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369775319063-81</Id><Title>apparently x6xxx234 has no 'nads' letalone a brain</Title><Msg>and must rely on the rwnj media aka mannie coulturless, sean 'lou costello' hannity, and the ever tirdgid Rush Limpballs/Karl Rovians for it's talking points</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1369775319063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369775356819-82</Id><Title>Bitten by a Turtle? There’s an Injury Code for that in Obamacare</Title><Msg>Speaking at the Iowa Republican Party’s Lincoln Dinner earlier this month, Kentucky Senator Rand Paul criticized the approximately 122,000 new medical diagnostic codes in Obamacare that physicians will have to use to inform insurers of their patients’ injuries. “Your government just wants to take care of you,” Paul said sarcastically, as some of the codes are downright ridiculous. “Included among these codes,” the senator continued, “will be 312 new codes for injuries from animals; 72 new codes for injuries just from birds; 9 new codes for ‘injuries from the macaw.”‘ “The macaw?” he asked. “I’ve asked physicians all over the country, ‘Have you ever seen an injury from a macaw?”‘ He continued, adding that he had found “two new injury codes under Obamacare for ‘injuries sustained from a turtle.”‘ “Now, you might say, ‘Well, turtles are dangerous’ — but why do you have to have two codes?” he asked. “Your doctor has to inform the government whether you’ve been struck by a turtle or bitten by a turtle.” He added: “There is a new code for … walking into a lamppost. There’s also a code for ‘walking into a lamppost, subsequent encounter.’” “I guess that’s if you don’t learn,” he added. “[T]here is [also] a code … for ‘injuries sustained from burning water skis.”‘ Speaking at the Iowa Republican Party’s Lincoln Dinner earlier this month, Kentucky Senator Rand Paul criticized the approximately 122,000 new medical diagnostic codes in Obamacare that physicians will have to use to inform insurers of their patients’ injuries. “Your government just wants to take care of you,” Paul said sarcastically, as some of the codes are downright ridiculous. “Included among these codes,” the senator continued, “will be 312 new codes for injuries from animals; 72 new codes for injuries just from birds; 9 new codes for ‘injuries from the macaw.”‘ “The macaw?” he asked. “I’ve asked physicians all over the country, ‘Have you ever seen an injury from a macaw?”‘ He continued, adding that he had found “two new injury codes under Obamacare for ‘injuries sustained from a turtle.”‘ “Now, you might say, ‘Well, turtles are dangerous’ — but why do you have to have two codes?” he asked. “Your doctor has to inform the government whether you’ve been struck by a turtle or bitten by a turtle.” He added: “There is a new code for … walking into a lamppost. There’s also a code for ‘walking into a lamppost, subsequent encounter.’” “I guess that’s if you don’t learn,” he added. “[T]here is [also] a code … for ‘injuries sustained from burning water skis.”‘</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369775356819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369775578709-83</Id><Topic><Title>apparently x6xxx234 has no 'nads' letalone a brain</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1369775319063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:08:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO......gett'n to you, eh! One thing is always certain about a Democrat. Whenever they insult you or accuse you of something......you can bet that's the very thing they are doing themselves.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369775578709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369775712444-84</Id><Topic><Title>State Department Served With Subpoenas Over Benghazi</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369774940811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just doin what corrupt liberals do. And BO acts like he wasn't a part of it. You can act that way when you never have governed over the last 5 yrs. "What? I'll see that will never happen again. " What, and FBI scandal? I'll clean that up, and see that it never happens again."</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369775712444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369775846709-85</Id><Title>Democrat's Assault on Freedom Continues - Proposed Regulations in Past 90 Days: 6,534</Title><Msg>According to Regulations.gov, 6,534 new regulations have been proposed in the past 90 days. Proposed regulations include everything from importing plants for planting, meetings of the sub-Saharan Africa Advisory Committee, solicitation of comments and more. As a reminder, regulations already in place are very expensive and are suffocating to the economy. “Red Tape Rising: Regulation in Obama’s First Term” reveals that annual regulatory costs increased by more than $23.5 billion during President Obama’s fourth year in office. This brings Obama’s first-term total to nearly $70 billion, a staggering level that is likely unmatched by any Administration in the nation’s history. And despite a much-touted initiative to weed out unnecessary regulations, only two major rule changes reduced regulatory burdens in 2012. And, the report points out, there are many more rules to come, with an extraordinarily large number of regulations in the pipeline, including hundreds required under the Dodd–Frank financial regulation law and Obamacare.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369775846709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369776481199-86</Id><Title>Is The Communist Party USA Now Directing the Democrat Party?</Title><Msg>When you Look at their websites they mirror each other. Same agenda, same propaganda and same ideology.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369776481199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369776551078-87</Id><Topic><Title>Is The Communist Party USA Now Directing the Democrat Party?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369776481199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is hard to imagine just how abysmally stupid you really are.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1369776551078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369776939794-88</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The actual name Agent Orange came from the barrels that the Dioxyn was transported in. Ranchhand studies confirmed that the dioxin was poisonous no matter WHAT color the barrels. To put it another way...if Dioxyn which was sprayed to kill vegetation so that Vietcong could not sneak up on troops ...snd that vegetation died in 24 hours, it is STUPID to suppose it would not affect our own boys.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369776939794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369777751610-89</Id><Topic><Title>Is The Communist Party USA Now Directing the Democrat Party?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369776481199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Have you ever been able to address an issue or have you been zombie all your life? Question for you......which system has produced a higher standard of living.....socialism or capitalism?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369777751610</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369777915914-90</Id><Title>100.11 0.11(0.11%)</Title><Msg>That is all! 10011011011</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369777915914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369778000859-91</Id><Topic><Title>100.11 0.11(0.11%)</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369777915914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:51:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is twenty tuesdays a good roll let's ask President Obama</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369778000859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369778255553-92</Id><Title>Definitely the routers neeed CISCO-type updating</Title><Msg>either that, Yahooty or the net getting congested</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369778255553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369778644173-93</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fact: BA up 240 percent in 4+ years. Lies, damn lies, and statistics. You claim an MBA. Surely, you've heard that statement before.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1369778644173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369779002863-94</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's MeNerny does he have anything to \with BA' s stock price] oois he just fodder under Himler and the messerschmitt</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369779002863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369780361112-95</Id><Topic><Title>Is The Communist Party USA Now Directing the Democrat Party?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369776481199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a whole lot of difference between the two given who is heading up, who are the leaders of the democrat party today.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369780361112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369781561812-96</Id><Title>The fasiscts in the republicon party are evermore delusional</Title><Msg>by evidence of their inscere postings and rwnj rantings... day by day</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369781561812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369781615572-97</Id><Topic><Title>100.11 0.11(0.11%)</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369777915914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:51:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>que sera, sera</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369781615572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369781858863-98</Id><Topic><Title>100.11 0.11(0.11%)</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369777915914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:51:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ding splat splat . ding ding splat. ding ding splat ding ding from apricot hill the first night of the game</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369781858863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369782646280-99</Id><Topic><Title>100.11 0.11(0.11%)</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369777915914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:51:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>splat ?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369782646280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369782965202-100</Id><Topic><Title>100.11 0.11(0.11%)</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369777915914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:51:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding you guys better run for your lives...I yelled out as ran up apricot hill not to be found lest they beat the pulp outta ewe(s) two lefties and a whitey rightie-tightie 10011011011 ding splat splat . ding ding splat. ding ding splat ding ding</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369782965202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369782987335-101</Id><Title>And Now, For Today's Red State #$%$?? Moment</Title><Msg>An Oklahoma woman was arrested last week after police found that she'd used Facebook to try to sell her two children. Sallisaw native Misty Van Horn, 22, was taken to Sequoyah County Jail Wednesday night after police learned that she'd contacted a woman who lived 30 minutes away in Fort Smith, Ark., to offer her youngest child, a 10-month old girl. According to a police report, Van Horn contacted the Fort Smith woman by sending a Facebook message: "Just come to Sallisaw, it's only 30 minutes away and I'll give you all of her stuff and let y'all have her forever for $1,000." NewsOK reports that in addition to the $1,000 price tag laid on her infant daughter, Van Horn tried selling a package deal including her 2-year-old child for $4,000. Both children were taken into state custody. Police have reported that they believe Van Horn was attempting to sell her children so that she could accumulate the bond money to get her boyfriend out of jail. Now she's in jail, awaiting charges of attempting to traffic minors, and facing a $40,000 bond. Don't sell your kids, okay? They're not for sale.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369782987335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369783281280-102</Id><Topic><Title>Baggers WRONG Five Years in a Row</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369750053468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 10:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369783281280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369783349917-103</Id><Topic><Title>Is The Communist Party USA Now Directing the Democrat Party?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369776481199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if mommies NOT a commie- then you better turn her in</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369783349917</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369783561471-104</Id><Topic><Title>Is The Communist Party USA Now Directing the Democrat Party?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369776481199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And don't forget the organization dedicated to the preservation of wooden toilet seats - The Jack Ash Society.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369783561471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369784065405-105</Id><Title>Tesla in short squeeze and I called it this morning befor the stock market open, how did I know read here</Title><Msg>"Tesla Motors TSLA +13.65%, already one of the wildest stocks of the past month, leapt 6.1% in the last 40 minutes of trading Tuesday and ended the day up 14% at $110.33. That’s an all-time high, again. In fact, the move marked the first time the stock has ever crossed $100. Tesla had no real news to speak of Tuesday, but the company has essentially been involved in a heavy short squeeze over the past month. Stocks like that can often be volatile near the closing bell." Easy I can read a nas short selling chart it was obvious the medium high number of shorts would have to bail at a loss and I would make a fortune . If the BA trolls would learn to read a stock chart and short selling numbers over the past 2.5 months is was obvious. Now I am loading up on another short squeeze stock and am going to make a bundle on it too. All the gibberish about 787 flying or plane orders is just that . It is the 787 delay, 4 years , the over cost of 30 billion dollars and the grounding , not the battery fake fix , in a fire box! That fix is like sweeping dirt under the rug, that is more bad news from the shills at Boeing they have numerous avatar names and monitor the BA message board. Today they said I was at it again and what are they going to do about it, answer nothing , you cant this is not your personal message board get it yet ? . Guess what BA boys you have no game left, BA is simply not as good as TSLA . guess what if and when TSLA is done like apple I will be able to give the next big stock move , why ? Because I already know which group of stocks has been over shorted and this will be a repeat of TSLA and all your BA news will not matter. The stock picker always wins over the hype of stories and hope . Get it now ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369784065405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369784403994-106</Id><Title>If $4 per patient vists becomes $8 per patient visit</Title><Msg>howl long until I become even... -doc holliday, ok corral</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369784403994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:40:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369784646597-107</Id><Topic><Title>NO MONEY</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369603019556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does this ignoramus remark have anything to do with it?</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369784646597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369784799972-108</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla in short squeeze and I called it this morning befor the stock market open, how did I know read here</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369784065405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>plain and simple dumber but you cant beat the facts so you lose al the time to the stock picker "by domerrrrr45 • Feb 7, 2013 3:50 PM Flag Plain and simple...u bash boeing i will bash you take it to the bank actually domerrrr45 aka joe dokes 45, aka whistlefanms aka , a bunch of loser avatar names Wayne I take 18 % gain on my stock TSLA today to the bank since Friday and over 100% gain now in 3 weeks because I am not a troll like you har har har , domerrrrr45, today what do you take home for your bashing and computer set up thumbs down ? why nothing har har har Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369784799972</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369784813248-109</Id><Title>IRS REQUEST FOR INFO</Title><Msg>SIGNED BY MS LEARNER- SPECIFICS Ohio Liberty Council Corp 27-0326042 Additional Information Requested: 1. Please have a member of your board sign page 1 of Form 1024. 2. Please provide a hardcopy printout of your organization's website. 3. Does your organization promote or publicize itself using any internet social media such as Facebook? If so, please list the social media outlets and provide hardcopy printouts of those outlets. 4. You filed Form 1024 on June 30, 2010. Please provide an updated narrative description of activities since that time. In your description, please do not merely describe the purpose of the organization. Rather, describe the activities that your organization will initiate and/or participate in to fulfill your purpose. Your description should include the answers to the following basic questions: a. What does the activity entail? b. Who conducts the activity and what are their qualifications? c. Where is the activity conducted? d. When is the activity conducted? e. How significant is the activity in relation to your total activities as described as percentage of time and a percentage of expenses? f. Who may participate in the activity? g. How are the participants selected? h. Is there a fee for participation in the activity? If so, provide a fee schedule, i. How does the activity further your exempt purpose? 5. Please describe the associate group members and their role with your organization in further detail. a. How does your organization solicit members? b. What are the questions asked of potential members? c. What are the selection criteria for approval? d. Do you limit membership to other organizations exempt under section 501(c)(4) of the Code? e. Provide the name, employer identification number, and address of the organizations.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369784813248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369784951191-110</Id><Topic><Title>IRS REQUEST FOR INFO</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369784813248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>6. Provide the following information for all the public events conducted or planned to be conducted by your organization: a. The time, location, and content schedule of each event b. Identify and provide copies of handouts to the audience c. Identify workshop materials that instructors will use d. The names and credentials of the instructors e. If speeches or forums were or will be conducted at the event, provide detailed contents of the speeches or forums, names of the speakers or panels, and their credentials. If any speakers or panel members will be paid, provide the amount will be paid for each person. If not, please indicate they volunteered to conduct the event. Ohio Liberty Council Corp 27-0326042 f. The names of persons from your organization and the amount of time they will spend on the event. Indicate the name and amount of time they will spend on the event. Indicate the name and amount of compensation that will be paid to each person. If no one will be paid indicate this event will be conducted by volunteers to each person. g. Indicate the percentage of time and resources you will spend on these activities in relation to 100% of all your activities. 7. Have you conducted or will you conduct candidate forums or other events at which candidates running for public offices are invited to speak? If so, provide the following details and nature of the forum including-a. The names of candidates invited to participate b. The names of the candidates who did participate c. The issues that were discussed d. The time and location of the event e. Copies of all handouts provided and distributed at the forum, including any internet or advertising material discussed or used at the forum. f. Indicate the percentage of time and resources you have spent or will spend conducting these activities in relation to 100% of all your activities. 8. Have you attempted or will you attempt to influence the outcome of specific legislation? If so, provide the following: a. Provide copie</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369784951191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369784970364-111</Id><Topic><Title>Is The Communist Party USA Now Directing the Democrat Party?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369776481199</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:28:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like up your alley] hee haw never discard to a natural royal flush IAM</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369784970364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369785004357-112</Id><Topic><Title>NO MONEY</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369603019556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 17:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, porrdumbastad is correct and you are not, Billions to the banksters. Billions for prisons. Billions for bloated military contracts. You know every special interest group has its own grip. He took gay partners out of immigration bill and now the gays hate the president when before he was super man. The gun bums complain about anything, even the smallest thing such as smaller magazines, if gun legislation comes up. And of course there are the bigots like you and your friend Ryan who fear a black man in charge. So next time we have Rubio and Rand to pick from. Unless the Con's cheat they are getting an inch closer to the White House. But you and your Bohner loving buddies will keep blathering because we all know how important your opinions and your distortion of the facts are relevant to keeping the earthing spinning on its axis.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369785004357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369785032582-113</Id><Topic><Title>IRS REQUEST FOR INFO</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369784813248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8. Have you attempted or will you attempt to influence the outcome of specific legislation? If so, provide the following: a. Provide copies of all communications, pamphlets, advertisements, and other materials distributed by the organization regarding the legislation. b. Provide copies of any radio, television, or internet advertisements relating to your lobbying activities c. Please indicate the percentage of time and resources you have spent or will spend conducting these activities in relation to 100% of all your activities. 9. Do you directly or indirectly communicate with members of legislative bodies? If so, provide copies of the written communications and contents of other form of communications. Please include the percentage of time and resources you have spent or will spend conducting these activities in relation to 100% of all your activities. PLEASE DIRECT ALL CORRESPONDENCE REGARDING YOUR CASE TO: US Mail: Street Address for Delivery Service: Internal Revenue Service Internal Revenue Service Exempt Organizations Exempt Organizations P. O. Box 2508 550 Main St, Federal Bldg. Cincinnati, OH 45201 Cincinnati, OH 45202 Attn: Joseph R Herr Attn: Joseph R Herr Room 4514 Room 4514 Group 7821 Group 7821 +++ WHO ME ? I DID NOT LIE, YADA YADA YADA</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369785032582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369785434448-114</Id><Topic><Title>Study: Republicans are “the less credible party”</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1369774758131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The article referred to Michele Bachmann as the "queen of the liars". :-)</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369785434448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369785901318-115</Id><Title>Love Song from the film Zabriskie Point</Title><Msg>so we went there on day in the old caddillac with thew tape-deck playing the song one February</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369785901318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369786147619-116</Id><Title>I wuz thinking of joining the mormon Church in 2008</Title><Msg>anything but the RWNJ faux-evangenlicals when stumbled into the Obama camp/and his nurse wife</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369786147619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369786161931-117</Id><Topic><Title>State Department Served With Subpoenas Over Benghazi</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369774940811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a freakin worthless witch hunt powered by the birthers, the college transcript crowd, and now a friviolous war over a word. Just like Clinton and how he choose to use a cigar. There isn't enough doctors and medication in the World to treat all of you inbreed, scandal driven, paranoid schizophrenic socio-psychopaths who aren't happy unless they can make the others around them as unhappy as they are. SICK SICK SICK</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1369786161931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369786402778-118</Id><Topic><Title>This week, which stock is better? Tesla or Boeing ? premarket tsla is up 2.3% ready to ring the bell at $100</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369736577585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 06:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Given the strong performance of Elon Musk’s other publicly traded venture, SolarCity /quotes/zigman/13139813 /quotes/nls/scty SCTY -0.39%, Seeking Alpha’s O’Neil trader saw fit to summarize the activity by quoting Dan Zanger: “Never short a stock founded by Elon Musk.” – Tom Bemis reasonable advice Musk good Mcnerney bad simple as pie or Mcnerney is no Musk he did not found any company let alone 3 before he was 40 year old . Mcnerney was told to leave GE by Jack Welch after being passed over for the CEO job and was not very good at MMM and was hired by a emergency Chairman of the Board of Boeing who had zero airplane experience Lewis Platt . To supercharge the BA failure Boeign adapted the Md bankruptcy business plan . It is the transfer of Boeing know how from a self supporting engineering and parts building design internal team of company engineers to a outsourcing business plan . Its a do nothing company now inline with a communistic strategy. The theory or system of social organization based on the holding of all property in common, actual ownership being ascribed to the community as a whole or to the state. So Boeing owns nothing the contractors pay for their own design and Boeing still is responsible however for the failure of the contractors That part is still capitalistic way to go Boeing leadership you just destroyed a 100 year old company in 6 years time now just watch it die.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369786402778</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369786657993-119</Id><Title>it’s undeniable that racism lurks beneath so many of the preposterously false charges against Obama</Title><Msg>By E.J. Dionne, Jr. WASHINGTON—You wonder if President Obama sometimes finds himself singing a variant on Kermit the Frog’s anthem about the burdens of being green: It’s not easy being Barack Obama. This is not simply or even primarily a matter of color, although the president’s racial background has been a source of both opportunity and trial. As the first African-American in the White House, he has won an unprecedented level of support in the black community and the good will of enough white Americans to build a national majority. Yet it’s undeniable that racism lurks beneath so many of the preposterously false charges against him—that this son of Hawaii wasn’t really born in the United States, that he is a secret Muslim who “hates America,” that he’s animated by a “Kenyan, anti-colonial” worldview. Within the African-American community, his persistent emphasis on responsible fatherhood, a key theme of his recent commencement address at Morehouse College, is sometimes cast as a way of pandering to white prejudice by hectoring a community to which he owes a large and still unpaid political debt. That’s just the start of it. Even more peculiar is an ongoing confusion over how he thinks and what he stands for. Some of this is Obama’s own doing. He has been a master, as good politicians are, at presenting different sides of himself to different constituencies. In 2008, he was the man who would bring us together by overcoming the deep mistrust between red and blue America and the champion of progressive change, the liberal answer to Ronald Reagan. Advertisement Also like most successful politicians, Obama probably saw no contradiction between his two politically useful selves. Since so many of the red/blue divides are based on misunderstandings—as he said in 2004, blue state folks worship “an awesome God” while red staters care about their gay friends—getting past them would be easy enough. This, in turn, would open the way to a forward-looking approach to government. In 2012, he thought his re-election would “break the fever” on the right. No such luck. For Obama’s rise was accompanied by a hardening of opinion in the Republican Party fostered by a long-term defection of moderates from the GOP primary electorate, the growing influence of right-wing media in shaping the conservative conversation, and the rise of the tea party and its allies as the most dynamic forces on the right end of politics. This has the effect of tugging the political center, as perceived and presented by the media, to the right, further distorting how Obama is viewed. In fact, Obama is a tempered sort of progressive who repeatedly annoys his party’s left with an incessant pursuit of Republican support for “grand bargains”—one reason why his health care plan is so state-oriented and gives Republican governors and legislatures so much opportunity to undermine it. But none of this has helped Obama with his adversaries on the right. They take any news that comes along, notably the IRS’ special scrutiny of tea party applications for 501(c)(4) status, and weave it into a pre-existing tale of a power-hungry, ultra-leftist centralizer of authority. Perhaps the clearest look we’ve had at the real Obama was his national security speech last Thursday, an honestly agonized and intellectually serious appraisal of the difficulty of striking “the appropriate balance between our need for security and preserving those freedoms that make us who we are.” He left room for all his critics, left and right, to express dissatisfaction: He will pick up the pace of closing Guantanamo, but it will not close immediately; he’ll put restrictions on the use of drones, but won’t stop using them; he declared an end to the “global war on terror,” but pledged to “a series of persistent, targeted efforts to dismantle specific networks of violent extremists.” This last bit—an attempt to displace a sweeping and terribly flawed definition of the anti-terror struggle with a careful, practical but also less stirring depiction of the task ahead—is a window on the Obama conundrum. He’s an anti-ideological leader in an ideological age, a middle-of-the-road liberal skeptical of the demands placed on a movement leader, a politician often disdainful of the tasks that politics asks him to perform. He wants to invite the nation to reason together with him when nearly half the country thinks his premises and theirs are utterly at odds. Doing so is unlikely to get any easier. But being Barack Obama, he’ll keep trying.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369786657993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369786768033-120</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla in short squeeze and I called it this morning befor the stock market open, how did I know read here</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369784065405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow on a big stock market day way up day Boeing went from 100 dollars to 100 dollars and 11 cents such a wild and crazy ride. I hope all you Boeing stock holders did not get dizzy watching the paint dry on BA stock price! yawn, now how about my stock , How about that TSLA up 13% today 5 % Friday wow only the third best single day gain for that stock just a average gain for TSLA up 100% since May 3 just 15 days ago when I posted you should be in Tesla then it was 55 dollars so maybe pay attention now eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369786768033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369786930490-121</Id><Topic><Title>CEO of BA and the CEO of TSLA which is better ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369772198649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:16:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Elon founded 3 companies that all made huge money before he was 40 the CEO of Boeing got kicked out of GE by jack Welch which is the better CEO ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369786930490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369787183082-122</Id><Topic><Title>If $4 per patient vists becomes $8 per patient visit</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369784403994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:40:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>put your guns in your holster and reach for the sky one hair on the nicest woman in the world who gave me me birth</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369787183082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369787245433-123</Id><Topic><Title>If $4 per patient vists becomes $8 per patient visit</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369784403994</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:40:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blam</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369787245433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369787772962-124</Id><Title>Boeing, hows that outsourcing working for you now ?</Title><Msg>Boeing is run by an embarrassing, blood sucking, sit around and do nothing leadership who thinks that buying a bankrupt MD company and then following the same business plan will work. Transfer of made in America and engineered in America to the lowest possible bidder result is a is a 4 year late and 30 billion dollar excessive costly 787 plane . next after 7 stop delays to fix it over the 4 extra years the plane is grounded for another 3 month time period. . Failure from day one was predicted by a technical fellow at Boeing read Hart-Smith report on outsourcing. , this is the MD business plan that bankrupted MD and now has been as applied to the 787plane. During the 3 months Boeing leadership decied to take away allt eh weight saving of the lithium battery and put it in a heavy fire bos . So now Boeing shareholders have a experimental lithium battery on boar each 787 plane that weighs more than a proven nicad battery technology. How is that good management they had time to redesign and get approval of the NiCad battery but nope doubling down on failure . airbus changed from lithium to NiCad for their 787 beater smart that is why Airbus has been number one for 11 years and their stock is up 139% for 5 years while BA stock is up less than 22% now for 5 years since the Beoing shills keep talking long term growth then eat the truth BA is second to Airbus by a large margin. Now wait until the Airbus airplane is delivered on time and on budget and watch Airbus stock value pull away even more from Boeing while the 787 has more problems going forward</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369787772962</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369789111797-125</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DDT is estimated to have prevented over 500 million Malaria deaths until it was banned banned you idiot. Scientist J. Gordon Edwards ate DDT often to show it was safe for humans and lived to be 85 years old. Rachel Carson the ignorant fiction writer who helped get DDT banned died at age 54 and was responsible for the death of millions.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369789111797</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369789436870-126</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW it was the National Academy of Sciences that put the lives saved at 500 million. Stick is one of dumbest and most anti science persons on this board. He obvoiusly reads no peer reviewed science and is clueless.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369789436870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369789627896-127</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ali...do you have a link showing that Roundupo diosny has saved more lives than have been taken by using t Roundup and other spray used by Monsanto and Dow ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369789627896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369789852124-128</Id><Topic><Title>Back short Friday, more today, timing is now right</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1369746235792</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:03:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So far so good</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1369789852124</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369789935406-129</Id><Topic><Title>it’s undeniable that racism lurks beneath so many of the preposterously false charges against Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369786657993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:17:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What-ev-er...</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369789935406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369790305695-130</Id><Topic><Title>IRS REQUEST FOR INFO</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369784813248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please stick to finding out about Bofferding's leather jacket.</Msg><Username>jumboyjetski</Username><Timestamp>1369790305695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369790457799-131</Id><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Msg>This week President Obama's disapproval rating in the polls was higher than his approval rating. And some are already speculating that the Democrats' biggest obstacle to take over the House in 2014 is the President. Obviously those speculators are forgetting that polls show a much larger disapproval of Congress. And Americans, so say the polls, dislike the Republicans more than the Democrats. They also blame the GOP for the sequestration. These speculators must have forgotten the election results this past November, when Democrats gained seats in both the House and the Senate. [See a collection of political cartoons on Congress.] This is the president's second term. Historically, unless there is some big political Hail Mary event, Americans seem less enthusiastic about president's the second time around. It is pretty well known in Washington that the president wants a Democratic controlled House in the next election, making it easier for him to get legislation passed that he has promised the American people. Looking at the new face (literally) of the voting population (Hispanics, African-Americans and women), I don't think Democrats have anything or anyone in their way to take over the House in 2014. Now certainly the seats that are up for grabs are in very red Republican conservative territory, but the American people are clear: work together and get something done Congress or we'll vote you out. Another reason I see the Democrats being able to capture the 17 seats they need to have a majority in the House? The Republican Party. It's badly divided. It lacks leadership. And I'm not sure the GOP knows who they want to be when they grow up. [See a collection of political cartoons on the Republican Party.] And if you factor in two Republican governors, Chris Christie of New Jersey and Rick Scott of Florida, who were very outspoken against the president's Affordable Care Act, and who are now gladly embracing the Medicaid extension and happily taking the federal government's cash: This shows that the president's "agenda" thus far has been successful. Repeal and replace what? So the president is not in the Democrats' way. And I'm not worried about a few polls that show a dip in the president's approval rating. Because from where I sit, the road to a Democratic takeover of the House looks pretty clear right now.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369790691521-132</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republican Congress: approval ratings somewhere between 15% and 22%.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1369790691521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369790807979-133</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 x better than either/all bushco;'s and/or the ray-gun in my book plus Ava Gardner used her snake imho let me get bach to ewe</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369790807979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369791291602-134</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i know one with with very sharp claws should i alert it</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369791291602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369791445567-135</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some more of us blue dots in very, very red areas of a blue state are more conservative and saner than most RWNJ's/Faux News;ers</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369791445567</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:37:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369792545835-136</Id><Title>Bob Dole's Advice</Title><Msg>Bob Dole says he couldn’t make it as a Republican today...“Reagan wouldn’t have made it....“I think they ought to put a sign on the national committee doors that says ‘closed for repairs’ until New Year’s Day next year and spend that time going over ideas and positive agendas,” Dole said.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1369792545835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369792560955-137</Id><Title>several fellows from the other school</Title><Msg>how far could you kick the world history I's teachers head the history of the world] 25 words or less everyone needs some vitamin C to v\balance all the A;'s for Adenosine/Cystine wars(s)</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369792560955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369792582678-138</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Scientific America: The EPA considers glyphosate to have low toxicity when used at the recommended doses. “Risk estimates for glyphosate were well below the level of concern,” said EPA spokesman Dale Kemery. The EPA classifies glyphosate as a Group E chemical, which means there is strong evidence that it does not cause cancer in humans. In addition, the EPA and the U.S. Department of Agriculture both recognize POEA as an inert ingredient. Derived from animal fat, POEA is allowed in products certified organic by the USDA. The EPA has concluded that it is not dangerous to public health or the environment. ____________________ Do you have specific scientific evidence that glyphosate is responsible for human deaths? If you do I suggest that you inform the EPA as they have no such scientific evidence.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369792582678</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369793159786-139</Id><Title>Israel Warns Russia</Title><Msg>Israel warned Russia not to send missiles to the Hizbollah backed regime of Syria. Russia is not big enough to defy I srael. I srael will destroy any missiles Russia dares to send to the Syrian dictator.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369793159786</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369793643842-140</Id><Title>My options were West Germany or Alabama</Title><Msg>and you know what Lynrd Skynrd said about Alabama, the band... for security reasons put not you eye-lid but hers... reqacxh for thew sky</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369793643842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369793872624-141</Id><Topic><Title>Google "Monsanto" and "Evil"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369742540846</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A very rare day when you and I agree on something. My concern is not necessarily what they are doing, but that they can hide it from us all under the law.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1369793872624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:17:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369793968518-142</Id><Topic><Title>IRS REQUEST FOR INFO</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369784813248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As EVIL DWARF2 would say Shupe have some T-Bird.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369793968518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369794765502-143</Id><Topic><Title>My options were West Germany or Alabama</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369793643842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How e-did that work out... the eigher 2-3 times just for war-me up-ing of course they gave the me same general's suite in Berchtesgarden every time there mostly</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369794765502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369795814868-144</Id><Topic><Title>My options were West Germany or Alabama</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369793643842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>after and arduous but unremarkable week x 10 I was informed that i could subimitr papere where I want to go notwithstanding the foray to Amsteraam and Holland letalone Berchtesgarden to Salzburg people need to be free like Lyrnrd Skynrd not Alabama</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369795814868</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369796418737-145</Id><Topic><Title>My options were West Germany or Alabama</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369793643842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>submit paper to whom...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369796418737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369796725677-146</Id><Topic><Title>Bitten by a Turtle? There’s an Injury Code for that in Obamacare</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369775356819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:09:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what's your point? Why shouldn't they have a separate code for turtle bites? Since it likely happened in dirty water, it has some unique health implications.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369796725677</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369796997596-147</Id><Topic><Title>My options were West Germany or Alabama</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369793643842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:14:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>across three intenational borders no papers maybe i will be back and maybe i won't6 holland</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369796997596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369797559326-148</Id><Title>After Hours : 101.35 1.24 (1.24%) 4:42PM EDT</Title><Msg>e d t</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1369797559326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369797822850-149</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By then all of us conservatives will be sent to the IRS reeducation camps, but opps I forgot, we have guns so that won't happen - forget it.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1369797822850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369797987451-150</Id><Title>In the realm(s) of all possibilities</Title><Msg>a 'manned' lunar landing has NEVER happened all else is cover--up the jack-hammer is putting p\President Obamas visage next to Crazy Horse ...beep</Msg><Username>stupidrightwingbigot</Username><Timestamp>1369797987451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369798095737-151</Id><Topic><Title>Bob Dole's Advice</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1369792545835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:55:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The IRS made him say that, if he didn't they would send some new black panthers over to Dole's old crib,</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1369798095737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369798344370-152</Id><Title>Democrats Will Win the House in 2014 - it is foretold in the Scriptures</Title><Msg>b e-cause if hollywood is like high school and washington d.c. i like like hollywood except/but for ugly people then America still has a chance please pleasse please do not reply</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1369798344370</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369798430825-153</Id><Topic><Title>Love Song from the film Zabriskie Point</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369785901318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is Kowallski and Vanishing Point, white 440 Dodge, no Caddie. and Super Soul on the Mopar AM radio. But you might be there already</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1369798430825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369798800628-154</Id><Topic><Title>Love Song from the film Zabriskie Point</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1369785901318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more boraxo diggers and 20 mule teams coont dig all the pearls beneath the dead sea let abalone beneath death valley for that kind of nicenesses your kindness smells from here</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1369798800628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369798802268-155</Id><Title>Lerner said she said stop</Title><Msg>Lerner said no but the IRS continued agents targeting supporters of the Constitution and the Bill of Rights. Who would have that kind of clout?</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369798802268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>