<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360646515450-1</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suggest going to the speea site- thento communications then to spotlite then to archive then to spotlites 2001 and read the feb and march 2001 issues Here is from feb issue for starters As weeks go, the first week of February 2000 was rough. Our Negotiation Teams believed nothing more could be gained by talking with the Company. The "second offer" was on the table. The indications pointed toward rejection. Meanwhile, our polling indicated growing support for a strike. However, a majority of members were still unwilling to strike for "as long as it takes." Our AFL/CIO advisors said, "You're not ready to strike!" It was clearly time for a miracle to happen. It wasn't a miracle, but rather our connections through the International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers (IFPTE) whose leadership arranged for Richard Barnes (Director of the FMCS, our nation's top federal mediator) to fly to Seattle to facilitate a settlement. We made this very visible in our publications and in the local media. We were serious about taking one last shot at working out a solution. The role of a mediator is to work for "the deal," rather than to take sides. In our case, the mediator did an excellent job of pressing us to carefully examine our needs. He artfully induced us to pare our proposal down to only the absolute necessities demanded by our members. When, at the end, he walked into our meeting room and said; "Sometimes a strike just has to happen," we had the comfort of knowing we had given it our best effort. A strike by SPEEA-represented employees was not our first option. It was not our second option. But, by the time we called for members in the two Puget Sound bargaining units to walk off the job at 9 a.m. on February 9th, 2000, we realized it was our only option. ++++</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360646515450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 00:21:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360648300701-2</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Crickets", that's a hoot, good one . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360648300701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 00:51:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360649228048-3</Id><Title>FOR SPEEA STRIKE 2000 BACKGROUND</Title><Msg>GO TO speea org go to communications go to spotlites go to previous years go to 2001 feb and march issues have a reprise on anniversary of strike</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360649228048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 01:07:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360649349777-4</Id><Topic><Title>FOR SPEEA STRIKE 2000 BACKGROUND</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360649228048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 01:07:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>starts Celebrating Respect Anniversary honors history-making event At 9 a.m. on February 9th, thousands of SPEEA represented employees will glance at the clock and remember. Whether leaders at The Boeing Company admit it or not, they too will note the tick of the clock. The moment marks the one-year anniversary of the point in time when SPEEA "walked the talk." Few people, including Union leaders and members, had any idea of what lay ahead of that moment. The most optimistic of leaders hoped 90 percent of the dues paying union members would walk off the job, or about 9,000 workers. By the end of the day, estimates placed the number of striking Boeing engineers and technical workers at 19,000. SPEEA the Union, its leaders and members, instantly changed. Forty days later The Boeing Company came to the same realization. Along the way, the AFL-CIO, and labor unions around the country, realized white-collar labor had changed. The strike is behind us. But, the memory remains. Memories of hardship and sacrifice will not easily be forgotten. Other memories are good. A better contract resulted. Friendships were forged. Everyone gained respect, from others and for themselves. Never again can anyone say SPEEA members do not have what it takes. SPEEA members showed what they are made of by waging the largest white-collar strike in history against a corporation in the United States during the winter of 2000. It was a strike few people expected. Even fewer people expected SPEEA members to win. The members of SPEEA knew. They won the strike. And, they are not likely to forget.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360649349777</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 01:09:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360650162335-5</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I were invited, I would do it, and I don't like flying all that much.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360650162335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 01:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360656345582-6</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush would have taken them out also, but they couldn't find their but from a hole in the ground.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1360656345582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 03:05:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360656474546-7</Id><Topic><Title>Has anyone in the Obama administration served??????</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360633387786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:43:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nor Bush nor Cheney nor Rumsfeld nor.........</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1360656474546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 03:07:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360659079931-8</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't hear any of you clowns complaining when duhbya was killing tens of thousands of innocent Iraqis. Now did I chuckles?</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1360659079931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 03:51:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360661516356-9</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would anyone complain about something that never happened, loon ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360661516356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 04:31:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360664643374-10</Id><Title>Weak demand, not tax worries, keeps firms from hiring</Title><Msg>SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Tax and regulatory uncertainty, blamed in some quarters for keeping companies from hiring, has little to do with high U.S. unemployment, according to research by the San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank published Monday. The main reason that U.S. unemployment has remained high is likely because households hurt by the housing crash simply are not spending, according to the research, published in the latest issue of the San Francisco Fed's Economic Letter. U.S. unemployment stands at 7.9 percent more than three years after the end of the Great Recession. Focusing on the reasons businesses cite for not hiring, the study's two authors -- Atif Mian, a Princeton University professor who is currently a visiting scholar at the San Francisco Fed, and Amir Sufi, a professor at the University of Chicago Booth School of Business -- found no correlation between worries about regulation and taxes, and employment growth. "Employment collapsed precisely when businesses began worrying about poor sales," they said. By contrast, "there was almost no correlation between job growth in a state from 2008 to 2011 and the increase in the percentage of businesses citing regulation and taxes as their primary concern." Indeed, states where businesses increasingly cited regulation and tax worries actually had greater job growth than states without such intensifying concerns, though the correlation was not statistically significant, they said. Clashing views about the reasons for high U.S. unemployment have been at the heart of the debate over U.S. monetary policy, which has gone far into uncharted territory with interest rates held near zero for more than four years now and the purchase of $2.3 trillion in long-term assets to push borrowing costs down further. The Fed last month reiterated its pledge to keep rates ultra-low until the unemployment rate falls to 6.5 percent, as long as inflation does not exceed 2.5 percent. Some, including Richard Fisher, president of the Dallas Fed, argue that tax and regulatory uncertainty is the main reason businesses are not hiring, suggesting there is little that Federal Reserve monetary policy can do to induce hiring. The study from the San Francisco Fed bolsters the view that combating unemployment is primarily about boosting demand rather than about providing certainty on tax and regulations. (Reporting by Ann Saphir; Editing by Leslie Adler) ...</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1360664643374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 05:24:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360665895189-11</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post. That little hypocrite uses aliases to make it appear that he has like minded "friends" that shout down the opposition. Right out of "cyber warrior 101".</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1360665895189</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 05:44:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360669466770-12</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“One of the saddest lessons in history is this: If we’ve been bamboozled long enough, we tend to reject any evidence of the bamboozle. The bamboozle has captured us. Once you give a charlatan power over you, you almost never get it back.” —Carl Sagan</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360669466770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 06:44:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360670659030-13</Id><Title>CNN Asks: Should Dorner Be Killed With a Drone Strike?</Title><Msg>TYT Feb 12, 2013 CNN’s Erin Burnett asked whether or not law enforcement should use drones as they try to find former cop turned revenge killer, Christopher Dorner. Is this what it’s come to? Are drone attacks abroad so normalized that we can honestly ask if drones would be a good idea to use domestically? Cenk Uygur, Jimmy Dore (TYT Comedy) and Ben Mankiewicz (Turner Classic Movies) discuss Burnett’s question and its implications.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360670659030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:04:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360670744006-14</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's another problem that's GROWING</Msg><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1360670744006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:05:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360672302899-15</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>helpful info, thanks</Msg><Username>jonathangreen686</Username><Timestamp>1360672302899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:31:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360672343141-16</Id><Title>The GOPig civil war continues to intensify -- Anger at "Propagandist" Karl Rove and His "Repulsive" Political Group</Title><Msg>Oh, this is sweet: ============= The GOP civil war continues to intensify, with numerous prominent conservative media figures lashing out at Karl Rove in recent days over vehement disagreements about the direction of the party. This is far from the first incident pitting Rove against fellow right-wing media figures. In recent years, conservative media personalities -- many of whom work with Rove at Fox News -- have called Rove a "propagandist," "not a conservative," and an "effete sore loser" who heads an "absolutely repulsive" political group. The New York Times reported on February 2 that Rove, along with allies behind his Crossroads political groups, has decided to launch the Conservative Victory Project. According to the Times, the group will work to "recruit seasoned candidates and protect Senate incumbents from challenges by far-right conservatives and Tea Party enthusiasts." Following the news, Rove quickly became the target of conservative ire, with several media figures accusing him of betraying conservative principles and the Tea Party. The outcry was loud enough that Rove ran to Sean Hannity's Fox News program to do damage control, touting American Crossroads' huge investment in Sen. Marco Rubio (and a few other Tea Party favorites) as proof of his conservatism. Conservative anger at Rove has been simmering for years, intensifying in the past few months after Rove's Crossroads political groups squandered several hundred million dollars during the 2012 elections. The reaction to Rove's Conservative Victory Project from conservative pundits has been swift and harsh: Mike Huckabee Accuses Rove's "Absolutely Repulsive" Group Of "Fratricide." During an appearance on fellow Fox host Geraldo Rivera's radio show, Mike Huckabee responded to the formation of the Conservative Victory Project by labeling the concept "absolutely repulsive" and saying that "Karl needs to go through a metamorphosis." Huckabee accused Rove's group of "fratricide," and suggested the money his group is spending would be better used building up the Republican Party, rather than trying to destroy candidates that "you don't think is up to your country club level": RIVERA: Karl Rove says the Republican Party has to go through a metamorphosis, has to change. You know Bill Kristol says wait a second, the Tea Party's not so bad. Where do you stand? HUCKABEE: I think Karl needs to go through a metamorphosis. You know this idea that somehow a handful of Republicans are going to attack Republicans that the handful doesn't like? I find that repulsive. I find it absolutely repulsive. This is not how you build a strong Republican Party, is by going after the people in your party who are different than you are. This is fratricide. And if the Republican Party wants to render itself utterly, utterly irrelevant, the best way to do it is to become several little parties within the party, which is apparently what some folks seem to think we ought to do. When you marginalize the Tea Party, marginalize the pro-life and pro-family part of the party, you lose every election coming up in the future. You lose every election. There may be a few local elections that you might win in some places outside the base of the party, but you're not going to win a national election again. [...] HUCKABEE: If you're going to spend millions of dollars, spend it to build up your Republican, the one you like, not millions to destroy a Republican that you don't think is up to your country club level. I find that just horrendous. [Cumulus Radio Networks, Geraldo, 2/8/13, via Media Matters] Mark Levin: Rove A "Propagandist" Who Is "Despised By The Grassroots." Radio host and frequent Fox News guest Mark Levin has repeatedly leveled criticism at Rove in recent days. In a Facebook post, Levin accused Rove of having "flat out lied" about Rep. Steve King (R-IA), whom the Conservative Victory Project reportedly doesn't support as a possible future Senate candidate. On the February 7 edition of his radio show, Levin labeled Rove a "propagandist" who wields a "stupid little third-grade whiteboard." According to Levin, both Rove and the Conservative Victory Project "are poison in conservative and Republican circles in many respects." Taunting Rove, Levin also urged him to "bring it on, Doughboy." [Media Matters, 2/9/13] Fox Contributor Erick Erickson Suggests Any Candidate Rove Group Supports "Should Be Targeted For Destruction." Responding to the formation of the Conservative Victory Project, in a post on his RedState blog, newly-minted Fox News contributor Erick Erickson mocked Crossroads for spending "hundreds of millions of rich donors' money and had jack to show for it" during the 2012 election cycle. Erickson suggested that the conservative movement should oppose any candidates supported by the new Rove group: American Crossroads is creating a new Super PAC to crush conservatives, destroy the tea party, and put a bunch of squishes in Republican leadership positions. Thank God they are behind this. In 2012, they spent hundreds of millions of rich donors' money and had jack to show for it. It is interesting though. The people who brought us No Child Left Behind, Medicare Part D, TARP, the GM bailout, Harriet Miers, etc., etc., etc. are really hacked off that people have been rejecting them. In 2012, about the only successful Republican candidates were the ones who directly rejected the legacy of these people. So now they will up their game. They don't like being shut out. They blame the tea party and conservatives for their failure to win primaries. They'll now try to match conservatives and, in the process, call themselves conservatives. I dare say any candidate who gets this group's support should be targeted for destruction by the conservative movement. They've made it really easy not to figure out who the terrible candidates will be in 2014. [RedState, 2/4/12]</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:32:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360672549839-17</Id><Title>Donald Trump Mocks "Total Loser" Rove</Title><Msg>Fox Regular Donald Trump Mocks "Total Loser" Rove. In a series of posts on Twitter, frequent Fox News guest and celebrity reality show host Donald Trump pondered why anyone would donate to "total loser" Rove and his new group after Crossroads "just wasted $400M":</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672549839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:35:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360673159161-18</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Advancement for The Boeing Company **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>jerome.lefthand</Username><Timestamp>1360671708331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very well done</Msg><Username>lyle.devos</Username><Timestamp>1360673159161</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:45:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360673185717-19</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please keep eating the Monsanto Genetically modified food and keep drinking the Flouridated water.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360673185717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360673617573-20</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't complain about Obama killing innocent Iraqis so I've been consistent. Bush didn't grant himself a licence to kill American's without due process as Obama has. You, Genna, Hooz and alias Bush haters were screaming impeachment and send him to the Hague for 3 water boardings that required a medical team present but now your fine with bloody murder of hundreds of innocent Pakistanis, including dozens of kids, as long as it's Emperor Obama doing all the killing. Why is killing OK now? Why aren't you screaming for Obama's impeachment or sending him to the Hague? Obama is clearly worse than Bush as Obama wants to target Americans for death too. .</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360673617573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:53:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360673647579-21</Id><Title>Timber - U.N. to move against batteries like the ones on Boeing 787</Title><Msg>Game over for Boeing. Now everyone is dumping lithiumion aircraft batteries and BA is left holding the bag. It now could take over a year for BA to figure out how to replace lithiumion aircraft batteries and by that time BA stock will be in the high 20's. A U.N. agency that sets global aviation safety standards is moving to prevent aircraft batteries like the one that caught fire on a Boeing 787 last month from being shipped as cargo on passenger planes, people familiar with the effort said.</Msg><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1360673647579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:54:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360673875382-22</Id><Topic><Title>Timber - U.N. to move against batteries like the ones on Boeing 787</Title><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1360673647579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:54:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One would think this news will hit BA stock hard today. But of greater concern - travelers across the world will not want to fly on any aircraft that has lithiumion batteries. No way is anyone going to take the chance, especially on medium to long distance flights. When the United Nations bans somethings - its the death knell for the item in question. So long BA batteries and hello $40 BA stock.</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1360673875382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:57:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360673944300-23</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks!</Msg><Username>sakariasberggren</Username><Timestamp>1360673944300</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:59:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360675104882-24</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very helpful info, thank you</Msg><Username>aronholmberg</Username><Timestamp>1360675104882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:18:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360675731993-25</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Advancement for The Boeing Company **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>jerome.lefthand</Username><Timestamp>1360671708331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who else is?</Msg><Username>adammichael126</Username><Timestamp>1360675731993</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:28:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360675740153-26</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great info, thank youu</Msg><Username>juliuspetersson</Username><Timestamp>1360675740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360676534433-27</Id><Title>We go ex dividend tomorrow...not much selling today !</Title><Msg>I think the dividend is 48 cents..</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360676534433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:42:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360676549679-28</Id><Topic><Title>Timber - U.N. to move against batteries like the ones on Boeing 787</Title><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1360673647579</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:54:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U.N. ??! The only movement they ever made was a big bowl movement. A totally worthless organization that scams money off of the free world economies.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360676549679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:42:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360677057402-29</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Advancement for The Boeing Company **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>jerome.lefthand</Username><Timestamp>1360671708331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they all go up huge</Msg><Username>navarrojohn968</Username><Timestamp>1360677057402</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:50:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360678010148-30</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Advancement for The Boeing Company **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>jerome.lefthand</Username><Timestamp>1360671708331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>andresmccoy369</Username><Timestamp>1360678010148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 09:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360678455426-31</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spart...You have no credibility...go take your meds.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360678455426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 09:14:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360679753814-32</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Advancement for The Boeing Company **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>jerome.lefthand</Username><Timestamp>1360671708331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I too am checking them out. I hope he is as amazing as I have witnessed in the past two months.</Msg><Username>grady.devos</Username><Timestamp>1360679753814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 09:35:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360680846522-33</Id><Title>So no news on how to fix 787 and BA shareholders think thats good?</Title><Msg>The silence on Boeing side regarding all the problems of the Dreamliner is deafening. It also shows the company has no clue on how to correct electrical problems, make the 787 safe or get it to pass FAA safety guidelines. In other words Boeing is sticking their head in the sand and hoping investors do walk or possibly run away.</Msg><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360680846522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 09:54:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360681101664-34</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go to sleep you IDIOT!</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1360681101664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 09:58:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360681355557-35</Id><Title>BA stock could crash after State of Union speech</Title><Msg>Because Tea Party Republicans will not be clapping when Obama says the sequestration threat should be extended. No the Tea Party Republicans are now saying let the sequestration cuts kick in and save the country from going over the fiscal cliff. BA about to test major lows.</Msg><Username>hold4triple</Username><Timestamp>1360681355557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:02:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360682002242-36</Id><Topic><Title>Fantastic Advancement for The Boeing Company **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>jerome.lefthand</Username><Timestamp>1360671708331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:21:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checking it out currently.</Msg><Username>velasquezdallas</Username><Timestamp>1360682002242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:13:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360682200828-37</Id><Topic><Title>When will the plastic planes fly again?</Title><Username>cramerblows_a_s_s</Username><Timestamp>1360640527470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:42:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Batteries too.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360682200828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:16:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360683117408-38</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're saying that millions of pounds of 'dumb bombs' and dozens of cruise missiles caused NO collateral damage, dopey?</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1360683117408</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:31:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360683184924-39</Id><Title>lithium battery problems</Title><Msg>Lets have a discussion about the 787 electrical system for some fun and be suggestive/ constructive with the conversations. My personal thought would be to install isolation transformers in the electrical system to allow onboard computers to communicate (talk) with each other as required to charge/ discharge the batteries. However, it is possible that these various onboard systems are not only talking to each other but are also seeing each other during their functions. The isolation transformers would not allow the d.c. power systems to see any other external/internal electrical system activity onboard the aircraft other than the battery system itself therefore eliminating any possible outside interference that could be causing the malfunctions with the battery computerized charging/dicharging system and causing the thermal meltdown.</Msg><Username>pioneer32920</Username><Timestamp>1360683184924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:33:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360683198339-40</Id><Topic><Title>So no news on how to fix 787 and BA shareholders think thats good?</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360680846522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 09:54:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They latest news is that these batteries won't even be allowed to be carried as cargo on planes. They are too dangerous. That doesn't sound to good.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1360683198339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:33:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360683297899-41</Id><Title>4 More Years</Title><Msg>of whiney wannabe teabaggers/rubes crying about Obama. Priceless!</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1360683297899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360683343091-42</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spoken like a true facist.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1360683343091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:35:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360683452147-43</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, leftys are very twisted and creepy people.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1360683452147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:37:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360683542941-44</Id><Topic><Title>The Graham Cracker</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360619537346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- "" I'd get out of town and watch from as far away as possible the bloodist civil war the world has ever known "" why do you say that Paul ?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360683542941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:39:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684072970-45</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of these ultra-righties start to salivate when there's any chance of a splendid little war. They want to bomb anyone who disses them back to the stone age. War is the first answer they come up with to any international "situation." The type was rampant in the early years of the Vietnam war, when you didn't dare question the use of, oh, say napalm or agent orange. Collateral damage to them is simply the othjer side asking for it. They are only anti-war when they use it to wail and whine to make some political point. It's like how they are now calling the Sequester the "Obama sequester," after Cantor and Ryan were strutting and crowing about it and #$%$ said he got 98 percent of what he wanted.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360684072970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:47:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360684198695-46</Id><Title>Gun Lobby Is Terrified of California</Title><Msg>Why the Gun Lobby Is Terrified of California —By Josh Harkinson California would ban the sale of all semiautomatic rifles that accept removable magazines, slap a hefty tax on ammo, and require every gun owner to take a yearly safety course under a new package of firearms laws that would give the Golden State the nation's strongest gun controls. These and many other proposed firearms laws were announced late last week by leading state Democrats and the mayors of San Francisco and Los Angeles. Many of the laws are expected to pass, in part because the Democratic Party in California now controls the governor's mansion and a supermajority in the Legislature. "As it is with many issues, California is out front on firearms regulations," said Mark Hedlund, a spokesman for California Senate President Pro Tem Darrell Steinberg. "We don't represent the NRA. We don't think that the NRA represents the majority of Californians, by a long shot." California's newly proposed gun laws would: Ban the possession of ammunition magazines that hold more than 10 rounds Prevent the future sale, purchase, manufacture, importation, or transfer of any firearms that can accept detachable magazines Close the "bullet button" loophole by banning tools that allow the quick changing of gun magazines Regulate ammunition sales like the state regulates gun sales. Ammunition dealers would need to be licensed and anyone buying from them would need to obtain a permit and complete a background check. Create a 5 cent tax on each bullet purchased, for the purpose of funding crime prevention Prevent felons and other adults barred from gun ownership from living in a house that contains any guns Prohibit the loaning or sale of a firearm between people who know each other personally Take steps to phase out legal possession of assault weapons that were purchased before California outlawed their sale Require all firearms owners to take an hours-long gun safety course every year, similar to what the state now requires for obtaining a concealed-weapon permit Require gun owners to purchase insurance to cover damage they may inflict Require CalPERS and CalSTRS, two of the nation's largest pension funds, to divest from companies that make, sell, or market firearms or ammunition California has already enacted some of the nation's strictest gun control laws, partly due to its experience with a Sandy Hook-style massacre: In 1989, a mentally unstable ex-con opened fire with an AK-47-style assault rifle on an elementary school playground in Stockton, killing five schoolchildren and wounding 28 others. The shooting contributed to the passage that year of California's assault weapons ban. Somewhat uniquely, California's state constitution doesn't guarantee the right to bear arms. The Golden State gives its cities the option of refusing to issue concealed-carry permits and doesn't recognize permits issued by other states. It requires the reporting of all handgun sales, and it cross-checks the data against the names of convicted criminals and violent mental patients. And unlike most states, it requires background checks for firearms purchases between private parties, closing a loophole that accounts for 80 percent of gun acquisitions made with intent to carry out a crime. Since the passage of California's strict gun rules, the incidence of mass shootings has plummeted. "California used to be the mass-shooting capital of the country, but instead of throwing up their hands, they addressed the problem head-on and are reaping the benefits," says Julie Piotrowski, a spokeswoman for the Violence Policy Center, a pro-gun-control group. "Their success will most certainly inspire action in other states and at the federal level." If enacted, the new laws might do for guns what California's pollution and fuel economy rules did for the nation's automobiles. In 2011 alone, Californians bought 600,000 firearms; only Texas sports more registered weapons. "The gun industry has a love/hate relationship with California," Hedlund says. "They hate our gun regulations because they are among the toughest in the country, but they love our marketplace." Not to mention how the state essentially does their marketing. No matter what, the weapons industry can rest assured that there will be no shortage of guns in Clint Eastwood flicks.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360684198695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:49:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684232824-47</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Lobby Is Terrified of California</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360684198695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:49:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Draconian !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360684232824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:50:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684474370-48</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360597143838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While moving top management to Chicago may have been a good signal for investors (they like hearing that company decisions will be made with no legacy loyalties) it was also a great way to encourage a disconnect between program managers and top decision makers. That would have been fine if lines of communication were open. But I've heard many accounts that suggest a real problem in communicating bad news upward. T</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360684474370</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:54:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684622642-49</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another classic reminder about jumbooooobjetsky.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1360684622642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:57:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684624930-50</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Spartapus gets all his best stuff from others. If it's not Alex Jones or Wing Nut Diaries then it's Jesse Ventura. In the case of "crickets," I believe it was first used here by gerbilfood4me. I liked it so well I've used it several times. I would not expect someone who uses "dumbo" in their screen name to grasp or remember that. Excuse me. I meant jumbo.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360684624930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:57:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684672195-51</Id><Topic><Title>It's Nice To See Left Wing Fanatics Supporting Obama's Mass Murder</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360633350830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 20:42:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can freedom be at risk when you own firearms?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360684672195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:57:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684785509-52</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, the Pope threw the towel in for the good of the Church. Pelosi and Reid should do the same....</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1360684785509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:59:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684876223-53</Id><Topic><Title>The GOPig civil war continues to intensify -- Anger at "Propagandist" Karl Rove and His "Repulsive" Political Group</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America is a very sick country. Our leaders have no vision and many that have visionary goals are actively working to destroy our culture. It's much like the USSR under Gorbachev. Obama may wind up like Gorbachev. Loved by the international elite, but hated in his own country. Or maybe he may be disliked by everyone, if things play out badly for the international econony. Let's hope the republicans can come up with a worthy leader because the Dems are hopeless.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1360684876223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:01:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684952901-54</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Bandar Bush have anything to do with the Kenyan birth certificate?</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1360684952901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:02:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360684967652-55</Id><Topic><Title>So no news on how to fix 787 and BA shareholders think thats good?</Title><Username>spectrumplay</Username><Timestamp>1360680846522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 09:54:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that the Boeing Co. simply isn't quite as eager to shoot off its mouth as a lot of half-backed specualtors who post here. Sometimes it's best to hold the tongue until there is something to say.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360684967652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:02:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360685068282-56</Id><Topic><Title>Former German Parliamentarian Exposes West’s Alliance with al-Q aeda</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360623954021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 18:05:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The worst thing that could happen to ANY sort of truth is that Spartapus would start to talk it up on the Boeing Board. I'm only guessing because I have never seen it happen.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360685068282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:04:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360685118639-57</Id><Title>The GOP Plan to Flush Your State’s Economy Down the Toilet</Title><Msg>By Lynn Stuart Parramore The new “red-state model” seeks to turn your state into Mississippi. The GOP has plans for a comeback. But it may cost you a lot. The idea is to capitalize on recent Republican state takeovers to conduct an austerity experiment known as the new “red-state model” and prove that faulty policies can be turned into gold. There will be smoke. There will be mirrors. And there will be a lot of ordinary people suffering needlessly in the wake of this ideological train wreck. We already have a red-state model, and it’s called Mississippi. Or Texas. Or any number of states characterized by low public investment, worker abuse, environmental degradation, educational backwardness, high rates of unwanted pregnancy, poor health, and so on. Now the GOP is determined to bring that horrible model to the rest of America. In Kansas, the Wall Street Journal reports that Governor Sam Brownback is aiming to up his profile “by turning Kansas into what he calls Exhibit A for how sharp cuts in taxes and government spending can generate jobs, wean residents off public aid and spur economic growth.” In remarks quoted in the same article, Brownback announced that "My focus is to create a red-state model that allows the Republican ticket to say, 'See, we've got a different way, and it works.’ " Brownback’s economic inspiration is Reagan-era supply-side economist Arthur Laffer and the folks at Americans for Prosperity, the conservative outfit backed by the deep coffers of the Koch brothers. This new austerity talk focused on “fiscal innovations” is emboldening Republicans in other states that have been gerrymandered into submission to the GOP, including Indiana, Louisiana, Nebraska, Ohio, Oklahoma, and alas, my home state of North Carolina. Republications have been eyeing the Tar Heel state with interest due to its recent swing status in presidential elections. The state was also the target of a gerrymandering strategy that worked out wonderfully for the Republicans, but not so well for democracy. Sam Wang, the founder of the Princeton Election Consortium, wrote recently in the New York Times about how Republican redistricting thwarted Democratic voters: "Although gerrymandering is usually thought of as a bipartisan offense, the rather asymmetrical results may surprise you....I have developed approaches to detect such shenanigans by looking only at election returns. To see how the sleuthing works, start with the naïve standard that the party that wins more than half the votes should get at least half the seats. In November, five states failed to clear even this low bar: Arizona, Michigan, North Carolina, Pennsylvania and Wisconsin. ... In North Carolina, where the two-party House vote was 51 percent Democratic, 49 percent Republican, the average simulated delegation was seven Democrats and six Republicans. The actual outcome? Four Democrats, nine Republicans — a split that occurred in less than 1 percent of simulations. If districts were drawn fairly, this lopsided discrepancy would hardly ever occur." The lesson of North Carolina tells you that the GOP red-state model is based, first and foremost, on efforts to flagrantly disregard the will of the people. NC’s discount-store mogul Art Pope, a longtime GOP donor and champion of free-market fundamentalism, has been appointed state budget director by the new Republican governor, Pat McCrory. In an incredible display of money buying political influence, Pope has gone well beyond his donor-counterparts in other states. Instead of just funding the politicians he wants, he has gone for direct rule by occupying government himself. Tax repeal is the centerpiece of his announced plans, but his hatred of public investment means he has much more than that in store for one of the most progressive states in the South. Pope is said to be more powerful than the governor, giving rise to the term “Pope administration” to describe the new political reality.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1360685118639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:05:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360685221428-58</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't understand how anyone can look at Pelosi and not see a crazy person. Leftys have a very different view of the world.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1360685221428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:07:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360685283054-59</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spart should change couch psycho's. Terrorists like OBL declare war on the West, attack the West, build out their infrastructure, training camps etc., and the whacko comes up with a conspiracy theory. He needs institutionalized. He sounds like in real life he is Obama's pastor, Rev. Wright. The "White guy" caused 9-11 !! The White Guy had Black children killed!! Sparts new name should be the Right Reverand.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360685283054</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:08:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360685943830-60</Id><Title>Boeing Wants to be Number 1</Title><Msg>Boeing wants to be the worlds largest aerospace company. Its wants to grow revenue, maintain strong financials - that is measured by stock price growth in order to increase R &amp; D, hire more workers, improve salaries for all its employees and sell better improved aircraft. Who wishes to stand in the way of these goals besides Airbus?</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1360685943830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:19:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360686787635-61</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appears long ago you were bamboozled. Somebody sold you some spiked homegrown, and you never recovered from it.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360686787635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:33:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360687026364-62</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you or this</Msg><Username>zacharybarrett774</Username><Timestamp>1360687026364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:37:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360687278568-63</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Wants to be Number 1</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1360685943830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:19:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing's worst enemy is itself.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1360687278568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:41:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360687326618-64</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Wants to be Number 1</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1360685943830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:19:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grow, grow, grow and ...explode.</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1360687326618</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:42:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360687628904-65</Id><Topic><Title>The GOPig civil war continues to intensify -- Anger at "Propagandist" Karl Rove and His "Repulsive" Political Group</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Let's hope the republicans can come up with a worthy leader because the Dems are hopeless." Given the clown car that showed up for the GOP presidential nomination your comment is beyond pathetically stupid.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1360687628904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:47:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360687881182-66</Id><Topic><Title>lithium battery problems</Title><Username>pioneer32920</Username><Timestamp>1360683184924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 10:33:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You looks like to be a genius.</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1360687881182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:51:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360687956809-67</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flying for what?</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1360687956809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:52:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360688081426-68</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you like to bet on that?</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360688081426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:54:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360688939698-69</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360597143838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They replaced approx 100 to 150 batteries per a press release so far. Let's say it's 125 batteries, That's an average of a battery replacement every 800 hours on the existing fleet of 50 or every 16 hours per plane including the 2 "bad" ones which is "regular" maintaince. That come's to 1.6% of these batteries failing during this time frame.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360688939698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 12:08:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360688982021-70</Id><Topic><Title>Thought of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360595834520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:17:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chicago does not need a Federal gun law. All they need to do is pass a city ordinance prohibiting guns in public inside the city limits, and then enforce it. As many have already posted, the problem is often not lack of laws, but lack of enforcement of existing laws.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360688982021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 12:09:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360689899287-71</Id><Topic><Title>The GOPig civil war continues to intensify -- Anger at "Propagandist" Karl Rove and His "Repulsive" Political Group</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The culture of divide, racism, economic oversight that is totally destructive to he economy, all the foundation of the democrat party, and it is purvasive now amongst many communities. Decent folks isolate themselves from that degenerative culture thus the gated communities.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360689899287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 12:24:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360690090135-72</Id><Topic><Title>The GOPig civil war continues to intensify -- Anger at "Propagandist" Karl Rove and His "Repulsive" Political Group</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clown car? Romney embarrass you with his high sense of morality?...embarrass you that he was so successful in business?...embarrass you that he gave a vast fortune away to those in need? And that is a clown car? You libs are lower than stench. " A diamond, in a snakes #$%$, would appear as the brightest star in the heavens above"...to you liberals.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360690090135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 12:28:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360690263500-73</Id><Title>They should just let the issue ride until one crashes into the Pacific !</Title><Msg>Just let the Dreamliner fly until one comes down over the pacific. It is not when but if. There are so many issue with the plane it will take dead floating bodies to wake up the Boeing zombies.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360690263500</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 12:31:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360690946872-74</Id><Topic><Title>The GOPig civil war continues to intensify -- Anger at "Propagandist" Karl Rove and His "Repulsive" Political Group</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney was the least clownish, at least until he cut off his own staff's credit cards before they even got back to their hotel, or made his pathetically stupid (and wrong) 47% comment, or said (through his son) afterward he really didn't want the job. And he was the CLASS of that pack. Bachmann is nuts (and an embarrassment to non-stupid, sane Americans), Herman Cain could not name key countries where we are at war, Gingrich is smart but a (moral) hypocrite who can't keep his focus on Earth, and Santourum wants to bring back the inquisition along with thinking getting a college education is "snobbish". Perry would have to triple his IQ just to remember the three....uhhh....things he feels so strongly about. CLOWN Car, and that is being kind.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1360690946872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 12:42:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360692367955-75</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Wants to be Number 1</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1360685943830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 11:19:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aerospace and Defense represent big bucks. Everyone wants a larger piece of that action. One way to get a larger piece is to force a competitor to grow smaller, by taking business that would have been his, or by figuring a way to discredit him in such a way as it does not reflect back on you.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1360692367955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:06:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360692640695-76</Id><Topic><Title>The GOPig civil war continues to intensify -- Anger at "Propagandist" Karl Rove and His "Repulsive" Political Group</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"GOPig" you have the intellectual capacity of a 4 year old</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1360692640695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:10:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360693210915-77</Id><Topic><Title>We go ex dividend tomorrow...not much selling today !</Title><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1360676534433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 08:42:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a 4 cent jump over last quarter. Not sure if it will be that much..</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1360693210915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:20:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360693690435-78</Id><Topic><Title>They should just let the issue ride until one crashes into the Pacific !</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360690263500</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 12:31:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just giving it the green light would resolve all issues. If one crashes you have a problem.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360693690435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:28:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360693769570-79</Id><Topic><Title>The GOPig civil war continues to intensify -- Anger at "Propagandist" Karl Rove and His "Repulsive" Political Group</Title><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1360672343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 07:32:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hang this little -unt, Rove and charge $5 a throw. All proceeds goes to ridding America of the stench Party, GOP. Yahoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo</Msg><Username>artsbest</Username><Timestamp>1360693769570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:29:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360693922597-80</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner will not fly for untlil 2014 at best</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1360581668811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 06:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your mama was obviously "scratching" while your daddy was pile driving her. A real botched abortion resulted...............you. Yahooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo</Msg><Username>artsbest</Username><Timestamp>1360693922597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:32:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360694138608-81</Id><Topic><Title>FOR SPEEA STRIKE 2000 BACKGROUND</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360649228048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 01:07:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>40 days of SPEEA - Part I Wed, Feb. 9 The largest strike by white-collar workers in history starts at 9 a.m. when more than 19,000 engineers and technical workers at Boeing facilities in Washington, Oregon, California, Utah and Florida walk off the job. Members of the IAM applaud in support as the workers walk out. More than 10,000 strikers in Washington State assemble at Renton Memorial Stadium for a kickoff rally. Union leaders from around the region join SPEEA in their call for "respect" from Boeing leaders. Executive Director Charles Bofferding tells The Seattle Times "We will stun the Company with our strike. We will stun the Company with our strength." Nearly 5,000 non-dues paying employees who are represented by SPEEA join Union members in the walkout. Thurs, Feb. 10 SPEEA strikers weather their first full-day on the picket line. Union leaders adjust sites after realizing no pickets were scheduled for Boeing's corporate headquarters. Bob Gorman, Washington State director of the AFL-CIO said other unions would honor the picket lines. UPS refuses to deliver packages across SPEEA lines. The price of Boeing stock on the New York Stock Exchange falls $2 a share in reaction to the strike. SPEEA member Tom McCarty starts work on the first "environmentally friendly" burn barrel. Fri, Feb. 11 Boeing officials say the strike will have no affect on the Company's ability to deliver or service airplanes. Meanwhile, a Quantas Airlines 747 sits on the runway in Bangkok as SPEEA members on the service team return home. The Federal Aviation Administration temporally suspends Boeing's ability to certify aircraft. Democratic presidential candidate Bill Bradley stops at the picket site outside Boeing Corporate headquarters. Sat, Feb. 12 Six members of SPEEA at Cape Canaveral in Florida settle into a schedule of picketing the Cape's main gate for shift changes. Sun, Feb. 13 Atlas Airlines confirms that Boeing has missed delivery of a $177 million 747-cargo airplane. While Boeing denies the delay, a spokesperson for the airline tells the Associated Press "It's because of the strike." In Everett, about 1,000 striking workers gather under clear skies for an afternoon rally. Mon, Feb. 14 The Boeing Company admits that the process for delivering airplanes has "slowed." The FAA confirms that Boeing is seeking to hire replacement engineers to help certify aircraft for delivery. Boeing stock continues to slide, losing another $1.68 in value. In honor of Valentines Day, SPEEA members bring spouses to the picket lines as part of "Bring your Sweetheart to the line." Tues, Feb. 15 Boeing CEO Phil Condit holds an afternoon press conference to say the Company is willing to weather a long strike. He says employees are losing $3.4 million a day in lost wages. Harry Stonecipher is quoted in the press as saying "I've been demonized." The Company admits it is now six airplanes behind in deliveries. At an impromptu rally outside the press conference, SPEEA announces publicly it wants a vote on Agency Fee.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360694138608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:35:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360694435633-82</Id><Topic><Title>The Graham Cracker</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360619537346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheney used all 9 deferments to avoid Nam. Then he produced a carpet licker. Bush snorted coke and drank himself half to death before daddy bailed him out. He then flew kites. And the GOP supports these losers? Yep. Losers in losers out.</Msg><Username>artsbest</Username><Timestamp>1360694435633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:40:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360694688816-83</Id><Topic><Title>Unstable or stable? Sell or buy? Latest report here</Title><Username>alexander.sinclair</Username><Timestamp>1360571772890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 03:36:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, that was helpful</Msg><Username>jamesmccarthy396</Username><Timestamp>1360694688816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360694796598-84</Id><Title>It Doesn't Matter - We Still Love Obama</Title><Msg>Yes, we know he lied when he said a $260 Billion deficit was a failure in leadership and unpatriotic, then has had nothing but $ trillion plus deficits every year of his presidency. It doesn’t matter, we still love Obama. Yes, we know Obama lied about all kinds of things to get Obamacare passed, like it would lower your insurance premiums and that if you like your doctor you can keep your doctor. Doesn’t matter we still love Obama. Yes, we know Obama doled out billions of tax payer’s money as payoffs for campaign donations. Doesn’t matter, we still love Obama. Yes, we know he took a bad economic situation and made it worse. Doesn’t matter, we still love Obama. Yes, we know his drone strikes on American citizens are hypocritical after criticizing Bush for waterboarding. Doesn’t matter we still love Obama. Yes, we know there are fewer people with jobs today than had jobs when he first took office. Doesn’t matter we still love Obama. Yes, we know more people are on food stamps today than ever in our history. Doesn’t matter we still love Obama. Yes, we know unemployment for Black people is at 15%. Doesn’t matter we still love Obama. Yes, we know a record number of people are now drawing disability income because they had lost hope of ever finding a job. Doesn’t matter we still love Obama. Yes, we know Obama loathes our military and wants to defund it as munch as possible. Doesn’t matter we still love Obama. Yes we know Americans have lost a lot of the freedom we hold dear under Obama things, like the patriot act, choice of medical care, EPA regulations, rules and regulations limiting private sector businesses. Doesn’t matter we still love Obama. Yes, it’s true he lied about not raising tax on the middle class. Doesn’t matter, we still love Obama. Yes it’s true, we don’t know of anything good he has actually done for the country but it doesn’t matter we still love Obama.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360694796598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:46:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360696010114-85</Id><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Msg>in WSJ "...The 787 is the first passenger jet to rely heavily on lithium-ion batteries. Boeing 787 chief engineer Mike Sinnett said last month the company chose lithium-ion "because it has the right chemistry" to discharge a large amount of power to start the auxiliary power unit in the tail of the jet or even its engines "and then allow us to recharge that battery in a relatively short period of time.".. One would think as Chief engineer he knows what he is talking about. Possibly in some sort of emergency it MIGHT start A main engine - but I doubt it ! Of course, this is the same guy who told SPEEA that he(Boeing) had lots of qualified Engineers in Calif and other places who could replace the SPEEA types, including the DER's which is absolutely untrue... Also a refugee from MDC and Military Seattle - Boeing - YOU HAVE A PROBLEM</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360696293204-86</Id><Topic><Title>The Graham Cracker</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1360619537346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:52:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And afterwards, they all ended up lobbying for the Institute for Incorrigible Douchebaggery, headed by The Donald.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1360696293204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:11:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360697038381-87</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mike Sinnett came up through BCA he is not from MDC. He was one of the original group of senior managers on the 787 and was the only one, in my opinion, who was on the ball (and he is the only survivor from that group). The batteries can be used to start one of the engines in an emergency during flight. Silnnett did not make the SPEEA replacement statement, Delaney did.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1360697038381</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:23:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360697625575-88</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt they would try to restart an engine that shut down either by itself or manually by the pilot, But if that were the case, the other engine should be generating enough power to accomplish the task. There are reduncies to protect any situations like that.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360697625575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:33:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360697630570-89</Id><Title>Lithium-ion Batteries Possible Terrorist Weapon</Title><Msg>If these batteries are so sensitive and can cause "dendrites" to form what would happen if a terrorist throws a hand full of sand or squirts so toothpaste in one of them? Especially since they seem to be in the rear galley.</Msg><Username>instantkarma22</Username><Timestamp>1360697630570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:33:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360698029429-90</Id><Title>California cop killer</Title><Msg>You following this man hunt on the news? Before the left could characerize the killer as a RWNJ, a message was found from the guy stating his love for Obama, other leftwingers, the lefts desire for gun control, and the ban on assault weapons, the police depts. racism, and other leftwing nutjob #$%$.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360698246117-91</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please don't confuse Don when is intent on showing how lazy and sloppy he is. Don loves to hear himself pontificate, he doesn't care whether reality gets in the way.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1360698246117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:44:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360698260035-92</Id><Topic><Title>Lithium-ion Batteries Possible Terrorist Weapon</Title><Username>instantkarma22</Username><Timestamp>1360697630570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:33:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're in the cargo area below the floor. Can't be reached by anyone in flight.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360698260035</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:44:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360698790266-93</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok I'll stand corrected - ist mistake this milllenium ! Here is where the confusion comes from boeing site 2010 The newly appointed leaders and their technical areas of responsibility are: Boeing Commercial Airplanes Mike Delaney -- Airplane Performance &amp; Product Architecture. Delaney was vice president, chief project engineer for the 787 program. Keith Leverkuhn -- Propulsion Systems. Leverkuhn was vice present/general manager of Propulsion Systems for Boeing Commercial Airplanes. Jim Ogonowski -- Airplane Structures. Ogonowski was director, chief structures engineer for the 787 program. Mike Sinnett -- Airplane Systems. Sinnett was vice president, systems chief engineer for the 787 program. As part of their new assignments, Delaney, Ogonowski and Sinnett will continue to focus on the 787 program, which is currently the most important engineering challenge for Boeing Commercial Airplanes.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360698790266</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:53:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360699018374-94</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't there a Lockheed Tristar (about 20 years ago) over the Caribbean that started losing oil pressure in each engine because maintenance had not installed "o-rings" on plugs. Crew shut down the first engine at first indication of a problem. Then the second and finally third engine failed as the plane was returning to Miami and the passengers were being prepared to ditch at sea when the crew restarted the first engine and was able to limp to the airport.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360699018374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:56:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360699418416-95</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing solves battery problem! Hires Energizer Bunny!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360359667150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 16:41:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me thinks the animal rights group PETA will protest and stop bunny exploitation! I think Boeing now is really up a creek and needs to go back to the drawing boards!</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1360699418416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:03:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360699497109-96</Id><Topic><Title>Did our strike in 2000 end up getting us a better offer?</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1360608791229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 13:53:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to the top</Msg><Username>zevach</Username><Timestamp>1360699497109</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:04:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360699639119-97</Id><Title>The NTSB is looking into the possibility that Boeing cut corners &amp; lied to FAA</Title><Msg>and now claims everything was just a simple misunderstanding. Notice how quiet BA is over the past five, six weeks. Hell even the CEO ain't said squat regarding the grounding the 787. We now have a "smoking gun" with these major battery problems, which will soon lead to other problems of shoddy workmanship, hiding faulty data from FAA and putting the flying public at risk. Things sure smell bad for Boeing, but as usual the company thinks it can bribe those in Washington DC and possibly within the FAA and as usual get away with murder.</Msg><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360699639119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:07:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360700633011-98</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360597143838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100,000 hours for the 50 plane fleet is "on average" about 2000 hours per plane. 125 replaced batteries for the 50 plane fleet is 2.5 batteries per plane. 2000 divided by 2.5 is 800 hours per plane, not the 16 number. Still a very bad number though.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1360700633011</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:23:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360700731740-99</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360597143838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They replaced approx 100 to 150 batteries per a press release so far. Let's say it's 125 batteries, That's an average of a battery replacement every 800 hours on the existing fleet of 50 or every 16 hours per plane including the 2 "bad" ones which is "regular" maintaince. That come's to 1.6% of these batteries failing during this time frame. more than one is 10 million flight hours then cbx!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360700731740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:25:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360700807085-100</Id><Title>The Drealiner will be lucky to be back in the year by 2014 at best</Title><Msg>The plane is all messed up and the implementation and name is trash.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360700807085</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:26:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360700929450-101</Id><Title>Need to change the name of the Dreamliner as nobody will fly it !</Title><Msg>It needs a new name and number. How about Deathliner 666?</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360700929450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360701008327-102</Id><Topic><Title>It Doesn't Matter - We Still Love Obama</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360694796598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:46:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we know the country is going to heeelll in a hand basket but it doesn't matter, we love Obama.</Msg><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360701008327</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:30:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360701116435-103</Id><Topic><Title>Need to change the name of the Dreamliner as nobody will fly it !</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1360700929450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:28:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Explain why morons like you continue to post BS like that? They should handcuff you and put you in an asylum to protect normal human life!</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1360701116435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:31:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360702131823-104</Id><Topic><Title>BA closes above 77</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1360586931008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 07:48:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may be right. "State of the Union addresses don’t usually get a big rise out of the market, even if they’ve been up the next day in 12 of the past 16 years." http://blogs.wsj.com/marketbeat/2013/02/12/stocks-and-the-state-of-the-union/?mod=MarketsMain You should go all in. Bet it all.</Msg><Username>liam_stanton_investor</Username><Timestamp>1360702131823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:48:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360702137330-105</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okey Joedokey. We understand that you believe all Democrats are terrorist killers.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360702137330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360702523588-106</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB challenges Boeing estimates of 787 battery safety</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1360597143838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 10:39:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My mistake, was not trying to mislead anyone, Your correct the 800 hour is per plane, good thing I'm not a safety inspector, I do believe I have the 1.6% failure rate correct (2/125=.016),</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360702523588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:55:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360703821556-107</Id><Title>California cop killer = RWNJ and registered Republican</Title><Msg>Just what you might expect from these right wing looonatiks</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360703821556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:17:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360704948191-108</Id><Topic><Title>The NTSB is looking into the possibility that Boeing cut corners &amp; lied to FAA</Title><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1360699639119</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 15:07:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Literally!</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1360704948191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:35:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360705286981-109</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this nut job Dorner is a gun nujtob and therefore a bonafide RWNJ- and he will soon wind up in the hottest circle of hell - guess who he will find there- all the RWNJ's who have gone on before him</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360705286981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:41:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360705481014-110</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually mr hope4 your minus 70 IQ says it all- its you and your kind that are responsible for most of the violent crime in this country</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360705481014</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:44:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360705671347-111</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Hate America so Much?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360704612729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you don't know anymore about freedom than your own a s.;s mr minus 70 IQ The liberals of this country have given us everything that's worthwhile - the RWNJs are responsible for all the evil in this country</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360705671347</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:47:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360705874934-112</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer = RWNJ and registered Republican</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360703821556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:17:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like his soulmate Tim McVeigh who killed 270 people in Oklahoma City</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360705874934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:51:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360706548734-113</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Hate America so Much?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360704612729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you reading from your manifesto again?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360706548734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:02:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360706671330-114</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you still working on your manifesto or is it finished?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1360706671330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:04:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360706827475-115</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Hate America so Much?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360704612729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmmmmmmmmm I though I sounded a lot like hope4white people and that he needed a little something to balance his hate propaganda- so why not emulate him - from the other side of course</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360706827475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360706914454-116</Id><Topic><Title>Why does the bigoted NeoCon hope4whitepeople Hate Americans so Much?</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1360706840445</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>corrrectooooo</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360706914454</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:08:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360706967379-117</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHAHA Told ya so. The whackos still call this Dorner a RWNJ even though he has confessed he's a leftist whackjob. The facts still get distorted by the commie pinkos.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360706967379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360707214547-118</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Hate America so Much?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360704612729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a GREAT question! That's like asking how big the Universe is!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360707214547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:13:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360707296679-119</Id><Topic><Title>Post of the Day</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360620626852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:10:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are part of the problem! a big part.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1360707296679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:14:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360709719838-120</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>San Fran Nan and Prince Harry should resign right now for the good of our country....The are not leaders, they are deal makers hinging on greed for themselves.</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1360709719838</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360710024933-121</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you didn't know what Party #$%$ Pelozi belonged to, you'd know after listening to that wierd broad in a heartbeat. She acts like she's on drugs. She fits the liberal profile to perfection.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360710024933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:00:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360710323062-122</Id><Topic><Title>An Ex- COP is the California COP killer !</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1360707783991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:23:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both are con-men, flip a coin. I prefer to follow this Dorner story. Sounds like a good James Bond movie. He bought scuba gear at a sporting goods store. He tried to steal a guy's boat, and told the guy he could get it back in Mexico, but the bow rope got tangled up in the prop, and the boat stalled out. The cops surrounded a cabin where he held hostages, and he excapes. The guy is just as slippery as Obama is, but in the end both will get caught. Both exemplify the saying, "crime does not pay."</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360710323062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:05:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360710340001-123</Id><Topic><Title>Pelosi and Ist AMENDMENT</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360618896124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 16:41:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep up the good work and please keep campaigning. It worked wonders for you last time and you keep reminding me of the phrase "President Obama."</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1360710340001</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:05:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360711269116-124</Id><Topic><Title>Why does the bigoted NeoCon hope4whitepeople Hate Americans so Much?</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1360706840445</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very good.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1360711269116</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:21:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360712870578-125</Id><Topic><Title>Why does the bigoted NeoCon hope4whitepeople Hate Americans so Much?</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1360706840445</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh look, Pauline is bleeding and bleating again during this time of month! If I may suggest Pauline - I wish you to read "White Girl Bleed a Lot: The Return of Race Riots to America." Maybe then, you will be able to come out of denial and throw away your Anti-American "explainations"! "When Colin Flaherty set out to write a book about an explosion of racial violence in this country over the last two years, he was often met with two reactions: Denial. Or explanations. “Often at the same time,” Flaherty said. “The same people who denied it in one breathe, explained it in another. Strange. That’s why I wrote the book. There are hundreds of cases of racial crime and violence in more than 50 cities in the last two years, and no one is talking about it.”</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1360712870578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:47:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360713395260-126</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Hit Another Home Run</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360706873242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't recall many "pitchers" or "catchers" hitting many homeruns Pecker. Would you please enlighten us as to whether your W_O_N is the pitcher or the catcher and exactly how many home runs he has accrued? As far as I know, he is just a switch hitter!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1360713395260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 18:56:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360713758894-127</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike all other Boeing commercial aircraft the APU and Engines are started by starter-generators. Not pnumatic air. The APU can supply electric for the engine restart, or an engine and cross power to restart an engine.Example the B767 has one external power plug for use on the ground, the B777 has two but still uses pnuematics starting system. The B787 has three external plugs. Most of the systems that use to be pnuematic or hyd are now electric. Including anti-ice, brakes, pacs to name a few. Last, batteries are a time change item and I've never changed a nicad for any other reason except time and they too are able to have thermal runaway..</Msg><Username>try2try</Username><Timestamp>1360713758894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:02:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360714479889-128</Id><Title>What you WILL see and what You WON'T See at tonites Sate of the Union address</Title><Msg>What you will see: Division, not Unity, wrapped in a facade of “Coming together to make tough choices.” You will see (with all of the drama, pomp &amp; circumstance of a televised awards ceremony) the president, his minions, and all of his supposed adversaries or “Faux Foes” gathered together and surrounded by lobbyists, power brokers, and invitees of the Obama administration. Flanked by American political royalty and sure to be in awe of the opportunity to attend this event, these invitees are not there merely because of their unique stories. They are there to punctuate the president’s agenda. In other words, they are there to be used as “Flesh Props.” While the nation is now getting over the nightmare of the Sandy Hook saga and the community of Newtown tries to heal, the State of the Union Address will be used to appeal to the emotional side of people’s conciousness, once again ripping open the scabs &amp; scars of the last 4 of the most sensationally covered mass shooting incidents in the U.S. You will see the guests of no fewer than 23 members of the U.S. House of Representatives, there to provide a backdrop of faces for the cameras of all major television networks to focus in on while wars of aggression proceed to kill millions overseas…for nothing more than profit. With the skills of a highly-trained orator, Obama will employ the cadence and intonation of John F. Kennedy and Martin Luther King to implore the American people to identify Second Amendment rights as the newest threat to their safety. All the while, you will notice the president’s tilting of the head, dramatic pauses, and slow blinking designed to put the population at ease, connoting confidence with the reassuring calmness that a population yearns for from a strong, protective, and compassionate leader’s speech. Intelligent, critically-thinking viewers such as listeners of The Alex Jones Show and Infowarriors will surely see through this mass psy-op. However, at the first ping of an emotional response, all viewers should ask themselves, “Why? Why are we obsessing over responsible citizens’ rights to own firearms (and gift them to family if desired) while the our military might claims the lives of innocents daily? Why are good Americans being on this issue while childhood and adult health disorders have massively increased in a very short time? Why are the fruits of our labors being systematically stolen by international banksters with full approval by government &amp; Congress, leaving average Americans to scramble for survival?” What you won’t see: • You will see absolutely zero criticism of Big Pharmaceutical companies and their peddling of psycho-active drugs such as SSRI drugs which are found to be an integral component of nearly every mass-shooting. Instead, they may suggest more drugs, phrased as, “Better funding for mental health.” • You will hear not one word of criticism of the Motion Picture Industry’s love affair with violence and overt glorification of shoot-outs &amp; death. • You will certainly not hear any concern over that fact that we’re basically training kids, with increasingly stunning virtual reality games, how to most efficiently shoot up a mass of people. • You will not hear any meaningful dialogue citing the overwhelming proof of lower violent crime rates in areas where citizens’ rights to keep &amp; bear arms are upheld. Remember: They will try to divide us upon every minor fissure, crack &amp; fault line in society. Anything that might be perceived as a difference between you and your neighbor or anyone else will be exploited. No one can deny that there’s a police state build-up across the nation… Without the Second Amendment, we will soon lose the rest of the Constitution. By then it may be too late.. The citizenry will have given up any means of effective resistance.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360714479889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:14:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360714487742-129</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Hit Another Home Run</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360706873242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1st off no one with any commonsense will listen to Obama tonite. Secondly, the word will get around that he wasted time talking, and lying about the need for gun control, and that will spur more gun, and ammo sales if that is even possible. His latest leftist lie is "we don't have a spending problem in WA. We have a tax revenue problem." Which validates my point that Obama thinks the Hoozes are stupid.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360714487742</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:14:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360714891828-130</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And this would matter to you why?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360714891828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:21:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360714928809-131</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are too stupid to realise that 9-11 was used to get us into the Middle East...that trillions were collected by the Carlysle Group, the Bin Ladin Group (that Bush did business with) and Halliburton (that Cheney did business with) that "fighting Terrorism" was used to take your rights you deserve the America you've gotten...just this month they are voting on taking your guns...you think thats NOT conencted to 9-11....instead of AlQaeda ..now the enemies are returning veterans and guys with John Deere hats......half the Constitution is gone...you had BETTER wake up....beacuse they ARE coming for the second half of the constitution and will probably do a false flag to do it....just like Fast and Furious was a False Flag...just like the Gulf of Tonkin was a False Flag...its coming...if you are the face of the NeoConservative movement ...I repudiate it.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360714928809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:22:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360715016457-132</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What awaits him wherever doesn't have anything to do with what political persuasion he is. I fear you guys are making EACH OTHER nuts. JMO.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360715016457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:23:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360715239544-133</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty, how do you have time to post here while you milk your organically fed cow and whip up your own peanut butter from your chemical-free peanuts?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1360715239544</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:27:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360715681054-134</Id><Topic><Title>California cop killer</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360698029429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:40:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What should await you is the reality....the gun Doner used didn't have anything to do with the accuracy that it was used to kill someone. It wasn't the gun. There are plenty of gun laws on the books, and people will always have access to guns in the USA. Identify the kookis that use them. You should know all about kooks being that's the folks you support.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360715681054</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:34:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360715915490-135</Id><Title>.Batteries for 787 Can’t Be Shipped on Passenger Planes</Title><Msg>The subject of this note indicates every airport the 787 flies into will need to have replacement batteries on hand or nearby, unless someone is willing to utilize a freighter plane to deliver them (or they would have to deliver them via ground transportation from the nearest source). This likely would not support the need for a quick swap-out of the batteries that could occur in service or as maintance at all the airports that will use the 787. .</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360715915490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:38:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360716476787-136</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Hit Another Home Run</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360706873242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is the worst thing to happen since the Great Depression! Just signed an impeachment petition of the President from Conservative Action Alerts!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360716476787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:47:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360717101633-137</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Hit Another Home Run</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360706873242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama just signed an agreement with Canadian Oil to sell America's drilling rights in the Gulf of Mexico to CNOOC Ltd of China. American Union Workers working for Gulf Oil in the Gulf of Mexico are befuddled by this President's actions.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360717101633</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 19:58:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360717832673-138</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Hit Another Home Run</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360706873242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like somebody passed around a petition at the Klan meeting. Wonder if it was in crayon.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1360717832673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:10:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360717956198-139</Id><Topic><Title>How many lies will Obama tell tonight?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717362518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:02:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how many words/minute can he read ? divide by two</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360717956198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:12:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360719041503-140</Id><Topic><Title>How many lies will Obama tell tonight?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717362518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:02:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No need to divide at all!</Msg><Username>angusomy</Username><Timestamp>1360719041503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:30:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360719092442-141</Id><Topic><Title>How many lies will Obama tell tonight?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717362518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:02:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easier to keep track of the truths that he will tell. You can sleep through it, and have the right answer.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360719092442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:31:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360719305371-142</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obama promise to Cut Spending.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360717643850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:07:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's already said they have cut all the spending they need to cut. I kid you not. No more need for spenidng cuts. Obama has already accomplished the task on the need for spending cuts. Now Obama wants to make "investments" in America.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360719305371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:35:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360719483845-143</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, yes they would and are designed to do just that. Short of a fire shutdown, why wouldn't want to restart? Guess you could just pull over and wait for triple A instead.</Msg><Username>try2try</Username><Timestamp>1360719483845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:38:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360719632665-144</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eastern Airlines flight 885 and yes.</Msg><Username>try2try</Username><Timestamp>1360719632665</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:40:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360719684706-145</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Will Hit Another Home Run</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360706873242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 17:07:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a eerie feeling that a lot of gullible people wearing custom hoodies and dancing to rap music are going to appreciate the president's speech tonight.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360719684706</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:41:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360720142290-146</Id><Topic><Title>It Doesn't Matter - We Still Love Obama</Title><Username>dipydem</Username><Timestamp>1360694796598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 13:46:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't that be hilarious if just as many democrats end up in Fema Camps as republicans while Obama is president?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360720142290</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:49:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360720568991-147</Id><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Msg>You probably know me as the writer of such songs as "Yesterday", "Eleanor Rigby", "Penny Lane", and "Let It Be". But tonight, I urge you to watch Barack Obama's State of the Union address and stand behind your president. He represents your country so well and you are most fortunate to have him as your leader. You are truly blessed, so enjoy the experience.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360721073174-148</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Evil...not just regular run of the Mill Evil...we're talkin 7th ring of hell evil</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360721073174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:04:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360721749826-149</Id><Title>Quiz For Gun Condrool Liberals:</Title><Msg>What was Dorner's magazine capacity, hmmm 'tards? "Shooting suspect Christopher Dorner, the subject of a week-long manhunt, has not emerged from a cabin destroyed by fire late this afternoon, according to The Associated Press. Police believe the disgruntled ex-LAPD officer barricaded himself in the mountain home after a deadly shootout with officers earlier Tuesday. A single gunshot was heard from inside the cabin just before the fire broke out about 4:30 p.m. PT, a law enforcement source who requested anonymity told the AP. Fox News and CBS News are both reporting that Dorner has died inside the charred cabin. Officials were waiting for the fire to burn out before approaching the ruins to search for a body, the AP reported." Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360721749826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:15:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360722160288-150</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He most certainly came from MDC. He is from Long Beach.</Msg><Username>whole_latte_love</Username><Timestamp>1360722160288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:22:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360722323594-151</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He said such nice things about you...</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360722323594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:25:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360722720108-152</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you supposed to be watching your fearless leader on the boob tube right now ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360722720108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:32:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360722788892-153</Id><Title>Fort Hood Hero Says President Obama 'Betrayed' Her, Other Victims</Title><Msg>From ABC News: Three years after the White House arranged a hero's welcome at the State of the Union address for the Fort Hood police sergeant and her partner who stopped the deadly shooting there, Kimberly Munley says President Obama broke the promise he made to her that the victims would be well taken care of. "Betrayed is a good word," former Sgt. Munley told ABC News in a tearful interview to be broadcast tonight on "World News with Diane Sawyer" and "Nightline." "Not to the least little bit have the victims been taken care of," she said. "In fact they've been neglected." Obama fanatics with multiple aliases love being misled by Obam and being useful idiots but others have to learn the hard way like I did that Obama is all image and no substance, a suit with a line of BS and nothing more. Unless cronyism is involved Obama doesn't care and has no interest.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360722788892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:33:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360722838511-154</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Hate America so Much?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1360704612729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:30:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a theory about that. I believe it's because liberal females have very little sex with their husbands. And husbands in return have learned to take their anguish out against America. I think I'm really really close on this one! "Ladies, you're not preforming your duties! Now do what you promised your husband you would do when you repeated those sacred words at the alter!"</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360722838511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:33:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360722984685-155</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Close but no cigar, (unless he is going by his middle initial now).. ST. LOUIS, Dec. 3 /PRNewswire/ -- McDonnell Douglas (NYSE: MD) today announced the appointment of three executives to new management positions. James M. Sinnett, 54, has been promoted to senior vice president of the New Aircraft and Missile Products (NAMP) unit of McDonnell Douglas Aerospace</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1360722984685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:36:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360722988790-156</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am. S.P. McCartney</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360722988790</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:36:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360723113433-157</Id><Topic><Title>Fort Hood Hero Says President Obama 'Betrayed' Her, Other Victims</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360722788892</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:33:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a dangerous manipulative man! He shows as much sympathy as I do when I'm flushing something that used to belong to me down the toilet.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1360723113433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:38:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360723337021-158</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG Bamboozle: 9-11 and the War on Terror !!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360638084183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 22:01:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He probably has 5,000# of leftover stuff from his own personal Y2K stash.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1360723337021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:42:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360723528315-159</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps James is Mikes Father ??? James M. Sinnett, retired vice president of Phantom Works Strategic Development, now part of the Boeing Company in St. Louis, was the 2001 Leadership Award recipient. Sinnett was cited for his contributions to the enhancement of aircraft survivability through leading the development of next-generation survivability technologies within the Boeing Company and throughout the military aircraft industry as a whole. Nothing wrong with a bit of Nepotism - MDC blood runs deep as do their FUBAR management methods -</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360723528315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:45:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360723642182-160</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you notice the ruckus at the SOTU just now? Mr. Nugent just dumped in his pants and got escorted out by the Secret Service, who wore hazmat disposal gloves.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1360723642182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:47:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360723897986-161</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps dJumbo should be watching. Minimum wage is the current topic, which will help you.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1360723897986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:51:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360724214440-162</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lmao!</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1360724214440</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:56:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360724720541-163</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, you are left, and always wrong</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1360724720541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:05:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360724880765-164</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Denny's Grand Slam with sausage or bacon?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360724880765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:08:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725039881-165</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jumbot just threw his beer through the tv. President was talking about (black) people waiting in line 5 hours to vote. The idea of black people voting infuriates some folks . . . .</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1360725039881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:10:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725064992-166</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The fact is that we have no way of knowing if the person who we think we are is at the core of our being. Are you a decent girl with the potential to someday become and evil monster, or are you an evil monster that thinks it's a decent girl?" "Wouldn't I know which one I was?" "Good God, no. The lies we tell other people are nothing to the lies we tell ourselves.” ― Derek Landy, Death Bringer</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360725064992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:11:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725225238-167</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a liar's liar and that's what makes him Hooz's idol. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1360725225238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:13:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360725335901-168</Id><Title>Dorner Too Fried To Fly Ever Again</Title><Msg>Fried to a crackly crunch.</Msg><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1360725335901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:15:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725383018-169</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sammy "shakedown", you are a perfect example of actual racism . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360725383018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:16:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725421988-170</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You want some peace and understanding So everybody can be free I know that we can get together We can make it, stick with me Its coming up" Me, 1980 ...but now talking about President Obama</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360725421988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:17:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725460812-171</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1360720568991</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 20:56:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps Jumbo makes more money than you ever will . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360725460812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:17:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725506394-172</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure, create more jobs oblama…. by shipping all big companoes overseas? sure, combat inflation...by printing trillions more in dollars through the Fed sure, stay in Afganistan to defeat AlQeada....and then arm tAlQaeda and the Muslim Brotherhood in Libya and Syria....... Wake up people....its the Matrix and you are hearing magnificant lies.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1360725506394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:18:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725566171-173</Id><Topic><Title>Quiz For Gun Condrool Liberals:</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360721749826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:15:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I'm waiting, numb nuts . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360725566171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:19:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360725964676-174</Id><Topic><Title>I Was Right... A Grand Slam</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1360723435690</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:43:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take your meds, whackjob. The Matrix is a movie, not reality, not that you have a clue what the difference is.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1360725964676</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:26:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360726012074-175</Id><Title>Sorry jUmB00</Title><Msg>You are right. You make more than I do. Even BEFORE they raise your minimum wage. s/ Sammy, happily retired. Now don't forget to pay your taxes, and resist that temptation to call in sick tomorrow. It won't help you at all.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1360726012074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360726139695-176</Id><Topic><Title>Post of the Day</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1360620626852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-11 17:10:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would prefer that he lied to you, like dims do ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360726139695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:28:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360726143245-177</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry jUmB00</Title><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1360726012074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:26:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do not pick on poor jumbosca*ski. It is not fair to take advantage of his intellect. Just be thankful for your own lot in life and don't laugh at others.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1360726143245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:29:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360726587772-178</Id><Topic><Title>787 CHIEF ENGINEER BLOVIATES</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1360696010114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 14:06:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mike Sinnett Employment History: Employment History Chief Project Engineer The Dreamliner Vice President and 787 Systems Chief Engineer The Boeing Company Senior Chief Engineer Airplane Systems for Boeing Commercial Airplanes Prior to that he held first and second level management positions on the 777 program. He may have had non-management postions early in his career at other locations but all of his management experience has been with BCA.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1360726587772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:36:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360726926926-179</Id><Topic><Title>Sorry jUmB00</Title><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1360726012074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:26:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike your case, "they", "they" meaning your surrogate parents the government, don't have a single thing to say about my wages . I am not a government dependant . I am an independent, self supporting, self sufficient real American in the best American tradition . Look up "rugged individualism" on the net and you will see my picture right there next to Teddy Rooosevelt's . I'm the better looking one with the hot young chicks on my arm . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360726926926</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 22:42:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360731097581-180</Id><Topic><Title>Quiz For Gun Condrool Liberals:</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360721749826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 21:15:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jumbodoba.s;s are you trying to tell us that a single shot Kentucky rifle is as deadly as a belt fed MG-42 or something- you certainly sound stoooopid enough</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1360731097581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 23:51:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>