<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371275172372-1</Id><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Msg>lets see, A350 on schedule, and much less then half the cost build. Wasn't even off the drawing board when the 787 had the roll out bash. What else, how about an 8% seat mile cost advantage over the 787, 25% over the 777. Quieter. And a strange thing, remember when the 787 first flight, and those wings were bent up so much? There is something wrong there. Anyhow the A350 wings didn't do that and they are similar wings, similar aspect ratios.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371275880124-2</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Airbus has the safe NiCad battery no need for a fire box. the airbus will eat away both the 787 and the 777 market share and the Boeing 747 is not selling as planed , the A380 is cutting into that plane. the Airbus has slightly more composite than the 787. Boeing plane cost 30 billion and is 4 years late and grounded for 4 month and the solution was to keep the fire starter battery lithium system, with admitting Boeing has no idea why it burns so they are going with a fire starter box and accepting passenger potential death as a consequence. Money before passenger safety is what a fire box says. . Any fire on a plane is a emergency landing requirement . Airbus will continue to eat up Boeing because Boeing has the MD bankruptcy business model. Boeing expects contractors to do everything while Boeing does not mind the store.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371275880124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371275990277-3</Id><Topic><Title>How Airbus compares to Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371221434638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:50:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>6 years under your current name and 4 more under your avatar name , care to stop being a old liar lawyer</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371275990277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371278273866-4</Id><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Msg>spartacus99991 For one year Airbus stock has increased in value 80% and Boeing has gone up 41%, for 5 years Airbus stock price has increased 162% compared to Boeing(pathetic) gain of 35%. So a less than a percent difference in stock price dividend between Airbus and Boeing is nothing considering Airbus stock for a year is better than Boeing by 39% and for 5 years Airbus shareholders are better than Boeing by 127%. Now spartacus9991 ,don't you feel like a fool Your ignorant user comment about dividends. Once more, spartacus9991, I am going to take you to stock market school . Like I did with you on Apple and ACAD and TSLA . Spartacus9991, you asked me about dividends in a manner, that indicated there was something there that I was not telling , WRONG the dividend difference is insignificant. Spartacus do you really think Airbus would not compete . The comparison of Boeing stock increase i(s pathetic) compared to the Airbus stock increase for the shareholder . • here is your dumb comment spartacus9991" Ever heard of dividends?" My answer yes , spartacus9991 I know all about dividends and make a lot of money on ACAD and TSLA and did on Apple while you post your troll crapola and make nothing.. I know all about dividends but I know you do not because you just asked me a question that will not help your Boeing hack cause. Airbus paid a .78 cent dividend one time per year. Boeing paid 4 dividends , that is a quarterly payout of .45 cents . The difference between Boeing and Airbus dividend is less than one percent so that has no bearing on how much better shareholders of Airbus are compared to Boeing shareholder. Here is your dividend yield as of today, stock price divided by dividend equals dividend yield so Airbus pays 1.3% and Boeing pays 1.9% dividend yield. Spartacus9991 a difference of .6 %. Now since Boeing is lagging Airbus in stock price appreciation by a wide margin that is not a significant amount of money. Way</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371279858198-5</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.45 quarterly dividend should be .48 so the dividend , divided by stock price equals dividend yield and Airbus is 1.3% dividend yield and Boeing is 1.9% dividend yield considering the huge better stock price gain for Airbus shareholders this was a ignorant comment by spartacus9991 BTW spartacus9991 you need to remember your 3rd grade math and convert to percentage move the decimal two places to get the percent der !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371279858198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:04:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371280234921-6</Id><Topic><Title>How Airbus compares to Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371221434638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:50:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever flown on an Airbus? I fly all the time and I don't like Airbus planes. They do not fly as smooth as a Boeing aircraft. Airbus will always want to be a Boeing wannabe!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1371280234921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371280305949-7</Id><Topic><Title>How Airbus compares to Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371221434638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:50:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true. And what are your former avatar names?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371280305949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371280322047-8</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is the matter spartcus9991 all you can do is give me the thumbs down because your too ignorant to understand dividends ! you will never get it, Boeing will be eaten up by the Airbus 350. Airbus has been doing this to Boeing for years . Airbus waits to see what Boeing is #$%$ then comes up with a better plane and takes more market share. spartacus9991, it is not the Boeing union wages it is the management. lack of skill, knowledge and ability, look at the history of James mcnerney, he is a less than a average contributor and a also ran at the top. , He was told to leave GE by Jack Welch and MMM has done much better with him gone , He was put in Boeing by a guy with zero aerospace experience a temporary CEO Lewis Platt . out sourcing did not work and Hart Smith, a Boeing senior fellow and engineer told Boeing that years ago , they did not listen Boeing executives are fools .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371280322047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371280493470-9</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus 350 first flight and burns 25% less fuel than a 787, no lithium batteries and TSLA up as I said,BA not so good</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371216663708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice comment techpath2000 your right on</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371280493470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371280542182-10</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus 350 first flight and burns 25% less fuel than a 787, no lithium batteries and TSLA up as I said,BA not so good</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371216663708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>al the BHT can do is thumbs down the facts are all there ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371280542182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371280751569-11</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"stock price is the only thing that defines a shareholders worth ANY OTHER ARGUMENT IS JUST BHT" You posted "only thing". I was just pointing out that there are stocks, such as utilities, that pay decent dividends but don't move a lot in price. Wayne: always trying to spin his mistatements. I've said for a long time that McNerney needs to leave and I won't own BA until at least he leaves. I've read Hart-Smith's paper and agree he was ignored and the company is paying big time for it. So when did I become a lawyer? My family wants to know.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371280751569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371281019413-12</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus 350 first flight and burns 25% less fuel than a 787, no lithium batteries and TSLA up as I said,BA not so good</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371216663708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was inclined to just forget your "25%" mistake and chalk it up to you're not being an engineer. But since you continue to think that's a fact and not acknowledge it then it's going to be fair game in the future to prove your lack of knowlege about airplane performance comparisons.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371281019413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371282353042-13</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus 350 first flight and burns 25% less fuel than a 787, no lithium batteries and TSLA up as I said,BA not so good</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371216663708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:31:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, the 777ER can already fly 12,000 miles without refuel. 777X will increase that range. Everyone talks about the 787, but the 777X is going to be the aircraft that the A350 will have to beat. The airlines love the 777, Nuff said!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1371282353042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371282611829-14</Id><Title>Windows on A350 looked small in comparison with 787</Title><Msg>Take a look at the pictures for each</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371282611829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 03:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371283293924-15</Id><Title>F-15 still in production--F-15K, F-15S and F-15SG are still being produced for export.</Title><Msg>MIG killer with a amazing---The F-15 in all air forces had a combined air-to-air combat record of 104 kills to 0 losses as of February 2008. No air superiority versions of the F-15 (A/B/C/D models) have been shot down by enemy forces. They may start production on the F-15SE Silent Eagle soon if not already happening</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371283293924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 04:01:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371283474574-16</Id><Topic><Title>Marines land Osprey aircraft on Japanese ship</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371264851057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:54:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is exactly what the Marines needed for that edge. Land anywhere and back to the ship or base. Great</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371283474574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 04:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371299363536-17</Id><Topic><Title>US to Arm Executioners in Syria !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1371228034320</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're saying Obama is arming AlQaeda...the same organization that attacks US troops and was involved in 9-11 ? Is that what you're saying ? This needs to be invesatigated further..can you google it and get back to me</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371299363536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 08:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371302221447-18</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So spartacus9991, , trying to save face now , by jumping on my side of your argument pro Boeing , eh ! so weak, you lost ,end of story, counselor , Spartacus99991,Counsel for Boeing, , you said, have I ever heard of dividends in response to a specific topic, comparing shareholder stock price increase between Boeing (pathetic ) to Airbus (excellent stock price gains in the duopoly race )making it very clear that Airbus is better than Boeing for shareholders. And in that context "any other argument (for Boeing by you) is just a Boeing hack troll comment not worth anything, and I am right. . Spartacus9991 as a old lawyer trick you made a attempt with your comment "ever heard of dividends", and I turned your response comment reply to the facts about Boeing stock price increase being weak compared to Airbus stock price gains being better Spartacus99991, as usual you have lost another debate with me. Spartacus 9991 you lost. Airbus is better than Boeing for stock ownership . spartacus9991 , you said you knew I was using a old lawyer trick so how would you know an old lawyer trick,does it take an old lawyer to know an old lawyer trick/ then you said it was your(legal opinion) that I am making statements about you that are on the margin of being sued for , if you not a lawyer then stop acting like you are an old lawyer counselor . Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371302221447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 09:17:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371302676428-19</Id><Topic><Title>How Airbus compares to Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371221434638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:50:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991, is that an old lawyer comment then ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371302676428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 09:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371303126653-20</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your right the 787 is a public relations nightmare, the plane catches fire, is not ready for 4 years after the company executive said it would be" flying in a couple of months" on roll out and is over cost by 30 billion dollars and the wings look like they are ready to snap off. The company executive should be turned out for this disaster. next the grounding for 4 months time and instead of changing to NiCad batteries for at least PR reasons, not to mention real safety of flight reasons, the company leadership puts the dangerous batteries in a heavy fire box. So instead of helping the planes image with the public , Boeing continued with a lithium battery and the 787 plane gained more weight with the fire box than a NiCad battery system actually weighs .Now that is stupid !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371303126653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 09:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371303679039-21</Id><Title>Lets see, Airbus windows comparerd to Boeing windows or which has better 787 fires which plane will I fly, I wonder?</Title><Msg>The A350 windows are wider; the 787's are taller, so r2d2, what is your point ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371303679039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 09:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371311818776-22</Id><Topic><Title>Marines land Osprey aircraft on Japanese ship</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371264851057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:54:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah great. Good thing no one was SHOOTING at them.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1371311818776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 11:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371312140874-23</Id><Topic><Title>Marines land Osprey aircraft on Japanese ship</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371264851057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:54:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll guess this is sabre-rattling about the disputed Diaoyu islands. Otherwise, who would care?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371312140874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371312338964-24</Id><Topic><Title>F-15 still in production--F-15K, F-15S and F-15SG are still being produced for export.</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371283293924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 04:01:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>F-15s can fly at 1800 mph. And yet NORAD could not catch up to 600 mph 757s and 767s on 9/11, and then lied about it so egregiously that the 9/11 Commission considered calling in the DoJ for a criminal investigation.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371312338964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371312966895-25</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys are absolutely right to a degree. It takes money and guts to bring new tech to market. It usually has its problems before it becomes standard. It takes foresight and engineering capabilities that reach out to the limits. Yep, you guys are right and the public will benefit greatly for the efforts made today by industry leaders like BA. It will be easy to copy the latest and greatest without costing investors a ton of money, but that is the way of business today. SAme with the Twin engine scare Airbus tried when the 767 and 777 hit the markets. Seems to me Airbus is trying to sell a lot of twins now. I guess it was smart to watch the leader then and that still seems to be the norm. This one might of cost shareholders a lot, but I think BA has redefined the way we are going to build future aircraft. Airbus had to be pulled kicking and screamming into the market with the A350 and will have to be dragged into the next market again by its own customers down the line. Composits are the way to go and Airbus finally has a quallity composit competitor. Good for the watchers with little investment or guts.</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1371312966895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:16:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371313688791-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post .....it does fit Obama's MO</Msg><Username>ballen310</Username><Timestamp>1371313688791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371315071224-27</Id><Title>Just returned from a month long vacation in S. America</Title><Msg>The 5 star deluxe hotels there out-do the ones in the USA although it's hard to find one in some of the more remote cities of the contentment. I'm always on the look out for good property and good tax havens so I can keep the money I earn out of the hands of corrupt politicians in the USA. my Chilean winery is doing exceptionally and is enjoying overwhelming success throughout most S.A. countries.....especially our unique Mir_Low. Looking at bring it to the US but the red tape is tremendous. Kalifornia, Oregon and Washington are afraid of competition.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315071224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371315236680-28</Id><Title>Most of South America has a Culture similar to that of U.S. Democrats</Title><Msg>....Lying, cheating and stealing is a way of life.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315236680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371316003367-29</Id><Topic><Title>Most of South America has a Culture similar to that of U.S. Democrats</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315236680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:53:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still big on Gold and silver ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371316003367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371316831519-30</Id><Title>It's easy to understand Why Democrats want an Amnesty Bill</Title><Msg>Democrats want poor uneducated people to flood into the US and be granted amnesty because they are most susceptible to believing the lies of Democrats and becoming reliable voters like black Americans. They do not want to pass laws that would open the immigration gates for highly educated eastern Europeans, East Indians and Most Asians. These are people that would benefit the country greatly but they tend to be unreliable votes for Democrats so Democrats and RINO politicians have erected tremendous barriers to keep them out. Want to hire a illegal Mexican immigrant to pick strawberries.....no problem. Want to hire a cardiac surgeon from Estonia with 25 years of experience in modern hospitals. First he has to complete a 7 year U.S residency, pass the USMLC for FMGs. Then you would have to advertise for 6 six months to see if a U.S. Citizen with the same qualifications wants the job you are going to hire him for. You will also be required to have expensive lawyers complete a mountain of legal work, red tape and bureaucratic nonsense. Why? Because this is a smart, well educated person who knows first hard the horrors of socialism and communism so he is not likely to vote Democrat</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371316831519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371317083553-31</Id><Topic><Title>Just returned from a month long vacation in S. America</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315071224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:51:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you looked at Belize as a shelter?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1371317083553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371317687001-32</Id><Topic><Title>Most of South America has a Culture similar to that of U.S. Democrats</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315236680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:53:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Affirmative......the collapse is coming.....it's just a matter of when All you have to do is Google the U.S. Debt clock and take a good look at the unfunded liabilities the Democrats have accrued for this country with their vote buying socialism .......those liabilities are several time the amount of the entire world's money. However, I've never viewed metals as a short term investment and I have more than I will ever need. I have now turned my attention to commodity producing assets. Farm land, oil and gas wells, and aqua farming. I've been in the Medical/hospital business a long time and will continue to expand that business. I'm getting too old for this.....but can't seem to stop.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371317687001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371318178363-33</Id><Topic><Title>Most of South America has a Culture similar to that of U.S. Democrats</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315236680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:53:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you're concerned about the debt you should advocate the redeployment of the US military to defending our own borders, the closing of 800 overseas bases, and the reduction of the Pentagon budget to 20% of its current levels.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1371318178363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371318179513-34</Id><Topic><Title>Marines land Osprey aircraft on Japanese ship</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1371264851057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:54:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a great A/C! Worked with a lot of great people in Philadelphia on this. Looking at Merion GC for the US Open brings back a lot of memories this weekend don't you say h_iamiam? Are you still working PN?</Msg><Username>av_week_reader</Username><Timestamp>1371318179513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371318351296-35</Id><Topic><Title>Just returned from a month long vacation in S. America</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315071224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:51:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I own a couple of acres on Ambergris Caye.....nice place to go diving. Belize is OK as a tax shelter but not for people with under $10million net worth. To really make it work as a tax shelter, you need to incorporate a business in Belize then you can protect most family assets with a Belize trust formation owned by the corporation.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371318351296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371319183113-36</Id><Topic><Title>Most of South America has a Culture similar to that of U.S. Democrats</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315236680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:53:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poortard.....I've been advocating that for years. I'm a Vietnam vet and I've seen first hand how the politicians use the excuse of war to transfer billions of dollars of hard earned wealth to people who didn't earn it while killing our youth in the process.....that's the biggest tragedy. On the other hand, I'm glad Germany was stopped in WW II. I want a DEFENSE second to none so no one will dare screw with us then secure our own border and stay out of other country's business. I'm not sure about the morality of ignoring another holocaust but I think it's a moot question while the US of A is actively participating in an a holocaust within its own borders.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371319183113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371321318332-37</Id><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Msg>Msg: 255793 of 255821 The Downfall of a Great American Airplane Company - An Insider's Perspective Subject Recently, there has been much attention focused on the "Boeing Brain Drain" that may have contributed to the February loss of Shuttle Columbia. However, most people do not realize that a similar "brain drain" is occurring within the Commercial Airplane division of Boeing. Because of Boeing's massive layoffs and strategy of offloading design work to foreign design centers, the company has lost control of its engineering processes. The recent actions of the Boeing Company in its Commercial Airplane division are seriously jeopardizing the quality and safety of its airplanes. Hopefully, the company's current course of action will not lead to the same tragic consequences that occurred on February 1, 2003. Our Credentials Before we begin, we wish to establish our credentials. Since we are current Boeing employees, we obviously don't want to give information that can positively identify us. This paper was composed by a group of aerospace design engineers with many years at the Boeing Company. We have been involved in several new airplane programs across a variety of functions and have intimate knowledge of the inner workings of Engineering at Boeing. We are "in the trenches" every day, involved in the nuts-and-bolts business of designing airplanes. We have a unique and in-depth insider's view of the damage being sown at the Boeing Company by Phil Condit and his cohorts. Introduction During the past several years, Boeing Commercial Airplanes has been offloading its design engineering work to foreign "design centers". American engineers and technical designers are being laid off by the hundreds while Russian engineers are quietly hired at the Boeing Design Center in Moscow. Many of the Russian engineers are not nearly as experienced as the American engineers being laid off. Engineering layoffs have cut so deeply into Boeing's talent pool that</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321389821-38</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many of the Russian engineers are not nearly as experienced as the American engineers being laid off. Engineering layoffs have cut so deeply into Boeing's talent pool that knowledge has been irretrievably lost. And the layoffs continue. Soon Boeing may reach (if it hasn't already) a "point of no return" where irreversible damage has been done to the company's ability to design and build safe airplanes, even with its so-called "risk-sharing partners". Boeing's senior management has often stated that they are not willing to "bet the company" on another new airplane program as they famously did with the 747. They are pursuing a strategy of accumulating a network of "risk-sharing partners" so Boeing can concentrate on its core competency of "large scale systems integration." We are willing to state that Boeing's management is "betting the company" on a misguided and ridiculous outsourcing plan that is gutting the company of its hard-won knowledge base and human assets. The safety and quality of Boeing airplanes is at jeopardy because of the foolhardy actions of Boeing's senior management, and even the hint of safety and quality issues with Boeing's airplanes can have disastrous results for its Commercial Airplane business. The former executives of McDonnell-Douglas (which arguably as a company was, in the end, a complete failure in the design and manufacture of commercial aircraft) have taken control of Boeing and seem determined to gut the commercial airplane business - all in the name of "increasing shareholder value". Harry Stonecipher, John McDonnell and Mike Sears, along with Phil Condit and Alan Mulally are destroying what was very recently a vital, dominant American company. These men will probably enjoy massive short-term gains in the value of their stock options, but there is a price; the loss of the long-term viability of Boeing in the commercial aircraft business.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321389821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321433924-39</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have to look back less than a decade to see where these men are leading Boeing - to the once glorious McDonnell-Douglas Commercial Aircraft division which has since faded into oblivion. The design and manufacture of commercial aircraft has been a lucrative business for the United States for many decades. The aerospace business has consistently been the largest exporter in the United States economy. Boeing is willingly and recklessly giving this business away to its future foreign competitors. It is time Boeing's practices become public knowledge. Some Perspective It is important to remember that Boeing's commercial aircraft business is a bit different from the standard manufacturing company. Boeing design airplanes - not washing machines, toasters or clock radios. Every day, millions of people entrust their lives and the lives of their friends and family to the quality of Boeing airplanes. Every day, your and our husbands and wives, sons and daughters, fathers and mothers climb aboard a 727, 737, 747, 757, 767 or 777 with faith that experienced Boeing engineers did their job well. Although many airplane passengers pray to God for a safe flight, it is often Boeing engineers who, with their skill and knowledge, have the power to grant that prayer. Currently, Boeing is making severe cuts in its design engineering staff. The cost savings probably look great on paper. But the real question is how do these cuts affect a company in which airplanes are designed? Airplanes - on which millions of people fly each year. Airplanes - to which we entrust our lives every time we fly. Airplanes - that can experience catastrophic failure due to engineering errors.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321433924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321478023-40</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Due to their current strategy of off-loading design work to inexperienced engineers and laying off their own highly experienced employees, Boeing management has created an environment where these errors are much more likely to occur. The most telling statement about the trend of engineering at Boeing is this statement, which is heard more and more often from fellow engineers: "After seeing how engineering is done here today, I'm afraid to fly on the next new Boeing airplane." Some Facts About Airplane Design It is obvious that an airplane, especially a large commercial aircraft, is a very complicated machine to design and build. What the general public does not understand is that, however difficult they think it is to design and build an airplane, their belief is not one-fiftieth as complicated as the reality. It takes many years of experience to learn the intricacies of airplane design. Not only does an engineer need to understand how to design detail parts, assemblies and installations, but also where the parts are manufactured, how the parts are manufactured and how they are put together. Engineers are required to understand lead-times and scheduling to make sure drawings are released on time to support vendor requirements. The responsibilities of an engineer are immense. In addition, engineers need to control the configuration of the airplane. The parts that go on an airplane depends on many factors: The base model (737, 747, 757, 767, 777) The derivative (737-700, 737-800, 737-900, 757-200, 757-300, 777-200ER, 777-300, 777-300ER, 777-200LR) Standard options (Small cargo door, large cargo door, overwing exits, in-flight entertainment systems) Customer-specific options (Seats, purser stations, the color of the carpet) There are literally millions of possible configurations. Knowing which parts go on which airplanes is a very important part of an engineer's job.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321478023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321512836-41</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are literally millions of possible configurations. Knowing which parts go on which airplanes is a very important part of an engineer's job. The systems Boeing has implemented to control airplane configuration (as part of the DCAC/MRM effort) are immensely complex and constantly changing. There are many technical designers and engineers who spend large portions of their time just learning and understanding these systems. Most engineers only have a cursory knowledge of these systems and rely on local "experts". The problem is that these local "experts" are becoming fewer and farther between and their numbers are diminishing rapidly as layoffs continue. Boeing is lucky that the FAA does not have an audit planned in the near future. The Offloading of Boeing's Design Engineering The key to Boeing's success has never been its plants, tools and buildings, but its superior engineering and its willingness to take calculated risks. Both of these assets are disappearing rapidly. Although much emphasis has been put on such manufacturing concepts as "lean manufacturing" and "just-in-time inventory", it is important to realize that regardless of the efficiencies of the manufacturing process, an airplane or any product cannot succeed without quality engineering design. In the past, Boeing's elite engineering corps has met the challenge and produced the world's best commercial aircraft. Currently, Boeing is rabidly pursuing a strategy of offloading engineering design work to overseas "design centers". This process began more than a decade ago with "design transfers" to the Japanese (Kawasaki, Mitsubishi and Fuji Heavy Industries). It continues today at a more rapid and frightening pace.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321512836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371321534536-42</Id><Title>Peope Afraid to Criticize Politicians of their own Political Party are.....</Title><Msg>....are not just being loyal. They're not only partisan....they're ant-American. With all that' this corrupt administration is being exposed for.....Democrats are still valiantly circling the wagons and defending the corruption and making excuses for the lies as though they are forbidden to criticize their corrupt politicians much less get rid of them come vote'n time no matter how much they trample on the constitution and work to reduce our liberty. To be sure Republicans ain't a whole lot better. Chief justice Roberts should be recalled for torturing the constitution. McCain should be recalled and replaced. I had have high hopes for Rand Paul and Marko Rubio but both are pushing the insane amnesty bill......shame on them. Ted Cruz is making more sense for the cause of liberty and constitutional obedience than anyone in congress. Look for Democrats to began to strongly attack him. I know of no one in the Democrat Party that places a high value on life, liberty and property. Most of them should be wearing red armbands with a hammer and sickle on them.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371321534536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321559116-43</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing Design Center - Moscow Currently, the fastest growing off-load "design center" is located in Moscow, Russia. There are around 350 engineers employed at this center. They are designing primary and secondary structures, interiors, floors and other systems. There appears to be a common misconception that Russia is a land of promise where the streets are paved with PhD aerospace engineers begging for jobs. The belief is that not only do these brilliant engineers have doctorates, but they have decades of top-notch aircraft design experience. In addition, they are willing to work for 20 to 25% of the pay that American engineers receive. How can Boeing lose? The reality is that BDC Moscow is manned with few experienced engineers and many, many greenhorns - inexperienced engineers who have graduated within the past few years. Boeing engineers are being pressured to off-load design work to Moscow - to these legions of inexperienced engineers. Even if we assume that all of the Russian engineers have PhDs and are experienced, ask yourself the following questions: How and where did they gain aircraft design experience? On what new Russian airplane programs have they cut their teeth in the past 10-15 years? How do Russian commercial aircraft compare to the quality, efficiency and safety of Boeing's airplanes? Which leads to the final question: Based on Russian commercial aviation history, do we really want to fly a commercial airplane designed by Russian engineers? The Russian engineers have to be given some credit. They are nice guys, likeable and smart with relevant college degrees, but they lack several important traits:</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321559116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321625011-44</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Russian engineers have to be given some credit. They are nice guys, likeable and smart with relevant college degrees, but they lack several important traits: Experience designing airplanes. The ability to speak English well enough to have an in-depth technical conversation. The ability to take initiative and to come up with creative solutions. This final point is an important one. Decades of communist rule have apparently made it difficult for some Russians to make decisions. They want to be told what to do, down to the most minute detail. Designing a new airplane with the Russians is like working with a bunch of new college hires - except these new hires don't speak English very well - if at all! Are there any volunteers for who wants to fly on their class project? All that seems to matter to Boeing's senior management is that Russian engineers are significantly cheaper than American ones. It is important to note that although the Russians are cheaper, a number of significant inefficiencies are introduced: The language barrier It is difficult enough discussing technical issues with an American engineer, let alone with a Russian who has only taken 3 months of English classes. Time zones The only way to communicate with BDC Moscow is via e-mail, conference calls and video conferences. The problem is that there is only a 1 or 2 hour window of opportunity to hold conference calls or video conferences. Because of the brevity and ineffectiveness of conference calls, Boeing engineers waste hours and even days trying to resolve issues via e-mail - when it would only take 10 minutes to walk to the next cube to explain to Phil what needs to be done.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321625011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321665430-45</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because of the brevity and ineffectiveness of conference calls, Boeing engineers waste hours and even days trying to resolve issues via e-mail - when it would only take 10 minutes to walk to the next cube to explain to Phil what needs to be done. Physical distance Documents take days to reach Moscow. Once again, if the work was done within Boeing, it would only take 10 minutes to walk to Harry's desk and drop off the document. CATIA models need to be transferred to Russia in a process that takes hours. If the work was done locally, a model could be transferred almost instantaneously. Out-sourcing has made a complicated process exponentially more complicated. In the engineering world, complicated processes are known to produce one thing consistently - errors. The initial results on the quality of work from BDC are frightening. Much of their work on recent programs has had to be completely re-done. Changes that were supposed to be made aren't made properly, and changes that shouldn't have been made are widespread. Luckily, (until recently) there have been enough experienced Boeing engineers to catch these errors. This is no longer the case after the last painful round of layoffs. It is only a matter of time before a potentially dangerous error slips by. Yet another concern is that the majority of Russian engineers working at the Boeing Design Center in Moscow are contract (temporary) employees who are overseen by a much smaller number of Boeing direct employees. What keeps these engineers from remaining loyal to Boeing? There is a very real threat that Boeing will face a situation in the near future where their domestic (American) talent has been ravaged and the Russian engineers move on to other opportunities (such as contracting overseas for much higher salaries or within Moscow at Airbus' newly opened Moscow Design Center). Is it really a wise business decision to hand over proprietary knowledge to foreign engineers or even worse, foreign c</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321665430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321761946-46</Id><Topic><Title>It's easy to understand Why Democrats want an Amnesty Bill</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371316831519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 13:20:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree</Msg><Username>usheartdoc</Username><Timestamp>1371321761946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321762293-47</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing's "Core Competency": Large-Scale Systems Integration Boeing has stated that they want to concentrate on their "core competency", which Phil Condit says is "large-scale systems integration". Integration takes place at the individual engineer level, which is where Boeing is cutting. The front-line engineer is where the rubber meets the road, but Boeing has made it clear that engineers are merely "costs" to the company, not assets. The relevant questions to ask here are: How can Boeing hope to successfully be a "large-scale systems integrator" if they don't have enough experienced, qualified engineers to do the integration? If Boeing's engineers no longer understand the technical aspects of the airplane's design and manufacturability, how can they integrate? At What Point Do Boeing's Suppliers Decide They No Longer Need Boeing? We have heard that Phil Condit's perfect vision for Boeing is where all of the design and manufacturing work is offloaded. Meanwhile, Boeing (consisting of Phil and his secretary) sits in a penthouse office in Chicago at the top of the pyramid and collects a fat profit margin, thus "enhancing shareholder value". As comic as this may seem, it is probably not far from the truth. Boeing is throwing away thousands of irreplaceable engineers while giving away to its vendors knowledge based on decades of empirical data from Boeing's countless tests and studies. This knowledge, both in the Design Manuals and in the engineers' heads is Boeing's competitive advantage. Boeing is training and arming its future competitors.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321762293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321802338-48</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing is training and arming its future competitors. The Boeing vision is that eventually the "partners" will design and manufacture body sections, already "stuffed" with the required systems (electrical wire bundles, hydraulics systems, insulation, etc). All of these activities would be coordinated and "integrated" by a small staff of Boeing engineers. The body sections would then be shipped to Everett (or Wichita or Long Beach or Fort Worth), where a small group of Boeing assembly workers would button the sections together. In all honesty, does this deserve the lion's share of the profits? How much better can the Japanese complete this function in Japan? At what point do Boeing's suppliers decide that they no longer need Boeing? JAI (consisting of Mitsubishi, Kawasaki and Fuji Heavy Industries) is more than capable to do the manufacturing. In addition, they can do the stress analysis and design work. Boeing has spent the last 10 years handing over their computer "templates" for stress analysis - along with books containing all of Boeing's hard-won knowledge of fatigue analysis, structural damage tolerance and corrosion prevention, which was accumulated over decades of testing and in-service experience. If JAI is capable of doing both the design and manufacturing of airplane structural components, Rolls Royce, Pratt and Whitney and GE provide the engines, Rockwell-Collins provides the avionics and interior components are BFE (Buyer Furnished Equipment), what does Boeing bring to the table? Boeing's doing the easy part! Why would these companies allow Boeing to sit at the top of the pyramid and take the fattest profits? (Hint: The answer isn't "Boeing's core competency of large-scale systems integration".) Employee Morale be described? There is no hyperbole too outlandish to describe how low morale has fallen. There is a strong adversarial feeling that has developed among</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321802338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371321835455-49</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Employee Morale How can current employee morale, especially among Boeing engineers, be described? There is no hyperbole too outlandish to describe how low morale has fallen. There is a strong adversarial feeling that has developed among engineers against management - especially upper management. Engineers believe that management would like nothing more than to eliminate the entire Boeing engineering department. Perhaps they're right. There is a pervasive feeling of doom and fatalism. Engineers believe that there is no future for them at Boeing. The engineers with 20 or more years at Boeing are stoically waiting for that golden day when they will retire and wash their hands of the mess that Phil Condit and Harry Stonecipher have created. It is frightening to see how few experienced engineers are left in the company. When the company is forced to bring in contractors to do high-level design work, it is indicative of a major problem. There are not enough people left to do even a small development program. How will Boeing handle the 7E7? In addition, Boeing is handing out WARN notices to direct employees while these same employees are surrounded by on-site Russian and Japanese engineers! Performance Management One of Boeing's criteria in its "Performance Management" is to measure how front-line management and lead engineers are offloading work to Moscow. The more work the lead engineers and managers are willing to offload and the bigger the smile on their faces as they do so, the more likely they will not be laid-off but will be promoted and given raises. Can you imagine it - having your career depend on how willing you are to give your job away and to train your replacement in the process? Even if you are cheerful in supporting the offloading of engineering work, your reward may still be a WARN notice. How's that for a morale-builder? How's that for an environment in which airplanes are designed?</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321835455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:43:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371322093577-50</Id><Topic><Title>Peope Afraid to Criticize Politicians of their own Political Party are.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371321534536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:38:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Precisely !!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>usheartdoc</Username><Timestamp>1371322093577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371322343286-51</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post! Even more relevent today then in 2003. If Condit, Stonecipher, and now McNerney had heeded them and Hart-Smith's2001 paper thngs would be a lot better today. A big if and now the company and shareholders have to live with their bad decisions.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371322343286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371322589318-52</Id><Title>Need Open Heart Surgery?</Title><Msg>Better ask a Democrat politician with no medical training or be ready to pay cash to a qualified surgeon.</Msg><Username>usheartdoc</Username><Timestamp>1371322589318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371323091766-53</Id><Topic><Title>Most of South America has a Culture similar to that of U.S. Democrats</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371315236680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 12:53:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In general a good post ..and I have no doubt that you are a very successful multi Millionaire. Problem is that war is profitable and the REAL rich folk find aggressive unending wars far too profitable to give them up now.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371323091766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:04:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371323365921-54</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you're not a certified finanacial advisor then stop acting like one. I thought you were a former shop worker who claims he told some courses at a jock school and now looks down on anyone who disagrees with your opinions.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371323365921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371323801344-55</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good and highly relevant post. Where did you find this?</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371323801344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371324397632-56</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from, an old post i had copied in 2003- it was not written by me but was on yahoo- there is more but ˆ had to take a break to allow me to post more part two coming up</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371324397632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371324883412-57</Id><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Msg>and I know you have no doubt that I'm a very successful multi-billionaire... and that I'm the real Paul McCartney. Clearly that's a fact. Just thought I'd check in to tell you that.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371324883412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371324926720-58</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a strong adversarial feeling that has developed among engineers against management - especially upper management. Engineers believe that management would like nothing more than to eliminate the entire Boeing engineering department. Perhaps they're right. There is a pervasive feeling of doom and fatalism. Engineers believe that there is no future for them at Boeing. The engineers with 20 or more years at Boeing are stoically waiting for that golden day when they will retire and wash their hands of the mess that Phil Condit and Harry Stonecipher have created. It is frightening to see how few experienced engineers are left in the company. When the company is forced to bring in contractors to do high-level design work, it is indicative of a major problem. There are not enough people left to do even a small development program. How will Boeing handle the 7E7? In addition, Boeing is handing out WARN notices to direct employees while these same employees are surrounded by on-site Russian and Japanese engineers!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371324926720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371324964331-59</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Performance Management One of Boeing's criteria in its "Performance Management" is to measure how front-line management and lead engineers are offloading work to Moscow. The more work the lead engineers and managers are willing to offload and the bigger the smile on their faces as they do so, the more likely they will not be laid-off but will be promoted and given raises. Can you imagine it - having your career depend on how willing you are to give your job away and to train your replacement in the process? Even if you are cheerful in supporting the offloading of engineering work, your reward may still be a WARN notice. How's that for a morale-builder? How's that for an environment in which airplanes are designed? The 7E7 and Future Airplane Programs It can arguably be stated that Boeing has cut their engineering staff so deeply that they do not have enough remaining talent to tackle a new airplane program. It is well-known that Boeing's engineering staff is greying. Many of the engineers are within 10-15 years of retirement age - and most of those are counting the years, months, days, hours and minutes until that magical time. Trust us when we say that there has already been a huge loss of "tribal knowledge" that can never be recovered. In 5-10 years, when these graying engineers begin to retire, the resulting knowledge loss may well prove fatal to Boeing Commercial Airplanes. Boeing is rapidly approaching, if they have not already passed, the "Point of No Return". The layoffs have been so deep that knowledge and engineering ability has been irrecoverably lost.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371324964331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371324997046-60</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Effect of Development Cost on Product Quality There were a series of lessons supposedly learned from the fantastic success of the 777 airplane program. A tremendous amount of money was spent developing this airplane, much of it on trail-blazing new techniques such as: Concurrent Product Design Digital Pre-Assembly/Mockup Co-location of personnel (i.e. designers, stress analysts, manufacturing engineers) Integration of customers into the design process This "front-loading" of cost, where money was spent on the engineering/development of the airplane, paid off spectacularly. The rework in the factory dropped precipitously, saving millions in ongoing manufacturing costs. The number of rejection tags dropped by over 50%. The factory said that building the 777 was like putting together Tinker Toys. Today, the 777 is one of Boeing's two best-selling airplanes. However, now Harry Stonecipher and John McDonnell want to cut development costs on the 7E7 to 40% of 777 levels. Do they expect to get an airplane of similar quality to the 777 for that price? Engineers are already forced to make unpleasant compromises with their design because of the shocking scarcity of resources - compromises that threaten the quality, safety and performance of the airplane.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371324997046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371325034650-61</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We believe that Boeing Commercial Airplanes is headed down the same path as McDonnell-Douglas. Tight-fisted executives dole out miserly portions of budget to "save money" and "increase shareholder value". What they end up with are inferior products that fail in the marketplace. If proof is required, ask yourself: "What is left of McDonnell-Douglas' commercial aircraft business?" The 717. Isn't that proof enough of where Boeing is being led? Are we willing to entrust the future of Boeing's Commercial Aircraft business to the same people who destroyed McDonnell-Douglas? Conclusion The Boeing Company is headed down a dark and dangerous path. It is heading down this path at a reckless pace with little regard to long-term consequences. High-level executives are making decisions that, on paper, may look promising, but are in truth destroying the company. The safety and quality of Boeing airplanes is at jeopardy because of the foolhardy actions of Boeing's senior management. There has been little discussion about this in the media. Perhaps this story is not newsworthy. However, everyone with whom we have spoken has been...let's say "shocked" (although that does not do it justice)...when told of what is going on. We am not prone to exaggeration. We are engineers. We live and breathe logic and facts. We are witnessing first-hand the destructive effects of Phil Condit's "Vision 2016". There may not be a Boeing Commercial Aircraft Company in 2016 because of Phil Condit. What has been described herein is truth. We can only hope it also turns out to be newsworthy. END END</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371325034650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371325168601-62</Id><Title>Doctors dump health insurance plans, charge patients less</Title><Msg>WICHITA, Kan., June 14 (UPI) -- A Kansas physician says he makes the same income and offers better quality care to his patients after he dumped all health insurance companies. Thirty-two-year old family physician Doug Nunamaker of Wichita, Kan., said after five years of dealing with the red tape of health insurance companies and the high overhead for the staff he hired just to deal with paperwork, he switched to a system of charging his patients a monthly fee plus the price of an office visit or test, CNN/Money reported. For example, under Nunamaker's membership plan -- also known as "concierge" medicine or "direct primary care" practices -- each patient pays a flat monthly fee to have unlimited access to the doctors and any medical service they can provide in the practice, such as stitches or an EKG. For adults up to age 44, Nunamaker charges $50 a month, pediatric services are $10 a month, and for adults age 44 and older it costs $100 a month. Although Nunamaker calls the practice "cash-only," he accepts credit and debit cards for the fees and services. Nunamaker and his partner negotiated deals for services outside the office. A cholesterol test costs the patient for $3, versus the $90 or more billed to insurance companies; an MRI can cost $400, compared with $2,000 or more billed to insurance companies. The practice encourages patients and families to also carry some type of high-deductible health insurance plan in case of an emergency or serious illness requiring hospitalization, Nunamaker said. Nunamaker said his annual salary is around $200,000, and he gets to spend more time with patients providing better care because he is not watching the clock and he gets to spend more time with this family. Most of Nunamaker's clients are self-employed, small business owners, or small companies that found the monthly fee and the cost of the high-deductible plan was a cheaper option, CNN/Money reported.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1371325168601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371325314142-63</Id><Topic><Title>Peope Afraid to Criticize Politicians of their own Political Party are.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371321534536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:38:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right On.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1371325314142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371325384306-64</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>quality? A neutered Quality Assurance, and when run by Mfg. Management, its certainly more user friendly.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371325384306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371325643384-65</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About those bendy wings. Its a design flaw, did Boeing do a fix on the QT. or will they wait for the failures. When those wings bend that much it causes stretch on the bottom and compression on the top, they will be needing fixing.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371325643384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371325688751-66</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991, I look down on you because I do not like you . I do not like you , because your full of crapola and are ignorant about Boeing. Spartacus9991, you make up crapola positive spin about Boeing and champion Boeing and talk down to me about and against better stocks like Apple, ACAD TSLA and you manipulate the facts. Spartacus9991, here is a job for you to do, you start January 1 this year with 200k invested in ACAD determine the gain until May 3, then put all that money into TSLA and sell in 15 or 16 trade days like I said to. Spartacus9991, and then tell me how much money you or anyone else would have had, Will you do this ? And what say you Spartacus9991 eh ! Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371325688751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371326788998-67</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stillinshock, your right , and the 787 is the comet for Boeing the comet lead Boeing into the jet age but was flawed windows cracked and plane crashed battery fire and plane will crash, and eventually while the comet was made safe like the 787 maybe in the long run it did not matter for the comet, or the 787 , too costly, 30 billion, too much time delay 4 year, too much grounding 4 months, too many after the ground false starts now , it is a dead horse plane . , guess who won that war, comet first on scene jet passenger plane war it was Boeing the second place jet pane like the second place carbon fiber pane now , stupid James mcnerney !. Now Boeing management has ignorantly repeated the comet scenario, and Airbus will take over , actually it has been #1 for 11 years and especially on stock price performance , this is the same with the British motorcycle Industry, first copied then bettered by Sochiro Honda , the leaders at Airbus are much sharper than Boeing leaders like james mcNerney, who actually wrote his own epitaph, he told the CEO of Airbus that Airbus had not guts and did not go first . That is like telling George Armstrong Custer, he was a brave man to use 200 soldiers with long range, single shot rifles, and close the advantage of distance from the top of the hill to get into the American Indians killing field, range of attack, The Indians had henry 18 shot repeater rifles and 5000 warriors to put on the field and bow and arrows. The Indians had a game like we do, they shot arrows in the sky and tried to place the arrow in a hula hoop circle , only at Little bighorn, the circle was a blue uniform, they were very good at it too. James Mcnerney has the guts and Airbus has the airplane market the rest is for history to record. The stock is better for Airbus over Boeing and it will just keep getting better too ! I said it here spartacus9991 wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371326788998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371327476010-68</Id><Topic><Title>Peope Afraid to Criticize Politicians of their own Political Party are.....</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1371321534536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:38:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1371327476010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371327551491-69</Id><Topic><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371324883412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post, Paul. Besides, as that commercial says, you can't put anything on the internet that isn't true. And I also read that on the internet.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1371327551491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371328656809-70</Id><Title>Hi, I'm Carlos Slim</Title><Msg>Compared to me guys like Paul McCartney are peons. Sure he can sing but so can Vicente Fernández only better.</Msg><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371328656809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371328976753-71</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fast forward to the early days of the 787. My structures friends were furious when the 87 chief engineer, Walt Gillette (a good power point jockey totally unqualified for the job), gloatingly told them that Moscow would be doing a large portion of the structural design and analysis because their hourly rate was only $35/hr (of course their overhead was not used to support his bloated management organization) and that they were just as good and probably better than Puget Sound structural engineers. That was the start of a long string of structural problems culminating with the failure of the 87 side of body joint during wing proof loading, something that had never happened with a commercial airplane before. Multimillion dollar hit.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371328976753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371329083431-72</Id><Topic><Title>Need Open Heart Surgery?</Title><Username>usheartdoc</Username><Timestamp>1371322589318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not going to be making $500,000 / yr under Obamacare?</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371329083431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371329124331-73</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Carlos Slim</Title><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371328656809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:37:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, but you're ugly. I was a sex symbol. And nobody sings better than I do. Plus, I was knighted.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371329124331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371329152833-74</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Carlos Slim</Title><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371328656809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:37:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I give more money away every year than Paul McCartney has earned in his entire life time.</Msg><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371329152833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371329551005-75</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Carlos Slim</Title><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371328656809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:37:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's no such thing as an ugly man who is as rich as I am. I'm sexier than you'll ever be and I've never had to settle for a one legged woman......what a dope. You're a has been......even that pauper Bono has passed you up.</Msg><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371329551005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371330364978-76</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re Walt G. I'll disagree re his qualifications. If one considers the early days of 787 being around 2002-2003, then walt by that time had nearly a decade of experience in composite structures and managing structures type engineers. He was forced to offload to Russia et all by the mcDummy crowd. Later when he and Hank Queen and Mulally voiced objections to the Chicago gang and the phony aero types from McDummy crowd - they got out of dodge. Now Boeing is touting the ONE BOEING !--- which was what Al M said early on when he went to Ford " ONE FORD " ... QED I had several dealings with walt in the mid 80's re structures and similar issues - he was at that time a manager on the B2 program- for which BA designed and built most of the wing major structure and a good part of the " body".</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371330364978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 17:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371331763426-77</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Carlos Slim</Title><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371328656809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:37:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is Carlos Slim's real nationality? Please don't respond Spanish/Latino.</Msg><Username>jeffsdavis</Username><Timestamp>1371331763426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 17:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371333398421-78</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm Carlos Slim</Title><Username>carlosslimrichguy</Username><Timestamp>1371328656809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 16:37:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm currently touring virtually the entire world to standing room only crowds. My Out There tour is a smash hit. Often four generations of people attend. Now mention the name Carlos Slim to the average American hand she'll say "Do they come in menthol"?</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1371333398421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 17:56:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371334039656-79</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree with about everything you posted there, except Boeing beat Airbus in 2012 in deliveries and orders, if that is how the industry usually determines #1.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371334039656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 18:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371334560734-80</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would rather take the $200K and buy some properties in Southern California (Orange County) and leverage the bank's money to make a killing so far this year. To each his own. BTW, I know enough about fuel consumption to realize that the A350 is not 25% better than the 787 as you posted. Airbus has never claimed more than 8% and that is not yet proven.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371334560734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 18:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371334804631-81</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P.S. I really don't care if you like me or not. In fact, you do not seem like someone who I would want to call a friend. But accusing me of being a lawyer, now that's stooping pretty low. I don't call you a financial expert. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1371334804631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 18:20:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371335483980-82</Id><Title>Total Security</Title><Msg>Is total Tyranny</Msg><Username>slingensam</Username><Timestamp>1371335483980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 18:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371338829840-83</Id><Title>Hey Carlos Skim or maybe Abdul Slim!</Title><Msg>Are you truly of Spanish extraction? I'll bet not!</Msg><Username>just69don</Username><Timestamp>1371338829840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 19:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371348052717-84</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the sociopath</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1371268481885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 23:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard Stalin had his wife killed. Obama is capable of a great number of things, but as a malignant narcissist, is he capable of terminating his wife if for some reason she becomes a threat to his goals as becoming the Muslim Caliphate for the Muslim World to draw strength from? Someone has to ask these questions. He's been protecting Islam all along while attacking Christianity at West Point and in Obamacare mandates over taxpayer funding of abortions.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1371348052717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371349973042-85</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice on more than one occasion I have pointed out this Boeing message board is being held hostage by only 6 Boeing Hacks who are evil trolls . The constantly under various avatar names, over time attempt to pump Boeing stock with a dog and pony show, no facts tah count and hate for any other user who compares the duopoly of Boeing to Airbus, Airbus does not have a Financial message board on Yahoo but you can buy the stock so this is a great place even for Boeing followers to compare airbus to Boeing. If Boeing were up as far as Airbus was ,I know these 6 BHT would be here just singling about it like songbirds sorry that is not the case</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371349973042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371350083060-86</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne are you sparty? or just paid outta the same community agitator pot?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371350083060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371350419861-87</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that is exactly right Don, and you can not ignore your core responsibility to self design the plane and use the best engineers and assemblers that money and training can buy and then develop the next generation in the place that was until about 1985 the best place to make airplanes Puget Sound. Condit is like a American Chief in command say Eisenhower , at the end of WWII that beat the Axis powers then at the surrender ceremony on the Missouri, give them the USA to rule. Condit in buying a failed MD was a giant mistake and it has killed Boeing the same way it killed MD. boeing is done a niche player at best now .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371350419861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371350623289-88</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored why haven't you been censored yet !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371350623289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:43:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371351161980-89</Id><Topic><Title>787 verus XWB A350</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1371275172372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 01:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I look at the whole picture and practically the Boeing message board is found under finance, then as a sub section it may include other areas but it is about stock ownership . Frankly unless your a major owner of boeing it is all about the stock appreciation and the current way Boeing is being run and if it is good or bad as it related to stock price</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371351161980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371351169880-90</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess we are going to have to agree to disagree. I have worked with Walt quite a bit on Commercial Airplanes. He was a competent aerodynamicist and manager up to the unit chief level. My realization that he was going to be trouble was at one of the initial planning meetings between him and his chief engineers (I was there to provide technical input) going over the schedule. With one exception all of the chiefs told him that they could not meet schedule and backed that up with facts and data. After two hours he told the group that the schedule was not going to change. I've seen managers pull off that sort of tough attitude if they had a good handle on the nuances of the project but Walt didn't. In the context of a brand new airplane loaded with new technology it was a catastrophic decision. Yes, maybe he was following orders but I have no respect for managers who put their careers ahead of doing what's right for Boeing. I respected Mullaley as a manager but could not fathom how he picked the gaggle of duds (except for Sinnett) to head the 87 project. The other point you and I differ on is the relative qualiity of legacy Boeing vs McDac. I detested Stonecipher and Sears but some of the McDac managers have turned out OK either as butt kickers (Delaney, but out of his depth now) or as very good technical managers (Fancher, Toups). The good news coming off the 87 debackle is that Boeing is better managed at the project level now than it was when the 87 started. At the corporate level not so much.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1371351169880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 22:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371352508909-91</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus9991 thinks dividend on Boeing Stock compared to Airbus is significant demonstrating his ignorance</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1371278273866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 02:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not yet, so you are sparty? sparty is similarly infatuated with the EU, as if they're somehow superior to USA. I suppose you could be another America hating parasite (just like sparty, it's anyones guess, most of the large cap stock boards have at least one or two dedicated dumbos/mobros stirring the pot. why are you so obsessed with bashing boeing?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1371352508909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 23:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371354287182-92</Id><Topic><Title>A BIT OF HISTORY RE BA OFFLOADING TO EAST NOWHERE AND 777</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1371321318332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remeber reading an article when Gillette said he would be on the flightline for the first 787 flight. This was just after the announcment that the wing would be carbon, designed and manufactured in Japan. I have to believe he was forced into those decision and it wasn't his choice to leave Boeing before the first flights would have started occuring per the origional schedule..</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371354287182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 23:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>