<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373256071913-1</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And have you have noticed that your so-called scorn has no effect on what I write? There is not one thing that I wrote which is not true; therefore, one might conclude that you have contempt for truth. Typical and pervasive liberal counter to any statement that is not in-kind with liberal group-think is to attack with vitriol. Say nasty things and then the truth will go away. But the truth will set you free - unless you like being in your liberal prison. That works for some; perhaps it does for you as well.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1373256071913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373256095480-2</Id><Topic><Title>did auto systems automate crash instead of allowing missed approach?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373254483182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>b p u c k y squared - eventually black box records will be made public Your mother is calling - time for beddy bye with our teddy bear !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373256095480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373256267756-3</Id><Title>More and more looking like Pilot's error. The Captain behind the yoke only had 43 hours with 777.</Title><Msg>And it was his first maiden flight to S.F.</Msg><Username>analysts_are_foolish_idiots</Username><Timestamp>1373256267756</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373256598478-4</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't try. They forgot already that McCain had to attain nomination from the party that is truly no longer sane. McCain is trying to rehabilitate his image before he retires.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1373256598478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373256971054-5</Id><Topic><Title>did auto systems automate crash instead of allowing missed approach?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373254483182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think he knows difference.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1373256971054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373257015115-6</Id><Topic><Title>PILOT IN TRAINING</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373245926363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:12:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong. He'd flown 747s and other airliners to SFO before. Approach speed was way too lo2, says NTSB. They tried to abort the landing. That's why the nose was high.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373257015115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373257079261-7</Id><Topic><Title>More and more looking like Pilot's error. The Captain behind the yoke only had 43 hours with 777.</Title><Username>analysts_are_foolish_idiots</Username><Timestamp>1373256267756</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:04:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true. He'd flown 747s and other airliners to SFO before.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373257079261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373257292814-8</Id><Topic><Title>PILOT IN TRAINING</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373245926363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:12:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SO REUTERS IS WRONG...?</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373257292814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373257864152-9</Id><Topic><Title>PILOT IN TRAINING</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373245926363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:12:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It may have been his first flight to SFO "with the jet". It wasn't his first flight to SFO.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373257864152</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:31:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373258241907-10</Id><Topic><Title>PILOT IN TRAINING</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373245926363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:12:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh well i flew a propeller to sfo too.. But am not qualified for 777 if i flew with guidance, hence i was in training..end of the story!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373258241907</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373258340764-11</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It shouldn't be so much a comparison of the men as the elections themselves. for some reason dictatorships really favor holding elections with one person on the ballot.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373258340764</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373258504218-12</Id><Topic><Title>here it comes - they going to blame the pilot instead of boeing</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373255541140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Azzfauk, the black box has confirmed so far that there was nothing wrong with the plane except for its altitude and speed, that points directly to the pilot error. Get a life moron.</Msg><Username>analysts_are_foolish_idiots</Username><Timestamp>1373258504218</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373258660595-13</Id><Topic><Title>here it comes - they going to blame the pilot instead of boeing</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373255541140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"keep shorting" is nothing but a screwball robot!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373258660595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373258704193-14</Id><Topic><Title>here it comes - they going to blame the pilot instead of boeing</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373255541140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...AND SO OTHERS WHO CLAIM PILOT WAS " NOT" IN TRAINING...BUNCH OF MORON'S!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373258704193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373258809853-15</Id><Topic><Title>PILOT IN TRAINING</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373245926363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 21:12:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not maiden flight to SF. First flight there in a 777. Had many hours in other planes, including 747.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373258809853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373259624490-16</Id><Title>1 of the 2 girls that died was killed by a firetruck</Title><Msg>ruh roh</Msg><Username>budfox_bachelor</Username><Timestamp>1373259624490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 01:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373260297616-17</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>H.L. Mencken, Born 1880 – Died 1956, was a journalist, satirist &amp; critic. He wrote an editorial while working for the Baltimore Evening Sun, which appeared in the July 26, 1920 edition. "As democracy is perfected, the office of President represents, more and more closely, the inner soul of the people. On some great and glorious day, the plain folks of the land will reach their heart's desire at last and the White House will be occupied by a downright fool and complete narcissistic moron." --- H.L. Mencken, The Baltimore Evening Sun, July 26, 1920</Msg><Username>jwm1031</Username><Timestamp>1373260297616</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 01:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373262634153-18</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And oligarchies favor holding elections where both candidates are tractable. See Lawrence Lessig's TED talk on "Lesterland"</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373262634153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 01:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373262747995-19</Id><Topic><Title>here it comes - they going to blame the pilot instead of boeing</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373255541140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its altitude was low because it was stalling. Why was its speed low?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373262747995</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 01:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373265575084-20</Id><Title>so the attempt to EXECUTE MISSED APPROACH failed because why?</Title><Msg>something the pilot said? doubt that. executing a missed approach is a full throttle event. isnt it true that all systems at that time should be relinquished to full pilot control? i see that the thumpers on this board and media are more interested in pumping the bull than doing the responsible thing and waiting until the systems record is released. so what is boeing saying about the missed approach turnaround capacity of this plane? i will take a guess on this... NOTHING. from the stall warning indicator to a full throttle missed approach, NOT A CORRECTION BECAUSE THE COCKPIT DID SAY MISSED APPROACH (from what i read) the only reason a plane executes a missed approach is when the current approach goes bad - no other reason my conclusion about this is that this plane cannot execute a missed approach in the seconds required to do so - my opinion.</Msg><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373265575084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 02:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373265850590-21</Id><Topic><Title>here it comes - they going to blame the pilot instead of boeing</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373255541140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure. especially by ceo's who dont want to acknowledge any responsibility whatsoever. better - such denial is also a promise not to do better. there are only to philosophpies with those types 1. make more doing less 2. make less doing more you should expect a ceo from sales and marketing is a minimalist type of person take intel for instance; put an engineer in charge, they make less money but huge advnaces and advantages in chips - good move but the greed of wallstreet is beyond repair and humility.</Msg><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373265850590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 02:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373280055270-22</Id><Title>Obama care now a complete Disaster</Title><Msg>Even before it is fully implemented, Obamacare is already starting to self-destruct. The White House announced last week it will simply invent its own interpretation of the law and “delay the enforcement” of the employer Obamacare mandate for another year, to 2015. This, we are told, is to allow businesses more time to “smooth” compliance with the law, but that’s only the cover story. In reality, the entire private sector economy was preparing to fire tens of millions of workers, cut their hours and radically downsize companies in order to avoid going bankrupt under Obamacare mandates that no one can afford.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280055270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:40:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373280087393-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama care now a complete Disaster</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280055270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:40:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Described as a “train wreck” by one of its original authors (Sen. Baucus), and called a “fiasco for the ages” by the Wall Street Journal, Obamacare is a massive government boondoggle that’s headed for complete disaster. In a desperate effort to get out of the way of that oncoming train, insurance companies are scrambling to flee the market entirely. America’s largest health insurer, UnitedHealth, has just announced it’s closing shop in California and walking away from all health insurance customers there. That’s how bad Obamacare really is, even for the insurance companies: it’s better to close up shop than even attempt to serve customers under the government’s onerous rules. U.S. businesses, meanwhile, are engaged in a new wave of job offshoring to India, Pakistan and the Philippines, where Obamacare doesn’t exist and an entire workers’ salary can be less than the cost of health insurance in the U.S. all by itself. The realization has hit everyone who owns or runs a business: Obamacare will bankrupt America’s private sector unless businesses take proactive measures to minimize the hiring U.S. workers. This is especially true in low-wage jobs — such as the food service industry — where an employee’s contribution to a business simply isn’t that valuable to begin with.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280087393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373280113134-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obama care now a complete Disaster</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280055270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:40:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When will the Obamacare train wreck completely derail? A d v e r t i s e m e n t All these are yet more signs that Obamacare’s socialist-inspired health care utopia is turning out to be a total nightmare. As we’ve predicted here on Natural News, much of the system will eventually have to be scrapped or sharply scaled back. Why? Because almost no one can afford the scheme. Employers have already begun slashing workforce hours in order to avoid the employer mandates, and individuals who need health insurance are starting to freak out over the reality that their rates are going to double or triple once Obamacare fully kicks in. Remember: This is a law that was advertised as providing either “free” or “affordable” care to everyone, including people with pre-existing conditions. What it actually turned out to be, however, was a monopoly handout to the sick-care industry and the health insurance giants. Instead of promoting health, it kept Americans trapped in a system that profits from chronic disease. Instead of being “affordable,” it’s making health insurance costs double or triple for many people. Obamacare actually designed to destroy the private sector and make everyone dependent on government There is one benefit to democrats in all this, however: the fact that employers are already firing workers and downsizing operations in anticipation of Obamacare mandates has results in millions of new people subsisting on welfare and food stamps… and that’s the ultimate goal of the socialist progressive state. The idea is to destroy the private sector economy and make everyone completely dependent on the government for their food, incomes, housing, education and health care. Only then will the collectivist utopia be fully realized, complete with a domineering spy state, tyrannical police, suffocating tax rates and selective persecution of political enemies by the IRS. Since Obama took office, food stamp rolls have exploded. From 2007 to 2011, the number of Americans on food stamps grew by 70% to 45 million, and as of 2012, food stamp expenditures have reached $75 billion a year. Over four million Americans are now on welfare, and another 5.6 million are living on unemployment insurance. In most U.S. states, welfare pays more than having an $8 / hour job! So as Obamacare kicks in, employers will start tossing people out of their jobs, forcing many of them onto precisely the spiral-of-dependence government programs the Obama administration has been desperately seeking to expand. As the number of Americans who depend on the government expands, so does voter support for whichever party happens to promise the biggest handouts… the democrats, of course. This is how democrats believe you create a perfect society: destroy all private-sector businesses and put the government in charge of everything. This is being done by design, and Obamacare is the lynchpin that will make the hiring of employees all but unaffordable for many businesses.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280113134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373280141193-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama care now a complete Disaster</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280055270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:40:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamacare delay a strategy to protect the 2014 elections The one-year delay of Obamacare is timed, no doubt, to make sure employers don’t feel the full punishment of Obamacare mandates until after the 2014 election. The White House wants to make sure voters and employers don’t fully realize just how tragic Obamacare really is when they go to the polls next year. After all, if democrats can achieve a majority in the House, they can ram through their full package of socialist, fascist policies without resistance. Right now, the House of Representatives is the only thing blocking a full-on socialist agenda that would criminalize the Second Amendment and legalize 11+ million illegal aliens so they can vote. (It’s every Democrat’s deepest fantasy!) Because once Obamacare really kicks in, all bets are off. All over America, tens of millions of workers will be getting pink slips. While those workers probably voted for Obama in the hope that their employer would be forced to provide them full health care coverage, the sobering reality is that no political mandate can alter the laws of economics. If federal law makes hiring employees prohibitively expensive, employers have little choice but to cut jobs and fire workers. No mandate from Washington can change the laws of economics Democrats, of course, tend to think that money appears as if by magic and that businesses can be forced to pay for things they can’t afford. But what they fail to recognize is that businesses always have the choice to simply go out of business or radically downsize, firing workers all the way down as they shrink below Obamacare mandate thresholds. Hence the term “49ers” which isn’t a sports franchise. It’s the nickname given to all the medium-sized businesses across America that are shedding workers to get below the 50-employee threshold where Obamacare mandates put you out of business. If you just happen to be employee number 50, 51 or 52, expect to be fired even though you’ve done nothing wrong. Thank Obama for forcing your employer to shrink to 49 employees. So all those Americans who suddenly find themselves jobless can thank Obama, Pelosi and all the other nincompoops in Washington for yet more socialist incompetence. What they all fail to realize is that there’s no such thing as a free lunch. Not even if it’s mandated by the White House. The laws of economics do not bow down to any president. Thanks to Obama’s delay of Obamacare until 2015, however, you may get to hold on to your job for another year. But unless you’re in a high-level position where your employer can’t live without you, be prepared to hit the street in late 2014 as companies start slashing jobs in a desperate bid to meet the “49er” requirement. You’ll be joined by a wave of other recently-jobless who were also let go because of Obamacare mandates. Good luck finding employment anywhere, since you’ll have loads of competition at precisely the same time no company wants to cross the 50-employee threshold. Thanks, Obama, for causing even more Americans to lose their jobs. It’s one more score for the same President that has expanded Gitmo, kept marijuana criminalized, refused to label GMOs and scaled up a massive domestic surveillance infrastructure run by the NSA. Is there anything Obama promised that hasn’t ended in complete betrayal?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280141193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373280476079-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama care now a complete Disaster</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280055270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:40:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven likes that.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373280476079</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:47:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373280557367-27</Id><Title>SHORTS GET NAILED AGAIN!!!!!</Title><Msg>Once again BA planes show there are superior to AIRBUST.Pilot error caused thie crash.If this was an AIRBUST plane alot more people probably would have died.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1373280557367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373281813607-28</Id><Title>101.61 bid</Title><Msg>short now ask questions later.</Msg><Username>didyousay226npa</Username><Timestamp>1373281813607</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 07:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373283115255-29</Id><Title>TSA conducted pat downs of family members of crash victims</Title><Msg>“Some passengers were found wandering, dazed, near the wreckage. Others made a beeline for the international terminal, where they waited for as long as five hours to be reunited with panicked friends and family.” The process was made more difficult, and slower, by a series of screenings conducted by the Transportation Security Administration, police said. Officials spent hours interviewing passengers inside the international departure gates. To get into the boarding area to meet up with them, loved ones were interviewed, searched and vetted by TSA officials. The vetting included checking that family names matched up and that the passengers knew the people trying to get through the security area. One by one, relatives walked through the glass doors that separate the terminal from the gates, hoping the children or spouses they had not heard from would be waiting inside.” In many ways this represents the worst example of TSA abuse ever recorded, underscoring the depth to which the federal agency’s regulations are mindlessly enforced with no consideration for circumstances whatsoever.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373283115255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 07:31:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373283268142-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama care now a complete Disaster</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280055270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:40:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama took something that was not perfect but manageable and turned it into a disaster. The man is truly a Manchurian candidate that is terrorizing America and turning it into a third World communist state...per the Dreams of his REAL Father...Frank Marshall Davis.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373283268142</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 07:34:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373283467492-31</Id><Title>104.35 up 15cents</Title><Msg>Shorts attention!!!! Get out the KY</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1373283467492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 07:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373284934932-32</Id><Title>#$%$ cnbc ba segment</Title><Msg>analyst said plane not to blame; ba gaining on airbus; on track for record q; delivering 5 dreamliners monthly on way to 7mth; joe k had no idea what to ask; nothing bad for ba but terrible segment</Msg><Username>vvvvvvrebel89130</Username><Timestamp>1373284934932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373285101536-33</Id><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Msg>LOL at the republicans, they are scared to death because they see it will be great. So they run articles saying it will raise cost n those who are paying $64 a month for insurance. WHo is paying that, total lie.</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373285371127-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your a complete idiot</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373285371127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373285672456-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I pay $900 a month currently, why would I not be happy to pay less. Why is there never an article like that</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285672456</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373286777928-36</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$ cnbc ba segment</Title><Username>vvvvvvrebel89130</Username><Timestamp>1373284934932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:02:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually was an excellent segment and honest opinion....take it to the bank!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373286777928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:32:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373287150628-37</Id><Title>777 crash TOTALLY UNRELATED TO AIRCRAFT !!!......PILOT ERROR AGAIN....!!!!</Title><Msg>Of course the stock will dip because of this accident because of so many dipsticks who act like Chicken Little and think this means the sky is falling. Pilot was inexperienced AND flying into an unfamiliar airport!!!! It's a testament to the aircraft's crash survivability than more people weren't killed or injured...!!! You know this if you are a rational investor.</Msg><Username>god_is_my_copilot</Username><Timestamp>1373287150628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:39:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373287570334-38</Id><Topic><Title>777 crash TOTALLY UNRELATED TO AIRCRAFT !!!......PILOT ERROR AGAIN....!!!!</Title><Username>god_is_my_copilot</Username><Timestamp>1373287150628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:39:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EXACTLY THE PLANE IS THE HERO...THE STOCK IS NOT EVEN DIPPING....$108- 110 BY EARNINGS ...$ 120+++++ BY YEAR'S END!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373287570334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373289569630-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did a government program ever save money? Keep dreaming.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1373289569630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 09:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373289643330-40</Id><Title>Go ahead and Short BA!!!</Title><Msg>you will lose. Blaming BA for this accident would be like @didyousay226npa crashing his bug into a tree and blaming Volkswagen. The quality of this plane likely prevented many more deaths. BA will come out of this accident very well. More airlines will be looking to upgrade to new BA planes.</Msg><Username>james.castalano</Username><Timestamp>1373289643330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 09:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373290292642-41</Id><Topic><Title>so the attempt to EXECUTE MISSED APPROACH failed because why?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373265575084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 02:39:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, Isn't it the least bit obvious that the decision to go missed was just a tad late? C'mon, severe clear with winds calm gusting to zero and this guy hits the seawall... Don't think it was the fault of the aircraft.........</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1373290292642</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 09:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373291754772-42</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True enough--description of W is spot on and glad he's gone.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1373291754772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 09:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373292015377-43</Id><Title>BA Should ba 110 soon...</Title><Msg>As soon as the dust settles again... ;-)</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1373292015377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373292081086-44</Id><Topic><Title>BA Should ba 110 soon...</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1373292015377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA Should BE rather ;-)</Msg><Username>cnarntz</Username><Timestamp>1373292081086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373292302648-45</Id><Topic><Title>BA Should ba 110 soon...</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1373292015377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$ 108-110 BY EARNINGS...$ 120+++++ BY YEAR END...TAKE IT TO THE BANK!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373292302648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373292303001-46</Id><Title>weird market - boeing should be up 5-10% after the plane crash</Title><Msg>that is how this sick wall street market works</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373292303001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373292648682-47</Id><Title>Breaking News BISU -- DIABETES CURE!!</Title><Msg>MONSTER NEWS!!</Msg><Username>sara.kljkl</Username><Timestamp>1373292648682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373293836608-48</Id><Topic><Title>BA Should ba 110 soon...</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1373292015377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like some folks loaded sell orders over the weekend before they had all the facts on teh crash. THey seem to have pretty much cleared them all out and we can get back to seeing the upward stock price trend..</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373293836608</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373293995634-49</Id><Title>cant believe boeing is not green - the plane crash is bullish</Title><Msg>should hit $105 by close</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373293995634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:33:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373294365139-50</Id><Topic><Title>BA Should ba 110 soon...</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1373292015377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thumbs up for you my friend ...so correct you are...</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373294365139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373295323038-51</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know I'm talking about the idiot in the WH now.</Msg><Username>jwm1031</Username><Timestamp>1373295323038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373295794006-52</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why post this irrelevant nonsense on an investment board for BA?</Msg><Username>renaultd0</Username><Timestamp>1373295794006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373295906150-53</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not paying attention to the messages in this thread started by the racist. Instead Chris I am pleased you posted my style no more than four words a line. Therefore, let me complement with your own words: He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373295906150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373295979847-54</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another not so big day after a very long weekend recovering after vacation.... 9:30 AM The President and the Vice President receive the Presidential Daily Briefing 10:30 AM The President holds a Cabinet Meeting; The Vice President also attends 11:50 AM The President makes a statement on his Management Agenda</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373295979847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:06:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373296147082-55</Id><Topic><Title>cant believe boeing is not green - the plane crash is bullish</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373293995634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:33:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here we go! if only that plane exploded, stock would hit $115 today</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373296147082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373296269772-56</Id><Topic><Title>cant believe boeing is not green - the plane crash is bullish</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373293995634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:33:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHY ARE YOU SUCH A DOPE...AMAZING!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373296269772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373296293955-57</Id><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Msg>anybody? he won't update his topic page with latest greatest thread (he won't allow "white house schedule" on the topic page. let's see if he lets this one through his fascist filter</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373296350815-58</Id><Title>spazticus won't allow my posts to appear on topic page</Title><Msg>wonder why that is?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296350815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:12:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373296467847-59</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't agree with "deliberately" but they definitely sabotaged their own chances by running a stiff cardboard cutout in place of a real man who could, at least in appearance, relate to the masses. Better luck next time. You would have done better to run that wacko, Sarah Palin. You think I'm joking........</Msg><Username>major_kudos</Username><Timestamp>1373296467847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373296503200-60</Id><Topic><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come you whine constantly? you remind me of one of my ex wives.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373296503200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373296665305-61</Id><Title>Pilot error. As I said. Even the airline company is leaning in that direction</Title><Msg>It's almost always pilot error. Boeing makes amazing planes and the people that work for this company, all the way down the person who empties out wastebaskets all day, are proud to work for it.</Msg><Username>big_mugumboo</Username><Timestamp>1373296665305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373297728423-62</Id><Topic><Title>Pilot error. As I said. Even the airline company is leaning in that direction</Title><Username>big_mugumboo</Username><Timestamp>1373296665305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when you get em too slow they seem to fall out of the sky dont they? For what ever reason the pilots misjudged the end of the runway and apparently would have had a wunner ful if wet landing had they not tried to go around</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373297728423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373297874514-63</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will you pro slavers reinstitute the slave patrols or just continue to rely on the coocluchsclan after you complete your takeover of the US govt</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373297874514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373298163820-64</Id><Topic><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus censor bumper fascist delusions of persecution mindless drivelmonger probable brain damage.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1373298163820</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:42:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373298660232-65</Id><Topic><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i don't imagine the clone (&amp; ID) queen is on the receiving end of his party's fascist suppression, he's an ACORN, paid to peddle disinformation and agitate for the barack hussein's regime / party</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373298660232</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373299444484-66</Id><Topic><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually dude you remind me of both my ex wives in the same room together. not one freaking bit of sense could be made out of anything.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373299444484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373299703227-67</Id><Topic><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no need to change IDs just for me roksta...rainbow sparty used to make up stories about being married too</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373299703227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373299767406-68</Id><Topic><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you we not so stupid you could be funny.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373299767406</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:09:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373299998061-69</Id><Topic><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so says the stay at home, taxpayer dependent, mobro...i mean sparty, err roksta</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373299998061</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373300003863-70</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, MB. But you DO realize I posted that a month ago ... right?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373300003863</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373300027145-71</Id><Title>DOES NOT MATTER WHAT YOU DO, MATTERS WHAT MONEY MANAGERS DO.</Title><Msg>I SEE THE STOCK UP AGAIN....</Msg><Username>jack_hoff_often</Username><Timestamp>1373300027145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373300220525-72</Id><Topic><Title>weird market - boeing should be up 5-10% after the plane crash</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373292303001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you participate in a sick market, you are as sick as anyone else.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373300220525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373300338506-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Marshall Plan. It saved us all the money of fighting WW3</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373300338506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373300426437-74</Id><Topic><Title>Obama care now a complete Disaster</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280055270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:40:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are insane.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373300426437</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373300484741-75</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>andse...been awhile since I've seen that ID, once a liar always a liar...no matter the ID</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373300484741</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373300704307-76</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We know Genna is pro slavery - he may try to dance around the issue and try to justify it as necessary to have a civilized society but the truth is, he thinks involuntary servitude is perfectly alright as long as the government puts its stamp of approval on its ability to take what one person earns and give it to someone who didn't earn it.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373300704307</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373300731294-77</Id><Topic><Title>How come spazticus, board censor and moderator, won't allow white house schedule thread updates?</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296293955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:11:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you ever get a clue or do you just force your head deeper into the darkness? you give me material for a new song to write lol something like a dark mental midget and the voices in his head. let me get to work on it .</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373300731294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373300890390-78</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus67517. It appears to me that the idiot is the one who doesn't know how to write :"you're" and writes "your"</Msg><Username>mailinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1373300890390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373301095104-79</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hahahahaha. What a troll.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373301095104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373301130726-80</Id><Topic><Title>here it comes - they going to blame the pilot instead of boeing</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373255541140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm surprised nobody is blaming GW!</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1373301130726</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373301495492-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>somebody's been fumbling through their ID bag...same dope peddler behind the ID though, lying bothers him not the least...in this respect he closely resembles his dear leader, our occupier n thief</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373301495492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373301636248-82</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>c4f, if you don't like taxes you are free to move to a Banana Republic. Please do so.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373301636248</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373301806243-83</Id><Topic><Title>spazticus won't allow my posts to appear on topic page</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373296350815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:12:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your question assumes facts not in evidence. It's no surprise that you are very, very confused.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373301806243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:43:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373302716468-84</Id><Title>The Myth that the Democrat Party is the Party of the "Little Guy"</Title><Msg>Who did Obama bale out with tarp: Certainly not the "little guy" or mom and pop businesses......Try Huge fat Cat Bankers and big corporations. Who got the Stimulus money - nope it wasn't "little guys" or mom and pop businesses. It was green energy companies but not just any green energy company......it was ones that made huge donations to Obama's campaign. Now who is getting to delay the implementation of Obamacare - Nope not the "little guy" ......it's only the large corporation. The little guy will see his insurance premiums skyrocket.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373302716468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373302725966-85</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just figured out how much money I will be saving by not having health insurance (or fire insurance or car insurance) I just wait till I get sick, have a fire or am involved in a car accident and then and only then will I get my insurance coverage, In the meantime I will sell my insurance stock.</Msg><Username>mailinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1373302725966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373303331844-86</Id><Title>So 107 is the historical high, you said?</Title><Msg>That one will be history faster than Obama.. LMAO.. Smell 120 yet?</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373303331844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373303430949-87</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is there still an American military presence in Germany? Duck and cover. I suspect you were born shortly after WWII. How much money and American blood was spent fighting that. When have you really ever really known peace. Korean war (still on going since 1950) Viet Nam (from which you suffer from today) Bay of Pigs Grenada Panama Persian Gulf Bosnia/Herzegovina Afghanistan (11 years and counting) Iraq and numerous other little conflicts requiring American money and blood ie Libya. Our military presence is located throughout the world on both land and sea.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373303430949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373303514450-88</Id><Topic><Title>Obama care now a complete Disaster</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373280055270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:40:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>compared too what?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373303514450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373303656371-89</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let us know when you pay less.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373303656371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373303921397-90</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will save me $400 a month</Title><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373285101536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:05:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamacare will only save you money if you get you vaginal exams and STD treatment at the community health clinic......otherwise you will pay more.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373303921397</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373304030530-91</Id><Title>Morsi Obama</Title><Msg>What's the difference...equally sinister, one is more dishonest</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373304030530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373304347042-92</Id><Title>State Department Officer Traded Visas for Sexual Favors</Title><Msg>The State Department seems to have a sexual exploitation problem on its hands. Three weeks ago we learned from a State Department whistleblower who works inside the Inspector General office that officials interfered with internal investigations into sexual misconduct. That misconduct included a US Ambassador soliciting sexual favors from prostitutes and minors. Now, we're learning a U.S. Embassy official has been removed for allegedly trading visas for sexual favors. Charles Johnson has more: A State Department officer has been accused of selling visas for sex and money in what may have been a massive human trafficking operation, The Daily Caller has learned. The State Department acknowledged last week that one of its officials is the target of a probe over “allegations of improprieties relating to a Consular Officer formerly assigned to Georgetown, Guyana” without providing further details. Local media are also claiming the official, who was recently withdrawn from normal duties pending completion of an official investigation, associated with drug lords as part of his visa scam. The scandal began when executives and tourists complained that their visa applications were being held up, and local media began reporting that a visa official was demanding bribes and sex in exchange for visas. Penalties for human trafficking are stiff in the United States and the State Department is supposed to sanction countries when their officials engage in sexual exploitation of trafficked victims. Human trafficking is a serious federal crime with penalties of up to imprisonment for life. Federal law defines “severe forms of trafficking in persons” as: “(A) sex trafficking in which a commercial sex act is induced by force, fraud, or coercion, or in which the person induced to perform such act has not attained 18 years of age; or (B) the recruitment, harboring, transportation, provision, or obtaining of a person for labor or services, through the use of force, fraud, or coercion for the purpose of subjection to involuntary servitude, peonage, debt bondage, or slavery.” [U.S.C. §7102(8)] In short, human trafficking is modern-day slavery. The State Department is clearly experiencing an epidemic of sexual exploitation in a culture of irresponsibility despite claiming to fight sex trafficking on its website. "It ought to concern every person, because it is a debasement of our common humanity. It ought to concern every community, because it tears at our social fabric. It ought to concern every business, because it distorts markets. It ought to concern every nation, because it endangers public health and fuels violence and organized crime. I’m talking about the injustice, the outrage, of human trafficking, which must be called by its true name -- modern slavery." – President Barack Obama And as a reminder, the Department of Justice has been ignoring the sex trafficking of minors for years under Attorney General Eric Holder. Crimes involving minors are meant to trigger an immediate and swift response by the FBI. Instead, these cases were not pursued by the Bureau.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373304347042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373304606462-93</Id><Title>Obamacare Subsidies: Brought To You By the Honor System</Title><Msg>On the heels of Tuesday's report that Obamacare's employer mandate would be delayed by a year, the Obama Administration delayed income-verification requirements for health exchange subsidies. This is another piece of the unraveling that has continued to take place even as the Obama administration has pressed forward with implementation. From the Washington Post's report: The verification systems are meant to determine who qualifies for new benefits under the Affordable Care Act. The law includes tax subsidies to purchase health insurance for Americans who earn less than 400 percent of the poverty line, about $45,000 for an individual. After encountering “legislative and operational barriers,” the federal government will not require the District and the 16 states that are running their own marketplaces to verify a consumer’s statement that they do not receive health insurance from their employer... The rule also scaled back states’ responsibilities to double-check the income levels that consumers report, which determine any tax subsidy they receive. Avik Roy writes that this is an example of President Obama's attitude of "subsidize first, ask questions later," and that it's a predictable consequence of the Obama administration being completely unprepared for the bureaucratic nightmare that is Obamacare: According to the law, you aren’t eligible for Obamacare’s subsidies if your employer has offered you what the government considers “affordable” coverage. But if employers are no longer going to report whether or not they’ve offered “affordable” coverage, how can the government verify whether or not workers are eligible for subsidies? Now we know the answer. The government is going with what Kliff and Somashekhar call “the honor system.” “We have concluded that the…proposed rule is not feasible for implementation for the first year of operations,” say the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services. The feds will also allow people to gain means-tested subsidized coverage on the exchanges without having to…test their means. There have not been any penalties outlined for people who lie to the government in order to receive insurance subsidies, but there's surely a small contingent of people who are put off by lying to the government in general. Nonetheless, considering fraud runs rampant through other government health programs, it's safe to say that we can expect that to be the case here as well. Roy also points to his colleague, who has suggested that the entirety of Obamacare be delayed by a year. At the rate that implementation is going, that may very well be the case. Obamacare is the law of the land, but it's still troubling that the Obama administration has decided it can selectively determine when certain parts of the law will actually affect Americans.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373304606462</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373304952734-94</Id><Topic><Title>weird market - boeing should be up 5-10% after the plane crash</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373292303001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you've been in cash since Dow 11,000?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373304952734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373305241750-95</Id><Title>Real crash test shows BA is the plane to go...</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373305241750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373305288908-96</Id><Topic><Title>weird market - boeing should be up 5-10% after the plane crash</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373292303001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, since the DOW was 11,000 in 1999. how about u?</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373305288908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373305321694-97</Id><Topic><Title>Real crash test shows BA is the plane to go...</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373305241750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:40:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Survivors will txll you to board BA planes only.. LMAO.,</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373305321694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373305325043-98</Id><Title>Up up and away</Title><Msg>we go</Msg><Username>endicotsteel</Username><Timestamp>1373305325043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373305336078-99</Id><Title>BOEING HITS 52 WEEK HIGHS ON NEWS OF THEIR PLANE CRASHING</Title><Msg>Gotta love this market. pilot error? sure! these planes fly by wire!!!</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373305336078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373305374983-100</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone herded into thinking its safe lol- ba down 7 next 2 days</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1373211956789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 11:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I said. This #$%$ hat is always wrong its uncanny.</Msg><Username>endicotsteel</Username><Timestamp>1373305374983</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373305496814-101</Id><Topic><Title>Real crash test shows BA is the plane to go...</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373305241750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:40:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373305496814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373305629870-102</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why move.....we have one right here.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373305629870</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373305639392-103</Id><Title>Real life crash tests tells you</Title><Msg>Survivors have time to take personal luggage.. Confidence?</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373305639392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373305874426-104</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone herded into thinking its safe lol- ba down 7 next 2 days</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1373211956789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 11:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cwtripps is the biggest jinx in stock market history.</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373305874426</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373306119749-105</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone herded into thinking its safe lol- ba down 7 next 2 days</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1373211956789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 11:45:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's infamous for bad calls on every stock board. I knew this would go up once he appeared and bashed it. What is really sad is he probably has no position in it. Just shows up and bashes for no reason.</Msg><Username>endicotsteel</Username><Timestamp>1373306119749</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373307392489-106</Id><Title>benghazi - search on it</Title><Msg>40 Minutes In Benghazi When U.S. ambassador J. Christopher Stevens was killed in a flash of hatred in Benghazi, Libya, on September 11, 2012, the political finger-pointing began. But few knew exactly what had happened that night. With the ticktock narrative of the desperate fight to save Stevens, Fred Burton and Samuel M. Katz provide answers. By Fred Burton and Samuel M. Katz its on vanity fair</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373307392489</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373307630866-107</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Caps4free-tell us what you think and believe, not what anyone else thinks and believes.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373307630866</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373307662378-108</Id><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Msg>By E.J. Dionne, Jr. WASHINGTON—Here is the sentence in the Declaration of Independence we always remember: “We hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men are created equal, that they are endowed by their creator with certain unalienable rights, that among these are life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness.” And here is the sentence we often forget: “And for the support of this declaration, with a firm reliance on the protection of divine providence, we mutually pledge to each other our lives, our fortunes and our sacred honor.” This, the very last sentence of the document, is what makes the better-remembered sentence possible. One speaks of our rights. The other addresses our obligations. The freedoms we cherish are self-evident but not self-executing. The Founders pledge something “to each other,” the commonly overlooked clause in the Declaration’s final pronouncement. We find ourselves, 237 years after the Founders declared us a new nation, in a season of discontent, even surliness, about the experiment they launched. We are sharply divided over the very meaning our founding documents, and we are more likely to invoke the word “we” in the context of “us” versus “them” than in the more capacious sense that includes every single American. There are no quick fixes to our sense of disconnection, but there may be a way to restore our sense of what we owe each other across the lines of class, race, background—and, yes, politics and ideology. Advertisement Last week, the Aspen Institute gathered a politically diverse group of Americans under the banner of the “Franklin Project,” named after Ben, to declare a commitment to offering every American between the ages of 18 and 28 a chance to give a year of service to the country. The opportunities would include service in our armed forces but also time spent in educating our fellow citizens, bringing them health care and preventive services, working with the least advantaged among us, and conserving our environment. Service would not be compulsory, but it would be an expectation. And it just might become part of who we are. The call for universal, voluntary service is being championed by retired Gen. Stanley McChrystal, in league with two of the country’s foremost advocates of the cause, John Bridgeland, who served in President George W. Bush’s administration, and Alan Khazei, co-founder of City Year, one of the nation’s most formidable volunteer groups. The trio testifies to the non-ideological and nonpartisan nature of this cause, as did a column last week endorsing the idea from Michael Gerson, my conservative Washington Post colleague. “We’ve a remarkable opportunity now,” McChrystal said, “to move with the American people away from an easy citizenship that does not ask something from every American yet asks a lot from a tiny few.” We do, indeed, owe something to our country, and we owe an enormous debt to those who have done tour after tour in Iraq and Afghanistan. McChrystal sees universal service as transformative. “It will change how we think about America and how we think about ourselves,” he says. And as a former leader of an all-volunteer Army, he scoffs at the idea that giving young Americans a stipend while they serve amounts to “paid volunteerism,” the phrase typically invoked by critics of service programs. “If you try to rely on unpaid volunteerism,” he said, “then you limit the people who can do it. ... I’d like the people from Scarsdale to be paid the same as the people from East LA.” There are real challenges here. Creating the estimated 1 million service slots required to make the prospect of service truly universal will take money, from government and private philanthropy. Service, as McChrystal says, cannot just be a nice thing that well-off kids do when they get out of college. It has to draw in the least advantaged young Americans. In the process, it could open new avenues for social mobility, something the military has done for so many in the past. Who knows if the universal expectation of service would change the country as much as McChrystal hopes. But we have precious few institutions reminding us to join the Founders in pledging something to each other. We could begin by debating this proposal in a way that frees us from the poisonous assumption that even an idea involving service to others must be part of some hidden political agenda. The agenda here is entirely open. It’s based on the belief that certain unalienable rights entail certain unavoidable responsibilities.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373307733157-109</Id><Title>Secretary of State Kerry's</Title><Msg>Wife hospitalized due to seizure.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373307733157</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373308080766-110</Id><Title>110 before ER date.</Title><Msg>No seller remorse no more.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373308080766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373308612294-111</Id><Title>Rick Perry Won't Run Again</Title><Msg>My prayers ARE answered!</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373308612294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373309061866-112</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry Won't Run Again</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373308612294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:36:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's tough for a state to have a leader who bears so much animosity toward certain factions of the populace.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373309061866</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373309138829-113</Id><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Msg>Remember when George Bush said we had to suspend the free market to save the free market? It was hogwash then and is still hog wash today. We should have let those banks fail.....that's how the free market works. Now we have Democrats saying we have to use the uncivilized behavior of involuntary servitude in order to have a civilized country. That's more total hogwash. Voluntary charity to help those truly in need is civilized. Involuntary servitude is only as civilized as slavery or theft is..</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373309654993-114</Id><Title>Econ 101 is killing America</Title><Msg>In the Middle Ages, people looked to the Church for certainty. In today’s complex, market-based economies, they look to the field of economics, at least for answers to questions concerning the economy. And unlike some disciplines, which acknowledge that there’s a huge gap between the scholarly knowledge and policy advice, economists have been anything but shy about asserting their authority. As we can see from the current dismal state of economic affairs, economies are incredibly complex systems, and policymakers who are forced to act in the face of this uncertainty and complexity want guidance. And over the last half century, neoclassical economists have not only been more than happy to offer it, but largely been able to marginalize any other disciplines or approaches, giving them a virtual monopoly on economic policy advice. But there are two big problems with this. First, despite economists’ calming assurances, we still know little about how economies actually work and the effect of policies. If we did, then economists should have sounded the alarm bells to head off the financial collapse and Great Recession. But even more problematic, even though most economists know better, they present to the public, the media and politicians a simplified, vulgar version of neoclassical economics — what can be called Econ 101 — that leads policymakers astray. Economists fear that if they really expose policymakers to all the contradictions, uncertainties and complications of “Advanced Econ,” the latter will go off track — embracing protectionism, heavy-handed “industrial policy” or even socialism. In fact, the myths of Econ 101 already lead policymakers dangerously off track, with tragic results for the economy and everyday Americans. Myth 1: Economics is a science. The way economists maintain stature in public policy circles is to present their discipline as a science, akin to physics. In Econ 101, there is no uncertainty, only the obvious truths embedded in supply and demand curves. As noted economist Lionel Robbins wrote, “Economics is the science which studies human behavior as a relationship between given ends and scarce means, which have alternative uses.” If economics is actually a science, then policymakers can feel more comfortable following the advice of economists. But if economics is really a science – which implies only one answer to a particular question — why do 40 percent of surveyed economists agree that raising the minimum wage would make it harder for people to get jobs while 40 percent disagree? It’s because as Larry Lindsey, former head of President Bush’s National Economic Council, admitted, “the continuing argument [among economists] is a product of philosophical disagreements about human nature and the role of government and cannot be fully resolved by economists no matter how sound their data.” -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Myth 2: The goal of economic policy is maximizing efficiency. Economists have one overarching principle that shapes their advice: maximize “efficiency.” As economist and venture investor William Janeway notes, “Efficiency is the virtue of economics.” But the goal of economic policy should not be to maximize static efficiency (the “right” allocation of widgets), but to create inefficiency — in the sense of disruptive innovation that makes widgets worthless. For it is the development of new widgets and better ways to make them (e.g., innovation), rather than efficiently allocating existing widgets, that drives prosperity. As noted “innovation” economist Joseph Schumpeter pointed out: “A system which is efficient in the static sense at every point in time can be inferior to a system which is never efficient in this sense, because the reason for its static inefficiency can be the driver for its long-term performance.” Myth 3: The economy is a market. In the world of Econ 101, “the economy” is usually treated as a synonym for “the market.” But an enormous amount of economic activity takes place outside of competitive markets dominated by for-profit, private firms. In the industrial nations of the OECD, government spending at all levels on average accounted for 46 percent before the Great Recession. Even in capitalist countries, the government is usually the largest employer, and the largest consumer of goods and services in areas like defense, education and infrastructure. Other non-market sectors responsible for goods and services production include the household (your chores are economic activity too, even if Econ 101 ignores them) and nonprofits like religious institutions, colleges and universities, charities and think tanks like ours. Markets, then, account for around half of a modern nation’s economic activity — maybe less, if uncounted household production is as big a part of the real economy as some have claimed. Myth 4: Prices reflect value. If the economy is a market, prices are what allow goods and services to be efficiently allocated. In Econ 101, because prices are set in “free markets,” the price of something must be a reflection of its real value. This principle — known as the efficient market hypothesis — was the reason why, when in the run-up to the Great Recession real house prices increased 40 percent (a more than seven-fold increase from decades prior), virtually no economist sounded the alarm, precisely because those higher prices must have reflected higher value. This is why Ben Bernanke stated in 2005 that rising home prices “largely reflect strong economic fundamentals” and Fed chairman Alan Greenspan assured us that, “It doesn’t appear likely that a national housing bubble, which could pop and send prices tumbling, will develop.” Had economists not been in the grip of the efficient market hypothesis, they would have realized that something was seriously amiss and helped rein in lending to reduce the bubble and subsequent collapse. But if they tell policymakers that prices don’t always reflect value, then the entire foundation of Econ 101 starts to crumble. Myth 5: All profitable activities are good for the economy. Another axiom of Econ 101 is the assumption that all profitable activities are good for the economy: After all, Adam Smith “proved” that pursuit of self-interest maximizes economic welfare. To be sure, even Econ 101 would recognize that societies use legal penalties to discourage economic transactions like prostitution and drug use that are considered immoral, to say nothing of Mafia contract killing. But the version of Econ 101 familiar to most politicians and pundits ignores the distinction between productive activities (e.g., making useful appliances or lifesaving vaccines) and pure rents (profiting from real estate appreciation, stock manipulation or the accident of owning mineral deposits that become more valuable). If the greatest fortunes are to be made in financial arbitrage, gambling in real estate or exploiting crony-capitalist political connections, the argument that private profit-seeking maximizes economic welfare and the public good is undermined. Myth 6: Monopolies and oligopolies are always bad because they distort prices. In the abstract universe of Econ 101, monopolies and oligopolies are always bad because they distort prices. Here populism, often opposed to neoclassical economics, is allied with it. The neoclassical vision of the normal economy with multiple small yeoman producers resonates with Jeffersonian antitrust policy, with its suspicion that all large enterprises must be conspiracies against the public. In the real world, things are not that simple. Academic economics includes a well-developed literature about imperfect markets. But it is reserved for advanced students and is never encountered by those who are told only the simplicities of Econ 101. In manufacturing industries with increasing returns to scale, like semiconductor or airplane production, markets characterized by a few large producers are usually more productive and innovative than ones with many small producers. The same is usually true in industries characterized by network effects, like railroads or communications infrastructures such as wired or wireless broadband. And as Joseph Schumpeter pointed out, temporary monopolies based on technological innovation are not only beneficial but are key enablers of seeding further innovation — particularly if the “innovation rents” or super-profits are funneled back into R&amp;D. Myth 7: Low wages are good for the economy. According to Econ 101, high wages are bad for an economy and low wages are a blessing. James Dorn of the libertarian Cato Institute declares that higher wages, by causing less demand for workers, mean that “unemployment will increase … No legislator has ever overturned the law of demand.” High-wage countries, we are told, price themselves out of a supposed global labor market. And in the non-traded domestic service sector in which most Americans work, a higher minimum wage, Econ 101 claims, would lead to permanent higher unemployment. When it comes to traded goods and services, this ignores the effects of relative currency values being the major determinant of prices of exports and imports. It also ignores the fact that high-wage workers who are highly productive, thanks to their machines and skills, can produce more cheaply than poorly paid workers with inferior technologies and skills. According to the Asian Development Bank, most of the high-value-added components of iPhones, which are assembled in China, actually come from high-wage nations like Germany, Japan, South Korea and the U.S. Michael E. Porter and Jan Rivkin state flatly in the Harvard Business Review: “Low American wages do not boost competitiveness,” which they define to mean that “companies operating in the U.S. are able to compete successfully in the global economy while supporting high and rising living standards for the average American …” The countries that beat the U.S. in the latest competitiveness rankings by the World Economic Forum are all high-wage nations: Switzerland, Singapore, Finland, Sweden, the Netherlands and Germany. In industries that cannot be outsourced, labor is only one of several factors of production that can be substituted for one another. Writing in defense of low-wage immigrant farmworker programs in the progressive magazine Mother Jones, Kevin Drum claims: “Most Americans just aren’t willing to do backbreaking agricultural labor for a bit above minimum wage, and if the wage rate were much higher the farms would no longer be competitive.” But if American farmworkers were paid better, then U.S. agribusiness would have an incentive to cut costs using technology, like automated tomato picking machines, as the agricultural sectors of Japan, Australia and other high-wage nations have done. While transitional unemployment as a result of innovation always has to be dealt with, the effects of high wages in encouraging investment in labor-saving technology should be welcomed, not deplored. Myth 8: “Industrial policy” is bad. Econ 101 tells us that letting markets determine how many “widgets” to produce maximizes efficiency. The worst thing government can do is engage in “industrial policy” — a catch-all pejorative used to discredit everything from funding solar energy companies to encouraging more college students to major in science. As former Bush economic adviser Gregory Mankiw stated: “Policymakers should not try to determine precisely which jobs are created, or which industries grow. If government bureaucrats were capable of such foresight, the Soviet Union would have succeeded.” In other words, how can government bureaucrats make better choices than business? Leaving aside the fact that banks issued trillions of dollars of bad loans leading to the financial crisis, for many investments private and public rates of return differ, often quite significantly. And unless society (through government) tilts investment to those activities where the public rate of return is higher (e.g., scientific research), growth will be less. If this is industrial policy, so be it. Myth 9: The best tax code is one that doesn’t pick winners. Econ 101 disparages industrial policy, even, or perhaps especially, when it is used in the tax code. Economists call anything other than a completely neutral tax code “distortions,” “special interest tax breaks,” “corporate welfare” or, as the Simpson-Bowles Commission labeled them, “perverse economic incentives instead of a level playing field.” Economists disdain tax incentives because in the words of the Obama administration’s Recovery Advisory Board, “certain assets and investments are tax favored, tax considerations drive overinvestment in those assets at the expense of more economically productive investments.” But as Canadian Treasury economist Aleb ab Iorwerth writes, “Distortions that favor the contributors to long-run growth will be welfare-enhancing.” In other words, tax “distortions” like the R&amp;D tax credit or accelerated depreciation for investments in new equipment lead to more growth since these investments are more productive than others and have significant positive externalities. Myth 10: Trade is always win-win. That trade always benefits both parties is perhaps the most fundamental dogma that people take away from their Econ 101 courses. In discussing trade theory with students and politicians, academic economists use fairy tales rather than history. There is the fairy tale about comparative advantage: England was good at producing wool, Portugal wine, so they trade and both are better off. There is the fairy tale about how because market transactions are always voluntary and always beneficial that trade, being simply a market transaction across borders, is always win-win. But Econ 101 never explains how nations like America, Britain, Germany and Japan have used national industrial policies over the past century to become industrial powerhouses. And Econ 101 never explains how foreign mercantilist practices, like those China is embracing, can hurt the U.S. economy. Higher-level students are sometimes introduced to the complexities of real-world trade, but academic economists fear that sharing nuances with the general public would unleash an epidemic of know-nothing protectionism. But for most of the production of traded goods and services, comparative advantage is meaningless – the Koreans and Japanese are not good at making flat panel displays because they have a lot of sand, they are good at it because their corporations and governments targeted it for competitive advantage. Moreover, corporations locate their subsidiaries in particular nation-states to take advantage of local government subsidies and tax breaks or increasingly because of government requirements to produce locally. Econ 101 to the contrary, the location of factories and innovative research complexes is not determined by comparative advantage. Increasingly it is the artificial outcome of negotiations among multinational corporations and territorial states. And the outcome of this “free trade” can be detrimental to the U.S. economy if it hurts, as it has, key U.S. high value-added industries. Conclusion When the U.S. economy faced little competition and was largely based on industrial mass production industries, it was perhaps not so bad that policymakers relied on Econ 101 as their guide to economic policy. But in a complex, global, technologically driven economy in which nation-states compete to capture markets and key links in global supply chains, relying on Econ 101 is like a physicist today relying on Newton. It’s time for economists to fess up and admit that theirs is not a science and that what passes for Econ 101 is largely misleading. But the public, the media and politicians shouldn’t wait, for it may be a long, long time coming. Rather, they need to understand that a dumbed-down Econ 101 version of neoclassical economics no longer should serve as a road map for economic policy.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373309654993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373309665800-115</Id><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Msg>I don't know WHY the media is not telling us this. One more thing is that the ONLY reason so many people survived is that most everyone walked out of the broken fuselage hole at the back of the plane (this hole is a MIRACLE because without this 15 foot by 25 foot opening in the rear, level with the ground outside,directly to the outdoors, it's doubtful that anyone would have survived this type of crash). Why did I notice so much, you ask? I have worked on the CRASH RECOVERY TEAM before so I notice these types of things that the media does not. These two points are the MOST important two points that the media is not telling us much about. This plane possibly ran out of fuel (Would we ever be told this if it was true? I hope so.) about 1000 feet before landing, this is the number one cause of plane crashes. Now this last point I state because I'm an expert who spent years working in the industry. This is the BA message board on Yahoo! Feel free to use this post on any media broadcast.</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373309749096-116</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're lost in space, dude. Only idiots like bumper (censored50) could possibly take you seriously.</Msg><Username>monster_scrotum</Username><Timestamp>1373309749096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373310075438-117</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$_scrotum.......if you can't answer the question or address the issue don't try to substitute name calling for your lack of logic.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1373310075438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373310232183-118</Id><Topic><Title>Should We have Elected an Unqualified President wh had No Experience....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1371054892683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 12:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you really equating taxation with slavery? God, that's so incredibly stupid.</Msg><Username>jan3226</Username><Timestamp>1373310232183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373310235754-119</Id><Topic><Title>Econ 101 is killing America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373309654993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats have never learned the basic concept of supply and Demand. What's worse is they have never learned you can't spend more than you produce forever.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1373310235754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373310400188-120</Id><Title>Thank God for Rick Perry and Texas being the Number One State....</Title><Msg>.....to do business in for the past 5 years.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1373310400188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373310585824-121</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Passengers felt the plane nose up and accelerate shortly before impact. That is not a sign of no fuel. Also, the families of the 2 deceased girls probably differ in your opinion of what a blessing it was that the tail broke off and created an exit, since they fell from there, most likely causing their deaths.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373310585824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373310937297-122</Id><Topic><Title>Odds are the GOP will keep the house and win the Senate</Title><Username>franknsteinx</Username><Timestamp>1373252991020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How will the GOP change anything they have been elected for years and years and the stuff still goes on.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373310937297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373311079644-123</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voluntary charity to help those truly in need is not even close to helping anything but making a few of sinners feel good.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373311079644</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373311868181-124</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God for Rick Perry and Texas being the Number One State....</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1373310400188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a reason why Texas is # 1 for business and why9 0r the top 10 states have GOP governors. On the flip side there is also a reason why the bottom ten states all have Democrat governors and New York and California are losing businesses in droves. Heck they're all going to Texas and Florida.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1373311868181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312493829-125</Id><Topic><Title>Odds are the GOP will keep the house and win the Senate</Title><Username>franknsteinx</Username><Timestamp>1373252991020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's true both parties have been corrupt and abusive of the power while not enhancing liberty but the Democrats have loathed liberty and freedom and their foundation is based on legalizing thievery.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1373312493829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312661618-126</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Donna, that's nice. What is your bra size?</Msg><Username>budfox_bachelor</Username><Timestamp>1373312661618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312717028-127</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Concur. And, I didn't see any rooster tail from the plane prior to it hitting the seawall in the video. And: The design of the Boeing 777 and broader aircraft safety features may have helped passengers survive the Asiana Airlines Flight 214 crash in San Francisco this weekend. Fire-resistant interiors and stronger seats are just two of the some of the aviation advances that experts say have contributed to more people surviving such accidents. About 200 of the 307 passengers and crew aboard Flight 214 were injured—some seriously—and two died. Boeing 777s were in development during the late 1980s and early 1990s, and the design took advantage of improvements available at the time, including exit doors that opened more easily Of particular relevance for the latest incident, the aircraft uses Federal Aviation Administration requirements—new at the time of its design—that passenger seats withstand impacts at least 16 times the force of gravity. Had the interior been built to older specifications, seats could have pushed together, pinning passengers and making escape more difficult, Curtis said. More fire-retardant seats and flooring may have also had an affect, said Rooney. New materials are slower to burn and don't give off dangerous fumes, both of which could impede evacuation of the plane.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1373312717028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373312789313-128</Id><Title>Blue States Are the Providers</Title><Msg>Red States Are the Parasites</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1373312789313</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312952171-129</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Mister we could use a man like Herbert Hoover again"</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1373312952171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312978216-130</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry Won't Run Again</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373308612294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:36:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A praying Commie. Now that's funny!</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1373312978216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313026063-131</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>......you don't want to make sinners feel bad do you? Voluntary charity is is an act of liberty and freedom.....things the Democrats loath. Obviously rockstar thinks he's just too dumb and stingy to direct his own charitable giving and therefore needs to give his paltry donations to government bureaucrats to direct for him.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1373313026063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313064773-132</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry Won't Run Again</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373308612294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:36:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well okay---but will he toss his hair-hat into the Presidential ring again? Late-night comedians can only hope.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1373313064773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313067149-133</Id><Topic><Title>Econ 101 is killing America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373309654993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that from your manifesto?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1373313067149</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313147637-134</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>empty_scrotum......your head is as empty as your sack.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1373313147637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313446222-135</Id><Topic><Title>Secretary of State Kerry's</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373307733157</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:22:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what happens when you flip-flop (marry a Democrat after a Republican).</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373313446222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313875443-136</Id><Topic><Title>Econ 101 is killing America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373309654993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, where does the buck stop?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373313875443</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313878496-137</Id><Topic><Title>State Department Officer Traded Visas for Sexual Favors</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373304347042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How else do you expect Democrat women to get sex......have you seen how ugly they are? The Democrat men are to busy with each other.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1373313878496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314049324-138</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right. No more taxes. Start by shutting down the FAA and the NTSB. Then the FDA, the FCC, and the SEC. Then the DOD, DOJ, NSA, FBI, CIA. Right? Is that what you want?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373314049324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314056302-139</Id><Topic><Title>State Department Officer Traded Visas for Sexual Favors</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373304347042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you two #$%$ are just angry because the State Dept guys are straight--</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373314056302</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314109665-140</Id><Topic><Title>Blue States Are the Providers</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1373312789313</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:46:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A crack-head cracker is a terrible thing to behold.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373314109665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373314160630-141</Id><Title>After Nancy Pelosi Drained the Swamp all that was at the bottom was.....</Title><Msg>...corrupt Democrat perverts and corrupt politicians.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1373314160630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314192116-142</Id><Topic><Title>Odds are the GOP will keep the house and win the Senate</Title><Username>franknsteinx</Username><Timestamp>1373252991020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Odds are the Tdouchebaggers will get their butts kicked out of the house and senate leaving a stronger Dem majority in both houses than there has ever been</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373314192116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314200591-143</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did most the hydro projects that create the power you use get built? how did the highway systems get built , airports , seaports how do we keep these working ? voluntary charity? After all when you can`t debate a topic and go right into name calling just shows most everybody that can think that you have zero argument and just nonsense that`s been programed into since birth just like a religion. you just repeat this propaganda without even giving a thought to the fact that it`s not reality.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373314200591</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314288906-144</Id><Topic><Title>Odds are the GOP will keep the house and win the Senate</Title><Username>franknsteinx</Username><Timestamp>1373252991020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the loather of liberty and feedom is the guy that squawks the loudest about it namely the coocluchsclaan--- boi pay4ityourself</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373314288906</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314463952-145</Id><Topic><Title>Odds are the GOP will keep the house and win the Senate</Title><Username>franknsteinx</Username><Timestamp>1373252991020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how is that any different than Republicans ? if you look at things over the last 50 years Republicans are worse spenders and done more tax increasing than the Dem`s have been. Your argument does not add up or is one bit factual. Its pretty much based on ignorance and hate from what I can tell.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1373314463952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314557604-146</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have one.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1373314557604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314948554-147</Id><Topic><Title>Rick Perry Won't Run Again</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373308612294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:36:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wendy Davis body slammed Perry, and has now pinned him.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373314948554</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373316387860-148</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please explain why we really need any of those alphabet organizations . 50 little countries can take care of their own problems and give their citizens a lot more choices in the process. We do not need a federal government to waste our money.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373316387860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373316685051-149</Id><Title>Texas Needs an Immigration Program</Title><Msg>To keep Californians and other liberals from moving in and bringing their liberal insanity with them. Austin is starting to look like San Francisco. It's becoming the fruitloop city.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373316685051</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373316740566-150</Id><Title>Video of Impact of Asiana's 777:</Title><Msg>...at SFGate-dot-c0m... (or google "Video shows Asiana flight's moment of impact at SFO") -- interesting because it shows that the description of the plane "cartwheeling" was not entirely off.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1373316740566</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:52:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373317167946-151</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a retired 777 Capt. One thing that I do not understand is why the autothrottles did not engage sooner to increase the airspeed. The 777 will automatically increase power if the speed gets too low, regardless of whether or not the autothrottles are engaged. Now if the pilots turned the autothrottles off, that would be another story. On the 777 it is SOP to leave the autothrottles on at all times, though they are routinely disengaged. Also, the pilots would have received a SPEED LOW amber annunciation when the speed dropped below the VREF of 134. Did they simply miss this or did it not annunciate. The bottom line is that the pilots should have recognized that their speed was too low and intervened to increase the speed...which apparently they did, albeit too late. Perhaps they were receiving erroneous airspeed indications on short final? If this was the case, the 777 has an AOA (angle of attack indicator) built into the PFD (primary flight display) which would have clearly illustrated to the pilots that they were flying very close to stall. Though all indications point to strictly pilot error there may well have been some airspeed indication display problems too.</Msg><Username>hometownmover</Username><Timestamp>1373317167946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373317316710-152</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check the video again and yes there is a "rooster tail" of white water spewing in the air, for about 200 feet, right before the tail hit the seawall and broke off. Naturally, no passenger could see this rooster tail since it was to the rear of the airplane. As for acceleration, that "sensation" does occur when the nose is quickly pulled-up as it obviously was in the smart phone video. I'm not saying this plane ran out of fuel. Isaid that running out of fuel is the number one cause of plane crashes and this aspect must be strongly considered on such a long flight. The media want to pretend like the pilot didn't know how to fly a plane. This makes most viewersl feel good I guess because it seems like an easy fix solution to correct. Oh, Size "DD" with very large protruding nipples. Why do you ask?</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373317316710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373317583248-153</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't see any such thing as hitting the water. Strange to no media has mentioned your ascertion at all, so I think you see it hitting maybe the rocks right before the sea wall---no 200 feet of water at all</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373317583248</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373317621871-154</Id><Title>Democrat Congressional Brain Trust</Title><Msg>Sheila Jackson I'm a freed slave Lee, Maxine let's nationalize the oil industry waters, Nancy we have to pass the bill to see what's in it Pelosi, Hank Guam might capsize Johnson, Debbie to call it Obamacare is insulting to Obama Wasserman Schultz and John why read the bill Conyers.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373317621871</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373317631242-155</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has been commented in the media the auto pilot had been turned off</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373317631242</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373317747636-156</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That pier of landing lights extending out several thousand feet into the bay looks remarkably intact for having had a 777 tail drag along it for 200 feet.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373317747636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373317937007-157</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALL indicators point to this airplane falling out of the sky, Sir. And there is only ONE cause such a thing... Would the public be told if an airliner ran out of fuel? As a 777 pilot you need to imagine this scenario and what would happen this close to landing. Am I right? What would have happen if the fuel ran out 30 seconds before landing?</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373317937007</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373318286829-158</Id><Title>House GOP apparently wants to be even more unpopular</Title><Msg>With the July 4 holiday behind them, House members might be expected to take up work on the immigration reform bill passed by the Senate. But they won’t. They’re looking at piecemeal reforms that will be heavier on border enforcement than the Senate bill – which doubled the number of border control agents, after the border control budget already doubled in size in the last decade — and even nuttier ideas. Instead the House GOP is apparently making big plans for another debt ceiling hostage-taking, and this time they’ve got a strategy to demand big budget cuts from President Obama and the Democrats. According to the National Journal, House leaders are working on a “menu” of budget-slashing offers to Obama in exchange for lifting the debt ceiling for a short, medium or long period of time. Their template is Rep. Paul Ryan’s budget – the budget so unjust and biased against the poor that the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops took time out from restricting women’s rights to criticize the Ryan plan. House members reluctantly voted to raise the debt ceiling in January promising to come back with a strengthened hand on behalf of budget cuts next time around (which will probably be the end of this year). So House Speaker John Boehner is reportedly meeting with Ryan and other conservatives like Louisiana Rep. Steve Scalise, who boasted about their talks to the National Journal. The key points: For a long-term deal, one that gives Treasury borrowing authority for three-and-a-half years, Obama would have to agree to premium support. The plan to privatize Medicare, perhaps the most controversial aspect of the Ryan budget, is the holy grail for conservatives who say major deficit-reduction can only be achieved by making this type of cut to mandatory spending. “If the president wants to go big, there’s a big idea,” said Rep. Steve Scalise, chairman of the Republican Study Committee. For a medium-sized increase in the debt-limit, Republicans want Obama to agree to cut spending in the SNAP food stamp program, block-grant Medicaid, or tinker with chained CPI. For a smaller increase, there is talk of means-testing Social Security, for example, or ending certain agricultural subsidies. …Even at the smallest end of the spectrum — another months-long extension of debt-limit — there is talk of pushing back the eligibility age for Social Security by an equal number of months. Are these people on drugs? These are wildly unpopular ideas that have no chance of passing the Senate. (“Republicans are eager to look like they are giving the White House plenty of options, convinced that it is in their interest to appear engaged and flexible at the negotiating table,” the NJ’s Tim Alberta reports, apparently unironically.) Unfortunately, the president himself has come out behind the chained CPI, but given the enormousness of House GOP demands and delusion, he’s unlikely to get much for that concession. So one cheer for House GOP delusion. Scalise seems to be the main source for the National Journal story, and you can imagine other members wincing at his clueless bluster. Not surprisingly, Scalise starred in another story today about the Obama team’s belief it will see some congressional movement on both immigration reform and the economy this summer. Not so fast, Scalise told the Washington Post: “We’re going to continue to be very aggressive in serving as a check and balance against the Obama administration. That’s what the country said in November. We’re very far apart.” It’s interesting to note that Paul Ryan is key to these debt-ceiling strategy talks, according to the National Journal, when he’s also supposed to be key to comprehensive immigration reform. To his credit, Ryan has come out for something along the lines of the Senate bill, but the question is whether he’ll expend any political capital getting other members to join him. So far, he hasn’t. It looks like another round of debt-ceiling hostage taking is a higher priority for him. Ironically, the fact that the deficit is falling faster than at any time since World War II is helping drive the House GOP’s extremism – they have to go for big, slashing cuts, because the deficit is already shrinking. Here’s hoping the extremism of the House GOP’s opening salvo will remind the Obama administration not to waste its time on another attempt at a “grand bargain” on deficit reduction.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373318286829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373318420881-159</Id><Title>History Of The Democrats And The KKK.....(Why the Democrats started the KKK)</Title><Msg>The original targets of the Ku Klux Klan were Republicans, both black and white, according to a new television program and book, which describe how the Democrats started the KKK and for decades harassed the GOP with lynchings and threats. An estimated 3,446 blacks and 1,297 whites died at the end of KKK ropes from 1882 to 1964. The documentation has been assembled by David Barton of Wallbuilders and published in his book "Setting the Record Straight: American History in Black &amp; White," which reveals that not only did the Democrats work hand-in-glove with the Ku Klux Klan for generations, they started the KKK and endorsed its mayhem. "Of all forms of violent intimidation, lynchings were by far the most effective," Barton said in his book. "Republicans often led the efforts to pass federal anti-lynching laws and their platforms consistently called for a ban on lynching. Democrats successfully blocked those bills and their platforms never did condemn lynchings." Further, the first grand wizard of the KKK was honored at the 1868 Democratic National Convention, no Democrats voted for the 14th Amendment to grant citizenship to former slaves and, to this day, the party website ignores those decades of racism, he said. "Although it is relatively unreported today, historical documents are unequivocal that the Klan was established by Democrats and that the Klan played a prominent role in the Democratic Party," Barton writes in his book. "In fact, a 13-volume set of congressional investigations from 1872 conclusively and irrefutably documents that fact. "The Klan terrorized black Americans through murders and public floggings; relief was granted only if individuals promised not to vote for Republican tickets, and violation of this oath was punishable by death," he said. "Since the Klan targeted Republicans in general, it did not limit its violence simply to black Republicans; white Republicans were also included." Barton also has covered the subject in one episode of his American Heritage Series of television programs, which is being broadcast now on Trinity Broadcasting Network and Cornerstone Television.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373318420881</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373318453694-160</Id><Title>The payout for the 777 crash landing will payout in the millions</Title><Msg>Asiana Airlines will likely end up paying hundreds of millions of dollars to passengers of its flight that crashed in San Francisco on Saturday, according to a leading aviation law expert. "I don't think there's a claim out there worth less than $1 million. Many will be worth multi-millions," said Arthur Wolk, one of the top personal injury attorneys specializing in air crashes. The Philadelphia-based Wolk said that, as of Monday, he had not been retained by any of the passengers or their families. The crash, the first fatal airline crash in the United States in nearly four years, occurred Saturday when the Boeing 777 jet attempting to land clipped the end of runway. There were 182 people hospitalized with injuries ranging from severe scrapes to paralysis. Wolk said even the 123 passengers on the plane who escaped without any physical injuries are likely to see seven-figure settlements from the airline and its insurance carriers due to Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD). "PTSD is an insidious illness," he said. "Many can't return to work. Even those who think they're fine and return to work, six months later they find out they're a blob on the floor because it finally comes home to roost." Wolk said his first settlement based on PTSD was for a flight attendant who escaped without physical injury when a United Airlines flight crashed in Sioux City, Iowa, in 1989. Since then PTSD settlements have become common for survivors of airline crashes. Wolk said that none of the US Airways passengers whose plane landed in New York's Hudson River in January 2009 filed suits following that crash. But he said US Airways (LCC, Fortune 500) gave each a cash settlement -- even though the flight crew was celebrated for landing the crippled plane and saving everyone's life. The airline did not return a call seeking comments on payments in that case. Related: Asiana shares tumble following crash The larger settlements will be for passengers who sustained major injuries, as we</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373318453694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373318826306-161</Id><Title>Democrat's Opposition to Civil Rights</Title><Msg>His book outlines the aggressive pro-slavery agenda held by the Democratic Party for generations leading up to the Civil War, and how that did not die with the Union victory in that war of rebellion. Even as the South was being rebuilt, the votes in Congress consistently revealed a continuing pro-slavery philosophy on the part of the Democrats, the book reveals. Three years after Appomattox, the 14th Amendment to the U.S. Constitution, granting blacks citizenship in the United States, came before Congress: 94 percent of Republicans endorsed it. "The records of Congress reveal that not one Democrat � either in the House or the Senate � voted for the 14th Amendment," Barton wrote. "Three years after the Civil War, and the Democrats from the North as well as the South were still refusing to recognize any rights of citizenship for black Americans." He also noted that South Carolina Gov. Wade Hampton at the 1868 Democratic National Convention inserted a clause in the party platform declaring the Congress' civil rights laws were "unconstitutional, revolutionary, and void." It was the same convention when Gen. Nathan Bedford Forrest, the first grand wizard of the KKK, was honored for his leadership. Barton's book notes that in 1868, Congress heard testimony from election worker Robert Flournoy, who confessed while he was canvassing the state of Mississippi in support of the 13th and 14th Amendments, he could find only one black, in a population of 444,000 in the state, who admitted being a Democrat. Nor is Barton the only person to raise such questions. In 2005, National Review published an article raising similar points. The publication said in 1957 President Dwight Eisenhower, a Republican, deployed the 82nd Airborne Division to desegregate the Little Rock, Ark., schools over the resistance of Democrat Gov. Orval Faubus. Further, three years later, Eisenhower signed the GOP's 1960 Civil Rights Act after it survived a five-day, five-hour filibuster by 18 Senate Democrats, and in 1964, Democrat President Lyndon Johnson signed the 1964 Civil Rights Act after former Klansman Robert Byrd's 14-hour filibuster, and the votes of 22 other Senate Democrats, including Tennessee's Al Gore Sr., failed to scuttle the plan. Dems' website showing jump in history The current version of the "History" page on the party website lists a number of accomplishments � from 1792, 1798, 1800, 1808, 1812, 1816, 1824 and 1828, including its 1832 nomination of Andrew Jackson for president. It follows up with a name change, and the establishment of the Democratic National Committee, but then leaps over the Civil War and all of its issues to talk about the end of the 19th Century, William Jennings Bryan and women's suffrage. A spokesman with the Democrats refused to comment for WND on any of the issues. "You're not going to get a comment," said the spokesman who identified himself as Luis. "Why would Democrats skip over their own history from 1848 to 1900?" Barton asked. "Perhaps because it's not the kind of civil rights history they want to talk about � perhaps because it is not the kind of civil rights history they want to have on their website." The National Review article by Deroy Murdock cited the 1866 comment from Indiana Republican Gov. Oliver Morton condemning Democrats for their racism. "Every one who shoots down Blacks in the streets, burns Blacks schoolhouses and meeting-houses, and murders women and children by the light of their own flaming dwellings, calls himself a Democrat," Morton said. It also cited the 1856 criticism by U.S. Sen. Charles Sumner, R-Mass., of pro-slavery Democrats. "Congressman Preston Brooks (D-S.C.) responded by grabbing a stick and beating Sumner unconscious in the Senate chamber. Disabled, Sumner could not resume his duties for three years." By the admission of the Democrats themselves, on their website, it wasn't until Harry Truman was elected that "Democrats began the fight to bring down the final barriers of race and gender." "That is an accurate description," wrote Barton. "Starting with Harry Truman, Democrats began � that is, they made their first serious efforts � to fight against the barriers of race; yet � Truman's efforts were largely unsuccessful because of his own Democratic Party." Even then, the opposition to rights for blacks was far from over. As recently as 1960, Mississippi Democratic Gov. Hugh White had requested Christian evangelist Billy Graham segregate his crusades, something Graham refused to do. "And when South Carolina Democratic Gov. George Timmerman learned Billy Graham had invited African Americans to a Reformation Rally at the state Capitol, he promptly denied use of the facilities to the evangelist," Barton wrote. The National Review noted that the Democrats' "Klan-coddling" today is embodied in Byrd, who once wrote that, "The Klan is needed today as never before and I am anxious to see its rebirth here in West Virginia." The article suggested a contrast with the GOP, which, when former Klansman David Duke ran for Louisiana governor in 1991 as a Republican, was "scorned" by national GOP officials. Until 1935, every black federal legislator was Republican, and it was Republicans who appointed the first black Air Force and Army four-star generals, established Martin Luther King Jr.'s birthday as a national holiday, and named the first black national-security adviser, secretary of state, the research reveals.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373318826306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:27:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373319192618-162</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both engines were operating so the aircraft did not run out of fuel.</Msg><Username>hometownmover</Username><Timestamp>1373319192618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373319454580-163</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The autopilot is separate from the autothrottle. They are two different systems though designed to work in tandem. It is normal to turn the autopilot off and leave the autothrottles on for landing. On takeoff the autothrottles are ALWAYS engaged when the aircraft is cleared for takeoff. Minimum altitude to engage the autopilot (on takeoff) is 500' AFL.</Msg><Username>hometownmover</Username><Timestamp>1373319454580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373320505719-164</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The video hosted at The Independent does seem to show a rooster tail.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373320505719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373320507058-165</Id><Title>How the media outrageously blew the IRS scandal: A full accounting</Title><Msg>The first few days of the IRS scandal that would consume Washington for weeks went like this: Conservatives were indignant, the media was outraged, the president had to respond, his allies turned on him … and only then, the Treasury Department’s inspector general released the actual report that had sparked the whole controversy — in that order. It’s a fitting microcosm of the entire saga, which has gone from legacy-tarnishing catastrophe to historical footnote in the intervening six weeks, and a textbook example of how the scandal narrative can dominate Washington and cable news even when there is no actual scandal. While the initial reports about the IRS targeting looked pretty bad, suggesting that agents singled out tax-exempt applications for Tea Party and conservative groups for extra scrutiny, the media badly bungled the controversy when supposedly sober journalists like Bob Woodward and Chuck Todd jumped to conclusions and assumed the worst from day one. Instead of doing more reporting to discover the true nature and context of the IRS targeting, or at least waiting for their colleagues to do some, the supposedly liberal mainstream press let their eagerness to show they could be just as tough on a Democratic White House as a Republican one get ahead of the facts. We expect politicians to stretch reality to fit a narrative, but the press should be better. And they would have gotten away with it, too, had their narrative had the benefit of being true. But now, almost two months later, we know that in fact the IRS targeted lots of different kinds of groups, not just conservative ones; that the only organizations whose tax-exempt statuses were actually denied were progressive ones; that many of the targeted conservative groups legitimately crossed the line; that the IG’s report was limited to only Tea Party groups at congressional Republicans’ request; and that the White House was in no way involved in the targeting and didn’t even know about it until shortly before the public did. In short, the entire scandal narrative was a fiction. But it had real consequences, effectively derailing Obama’s agenda not long after a resounding reelection, costing several people their careers, and distracting and misinforming the public. It’s not that nothing went wrong at the IRS, but that the transgression merited nowhere near the media response it earned. But instead of acknowledging its error or correcting the record, the mainstream political press has simply moved on to the next game. Now that the emperor has been revealed to have no clothes, it’s worth looking back at what went wrong. The pace at which the scandal went from zero to Watergate was breathtaking, with the narrative of a Nixonian plot to sic the feds on political enemies forming in the immediate hours after the IRS’ initial apology for the targeting on Friday, May 10. On NBC’s “Nightly News” that day, the first words out of White House correspondent Chuck Todd’s mouth were: “It harkens back to a Nixonian-type tactic, if you will, a political tactic here in the White House.” Coming at the end of a week of renewed media interest in the Benghazi attack — another scandal that was at least two-parts hype to one-part reality — the two scandals reinforced each other and together created a narrative more powerful than either could possibly hope to be on its own. By Sunday morning, the hosts, guests and pundits on the morning political talk shows easily connected the two and soon there was a cloud of scandal hanging over the White House that every serious person on cable news agreed could doom Obama’s entire second term. David Gregory invoked the “second term curse,” George Will read the portion of Richard Nixon’s Articles of Impeachments that focused on the IRS, David Brooks pointed out that “second terms are generally hit with scandal.” Heading into that week, the “compromised second term” narrative was already cemented and would prove impervious to contradicting information for weeks. Brendan Nyhan, a Dartmouth political scientist who studies the media’s role in creating scandals, wasn’t particularly surprised. “In other circumstances, the first reports might not have immediately turned into a media firestorm, but the context was very favorable for a scandal to develop and so the media largely embraced the targeting story before all the facts were known,” he told Salon. What’s often important in scandals is not that someone violated ethical norms, but that “a public figure or institution are successfully construed as violating ethical norms,” he wrote in a recent research paper. Scandals are social constructions and how big one gets often has little to do with the actual severity of the ethical transgression in question, and a lot to do with the political and media context. ”In some cases, it will only take a spark from a relatively ﬂimsy allegation to set off a signiﬁcant controversy, while other environments will be much less prone to scandalous conﬂagrations.” In other words, it takes two to scandal — the opposition party needs the media (Fast and Furious didn’t work because the press mostly ignored it) and the press needs the opposition party’s furor to advance the scandal narrative and provide political cover. Only when both groups’ interests align in favor of scandal do they emerge. There is where the “second term curse” has some reality. The conditions are often ripe for scandal after presidential reelections, when the media is looking for a new story and opposition parties are looking for a new way to respond to their base’s animosity toward the president, now that it can’ t be channeled into an election. On Monday, May 12, news broke that the Justice Department had obtained phone records on AP reporters while investigating a national security leak and the scandal narrative exploded. The White House decided to get in front of the scandal story overtaking Washington, employing the same wisdom that worked so well for them in the Shirley Sherrod scandal, when the administration fired an obscure Agriculture Department official before even trying to determine if the tape exposing her wrongdoing was accurate (it was not). The Sherrod case was in many ways a distilled version of the IRS one, when initial facts that looked damning were later exonerated, but the damage had already been done in the panic to respond quickly. The president took the rare step of responding personally, calling the alleged targeting of conservative groups “outrageous” — if true, though that latter part seemed to be largely overlooked. That night, even Jon Stewart was ready to toss the president overboard. By Tuesday morning, Politico declared that Washington had “turned on” Obama and that this was “very bad news for this White House.” On liberal MSNBC, that lapdog of the White House, Andrea Mitchell declared the IRS targeting of Tea Party groups “one of the most outrageous excesses that I’ve seen in all my years in journalism.” Robert Gibbs, enjoying his new role as MSNBC contributor after spending years as Obama’s spokesperson, slammed his former boss’s “exceedingly passive” response to the controversy. On Wednesday, Obama lost Chris Matthews. “The story that’s going to haunt the Democratic Party is going to be this IRS story,” the liberal lion of MSNBC’s prime time said. Even Bob Woodward, held up as the paragon of American journalism, overhyped the scandal in an appearance on Bill O’Reilly. Still, on “Morning Joe” he stopped short of saying the IRS targeting was Watergate — “yet.” From there, there was no going back. Instead of waiting for more reporting to determine whether the IRS targeted other kinds of groups too, or to see if the White House was actually involved (it was not), the punditocracy had already made up their minds. And in doing so, they did a disservice to the public. By mid-June, half of the American people erroneously thought the White House ordered the targeting of Tea Party groups, up 10 points from the previous month. Obama’s approval rating dropped 8 points and his agenda stalled. At no point did anyone seem to pause and say, let’s wait to see what really happened here. Well, almost no one. One day on “Morning Joe” after the National Journal’s Ron Fournier said that it looked like the White House was using the levers of federal power against opponents, Carl Bernstein, who broke the actual Watergate scandal, cautioned, “We have no evidence of that whatsoever.” For that, he got mocked. “How could we, Carl? Of course we don’t have any evidence of that, but that’s why you have investigations. You know that,” Joe Scarborough said derisively. But eventually, in the weeks that followed, new facts emerged and the scandal narrative started to fall apart. No one was able to produce evidence that the White House was involved and those involved said it wasn’t; Republicans seemed to be obfuscating; we learned that liberal groups were targeted too. Beginning in late May, Republicans started talking about the scandal less and less. Darrell Issa’s regular appearances on cable news ended. A new conventional wisdom was spreading: GOP overreach. When Mitch McConnnell stopped trying to prove the White House ordered the targeting and instead insisted that the president had to disprove the allegations, New York’s Jon Chait saw it as a sign that Republicans were giving up on making the scandal stick in reality. It was a “covered retreat,” Chait wrote, “signaling the IRS scandal’s turn into a vague trope that conservatives use with other members of the tribe, the way liberals liked to say ‘Halliburton’ during the Bush years, to signal some dark beliefs they don’t need to back up.” It had moved into Solyndra and Fast and Furious territory. But the the GOP really lost its media buy-in when Issa refused to release the full transcript of his interviews with IRS agents. Democratic Rep. Elijah Cummings, the ranking member of Issa’s oversight committee, released the transcripts himself, which revealed that a self-described conservative Republican ordered the targeting. Matthews concluded the scandal was nothing more than people trying to do their jobs and screwing up (something many of us were saying from day one). Todd said Republicans were “overplaying their hand” and that it was “a bureaucratic scandal,” not a political one. In the beginning, the Washington Post’s Greg Sargent noted, “The idea then was to create an atmosphere of scandal, in hopes of getting the press to place each and every new fact about the unfolding stories into that framework, with no sense of balance or perspective about how significant each new piece of information really was. That worked for a time, but GOP scandal overreach really did produce a media backlash of sorts.” But mostly, the scandal faded into the background and then disappeared without much recognition, let alone accountability for the people who helped create it. As the journalism adage goes, everyone reads the false report and no one reads the correction. ”My objection to the media coverage is that many reporters and commentators were more interested in the Obama scandal narrative than the facts of the case,” Nyhan told me. “Do I fault the press for this? Yes, but at the same time, it’s the reality of how the media works and is unlikely to change.” Conservatives get one thing right about the media — many of its members personally lean liberal. But what they get wrong is assuming that this translates to favorable coverage of Democrats. Often it’s the opposite. Sensitive to criticism of bias and eager to prove their independence and objectivity, the mainstream media often seems to overcorrect by showing less mercy to Democratic administrations than they do to Republican ones. Steve Almond, writing for Salon, argued that the IRS scandal was “Whitewater all over again,” referring to the Clinton-era non-scandal scandal. No one cared when the IRS went after liberal groups like the NAACP and even progressive churches under George W. Bush. And who could imagine the conservative press disowning the Bush White House as quickly as the liberal pundits on MSNBC did. Bill O’Reilly and his gang at Fox will defend their team to the death, no matter how bad things get and how much flip-flopping is needed to get there. In many ways, this is a compliment to liberal pundits for trying to be more intellectually honest than their conservative peers. But trying to show fair-mindedness by imposing a false balance is just a different form of dishonesty. UPDATE: MSNBC host Lawrence O’Donnell is distressed that we did not name him as an exception to the media’s poor coverage of this story. Here, then, is an example of where he did get it right (along with some others on the left).</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373320507058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373320570672-166</Id><Title>shorts and republicans</Title><Msg>in the finals for biggest loser. Hard one to call.</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373320570672</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373321048725-167</Id><Title>Thought For The Day</Title><Msg>Abortion didn’t start with Roe v. Wade; SAFE abortion started with Roe v. Wade.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373321048725</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373321059955-168</Id><Topic><Title>House GOP apparently wants to be even more unpopular</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373318286829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:18:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shouldn't the debt clock be running backwards now since you believe that the deficit is falling so fast? lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1373321059955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373321069093-169</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The raw video is up on Youtube now. I see the rooster tail, and I heard an account by a survivor who was near the back say he saw water spraying up past the windows on both sides. The runway is 13 above MSL so they had to climb for that guy to have survived. If they had run out of fuel they all would have died at the sea wall.</Msg><Username>silas_farmer</Username><Timestamp>1373321069093</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373321211057-170</Id><Topic><Title>Thought For The Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373321048725</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz we all care deeply about you and we are concerned that one thought per day may make your brain burst so we suggest you go to thought of the month for your own safety.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1373321211057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373321620363-171</Id><Topic><Title>Odds are the GOP will keep the house and win the Senate</Title><Username>franknsteinx</Username><Timestamp>1373252991020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 23:09:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rockhead: " Your argument does not add up or is one bit factual. Its pretty much based on ignorance and hate from what I can tell." TFF!...TFF!...Coming from a BHO #$%$ kizzer at minimum!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1373321620363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373321963516-172</Id><Topic><Title>How the media outrageously blew the IRS scandal: A full accounting</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373320507058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:55:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for helping to set the record straight, and for helping to prove beyond a doubt that the GOPig is an incorrigible pile of liars.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1373321963516</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373322178272-173</Id><Title>San Francisco's 777 real life crash test showed that BA still has the planes you can count on..</Title><Msg>I can't believe these passengers grabbing the luggage as they slide down for the ride of the the life time.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373322178272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373322226371-174</Id><Topic><Title>How the media outrageously blew the IRS scandal: A full accounting</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373320507058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 17:55:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While the media was on their knees with you worshipping the magic chimp ( I use the word chimp with all the respect that was given to Bush when was called a chimp on this board) Obonzo, you had no problem but now that you're the only one still on your knees you're upset. Your propaganda is no longer acceptable to an informed public. You should see the press coverage overseas. They want Obonzo in the Hague.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1373322226371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373322515513-175</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like your post because you are a thinking person. The thing about that people would have all died if the plane ran out of fuel is false because 90% of the airplane was pitched "up" and well above the level of the runway. This is why the tail broke off, it was WAY down and dragging in the water before it hit the rock seawall. This is a scene of an aircraft running out of fuel. Pilots also call this scenario a "stall". Pilot error is VERY doubtful. These guys may be new at this aircraft but they are not idiots on the flight requirements of this aircraft.</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373322515513</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373322645081-176</Id><Title>101 Million Get Food Aid from Federal Gov’t; Outnumber Full-Time Private Sector Workers</Title><Msg>More fallout from Obonzonomics. The number of Americans receiving subsidized food assistance from the federal government has risen to 101 million, representing roughly a third of the U.S. population. The U.S. Department of Agriculture estimates that a total of 101,000,000 people currently participate in at least one of the 15 food programs offered by the agency, at a cost of $114 billion in fiscal year 2012. That means the number of Americans receiving food assistance has surpassed the number of full-time private sector workers in the U.S. According to the Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS), there were 97,180,000 full-time private sector workers in 2012. The population of the U.S. is 316.2 million people, meaning nearly a third of Americans receive food aid from the government.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1373322645081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373322749592-177</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Needs an Immigration Program</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373316685051</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:51:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tejas already has such an immigration program: it is hot, dry, miserable, racist, ugly, polluted, loony, filthy, and nearly last in all rational examinations.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1373322749592</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373322936226-178</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if they were low on fuel why did they not declare an emergency and ask for priority clearance to land?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373322936226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373323156282-179</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much time in uniform did you give ? How much time in Uniform did your hero masquerading as President have ? ...oh well...we know the answer ...but I do have to admit Mchrystels idea is great...at the least we would know at least TWO years that we can say our President served prior to age 30 without calling in forensic experts to authenticate his documents or have them hidden from the public</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373323156282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373323267003-180</Id><Title>John Corsine found not gulty of wrong doing in MF Global scandal</Title><Msg>If you are a billionaire former Goldman Sachs CEO, ex-governor, and one of Obama’s biggest donors and steal $1.2 billion directly from the accounts of your customers and cover-up that theft, then you are not a criminal. If you reveal the un-Constitutional spying on all American citizens by the government, you are a traitor and face life imprisonment. This is your American Republic in a nutshell. Anyone that doesn’t believe we are a corporate fascist oligarchy run by the ultra-wealthy for the benefit of the ultra-wealthy, just isn’t thinking. And the beat goes on.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373323267003</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373323268394-181</Id><Title>It’s a Wendy Davis nation, now</Title><Msg>The shouting came, like water bursting from a broken levee, just before midnight. The hundreds, maybe thousands, of orange-shirted activists camped out in the Texas Capitol had done everything they could to stall a vote on an abortion-restricting bill — from staging a citizen’s filibuster late last week, to cheering on the 13-hour one by Sen. Wendy Davis that Tuesday night. “At what point must a female senator raise her hand or voice to be recognized over the male colleagues in the room?” demanded an exasperated Sen. Leticia van de Putte, who had come from her father’s funeral and was trying to prevent the filibuster from being dismantled on procedural grounds. Her words were what did it. Minutes to the deadline for the end of the special session, Senate Republicans seemed to be calling a vote, and shouting was all that was left. For years, observers have said the enthusiasm and mobilization is on the antiabortion side, but not that night. It was still a game of defense, but pro-choice politicians and activists were pushing back harder than ever seen before. Cecile Richards — president of Planned Parenthood and daughter of legendary Texas Gov. Ann Richards — was there, shouting too. ”My mother would have said, I hear America singing,” Richards told Salon after leaving the Capitol. “It was literally an explosion of participatory democracy that I haven’t seen the likes of in Texas in my memory.” The official Twitter account for Barack Obama agreed, tweeting a link to the livestream with, “Something special is happening in Austin tonight.” When the shouting began, pro-choice activist and writer Jessica Luther, who had been prodigiously tweeting, saw her followers outside Texas, who were watching the livestream, say to keep it going, that it was working. In the end, “The yelling was how it was defeated,” said Luther. “They couldn’t get the votes done because they couldn’t talk to each other.” The Texas fight is by no means over: On Wednesday evening, Perry announced he would call another special session, one too long to filibuster, and the probable vote count remains in his favor. But this time, no one will be surprised when opponents — likely hundreds more — put up a massive fight.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373323268394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373323883624-182</Id><Title>Classic Obama quote:</Title><Msg>This is what Senator Obama ran on. In June 2007 he told a crowd in Texas, “We’re going to close Guantanamo. And we’re going to restore habeas corpus… We’re going to lead by example—not just by word but by deed. That’s our vision for the future.” A few years later he won a Noble Peace Prize....and then subsequently presided over the longest war in US History, kept Gitmo open and signed the NDAA, ......ENDING Habeus corpus and rolling back detention to before Magna Carta ...EFFECTIVELY institutionalizing Martial LAW !!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373323883624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373323952341-183</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If only Obonzo had served his country rather than smoked dope with his Chume gang, he might be supportive of the USA now instead of hating on the USA and embracing a love for Marxism.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1373323952341</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373324280964-184</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just reread the Constitution, Loon. I didn't see anything about having serving in the military being a requirement to have an opinion. I also didn't see that those who have served have more valid opinions than those who did not. Time spinning whiz wheels doesn't make you an expert on anything but, well, whiz wheels. And remember, you started this shtik about 25 years in draped in yada yada yada. Maybe one is only entitled to one opinion for every piece of metal in him. Har har har.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373324280964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373324568333-185</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A thinking person knows that a stall has almost zero to do with whether the plane has power or not. A plane can stall with the engines at full throttle, and it can fly well, for a time, with all the engines shut down. It's a matter of pitch attitude.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373324568333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373324900255-186</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While you may be correct re tail hitting water - or tail skid hitting water- you are full of it re most gettting out of tail pressure bulkhead. Apparently two were thrown out of it and later died or one run over. Photos clearly show others using doors and slides. No it did not run out of fuel - source chairperson of NTSB - and CVR and flight recorder data show it was to slow and too low and NOT on stabilized glide path. Engines spooled up approx 7 seconds before impact Not too sure what industry you worked in as an ex spurt - but jet aircraft of this size was not one of them No responsible media would pay any attention to you.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373324900255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373324924359-187</Id><Title>Wisconsin GOP Governor Leads '11th Hour Attack' on Women's Choice</Title><Msg>In yet another GOP-led "campaign to outlaw abortion," Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker launched an eleventh hour attack on reproductive rights on Friday when he signed an anti-choice bill into law with two restrictions designed to severely limit women's right to abortions within the state. The law, which goes into effect Monday, requires that women undergo an ultrasound before terminating a pregnancy and bans doctors without admitting privileges at nearby hospitals from performing the procedure. The ACLU, ACLU of Wisconsin, and Planned Parenthood, outraged by the proposal, filed a lawsuit on Friday challenging the law. "This law will drastically limit a woman's ability to obtain a safe and legal abortion in Wisconsin by imposing burdensome and medically unnecessary requirements on doctors that provide this essential care," said Larry Dupuis, legal director for ACLU of Wisconsin, in a joint press release. "This law was rammed through the legislature in a matter of days and now, with a stroke of his pen, the governor has put the very health and wellbeing of Wisconsin women and families at immediate risk." Deputy Director of the ACLU Reproductive Freedom Project Talcott Camp said that this "eleventh hour attack" has forced Wisconsin to join "the ranks of Mississippi, Alabama, and others, in a national campaign to outlaw abortion." "Enough is enough," he continued. "Politicians can no longer be permitted to shut down clinics that provide safe abortions and prevent a woman from making the best decision for her and her family." As the Huffington Post reports, the ultrasound requirement compels doctors not only to perform the test but also to meet with patients to discuss the findings, with an emphasis on pointing out the fetus' organs and external features. Supporters make no attempt to mask their intentions, saying that they hope this "will help the woman bond with the fetus and convince her to save it." Donna Crane, a policy analysts for NARAL Pro-Choice America, added that this law has nothing to do with health. Crane explained, "this is politicians saying we want you to [have an ultrasound] because we don't like the choice you're making and we're going to make it as hard as possible and as expensive as possible [to have an abortion], only to satisfy our politics." The second part of the bill—necessitating admitting privileges—is just as extreme and will decrease the amount of doctors able to perform terminations with unconventional restrictions. According to the ACLU, physicians are usually unable to gain admitting rights to hospitals due to a number of factors including facilities' opposition to termination, the limitation that a doctor must be within 30-miles of a hospital, or the requirement that doctors admit a minimum number of patients to the hospital. The ACLU explains that "because abortion is extremely safe and rarely results in hospitalization, it is impossible for physicians who provide abortions to meet the minimum requirement." Gov. Walker's hastiness in passing the bill has also nearly eliminated the time doctors could apply for privileges before the state forces them to stop. The bill forces two health centers within the state to close and will require a third Planned Parenthood clinic to cut staff and limit services.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373324924359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:08:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373324975905-188</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tail skid *may** have hit water thus the roostertail ( look at pics of hydroplane races from years ago to comprehend )</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373324975905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373325214456-189</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the aircraft ran out of fuel, the public would be told. It has happened before.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373325214456</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373325362487-190</Id><Title>BA plane crashes stock goes up</Title><Msg>#$%$ shorts</Msg><Username>endicotsteel</Username><Timestamp>1373325362487</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373325379900-191</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>capt - suggest you access PPrunE site or forum- There does seem to be some discussion as to an odd feature of autothrottle in certain cases - I do not understand ( not a pilot and dont play one on tv ) but several posters on that site are apparently quallified. Also try a site re flyingprofessors net for a great analysis</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373325379900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373325514994-192</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hometown, best added input so far.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373325514994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373325757538-193</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that pier is not on centerline of 28L check the overhead shots</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373325757538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373325767930-194</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton's version of sacred honor. Bill says: "If she'll let you get on her, by all means get on her" "If she lets you stay on her, stay on her as long as you can" There's more but it gets too blue.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1373325767930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373325985082-195</Id><Title>Hersman is very beautiful</Title><Msg>does anyone else thinks she is quite pretty and sexy ? I wonder how someone with political science degree gets to such a prestigious &amp; well paid position.</Msg><Username>ca_la_resident</Username><Timestamp>1373325985082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373326924306-196</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thought the guy was trying to say the tail drug through 200 feet of water.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1373326924306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373327020601-197</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"serving in the military being a requirement to have an opinion" I didn't ASK for his opinion....the op ed implied service should be highly encouraged and I asked the #$%$ where he served ? "25 years in yada yada" Exactly...and that would be roughly 10 times as much yada yada as yours Raven "only entitled to one opinion for every piece of metal in him" Is it metal phallic felatio night at the Kent bathhouse ?.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373327020601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373327366049-198</Id><Title>People with a Chip on their Shoulder and the "N" word</Title><Msg>What makes the "N" word so offensive? When the yankeedoodledimwits refer to southern country boys as crackers or rednecks there's no big offense taken....in fact they'll wear the term as a badge of honor.....because it means they're not yankeedoodledimwits. You people who are ignorant about Cajun culture may make the mistake of trying to insult a Cajun by calling him a coonass but before he kicks the poop outta ya and sprays you with a tall can of whoopass just for being a yan kee he'll let you know he's honored to be called a coonass in fact he's got coonass on his pick-up window so people will know he's proud to be one. Why can't black people feel the same way about the "N" word......if it's used to describe a black person, they should wear the term proudly.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373327366049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373327730434-199</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Is it metal phallic felatio night at the Kent bathhouse ?" I'm disappointed you would write something that pathetic. I'm not surprised, however.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373327730434</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373327763859-200</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's in the Constitution right in between the enumerated powers authorizing Social Security and Medicare.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373327763859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373327904029-201</Id><Topic><Title>Hersman is very beautiful</Title><Username>ca_la_resident</Username><Timestamp>1373325985082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:26:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the Hersman went to the best offensive college football player.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373327904029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373328153049-202</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes that is what BILL would say about sacred On-Her........but Barrys lover ...Larry Sinclair ...instead of Sacred on-Her....would that make it On-HIM ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373328153049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373328338189-203</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you believe Larry Sinclair's story, you've lost the remaining 5% of your brain that possibly functioned.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373328338189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373329060448-204</Id><Topic><Title>People with a Chip on their Shoulder and the "N" word</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373327366049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:49:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>classic mind control...if the Orwellian superstructure can get you to limit your vocabulary to their predesignated verbiage you re half way to being a slave.....Its like having to say "GAY" instead of Homosexual...even though the obverse is Hetero sexual...the political correct Nazis insist on their own dictionary.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373329060448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373329211935-205</Id><Topic><Title>People with a Chip on their Shoulder and the "N" word</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373327366049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:49:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"classic mind control" Spartacus, you've never been in control of your mind.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373329211935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373329753894-206</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since it was E.J. Dionne's op ed, what does anyone else's service have to do with that post? Hmmm, Loon? Anyway, I'm sure E.J. would be glad to answer you about HIS service, if you asked him nicely. 25 years without ever doing anything may be eight times LONGER than I served, but I wonder if it taught you any more. Seem like it just popped your gaskets.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373329753894</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:29:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373329950896-207</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Obama = Hoover ???? The altered sense of reality here is mind boggling.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1373329950896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373330032477-208</Id><Title>hometownmover(pilot) Q. Why would Execute Missed Approach attempt FAIL from seconds before touchdown?</Title><Msg>the reports says that the pilot said he was going to execute a missed approach either 4 or 7 seconds prior. i am seeing that there was no thrust available.</Msg><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373330032477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330148580-209</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It *IS* on the centerline, Don. Check a straight overhead such as Google Earth rather than any oblique shot. It would have to be, wouldn't it? since it carries approach lighting intended to line a plane up with -- wait for it -- the centerline. It's really moot anyway, considering that there is no evidence the plane was centered on the runway and EVERY indication, from the debris path, that it was some distance to the plane's right of the center line.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373330148580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330413856-210</Id><Topic><Title>People with a Chip on their Shoulder and the "N" word</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373327366049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:49:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hoozdik you've never had a mind of your own.....you've always had chrissie's.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1373330413856</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330520348-211</Id><Topic><Title>People with a Chip on their Shoulder and the "N" word</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373327366049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:49:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then he's in good company.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1373330520348</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330597060-212</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, now settle down dipstick and let the real pilots and engineers discuss the event.............we don't need amateurs and wannabees dropping their two cents like fresh turds in a toilet bowl every time there's an incident.............</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373330597060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330689229-213</Id><Topic><Title>People with a Chip on their Shoulder and the "N" word</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1373327366049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:49:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mind control doesn't work on you, but a Twinkie would.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373330689229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330785984-214</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep- I messed up on my post re centerline as was focusing on debris path... First mistake this millenium In any case- since debris from the aft of bulkhead section have been reported to be found embedded in the rocks/seawall, it becomes more likely that what was seen before impact on the video from across the bay probably was a rostertail. But I doubt any passenger would have seen it without looking backwords from a rear window- and even then . .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373330785984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330788263-215</Id><Topic><Title>Freedom and ‘Our Sacred Honor’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373307662378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice how the Kent Raven thinks anyone with an opinion other than his, is either a "loon" or "insane"?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373330788263</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373330819865-216</Id><Title>Asiana plane landed far below required speed-- 119mph vs target speed of 158----25%less</Title><Msg>All 4 pilots being interviewed. Pilot at controls was verified still in training on Boeing 777 jets.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373330819865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373330874658-217</Id><Topic><Title>Asiana plane landed far below required speed-- 119mph vs target speed of 158----25%less</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373330819865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:46:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does this happen with 3 other pilots in the #$%$ pit??</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373330874658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373331019257-218</Id><Topic><Title>Classic Obama quote:</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373323883624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 18:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pathological Liar! That's what the President is. Follow this president to your own demise and love him while you're doing it. America is no longer in the 21st century. America has fallen 70 years in Public Education.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1373331019257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:50:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373331058373-219</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone of your comments is untrue. Already verified landing at 25% less than required speed</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373331058373</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373331071103-220</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The private sector can build power generating dams....we know it because they have. So can power co-operatives. We could have a lot more of them if the federal government and the eco-nuts woulf get out of the way. Highways systems can be built with fuel taxes. The people who use them will pay for them. airports same thing, users pay. You collectivist need to remember the words of Claude Frédéric Bastiat penned more than a 160 years ago: " Socialism, like the ancient ideas from which it springs, confuses the distinction between government and society. As a result of this, every time we object to a thing being done by government, the socialists conclude that we object to its being done at all. We disapprove of state education. Then the socialists say that we are opposed to any education. We object to a state religion. Then the socialists say that we want no religion at all. We object to a state-enforced equality. Then they say that we are against equality. And so on, and so on. It is as if the socialists were to accuse us of not wanting persons to eat because we do not want the state to raise grain."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1373331071103</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373331078026-221</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIE</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373331078026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373331139096-222</Id><Topic><Title>hometownmover(pilot) Q. Why would Execute Missed Approach attempt FAIL from seconds before touchdown?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373330032477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then you disagree with NTSB thrust or engine spool up was added at about 7 seconds, call for go around at about 1.5 seconds before impact - at 100 mph, horiz movement is about 150 feet/second so in 1.5 seconds horizontal movement is about 200 225 feet. And sink rate would have to reverse considerablyn in that time - 777 is NOT a fighter with extreme thrust to weight ratios, etc Simply put - to low, too slow, and too late !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373331139096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373331367635-223</Id><Topic><Title>Asiana plane landed far below required speed-- 119mph vs target speed of 158----25%less</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373330819865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:46:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops--did not spell cockpit correctly and had it as 2 seperate words and the auto-censor changed it to that. That is their main concern? Yahoo should be more concerned with getting the known shorts off the board instead of a word not spelled correctly.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373331367635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373331468533-224</Id><Topic><Title>hometownmover(pilot) Q. Why would Execute Missed Approach attempt FAIL from seconds before touchdown?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373330032477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should apply for a position on mir's private-enterprise NTSB. We'd have the answers 30 hours after a crash. Of course those answers would be hogwash.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373331468533</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373331974121-225</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could never compete with YOUR little brown pearls of wisdom, air(head) Floyd.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373331974121</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 21:06:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373332335802-226</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wrote these words 45 years ago: "Blackbird singing in the dead of night Take these broken wings and learn to fly All your life You were only waiting for this moment to arise Blackbird singing in the dead of night Take these sunken eyes and learn to see All your life You were only waiting for this moment to be free Blackbird fly, blackbird fly Into the light of the dark black night Blackbird fly, blackbird fly Into the light of the dark black night Blackbird singing in the dead of night Take these broken wings and learn to fly All your life You were only waiting for this moment to arise You were only waiting for this moment to arise You were only waiting for this moment to arise</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1373332335802</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 21:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373334036813-227</Id><Topic><Title>hometownmover(pilot) Q. Why would Execute Missed Approach attempt FAIL from seconds before touchdown?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373330032477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Naw- we would have the answers about 3 hours BEFORE the crash- plz reset ur watch ;-PP</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373334036813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 21:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373334566050-228</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The overhead shots of the breakwater and scrap marks/debris field show path maybe 15 feet right of centerline. The 777 horizontal stabilizer is about 70 feet wide (35 feet tip to airplane centerline). Those light would have been history if the impact point was anywhere but right on the rocks.Some debris hitting the rocks was then probably thrown back into water as plane continued to slide along runway. BTW, Wayne has experience with hyro racing (so he informed us). Maybe he can enlighten us about roostertails.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373334566050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 21:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373334718674-229</Id><Topic><Title>Asiana plane landed far below required speed-- 119mph vs target speed of 158----25%less</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373330819865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:46:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Relief pilots may not have been in the front area of the airplane where the dials and levers are (hope that fools the censors).</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373334718674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 21:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373335219318-230</Id><Topic><Title>hometownmover(pilot) Q. Why would Execute Missed Approach attempt FAIL from seconds before touchdown?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373330032477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7 seconds. should stop a drop in 3 seconds or less FULL THRUST FAILED WHY? something is being hidden from the public the company refuses to release these number? the company has the numbers because they have not been made known - it smells the THRUST FIGURES ARE THE SAFETY NET - THEY ARE MOST IMPORTANT. WHAT ARE THEY?</Msg><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373335219318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 22:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373337194151-231</Id><Title>More on the Snowden Affair</Title><Msg>Mr. Clapper, Director of Intelligence admitted in a formal letter of apology to the Chairwomen of the Senate Intelligence Committee Dianne Feinstein that he made erroneous statements to Congress regarding the top secret agency in denying that the NSA gathers data on millions of Americans. Edward Snowden could not live with that lie on the American people and the implications that has on American constitutional civil liberties. Plus, Mr. Snowden could not accept the secret underhanded ways his boss deals with our allies as if they were the enemy. Mr. Snowden is an honest man and wanted Congress and the American people to know the truth. If anybody ever saw the movie " 6 days in May" of a secret government agency that acts independently you would understand why I call Mr. Snowden a US patriot why I think he should be pardoned by the President for any crimes committed in whistleblowing to the American people the truth. I understand that our government is embarrassed by the truth due to the NSA corruption. Thanks to Mr. Snowden the NSA will come to re-focus itself on pursuing terrrorists and US enemies the way Congress originally intended.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373337194151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 22:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373337843204-232</Id><Topic><Title>Hersman is very beautiful</Title><Username>ca_la_resident</Username><Timestamp>1373325985082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:26:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "Herman" (sic) trophy? You must be thinking of some type of K.Lan trophy or something else equally deluded.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1373337843204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 22:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373337908035-233</Id><Topic><Title>hometownmover(pilot) Q. Why would Execute Missed Approach attempt FAIL from seconds before touchdown?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373330032477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALL of the thrust was available. The aircraft was what is called "behind the power curve". I'm not going to get into a discussion of aerodynamics here but the only way that the Asiana crew could have flown out of the situation that they found themselves in would have been to lower the nose to increase airspeed. Now if they had been at a much higher altitude this would have worked. At their altitude it would have been impossible to lower the nose for obvious reasons. Here is an excerpt from another forum that does a pretty good job (not perfect) of describing what it means to be behind the power curve: "As far as piloting is concerned, there is a point called being behind the power curve in the landing phase where induced drag exceeds available power and you are going to continue descending no matter how much power is added. Induced drag rises by a power of four as speed decreases. In turbines the power curve is such that at certain speeds it would be impossible to go around if power was reduced to idle. That's why they usually carry power on approach. It is also the reason after putting in full power on a go around you raise the flaps a notch and throw out the dog (kidding). Climb is not possible with that much drag. The subject of power, efficiency, engine type, and altitude is a complicated subject that does not lend itself to a forum, but a book on aircraft performance like Aircraft Performance and Design by John D. Anderson explains the subject pretty throughly. Each engine has a power curve. The main categories are piston, turboprop, turbojet, high bypass jet, turbojet/high bypass jet with afterburner, and ramjet. They all have their distinct performance patterns with changes of density altitude, forward speed, and rpm. For pilots The Airplane Flying Handbook (FAA 8083) is enough information.</Msg><Username>hometownmover</Username><Timestamp>1373337908035</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 22:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373338153565-234</Id><Topic><Title>Hersman is very beautiful</Title><Username>ca_la_resident</Username><Timestamp>1373325985082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:26:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Herman, Heisman, Hersman, Hermann, H_____whatever--you are dealing with a mental midget with the proverbial I.Q. of a fence post. So don't respond to hope4klansmen's type. It only encourages them.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1373338153565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 22:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373338403667-235</Id><Topic><Title>That 777 Tail Hit The WATER about 200 feet BEFORE it hit the rock seawall:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373309665800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said "While you may be correct re tail hitting water - or tail skid hitting water- you are full of it re most gettting out of tail pressure bulkhead." Passengers were interviewed and most of them stated that they walked out of the "big hole" in the rear of the aircraft. Do you even watch the news? This is why it will take a full year for an official report to be put together dude. You seem an idiot but that is subjective. Do you really believe that the pilot didn't know what he was doing and slowed the aircraft down to 30 knots below stall speed by mistake? Even if the pilot had NO experience on this aircraft he would not do such a thing. No pilot would. I doubt this aircraft ran out of fuel but nonetheless this possibility must be investigated (it is the number one cause of plane crashes!). "They powered -up the engines" a few seconds before impact? This is sounding like the beginnings of a "cover-up" to me. Did you even know that "Running out of fuel" is considered pilot error? All I hope for is that we are told the truth about why this plane got busted-up. Thank God so many people escaped uninjured. A miracle by any measure!</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373338403667</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 22:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373340179738-236</Id><Topic><Title>Hersman is very beautiful</Title><Username>ca_la_resident</Username><Timestamp>1373325985082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:26:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul McCartney had to settle for a woman with one leg.....even then he couldn't hold on to her and she just hopped of with half his fortune.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1373340179738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 23:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373340544811-237</Id><Topic><Title>Do we Really Have to Resort to Uncivilized Behavior to be a Civilized Nation?</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1373309138829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, goody! Another Mir(de) lecture containing Bastiat cut/paste drivel. Maybe if we are REALLY REALLY lucky Mir(de) will orate again about converting C to F.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1373340544811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 23:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373341070536-238</Id><Topic><Title>hometownmover(pilot) Q. Why would Execute Missed Approach attempt FAIL from seconds before touchdown?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373330032477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is one possibility as to why this whole situation could have happened: 1. Pilots knew they were critically low on fuel (not out of fuel). 2. Pilots decided to conserve fuel by descending at a reduced engine thrust. 3. Pilots were planning on recovering at the last moment with a burst of thrust but waited about 20 seconds too long. We will know the true answer in about one year! As a jet mechanic (in my past), and crash recovery team member (in my past), the above is my educated 2 cents worth.</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1373341070536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 23:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373342137371-239</Id><Topic><Title>hometownmover(pilot) Q. Why would Execute Missed Approach attempt FAIL from seconds before touchdown?</Title><Username>hayzeuschrist</Username><Timestamp>1373330032477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flight test source tells me the Asiana 777 engines take about 5 seconds to spool up from approach idle to 95% thrust. Note the comment about being behind the power (we use energy) curve meaning it would take some time to turn around the situation once maximum thrust was obtained. In the early days of the jet age several planes hit the ground early because the pilots were used to prop planes and did not make the mental adjustment needed because of the slower response time of jets. But working the energy curve is drilled into todays pilots and there should be no reason for any commercial pilot to get behind the energy curve today.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1373342137371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 23:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>