<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373774437829-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the New Black Panther party ALWAYS on hand to fan the flames of hatred</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373729977709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lot of truth to that. I had a liberal approach me today about Medicare. He said GOP are trying to get rid of Medicare. I said, I thought they were trying to save it for future generations. He stormed away. Its like the Chicago pension plans nearly $1B in the red, but somehow that's ok with them.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1373774437829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373774767453-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama going to lead protest march and race riots across America.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1373773631903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 23:47:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a Boeing forum take your hate somewhere else please. Hate is such a bad disease to have, it's like cancer. Once you infected, it slowly eats you away and before you know it you will dies a miserable human being. Good Luck and try to stay health.</Msg><Username>kingrobethe1st</Username><Timestamp>1373774767453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373775006284-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the New Black Panther party ALWAYS on hand to fan the flames of hatred</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373729977709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>once pensions plans in Illinois go bankrupt and the checks stop there will be riots in the street. the Dem Party will not balance their budget...all for the vote. The gov has stopped state congress paychecks to get it done but it won't. When the riots start Obama will justify the pensions in the Federal Budget. Then the next Liberal State will follow suite NJ, CA and that will bring our Society hating each other. Liberals politicians chasing the vote while the nations falls off a cliff. Thanks Liberals. spreading the message of hate, rage and race.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1373775006284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373775036652-4</Id><Title>BURN BABY BURN.</Title><Msg>Way to many issues here. Boeing needs to take action real quick before something serious happens.</Msg><Username>kingrobethe1st</Username><Timestamp>1373775036652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373775384364-5</Id><Title>Liberals Right Again!!</Title><Msg>Right about George Zimmerman . He picked a fight and got his butt kicked so bad he had to shoot his victim Right about illegal immigration . We need the foreign labor among other things Right about the NSA, the DOJ, and the IRS . You bet we spy on our enemies- ignorant rednecks dont Right about gun control . We need to prevent loons like jumbojetski from acquiring guns Right about sequestration . US needs to pay bills by raising taxes Right about "Green Energy" . We need to lower the CO2 footprint- be independent of foreign oil Right about Iraq . There really werent WOMD- we lost 4000+ American KIA for what?????????? Right about "The Surge" . in Iraq- we didnt need to be there in the first place Right about "Glow-ball Warming" . MMGW continues to melt the ice caps and sea level continues to rise Right about O'bama care . a lot of people need medical insurance so the rednecks dont have to pay for the needy peoples emergency room care- rednecks are too dumb to catch on Right about the trillion dollar stimulie . Bernanke has headed off the great Bush DEPRESSION Right about ect., ect., ect.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373775384364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373775686464-6</Id><Topic><Title>Why is the New Black Panther party ALWAYS on hand to fan the flames of hatred</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373729977709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 11:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two DOJ were prosecuting a voter intimidation case in Federal Court only waiting for the verdict. The case was won.....at the last minute Obama withdrew the suite and the Black Panthers were released. The two DOJ attorneys who had won the case wrote a book of course after they quit. A great read This president is as evil as they come, Intimidation is his justice and the IRS gives him the power to chase individual Americans.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1373775686464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:21:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373777752993-7</Id><Topic><Title>busloads of Trayon Martin supporters arriving in Sanford, Florida by the hundreds.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1373663473513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 17:11:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess they were a couple of busloads short......</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1373777752993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373778087208-8</Id><Topic><Title>A third victom of the BOEING 777 crash has died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373685900214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 23:25:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a little info, McNurdy doesn't run Boeing, the engineers do. Take it to the bank!</Msg><Username>dapoooch</Username><Timestamp>1373778087208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373778294522-9</Id><Title>Who runs Boeing!</Title><Msg>McNurdy not. It's the engineers that have vision of the future of flight. Every program at Boeing is flying high.</Msg><Username>dapoooch</Username><Timestamp>1373778294522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373779386690-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ethiopian Dreamliner is totaled</Title><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373678812740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:26:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uh broad and south- I can assure you I have probably seen more Composite / carbon composite aircraft structures layed up ply by ply , autoclaved, cut and trimmed - inspected via ultrasound and assembled than you probably have. Such as B2, 767, 777 and including copper plating of same. And you ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373779386690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373780259065-11</Id><Topic><Title>busloads of Trayon Martin supporters arriving in Sanford, Florida by the hundreds.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1373663473513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 17:11:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, ask Johnnie Cochran (O.J.'s attorney).</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373780259065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373781933653-12</Id><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Msg>, July 13 (Reuters) - Investigators classified the fire that broke out on a Boeing 787 Dreamliner parked at London's Heathrow airport as a "serious incident", Britain's Air Accidents Investigation Branch (AAIB) said on Saturday. The question of whether the fire was connected to the batteries just 1 of many crucial issues because the entire global fleet of Dreamliners, was grounded for three months this year due to battery-related problems. The AAIB designation fell just short of a full-blown "accident" on the scale it uses to describe investigations. The agency's preliminary probe is expected to take several days, opening up Boeing to more questions about BOEING’S cheap outsourced 787 plane. With the uncertainty surrounding the blaze, airlines around the world cautiously continued to operate the Dreamliner.. The fire broke out on the BOEING plane on Friday afternoon, and was discovered when smoke was seen on the plane eight hours after arriving.. "There has been extensive heat damage in the upper portion of the rear fuselage, a complex part of the aircraft, and the initial investigation is likely to take several days," the AAIB said in a statement.." The Financial Times on Saturday reported that airline staff had discovered a problem with the aircraft's air conditioning system during a routine inspection Separately, Britain's Thomson Airways said one of its Dreamliners that turned back during a flight from Manchester to Sanford in Florida on Friday had suffered a " technical issue" and had now had a number of components replaced. Britain's Sky News television channel said it had learnt that some 100 Thomson passengers had called the airline's to cancel once it was learned they were flying on the troubled BOEING 787.. Sky News did not give a source for the information and Thomson declined to comment. this a new blow for Boeing after the entire global fleet of Dreamliners had to be grounded for almost 4 months</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373783205699-13</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The agency's preliminary probe is expected to take several days, opening up Boeing to more questions about BOEING’S cheap outsourced 787 plane." - Wayne's edited version The agency's preliminary probe is expected to take several days, opening up Boeing to more questions about its top-selling plane. - Reuter's original article Wayne is so transparent with his "writings". Better stick to that inventing thingy that will change aerospace. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373783205699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373783458535-14</Id><Title>BOEING'S 787 IS DYING THE DEATH OF A THOUSAND CUTS</Title><Msg>787 is dying a "death of a thousand cuts"- both literally and metaphorically. One shudders to think what would have happened if this fire happened in flight. In the 8 years since the launch of the BOEING 787 If the cause of this fire is something that Boeing hasn't already discovered and re-engineered, is that really such good news? I'm not convinced that another source of ignition is good news. The electrical nightmares in the 787 are a continuing problem - from the fire on the test flight to continued reports of electrical gremlins, the public should wonder if Boeing's design and quality control are sufficient. If a similar fire were to break out on an aircraft hours from the nearest airfield, there might not be survivors. A series of delays and mishaps have plagued the aircraft since its launch in 2004: It’s been 9 years since the BOEING 787 launch and nothing but delay and constant incidents . when will BOEING OR THE PUBLIC SAY STOP THE INSANITY SHUT DOWN THIS PLANE FOR GOOD.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373783458535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373783768659-15</Id><Title>Timbeeeerrrrrrrrrr</Title><Msg>down, down, and down. Short</Msg><Username>smockbee</Username><Timestamp>1373783768659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:36:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373786074198-16</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I did was compare the original Reuter's paragraph with your attempt to distort it. Ain't Google wonderful? How's that invention coming along that will change aerospace technology? The world (and your Collier's Trophy) are waiting. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373786074198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 03:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373786710338-17</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" and your story of how you were just lucky on trading boeing stock what you did after the fact was reviewed the low on boeing and the high and claimed " You are the biggest bogus person to make this claim, you do it all the time</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1373786710338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 03:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373790124567-18</Id><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Msg>Hooz vows to engage in endless tirades on the racism of it all.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373790243308-19</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry, FAA and Boeing will minimize the incident.</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1373790243308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373791053925-20</Id><Topic><Title>It's a Beautiful Day</Title><Username>fliprnoble</Username><Timestamp>1373755106629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 18:38:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TbA_TZn35LA</Msg><Username>wonderdoc</Username><Timestamp>1373791053925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373792735115-21</Id><Title>Dell looses miilions</Title><Msg>On his short position on BA.Dell a digruntled janitor that was employed by BA who was let go because he could'nt stay out of the mens room.So now he sits home in his moms basement posting 24 hrs a day.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1373792735115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 05:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373792940352-22</Id><Title>Experts Destroy Obama's Argument That Americans Must Sacrifice Privacy For Security</Title><Msg>Off the World News Desk: "On June 7 President Barack Obama defended the two secret National Security Agency (NSA) spying programs that were exposed by whistleblower/leaker Edward Snowden, saying: "You can’t have 100% security, and also then have 100% privacy and zero inconvenience.” Obama insisted “the right balance” had been struck between security and privacy, and said that we are "going to have to make some choices as a society Americans" so that the country can effectively fight terrorism. This is a false choice, and a dangerous one for a free nation, according to several experts who spoke with Bob Sullivan of NBC News. "You have pollsters and pundits and (National Intelligence Director James) Clapper saying, 'Do you want us to catch the terrorists or do you want privacy?' But that's a false choice. It's like asking, 'Do you want the police to exist or not?'" Dan Solove, a privacy law expert at George Washington University Law School, told NBC. Cybersecurity expert Bruce Schneier agrees. "I've never liked the idea of security vs. privacy, because no one feels more secure in a surveillance state," Schneier, author of "Beyond Fear: Thinking Sensibly About Security in an Insecure World," told NBC. "There's plenty of examples of security that doesn't infringe on privacy. They are all around. Door locks. Fences ... Firewalls. People are forgetting that quite a lot of security doesn't affect privacy. "The real dichotomy is liberty vs. control," Schneier added (emphasis ours)."</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373792940352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 05:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373793618204-23</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 IS DYING THE DEATH OF A THOUSAND CUTS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373783458535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TH 787 WILL END UP AT THE BOTTOM OF THE PACIFI.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1373793618204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 05:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373793744289-24</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FAA AND BOEING WILL PUT A GOOD SPIN ON IT.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1373793744289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 05:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373795233389-25</Id><Title>Unrelated to battery. poor dickheadwayne. gap up monday</Title><Msg>see you at 106</Msg><Username>rb15301</Username><Timestamp>1373795233389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 05:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373795235335-26</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got that right. He has used racism to divide people, which is right out of the Marxist playbook...............</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373795235335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 05:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373795293967-27</Id><Title>NOT GUILTY</Title><Msg>The jury has spoken.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373795293967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 05:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373795978581-28</Id><Topic><Title>For all those happy birds that bought Friday let me know how you feel Monday at 10am, edt. ?????</Title><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1373752582442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 17:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The battery problem aside, this new incident will keep enough uncertainty to put this stock back at 90, and also the China GDP figure will also put pressure on the overall market Monday.</Msg><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1373795978581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 05:59:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373797202342-29</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 IS DYING THE DEATH OF A THOUSAND CUTS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373783458535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100 Thompson customers cancelled flights when they new they were to fly in a 787 who can blame them, i personally hate flying, but i at least try to comfort myself when several thousand feet in the air with the knowledge, (hopeful belief) that the aircraft is designed to be 100% reliable. 3 fires, in such a short time 2 of which Boeing and the FAA admit they have no idea of the root cause, the latest which seems to be more than, somebody leaving a coffee pot on, and reports of airlines replacing numerous failed components (this weeks Manchester-Sanford flight one example) this all adds up to very little faith in the aircraft's build quality. Hopefully it will not take the deaths of innocent passengers,before safety becomes precedent to profit, or the technical boffins, actually fully understand what they have built, and get a handle on either the design flaws or any underlying component quality issues. At present i believe passengers in this aircraft are entitled to feel very edgy when trusting themselves and their families lives traveling in this aircraft</Msg><Username>anthony865564</Username><Timestamp>1373797202342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 06:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373797546608-30</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wont be long before Obama will be on TV stating how Trayvon was like the "son" he never had...and Hooz or the Raven well be claiming jurys are old fashion remnants of an out of date document called the constitution...and how only racists defend themselves.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373797546608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 06:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373797728648-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ethiopian Dreamliner is totaled</Title><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373678812740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:26:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like a hot dog!</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1373797728648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 06:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373799713919-32</Id><Topic><Title>Ethiopian Dreamliner is totaled</Title><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373678812740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:26:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My experience is with military aircraft. All CF composites. Primary and secondary structures. If you know so much about composites, how do you endorse a field repair of a primary composite structure? The resin systems are different. Woven prepregs vs. unidirectional? How do you recertify the airworthiness of the repaired structure?</Msg><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373799713919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 07:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373801693926-33</Id><Topic><Title>zimmerman not guilty</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373767624960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would compel a 17 yo kid to attack a complete stranger? He's got a hoodie on and the stranger is eyeing him. Trayvon did not have the judgment or intelligence (listen to his girlfriend) to leave the scene. No, he figured he would wup up on Z man. But the tables got turned. Now we have a race issue in this country. Not. We have an issue with youngsters who will never grow old because they are so stupid and full of themselves to get into these situations. Hernandez ex of the Patriots is this way also.</Msg><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373801693926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 07:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373801862109-34</Id><Topic><Title>Ethiopian Dreamliner is totaled</Title><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373678812740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:26:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a never ending fiasco that will end in a eternal tears!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1373801862109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 07:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373803979879-35</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The jury found him NOT GUILTY what part of NOT GUILTY don't you understand? Levon was a criminal thug.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373803979879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373804149474-36</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice that The Kent Raven is ALWAYS on the WRONG side of any debate or issue? He is consistently wrong.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373804149474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373804815306-37</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you see a civil trial coming soon to a theater near you? One in which the "Z Man" will be REQUIRED to take the stand? He will lose that one. Pass the popcorn... it is going to be fun to watch him go up in flames.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373804815306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373804911101-38</Id><Title>Ask yourself do you feel safe flying on the 787?</Title><Msg>With constant fires in air, and worse even on the ground when parked, ask yourself do you feel comfortable flying on the 787? There are very few planes out in service and the constant problems, even another 787 had to return to the UK the other day. This thing is going to be like the Concorde after the crash, it was a cool plane and idea, but no one is going to want to fly it and ultimately with that stigma flyers will choose not to use those airlines, whose profits are razor thin to begin with, so those operators will retire them.</Msg><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1373804911101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373805982509-39</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The defense in this case pleaded 2nd degree murder and manslaughter. They cannot go back and plead civil right charges. It's double jeopardy otherwise. The civil case can result in a jury award. But how much money does Zimmerman have?</Msg><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373805982509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373807088116-40</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zimmerman will never have any money- he will have to pay all his livelong life on the trillion dollar judgment against him for Trevons murder</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373807088116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373807194047-41</Id><Topic><Title>Ask yourself do you feel safe flying on the 787?</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1373804911101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ask yourself why Boeing experimental was able to fly 5 airplanes for 2 years without incident. Then ask yourself if it isnt tempting for some high rolling investment crooks to sabatoge the 787 ---</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373807194047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373807848388-42</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True. Al Sharpton lost a civil case arising from his stupid assertions in the Twana Brawley case. Al has no assets. But he still lives. He keeps his money in his friends names. Same with Zimmerman. The Martin family may just move on; the legal fees will not merit the lawsuit.</Msg><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373807848388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373808399854-43</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It really takes someone with a sick mind to take pleasure in such a tragic event.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373808399854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373808441854-44</Id><Topic><Title>zimmerman not guilty</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373767624960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It works Most of the time...don't forget that circus in LA 20 years ago</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1373808441854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373809215232-45</Id><Title>Hey There Georgie Boy</Title><Msg>After you're found guilty in the civil case, you will spend the rest of your miserable days looking over shoulder, watching your back... as the Good Book says, "an eye for an eye". Have a nice life.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373809215232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809294015-46</Id><Topic><Title>These Planes Are Chock Full Of Cheap Foreign Made Electrical Components......Fire On The Wing</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1373756947061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 19:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheap electrical components are fires waiting to happen.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1373809294015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809593841-47</Id><Topic><Title>Hey There Georgie Boy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373809215232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hooz we know you're low information, you also one o dem people of color who also happen to be racists? seems like you've got it on for a guy who simply defended himself against @no_limit#$%$ who was pounding his head into the sidewalk?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373809593841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809658810-48</Id><Topic><Title>Hey There Georgie Boy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373809215232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now all the sudden you've found religion.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373809658810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:47:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809850647-49</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With O.J. Simpson, his defense team was able to shelter a pension from the Goldman family because he played football and did commercials. Zimmerman could lose a lawsuit that could conceivably follow him for the rest of his life. It's likely he will lose a civil case and there would be justice for Trayvon's family. The Goldman family just wanted justice, and they knew that they would likely win the civil case... as will the family of Trayvon.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373809850647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373810053263-50</Id><Topic><Title>Hey There Georgie Boy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373809215232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep your opinion on another channel we know everyone has an opinion even an arsshole like yourself</Msg><Username>drq_39</Username><Timestamp>1373810053263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373810174030-51</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't force/require him to take the stand.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373810174030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373810396734-52</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In this case, It does seems that Hooz is to the martin case as Wayne is to BA.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373810396734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373810582313-53</Id><Title>Hello My Name is Ed Snowden</Title><Msg>Hello. My name is Ed Snowden. A little over one month ago, I had family, a home in paradise, and I lived in great comfort. I also had the capability without any warrant to search for, seize, and read your communications. Anyone's communications at any time. That is the power to change people's fates. It is also a serious violation of the law. The 4th and 5th Amendments to the Constitution of my country, Article 12 of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, and numerous statutes and treaties forbid such systems of massive, pervasive surveillance. While the US Constitution marks these programs as illegal, my government argues that secret court rulings, which the world is not permitted to see, somehow legitimize an illegal affair. These rulings simply corrupt the most basic notion of justice that it must be seen to be done. The immoral cannot be made moral through the use of secret law. I believe in the principle declared at Nuremberg in 1945: "Individuals have international duties which transcend the national obligations of obedience. Therefore individual citizens have the duty to violate domestic laws to prevent crimes against peace and humanity from occurring." Accordingly, I did what I believed right and began a campaign to correct this wrongdoing. I did not seek to enrich myself. I did not seek to sell US secrets. I did not partner with any foreign government to guarantee my safety. Instead, I took what I knew to the public, so what affects all of us can be discussed by all of us in the light of day, and I asked the world for justice. That moral decision to tell the public about spying that affects all of us has been costly, but it was the right thing to do and I have no regrets. Since that time, the government and intelligence services of the United States of America have attempted to make an example of me, a warning to all others who might speak out as I have. I have been made stateless and hounded for my act of political expression. The United States Government has placed me on no-fly lists. It demanded Hong Kong return me outside of the framework of its laws, in direct violation of the principle of non-refoulement the Law of Nations. It has threatened with sanctions countries who would stand up for my human rights and the UN asylum system. It has even taken the unprecedented step of ordering military allies to ground a Latin American president's plane in search for a political refugee. These dangerous escalations represent a threat not just to the dignity of Latin America, but to the basic rights shared by every person, every nation, to live free from persecution, and to seek and enjoy asylum. Yet even in the face of this historically disproportionate aggression, countries around the world have offered support and asylum. These nations, including Russia, Venezuela, Bolivia, Nicaragua, and Ecuador have my gratitude and respect for being the first to stand against human rights violations carried out by the powerful rather than the powerless. By refusing to compromise their principles in the face of intimidation, they have earned the respect of the world. It is my intention to travel to each of these countries to extend my personal thanks to their people and leaders. I announce today my formal acceptance of all offers of support or asylum I have been extended and all others that may be offered in the future. With, for example, the grant of asylum provided by Venezuela's President Maduro, my asylee status is now formal, and no state has a basis by which to limit or interfere with my right to enjoy that asylum. As we have seen, however, some governments in Western European and North American states have demonstrated a willingness to act outside the law, and this behavior persists today. This unlawful threat makes it impossible for me to travel to Latin America and enjoy the asylum granted there in accordance with our shared rights. This willingness by powerful states to act extra-legally represents a threat to all of us, and must not be allowed to succeed. Accordingly, I ask for your assistance in requesting guarantees of safe passage from the relevant nations in securing my travel to Latin America, as well as requesting asylum in Russia until such time as these states accede to law and my legal travel is permitted. I will be submitting my request to Russia today, and hope it will be accepted favorably.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373810582313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373810705223-54</Id><Title>Hello my name is Ed Snowden</Title><Msg>Hello. My name is Ed Snowden. A little over one month ago, I had family, a home in paradise, and I lived in great comfort. I also had the capability without any warrant to search for, seize, and read your communications. Anyone's communications at any time. That is the power to change people's fates. It is also a serious violation of the law. The 4th and 5th Amendments to the Constitution of my country, Article 12 of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, and numerous statutes and treaties forbid such systems of massive, pervasive surveillance. While the US Constitution marks these programs as illegal, my government argues that secret court rulings, which the world is not permitted to see, somehow legitimize an illegal affair. These rulings simply corrupt the most basic notion of justice that it must be seen to be done. The immoral cannot be made moral through the use of secret law. I believe in the principle declared at Nuremberg in 1945: "Individuals have international duties which transcend the national obligations of obedience. Therefore individual citizens have the duty to violate domestic laws to prevent crimes against peace and humanity from occurring." Accordingly, I did what I believed right and began a campaign to correct this wrongdoing. I did not seek to enrich myself. I did not seek to sell US secrets. I did not partner with any foreign government to guarantee my safety. Instead, I took what I knew to the public, so what affects all of us can be discussed by all of us in the light of day, and I asked the world for justice. That moral decision to tell the public about spying that affects all of us has been costly, but it was the right thing to do and I have no regrets. Since that time, the government and intelligence services of the United States of America have attempted to make an example of me, a warning to all others who might speak out as I have. I have been made stateless and hounded for my act of political expression. The United States Government has placed me on no-fly lists. It demanded Hong Kong return me outside of the framework of its laws, in direct violation of the principle of non-refoulement the Law of Nations. It has threatened with sanctions countries who would stand up for my human rights and the UN asylum system. It has even taken the unprecedented step of ordering military allies to ground a Latin American president's plane in search for a political refugee. These dangerous escalations represent a threat not just to the dignity of Latin America, but to the basic rights shared by every person, every nation, to live free from persecution, and to seek and enjoy asylum. Yet even in the face of this historically disproportionate aggression, countries around the world have offered support and asylum. These nations, including Russia, Venezuela, Bolivia, Nicaragua, and Ecuador have my gratitude and respect for being the first to stand against human rights violations carried out by the powerful rather than the powerless. By refusing to compromise their principles in the face of intimidation, they have earned the respect of the world. It is my intention to travel to each of these countries to extend my personal thanks to their people and leaders. I announce today my formal acceptance of all offers of support or asylum I have been extended and all others that may be offered in the future. With, for example, the grant of asylum provided by Venezuela's President Maduro, my asylee status is now formal, and no state has a basis by which to limit or interfere with my right to enjoy that asylum. As we have seen, however, some governments in Western European and North American states have demonstrated a willingness to act outside the law, and this behavior persists today. This unlawful threat makes it impossible for me to travel to Latin America and enjoy the asylum granted there in accordance with our shared rights. This willingness by powerful states to act extra-legally represents a threat to all of us, and must not be allowed to succeed. Accordingly, I ask for your assistance in requesting guarantees of safe passage from the relevant nations in securing my travel to Latin America, as well as requesting asylum in Russia until such time as these states accede to law and my legal travel is permitted. I will be submitting my request to Russia today, and hope it will be accepted favorably.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373810705223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373810874395-55</Id><Title>Zimmerman now free to pack heat and blow</Title><Msg>Zimmerman now free to pack heat and blow those suspicious black kids away</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373810874395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373810931308-56</Id><Topic><Title>Hey There Georgie Boy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373809215232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hoozdik simply points out our overzealous racist occupier and his racist injustice appointment together with their lap dogs have ruined zimmerman's life.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373810931308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373811018080-57</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman now free to pack heat and blow</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373810874395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:07:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean he's still able to defend himself against physical assault?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373811018080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373811075629-58</Id><Title>And I quote</Title><Msg>"Zimmerman will lose this case." - hooz 7/2/13 Now he is babbling about popping popcorn.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373811075629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373811257323-59</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman now free to pack heat and blow</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373810874395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:07:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosima you related to hoozdik, err chrissy/spart...me thinks your are, another one of dem race baiting racists. you also seem to have quite a bit of time on your hands to agitate, just like your other aliases...one o dem taxpayer funded Yahoo ACORNs.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373811257323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373811281408-60</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey B&amp;S - civil and criminal charges are seperate- not double jepordy. Think OJ simpson- won on criminal- lost big time on civil However- in this case- no evidence of a deliberate hate crime- except for holder and his minions who already spent your tax dollars bussing people in, forcing police chief out, etc. Then of course, Zimmerman can file against NBC for rigging a phony tape of 911 call.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373811281408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373811578079-61</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman now free to pack heat and blow</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373810874395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:07:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored I guess you are the only one with special permission to agitate eh---------time on my hands?? how about yourself- ---ACORNS?? least they aren't Tdouchebaggers</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373811578079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373811615656-62</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lose you Short bashing idiot. WD Dicken!</Msg><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373811615656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373812012336-63</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman now free to pack heat and blow</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373810874395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:07:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err race baiter all the time err acorn err spaz-in-brain-stem err brain damage err dropped on head as infant err deluded massively err bumper err fascist</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1373812012336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373812166096-64</Id><Topic><Title>Hey There Georgie Boy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373809215232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:40:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree Zimmerman's life is pretty much over... but he did this to himself. He has to take responsibility for what has happened.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373812166096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:29:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373812434236-65</Id><Title>On Sunday, all Airlines stated they gave 100% Confidence in the Safety of Boeing's Dreamliner!</Title><Msg>"We want to reassure our customers that we have every confidence in this aircraft and would never operate it if we weren't 100 percent sure of its safety," a TUI Travel spokeswoman said. Those who shorted BA be prepared to lose millions when it opens at $105 on Monday morning! Going to 52 week high by the end of next week!</Msg><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373812434236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373812581938-66</Id><Title>slavery and race hatred have been with us for 500 years</Title><Msg>and at least race hatred will likely last another 500 years in the old confederacy</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373812581938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:36:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373812935283-67</Id><Topic><Title>Ask yourself do you feel safe flying on the 787?</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1373804911101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask yourself how come the FAA grounded the entire fleet out of Safety concerns after a couple little fires. Then ask yourself how a PARKED airplane burns up with a high heat fire. And on the same day an inflight 787 has to return to airport of departure for problems? Do you want to fly on one of these?</Msg><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1373812935283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:42:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373813063855-68</Id><Topic><Title>On Sunday, all Airlines stated they gave 100% Confidence in the Safety of Boeing's Dreamliner!</Title><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373812434236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:33:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What else are the airlines going to say? That they have bad planes and people shouldn't fly on them? It's typical spin and people aren't dumb and see right through it. However the consumer will vote with their wallets and refuse to fly on the 787 and the operators will be forced to change.</Msg><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1373813063855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373813676489-69</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 IS DYING THE DEATH OF A THOUSAND CUTS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373783458535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Boeing lost a huge part of its quality by making this too much of a "world project". For example, look at the colossal mess the Aussies made of this project. What a joke! Who ever uses "Australia" and "heavy manufacturing" in the same sentence? What were you thinking of Boeing? Also, while I like the idea of the design plans all being on a central computer, the idea of shoving all the social commentary onto a portal is not good. While in theory portals open a grand platform for communications, in reality they do not. Much of the ability to squawk down bad ideas has been lost. Previously, concerns were voiced around the water cooler and the smoking lounge and thoughts and opinions could be spoken with a full voice,and many hands on people would kick around ideas (out of the spotlight) and upon consensus, somewhat "en masse voice" down a bad idea. Portals are intimidating. What junior engineer is going to publicly shoot down a senior manager on a portal all by himself? In manufacturing, the hands on grunts, know more than their superiors. It was better in the past when the cauldron of thought was allowed to boil more freely.</Msg><Username>evertrueflame</Username><Timestamp>1373813676489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373814386423-70</Id><Title>Is Obama to Blame for Recent Missile Failures? Answer: No.</Title><Msg>If Elon musk were the manufacturer of the missles they would be successful. Otherwise, failure means more taxpayer money to the major manufacturers. Sad reality of lobbyist money.</Msg><Username>businessisnecessary</Username><Timestamp>1373814386423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814677723-71</Id><Topic><Title>Is the wiring of an aircfaft inside steel (fireproof) conduit?</Title><Username>whenindoubtdoresearch</Username><Timestamp>1373725360247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 10:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Union protocol training is superior. In fact, the most productive country on Earth is Switzerland where on the job physical job training is mandatory and comprises over 30 percent of education in Switzerland. Switzerland is 8 times as productive as China and 100 percent more productive than USA.</Msg><Username>obeythe27rulesofinvesting</Username><Timestamp>1373814677723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:11:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814719154-72</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 IS DYING THE DEATH OF A THOUSAND CUTS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373783458535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will take a full blown crash to make them ground it. I am sure the FAA and Boeing would blame it on a bomb or pilot error.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1373814719154</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814782707-73</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 IS DYING THE DEATH OF A THOUSAND CUTS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373783458535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:30:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You appear to be the biggest idiot on this board considering that all of the airlines that ordered 787s stand by them. Not a single cancellation, and more have been ordered!</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1373814782707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373814944862-74</Id><Topic><Title>Is the wiring of an aircfaft inside steel (fireproof) conduit?</Title><Username>whenindoubtdoresearch</Username><Timestamp>1373725360247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 10:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clearly not.</Msg><Username>businessisnecessary</Username><Timestamp>1373814944862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815112908-75</Id><Topic><Title>Ask yourself do you feel safe flying on the 787?</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1373804911101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Brad, why don't you wait til the investigation is complete before saying something stupid like already have.</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1373815112908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815202762-76</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some Fast Facts (CNN) -- Here's a look at what you need to know about the shooting death of 17-year-old Trayvon Martin in February 2012. Former neighborhood watch captain George Zimmerman has been charged in the shooting. Facts: Trayvon Benjamin Martin, born February 5, 1995, was a 17-year-old African-American high school student who lived in Miami Gardens, Florida with his mother Sybrina Fulton. In February 2012, Martin was visting his father Tracy Martin in Sanford, Florida after receiving a ten-day suspension from Krop Senior High School. The suspension stemmed from the discovery of drug residue in Martin's book bag. George Michael Zimmerman, born October 5, 1983, was a part-time student at Seminole State College and a neighborhood watch captain at the Retreat at Twin Lakes gated community in Sanford at the time of the shooting. He is married to Shellie (Dean) Zimmerman and is the son of Robert and Gladys Zimmerman. Timeline: February 26, 2012 - George Zimmerman, a neighborhood watch captain in Sanford, Florida, calls 911 to report "a suspicious person" in the neighborhood. He is instructed not to get out of his SUV or approach the person. Zimmerman disregards the instructions. Moments later, neighbors report hearing gunfire. Zimmerman acknowledges that he shot Martin, claiming it was in self-defense. In a police report, Officer Timothy Smith writes that Zimmerman was bleeding from the nose and back of the head. February 27, 2012 - Martin's father, Tracy Martin, files a missing persons report. Officers with the Sanford Police Department visit Tracy Martin. He is able to identify Trayvon Martin's body using a photo. March 8, 2102 - Investigators receive a fax from the Altamonte Family Practice containing the medical records identifying the injuries sustained by Zimmerman on the night of the shooting: Open wound of scalp, without mention of complication; nasal bones, closed fracture; assault by other specified means. March 12, 2012 - Sanford Police Chief Bill Lee says that Zimmerman has not been charged because there are no grounds to disprove his story of the events. March 13, 2012 - Sanford Police Department's homicide detective Christopher Serino recommends Zimmerman be charged with manslaughter. Zimmerman "failed to identify himself" as a concerned citizen or neighborhood watch member on two occasions that night. Serino reports that he thought Zimmerman's head injuries were "marginally consistent with a life-threatening episode, as described by him, during which neither a deadly weapon nor deadly force were deployed by Trayvon Martin." March 14, 2012 - The case is turned over to the Florida State Attorney Norm Wolfinger. March 15, 2012 - In a letter to the Orlando Sentinel, Robert Zimmerman, George Zimmerman's father, writes that George has been unfairly portrayed as a racist, and that George is Hispanic and grew up in a multiracial family. March 16, 2012 - Authorities release seven 911 calls from the night of the shooting. In one of the 911 recordings, Zimmerman, against the advice of the 911 dispatcher, follows Martin. In one of the recordings, a voice screams "Help, help!" in the background, followed by the sound of a gunshot. March 19, 2012 - The Justice Department and the FBI announce that they have launched an investigation into Martin's death. March 20, 2012 - A lawyer for the Martin family, Benjamin Crump, holds a news conference, telling reporters that Trayvon was on the phone with his 16-year-old girlfriend at the time of the shooting. The girl, who wishes to remain anonymous, says she heard someone ask Martin what he was doing and heard Martin ask why the person was following him, according to Crump. The girl then got the impression that there was an altercation in which the earpiece fell out of Martin's ear and the connection went dead. March 21, 2012 - CNN analyzes one of the tapes of Zimmerman's call to dispatch, in which he is purported to have used a racial slur against blacks. The results are inconclusive.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373815202762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815540145-77</Id><Topic><Title>Ask yourself do you feel safe flying on the 787?</Title><Username>brad_welsh</Username><Timestamp>1373804911101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 787 future weighs heavily on Boeing's future. In fact, at this point, it is their number one hope.</Msg><Username>monitoryeildcuves</Username><Timestamp>1373815540145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815687428-78</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes...Hooz is a sociopathic race bating slug</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373815687428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815737930-79</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Real fact Zimmerman "NOT GUILTY".</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373815737930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815831403-80</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any debate that has to do with freedom or justice ..yes he is wrong...He is only right about issues of foreign policy and war when a Republican is in office however.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373815831403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815941190-81</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Accurately predicting that a Civil Trial is not enough. Soon Hooz will be saying that Zimmerman should be killed and if he floats he was innocent.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373815941190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373816318152-82</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In round one. I am already reading new charges on the federal level are being examined as I write this.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373816318152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373816427480-83</Id><Title>Race Baiting /rioting/ acquittal...ALL PLANNED to keep you distracted from the REAL criminal activity.</Title><Msg>As the Central Bankers rob you blind and engage in all kinds of criminal activities ranging from arming Alqaeda in the middle East and demonizing Tea Party members or having the NSA watch your every movement or pass laws having Imperial Droids (smart meters) monitor your electrical grid at home or any number of unconstitutional nonsense...the NWO is making sure race baiting in the Travon Martin Case keeps you distracted from even noticing or caring. It well reach a crescendo ALL AS PLANNED</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373816427480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373816587712-84</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the new Charge and what is the evidence to substantiate such charges ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373816587712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:43:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373817103317-85</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New Charges Coming For Zimmerman The NAACP, the Rev. Jesse Jackson and other civil rights activists are calling on the U.S. Department of Justice and Attorney Gen. Eric Holder to press federal civil rights charges against George Zimmerman, the former neighborhood watchman who was acquitted by a Sanford, Fla., jury Saturday in the shooting death of 17-year-old Trayvon Martin. “The most fundamental of civil rights — the right to life — was violated the night George Zimmerman stalked and then took the life of Trayvon Martin," NAACP President Ben Jealous wrote in a letter to Holder shortly after the verdict was announced. "We ask that the Department of Justice file civil rights charges against Mr. Zimmerman for this egregious violation. Please address the travesties of the tragic death of Trayvon Martin by acting today.” “This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice," Barbara Arnwine, president of the Washington, D.C.-based Lawyers’ Committee for Civil Rights Under Law, said in a statement. "Yet, there is still the potential for justice to be served through a civil suit brought about by Trayvon Martin’s surviving family members, and also through civil rights charges being brought against Mr. Zimmerman by the Department of Justice." The Justice Dept. launched a probe of the Zimmerman case earlier this year, but has yet to comment on Zimmerman's acquittal.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373817103317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373817125899-86</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously the person who made that quote does not understand the concept of "benefit of the doubt"...OJ had it too</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373817125899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373817198908-87</Id><Topic><Title>For all those happy birds that bought Friday let me know how you feel Monday at 10am, edt. ?????</Title><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1373752582442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 17:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will buy more.</Msg><Username>snelsonagain</Username><Timestamp>1373817198908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373817558435-88</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But OJ did have to take the stand in the civil case ( not civil rights... there wasn't one with OJ, I know ) and, with a disastrous performance, lost. Zimmerman will probably be worse than OJ on the stand. When Zimmerman loses that case, justice will be served.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373817558435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373817763580-89</Id><Title>Rapper Lupe Fiasco Calls Out Race Baiting Media On Trayvon Martin Case</Title><Msg>Anthony Gucciardi July 14, 2013 While many celebrities tossed their 140 characters of nonsense into the realm of Twitter, rapper Lupe Fiasco revealed the truth regarding how the media used the Trayvon Martin case to further ‘antagonize US race relations’. Going on to talk about why the case should have never been televised and turned into a media sensation that is now causing so-called ‘protesters’ to go out and destroy private property, Lupe Fiasco is right on point with this one. As a major black artist, Lupe is obviously not ‘racist’ for calling out the mainstream media on their blatant race baiting and spin of the Trayvon Martin case, and neither am I when I point out this same fact. It simply comes down to looking at the way the media spun the entire case, let alone the ruling, in a way that has justifiably led to concerns that public backlash could result in riots or homicides. And after seeing the slew of Twitter threats from users who said they’d hunt down and kill Zimmerman and others if he was not found guilty, it’s obvious the media has turned this case into a race-driven war. As I’ve discussed earlier, there is a real level of corruption that threatens black individuals, Hispanic individuals, and white individuals. In fact, it’s the biggest threat we face today: corrupt government that has zero regard for our rights in any capacity. So why are we being tricked into fighting each other based on skin color under the guise of stopping the very same racism? It’s simple, and it comes down to political brainwashing 101. HUMANITY COMING TOGETHER = REAL CIVIL LIBERTIES VICTORY If we were all to come together, regardless of skin color, regardless of our so-called ‘political affiliations’, and stand up for our rights and the Constitution — we would assuredly</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373817763580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373817883961-90</Id><Title>Spazticus/Hooz</Title><Msg>Speaks for Hoodlums and Community Agitators among us</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373817883961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373818055844-91</Id><Title>Civil justice forum here now?</Title><Msg>Thought it is a stock forum.</Msg><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373818055844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:07:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373818958732-92</Id><Topic><Title>Is the wiring of an aircfaft inside steel (fireproof) conduit?</Title><Username>whenindoubtdoresearch</Username><Timestamp>1373725360247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 10:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing is fireproof. Items are rated as fire resistant in how long they can withstand hot flames. Steel is on the low end</Msg><Username>andse2003</Username><Timestamp>1373818958732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373819970823-93</Id><Topic><Title>Spazticus/Hooz</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373817883961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:04:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Hoodlums"? What year is this?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373819970823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373820086450-94</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The most fundamental of civil rights — the right to life — was violated" The jury didn't think so....or don't you believe in jury's ...Z Man got the benefit of the doubt. As for a civil trial...what is the legal principle involved ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373820086450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373820462220-95</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't it bother you that Zimmerman called Trayvon an expletive ( from wiki... which posted Zimmerman's call to the police ): "On the recording, Zimmerman is heard saying, "these #$%holes, they always get away." And then promptly disobeyed the orders he received from the police? You mean there is no way that Trayvon's skin color played any role in Zimmerman's motivation to ignore the advice of the police? When he said these #$%holes, was he referring to African-Americans?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373820462220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373820500585-96</Id><Topic><Title>Rapper Lupe Fiasco Calls Out Race Baiting Media On Trayvon Martin Case</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373817763580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>achieve victory against all forms of civil liberties abuse. Against the Patriot Act which allows warrantless wiretapping of US citizens, against the NDAA which allows the indefinite detainment of US citizens, against the DHS-enacted 100 mile ‘border’ where the Constitution does not exist. Against all these real issues. I agree with Lupe Fiasco, it’s time to reclaim our rights together — don’t let the media divide and conquer us in such a simple manner. This post originally appeared at Story Leak</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373820500585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373820501506-97</Id><Title>If the Kent Raven had a son, he'd look like a</Title><Msg>Twinkie.........or perhaps a shorter version of J Reno.........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820501506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373820605250-98</Id><Title>The Kent Raven HATES it when justice is served......</Title><Msg>he can't stand it........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820605250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373820689927-99</Id><Title>The Kent Raven hasn't been this emotionally upset</Title><Msg>since his handout check was late and he had to waddle down his driveway in 3 inches of snow to retrieve it.........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820689927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373820712023-100</Id><Title>The real life crash test in SFO shows you</Title><Msg>the advance of safety features that allows almost all passengers walked out alive for a crash like that. Can you image your car smash to water at 120 mhr?</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373820712023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373820726374-101</Id><Title>REAL AMERICANS 1, DFC's 0</Title><Msg>the jury has spoken.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820726374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373820905020-102</Id><Topic><Title>Spazticus/Hooz</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373817883961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:04:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hood-lums...better? perhaps you prefer @no_limit#$%$? sparty, err hooz, when the dumbo/mobro slush fund dries up maybe can get a job with the NAACP they're always looking for a few good race baiting racists, i mean community agitators.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373820905020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373820931044-103</Id><Title>Boeing and McDonnell Douglas and stock price and how to pick a stock</Title><Msg>Boeing shares closed down 4.7 percent on Friday after the Heathrow fire, knocking $3.8 billion off the company's market capitalization. This is another warning to get out of Boeing . the confidence in the LATEST fire on the BOEING 787 WHICH NOW IS LATE BY 8 years and STILL learning about new ways to catch a fire with the outsourced engineering this will continue to be a ongoing failure. THE REASON IS BOEING went with the already studied and proven failure. BOEING LEADERSHIP will BANKRUPT Boeing, ITS CALLED A outsourced BUSINESS plan. NOW THE AIRLINES , BOEING MANAGEMENT , THE SUPPLIERS AND THE INVESTIGATORS ARE ALL PUTTING A SPIN ON THE SITUATION THEY ALL HAVE AN INVESTMENT IN THIS COLLOSIAL FAILURE. THIS BOEING 787 FAILURE IS LIKE A STOCK MARKET CRASH , THE EARLY STAGES, BOEING CAN BRING DOWN THE DOW JONES BY 200 POINTS NOW. ALL THESE INTERESTED PARTIES ARE ACTING LIKE A JP Morgan AND BANKERS AND ARE attempting to assure BOEING investors that ANOTHER fire, NOT RELATED TO THE LITHIUM BATTERIES , IS NO PROBLEM ! ITS IS A MAJOR PROBLEM THIS MEANS AFTER 8 EXTRA YEARS TO GET IT RIGHT ANOTHER FIRE PROBLEM WHATEVER THE CAUSE EXSISTS ON THE BOEING 787 NOW BOEING AND THE INTERESTED PARTIES INCLUDING THE INVESTIGATORS WILL ATTEMPT TO CONVINCE YOU ANOTHER FIRE IS A GOOD THING ON A BOEING 787, ANY FIRE IS A BAD THING END OF STORY. THE PEOPLE INVESTED IN BOEING WILL SUGGEST you should hold your BOEING shares . what a bunch of crapola. In five years AIRBUS STOCK HAS BETTERED BOIENG . AIRBUS STOCK IS UP 219% COMPARED TO BOENG Up 60% In August of 1997 when Condit of Boeing and Stonecipher of MD took over you should have put all your money in Apple then ! Now you should be in TSLA and SCTY or Airbus .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373820931044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373820935918-104</Id><Topic><Title>The real life crash test in SFO shows you</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1373820712023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Luck has more to do with that .... You may not realize that the runway was JUST extended 300 feet (more buffer away from water). Had this not done recently, the plane could have smashed into the sea wall (most of the plane instead of just the tail) and the outcome could be disastrous.</Msg><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373820935918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373821152972-105</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's calling Trayvon an expletive prior to ignoring police instructions that leads folks to believe a federal civil rights case will be forthcoming. There will definitely be a civil case demanding financial compensation. Zimmerman's going down.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373821152972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373821276328-106</Id><Title>$110 next week</Title><Msg>scam!</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373821276328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373821315399-107</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what expletive?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373821315399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373821550384-108</Id><Topic><Title>$110 next week</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373821276328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you mean? Fire was a scam, or $110 is a scam?</Msg><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373821550384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373821738856-109</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chouse263 look it up fool Boeing is not a short, it only has 1.4% short it is a stay out of stock your statement shows you to be rooky stock market investor</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373821738856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373821833915-110</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jackripeu read my other post on BA and MD and how to pick a stock I think you will find your answer to your comment there ! Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373821833915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373821905239-111</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>food stamp nation please read my post on BA and MD and how to pick a stock I think you will find an answer to why the interested parties will put a positive spin on the fire there Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373821905239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:11:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373821970465-112</Id><Topic><Title>Hello my name is Ed Snowden</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373810705223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:05:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US is no longer the FDR America as we knew it promoting the 4 Freedoms and democratic values. America has become the New Roman Empire bullying nations to fall in line with American interests or face the consequences such as economic sanctions. It keeps all nations under check by its secret NSA surveillance programs. America has put fear in the eyes of our allies. I want back the America that I could trust to tell the truth to the American people, and not find out we been lied to as a result of leaks.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373821970465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822010371-113</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 is taking once sentence out of the news report and writing his own conclusion about me that is called a liar statement by spartacus9991 very typical of this boeing hack</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373822010371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:13:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822023576-114</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I posted it just prior to that last post. I only said "expletive" because yahoo wouldn't let me post it.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373822023576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822055647-115</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and McDonnell Douglas and stock price and how to pick a stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373820931044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've worked at Boeing for almost 25 years. Let me tell you one thing straight up. Boeing builds extraordinary quality in their products and safety always comes first regardless of the bottom line. Was outsourcing a mistake? Well, for the most part, that's obvious. When one critical supplier went south due to quality, schedule, rework, etc, Boeing bought the company in South Carolina and now it has successfully turned that plant into a full up production line in about 3 years doing amazing things. This is cutting edge technology. I read your posts with a great deal of skepticism. Apparently you like to post bashings on a variety of topics. That's okay. I guess you got to make a living by doing something. What's the going rate these days per bask post?</Msg><Username>russellg</Username><Timestamp>1373822055647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822090737-116</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and McDonnell Douglas and stock price and how to pick a stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373820931044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>every time I see a thumbs down another investor goes to Airbus and sell Boeing stock</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373822090737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822097814-117</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He probably lives in Alabama.</Msg><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373822097814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822286618-118</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>meaning you don't wanna repeat it otherwise you'd sound stupid AGAIN, huh hooz...i'm not gonna chase your prior posts, yahoos have made it darn near impossible</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373822286618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373822379647-119</Id><Title>New justice system</Title><Msg>why bother with a trial ? Just use a petition to convict By ALEXIS SHAW (@ashaw109) July 14, 2013 A NAACP petition calling for a federal prosecution of George Zimmerman collected 225,000 signatures in the hours after he was acquitted of killing Trayvon Martin, but the effort was temporarily cut short when the site crashed under the heavy traffic. The rush to add to the petition -- which had more than 350,000 signatures by noon today -- was match by the outpouring of anger on social media. Protests, which police had feared could turn violent, were muted, but the rhetoric was impassioned and often framed around the issue of race. Zimmerman, 29, is a white Hispanic and Martin, 17, was black. ++++ against Zimmerman we have ... sharpton, jackson, holder, obuma, 80 percent of news media</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373822379647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822468558-120</Id><Topic><Title>Is the wiring of an aircfaft inside steel (fireproof) conduit?</Title><Username>whenindoubtdoresearch</Username><Timestamp>1373725360247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 10:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The product, the company, and the union.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1373822468558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822600528-121</Id><Topic><Title>Is the wiring of an aircfaft inside steel (fireproof) conduit?</Title><Username>whenindoubtdoresearch</Username><Timestamp>1373725360247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 10:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no need to change IDs just for us sparty, err hooz...though i gotta say your current costume fits perfectly</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373822600528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822683227-122</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and McDonnell Douglas and stock price and how to pick a stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373820931044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>russellg I have a full pension from Boeing and your full of crapola one supplier went south due to quality makes zero sense tht that caused a shift from Everett to Carolina and it is not true your so full of crapola ,. I do not think you ever worked for Boeing your not making any sense here. I am in TSLA, read my history I called it on May3 and in 15 trade days I made 100% I am in SCTY and it is up 270% I was in apple for many years just ask spartacus9991, he missed it all, arguing with me for years about why Boeing should be the one to go with or then saying he was actually not in Boeing the guy , like you ,is a lair and I was in ACAD last year and part of this year and made over 1200% I posted the ACAD gains at 25% and at 60% Spartacus 9991 . lied and said he was in a non existent stock called IGZ and ist was up 144% which is a symbol used to test the system all you hacks are the same liar and evil trolls a bunch of fools</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373822683227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373822717176-123</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimmerman's call to police was posted on wiki. On the recording, Zimmerman is heard saying, "these #$%holes, they always get away." On the subject of freedom, are Americans like myself entitled to feel that he meant African-Americans when he said that?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373822717176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373823039490-124</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and McDonnell Douglas and stock price and how to pick a stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373820931044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep I just pulled your history russellg you have only one post listed, the above one, your a Boeing hack and this is just another name for spartacus9991</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373823039490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373823346538-125</Id><Topic><Title>On Sunday, all Airlines stated they gave 100% Confidence in the Safety of Boeing's Dreamliner!</Title><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373812434236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:33:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong, you lose!</Msg><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373823346538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373823353624-126</Id><Topic><Title>Is the wiring of an aircfaft inside steel (fireproof) conduit?</Title><Username>whenindoubtdoresearch</Username><Timestamp>1373725360247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 10:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would add a lot of weight and increase fuel consumption. Generally the only places run in any form of a fireproof conduit is when the have to pass by a part of the aircraft that could subject them to damaging temperatures. One thing I think made the latest situation a lot worse is the plane was unattended, which allowed the fire to grow a lot worse than it would of otherwise. If the plane was manned I suspect the breakers would have been turned off very soon after the malfunction which might prevented the fire, and if not it would not have taken a lot of effort put out the fire since it would have been dealt right away instead of maybe smoldering for hours.</Msg><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1373823353624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373823442048-127</Id><Title>@waynedick: Did I read you correctly?</Title><Msg>Are you saying BA shares will trade lower on Monday? Friday closing was $101.87. I have thousands of shares from put assignment. What is your basis of saying that?</Msg><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373823442048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373823690896-128</Id><Title>Changing Sparty's Focus</Title><Msg>on July 1st... Four south Cobb teenagers are in custody in connection with the beating death of a 36-year-old Mableton man on Mableton Parkway early Sunday morning. According to the warrant, the four teenagers are accused of starting a fight with Chellew at a Chevron gas station in the 6200 block of Mableton Parkway near Community Drive at about 1:20 a.m. Sunday. They repeatedly punched and kicked him, according to police. While attempting to escape, Chellew backed into the center five-lane highway and was pushed to the ground and knocked unconscious, the warrant states. They then walked away from Chellew, “leaving him helpless,” and he was eventually hit by a car, the warrant states.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373823690896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373824189052-129</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The discussion that needs to take place is how to change the behavior of our youth to prevent such perceptions. If you walk like a thug, talk like a thug and dress like a thug, people will have the perception you are a thug. So be prepared to be treated as a thug. Trayvon's death is unfortunate, and I pray his family can heal and have peace. We will be accepting this behavior, and worse, if the only discussion is how to stop profiling without a discussion on changing the underlying behavior.</Msg><Username>texastrader61</Username><Timestamp>1373824189052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373824388605-130</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A party does not lose his Fifth Amendment right against self incrimination in a civil suit</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373824388605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373824480730-131</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty puts on his lawyer pantsuit</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373824480730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373824526602-132</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It also does not stop Zimmerman from suing NBC for falsly editing the emergency call to the police</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373824526602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373825216166-133</Id><Title>An important part of the investigation will be...............</Title><Msg>If the fault occurred in flight, what is the likelihood it would have turned into the major fire this was? Secondly did the damage render the plane un able to fly despite all the damage? I think a large contributing factor was the plane was unattended. I doubt the fire would have ever gotten any where close to what it did if it had happed in the air, Breakers at the first sign of smoke would have been turned off, and if it continued to smoke a few blast of CO2 from a fire extinguisher likely would have put an end to it. Instead we had a fire the may have smoldered all night before it burned a hole through the fuselage allowing all to see too late what likely started as a minor fire was a major one. I have heard some accounts that the plane was powered down all breakers open, I am pretty sure that was not the case as I don't see how this could have happened if that was the case.</Msg><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1373825216166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373825696746-134</Id><Topic><Title>@waynedick: Did I read you correctly?</Title><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373823442048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:37:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You also claimed you made the right call on TSLA. I did not see your call. I was there. You are full of it.</Msg><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373825696746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373826078795-135</Id><Title>oldtimer stick to what you do right eh !</Title><Msg>oldtimer2013 • Reply Elon Musk knows more about the stock market than the shorts, it appears. so that is you best post according to me . so oldtimer, I am not sure what your point is and I do not care at all, I do want you to know that Boeing is a stay out stock, certainly not a short or a long here is why. That would make sense. Elon is the $ billionaire here. If the shorts were as smart as they claim, they would be billionaires already. Boeing is only 1.40% of the available number of shares short or only 9.7 million shares short . use whatever source you like , I made 100% on the TSLA short squeeze that I new was coming on TSLA on may 3 in just 15 trade days . I had been in tesla for a year and then the shorts were about 36% of the available stock a huge amount. I caught the panic to cover when TSLA kept going up like it is doing now. Different story todday, TSLA shorts are down to about 27% now With Boeing, only at a very small percent short , your a fool to short Boeing and your a fool to be in Boeing when you could be in TSLA or SCTY or Airbus if you want slow growth! For slow growth with a similar dividend to Boeing go with a better airplane maker and much better managed company! Airbus bettered Boeing over 5 yeas Airbus stock price has gained 219% while Boeing has gained 60% mainly on stock buyback since the 4 month 787 grounding. Boeing may dump big time but I would never short a stock like Boeing now with only 1.4% short interest on a very small portion of the available stock are you sure you know anything about how to make money in the stock market I think your a total fraud ! Boeing short intesrets Short Interest (Shares Short) 9,740,100 Days To Cover (Short Interest Ratio) 1.7 Short Percent of Float 1.40 % Short Interest - Prior 9,724,100 Short % Increase / Decrease 0.16</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373826078795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373826596168-136</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and McDonnell Douglas and stock price and how to pick a stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373820931044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have a full pension from Boeing? and yet you pound them day and night, sounds to me like an ingrate, that's biting the hand that feeds him .IF you are a past employlee ,you would know of the quality that goes into these planes. But then, janitors don't have much to do with building planes,do they?????????</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1373826596168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373826720504-137</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once again a high priced lawyer shows how money impacts justice. I saw some of the #$%$ he got away with in court while the prosecutors stood there with their mouths shut when they should have been objecting like mad. Most damaging was allowing the defense demonstration using a light dummy to show how Zimmerman was being pounded into the sidewalk to go on un-objected. They allowed the defense to bound the head of that dummy off the floor like the rag doll it was and present that as evidence of how Trayvon was beating up Zimmerman, total #$%$. Zimmerman did weigh about 10 pounds like the dummy they used, and the dummy presenting no resistance to that like a real person would have. I would have objected to the whole demonstration the second they took out the dummy, and if it had gone forward it would have been with a real person that resisted, and I will tell you chances are high they would have ripped their shirt off before they could move them anywhere close that what they did with the dummy.</Msg><Username>send_this_pig_to_hell</Username><Timestamp>1373826720504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373826837480-138</Id><Topic><Title>To what standards do you build something new and innovative like the 787 (learning experiences)</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1373741981525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flying is a death trap if you want to be picky. But, your own automobile is too. No matter how defensive and careful driver you are you could get hit with a drunk running red lights or going the wrong way etc. can happen. Look at the fatality statistics. Dues the potential for death in an automobile stops you from driving your car. We live in a dangerous world. You are never going to eliminate all the dangers in the world.</Msg><Username>michaeljoseph4040</Username><Timestamp>1373826837480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:33:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827639876-139</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now we can see something of Wayne's thinking. He habitually talkes an AP, Reuter's or newspaper article that contains factual info on Boeing's problems and changes a phrase or sentence to back up his bias. That's called plagarism or worse and he sees nothing wrong with that. Then he blames the person who pointed out his distortions. Sad.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373827639876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827775138-140</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373827775138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827805175-141</Id><Topic><Title>An important part of the investigation will be...............</Title><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1373825216166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:06:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The situation is closed to a parked car catching fire. Not a very likely event but it does happen. With autos, fires are associated with the catalytic converter which stays very hot well after engine shut down. Was it an oven in the 787? It's all a mystery at this time. Of prime importance is how the market will react to the news once it is out.</Msg><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373827805175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827808447-142</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do you say African-American ? I don't say Polish-American, Italian-American, German-American, no I say American we are all AMERICANS thats it, unless of course you were born in another country, GET IT, stop using the racist term African-American.</Msg><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1373827808447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827857334-143</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Only in America can a dead black boy go on trial for his own murder." - Syreeta McFadden.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1373827857334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827861046-144</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry me a river.......do.. sh.. bag.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373827861046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373827967712-145</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uhh it was the prosecution that introduced the dummy !!!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373827967712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373828735951-146</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Know doubt you could have used you for the dummy.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1373828735951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373828841209-147</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven, you need to get over it before you blow a gasket!!!!! You sick freak! HA HA HA HA!!!!!</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1373828841209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373829021867-148</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 not making any reference to anything I posted and claiming I modified it that is called liar statements so we do know as usual you spartacus9991 like you liar claim on IGZ are still and always making liar statements here is a reference to your liar statements "waynedickenson961 • Apr 11, 2013 7:01 PM • • • IGZ • Reply so sparti you asked me to stop pointing out that your a very poor critic and I used your ignorant claim about a stock IGZ, you attempted to criticize my 19 day ago 26% gain on ACAD with a bogus trade and 1445 gain on . IGZ . spartacus9991, guess what fool, IGZ is not a real stock you’re a fool. IGZ you thought was up 144% but it is a test symbol for working on the stock market software, not a real stock. Fool. You picked a stock you know nothing about, after the fact to my real time trade on ACAD. spartacus991 you’re a antagonist , and have it in for me that is your only reason to be here . First of all sparti , you started the crapola years ago with me on Apple and now you want to cry uncle? Why would I stop , you have been dogging me for years , you could have moved on or actually made some real money off my stock suggestions at the time they were apple for 15 years , you dogged me about it for 15 years as you claim it is spirited dialog, nope your a Boeing Hack, spartacus9991 as a liar your easy to catch, Sparti, I have been pointing out now that Airbus long term is far better than Boeing and ACAD is a great stock, did you follow ACAD or Airbus , nope your a Boeing Hack . so once more and as usual for you listen up, ACAD just made me another 67% today just 19 trade days after you tried to slam me with a bogus stock IGZ you claimed then IGZ was up more than ACAD short term, well spartacus9991 IGZ once more is not a real stock. is not a stock , it is a symbol used by the stock market to test their system. , get it now ?( ACAD topped at over 1200% for me I am in TSLA and SCTY and SBUX since IPO) Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373829021867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373829063069-149</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1445 should be 144%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373829063069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373829270040-150</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dummy up, meathead.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1373829270040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373829756399-151</Id><Title>BOING !! $93 by WED JULY 17th AND $88 by FRIDAY JULY 19th</Title><Msg>Only the institutional people, WHO PROSTITUTE THEIR COMPANIES AND MISMANAGED funds AND malpracticing fund mangers WILL HANG ON, FOR THEIR pimp WHICH IS ONE OF MANY (aka- Boeing) who fund their bonds and refinance their debt will support this ELEPHANT WITH A BIG THORN IN BETWEEN IT's TOES ; now...</Msg><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1373829756399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:22:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373829811253-152</Id><Topic><Title>An important part of the investigation will be...............</Title><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1373825216166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:06:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Of prime importance is how the market will react to the news once it is out." Of more importance is whether this would have been a safety issue had it occured in-flight. Seems like it would have been very difficult to get to a fire to extinguish it without tearing out the ceiing/interiors of the plane first for access What is more important, peoples lives or the stock price. Amazing how money can make a person think about safety issues. Not trying to single out your post, this attitude of money over lives seems to be rampant everywhere.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1373829811253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373829883589-153</Id><Topic><Title>$110 next week</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1373821276328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not any more...Only the people who sold CMOs to ICELAND will market this Bad Boy, going forward.</Msg><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1373829883589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373830676575-154</Id><Topic><Title>An important part of the investigation will be...............</Title><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1373825216166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:06:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, it's not an issue of money vs. lives. We don't know if this fire could have happened in flight. The market is on tenterhooks with respect to the all composite, all electric 787 that is assembled from a large number of vendors. Very new concepts in all. How many shoes need to drop before investors can sleep well.</Msg><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373830676575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373830679180-155</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there anyway we can pay them off to get a favorable conclusion? Remember there are a lot of jobs at stake</Msg><Username>av_week_reader</Username><Timestamp>1373830679180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373830843806-156</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe a change in name will fool the public? Instead of 787 how about MD-788!</Msg><Username>caveman2501</Username><Timestamp>1373830843806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373831445497-157</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No it doesn't represent a tragic miscarriage of justice. It represents a victory for a brilliant defense. This case has established Mark O'Mara as one of today's best criminal defense lawyers. The prosecution lawyers were sadly lacking strategy. They made mistakes from the start in prosecuting the case against Zimmerman. For example, instead of aiming for first degree murder, they should have aimed for manslaughter. The prosecution never had witnesses nor evidence to establish murder in the first degree. You can't win a case based on suppositions and castles in the air.</Msg><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1373831445497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:50:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373832238515-158</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In New York, Zimmerman would be convicted of manslaughter. There's no Stand Your Ground for Zimmerman to fall back on in New York. He would be guilty of reckless vigilantism and failure to heed the "Do not follow suspect" order from the 911 dispatcher. In New York, Zimmerman would get 10 to 15 years minimum. We don't tolerate such criminal behavior in New York.</Msg><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1373832238515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373832367408-159</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you claiming you didn't add " BOEING’S cheap outsourced 787 plane" to the original Reuter's article? I posted both versions for all to compare. Now you're the liar.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373832367408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373832540996-160</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>C'mon, Dell, everyone on this board knows how you like to twist the facts to suit your warped mind's needs. If there were ever a liar on the board, you take the top billing in that department. As I have said before, I do not believe anything you say, especially about your alleged stock trading gains. Isn't there an Airbus board you could inhabit? Have a nice day!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1373832540996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373833065765-161</Id><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Msg>you can listen to spartacus9991 and buy IGZ ha ha or you could have folled me for apple for over 10 years until steve jobs died or ACAD for a year up over 1200% or be in TSLA and SCTY now or go with Airbus up 218% over 5 years bettering Boeing up 60% in the same time your choice, MAKE A GOOD CHOICE WAYNE</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373833133685-162</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep the world of IF ... my aunt would have had *** she would have been my uncle . . The prosecution had zip evidence - the defense had more FACTS. martin had 4 minutes to walk home in a different direction than zimmerman when he parked his car - zimmerman had a nosebleed and cuts on the back of his head - not self inflicted martin had grass stains on his knees and zimmerman had them on his back the prosecutors office held back evidence on discovery- wheich may not have been admissible anyhow MSDNC and affiliate NBC or vice versa cut the tapes of the 911 call to make it sound like zimmerman volunteered martin was black- the full tape proved he was responding to a question by 911 And your DOJ - community organizer kommitee rattled the cage, bussed in non locals, and set up a campaign which resulted in firing a police chief cuz he found no grounds to arrest. The prosecution bypased a required grand jury indictment The prosecution cvlaimed Zimmerman told his friend to tell his wife he had just killed someone- which was a false statement when compared to the testimony of the witness involved. ObUma stuck his nose in FBI investigated re civil rights - still no answer-result Facts /evidence in a criminal case sometimes cannot be used in a civil case and vice versa- its called double jepordy And now- naacp is pushing a petition for some sort of federal intervention re civil rights</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373833133685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373833420809-163</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you claiming I did ad that? spartacus9991 simple all you have to do is show me the article first eh ! your a liar spartacus9991 show me the article you still have not done that why not spartacus9991 !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833420809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373833440539-164</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When he said these #$%holes, was he referring to African-Americans? L No he thought it was YOU !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373833440539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373833477640-165</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING'S 787 FIRE CLASSIFIED AS SERIOUS INCIDENT , ONE STEP BELOW FULL BLOWN ACCIDENT AND GROUNDING SO FAR</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373781933653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 02:05:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good day wayne, i think what chouse263 is talking about is that ba became the 21st most shorted stock replacing pg per june 27 headlines. also, if you read some old headlines, one person predicted to buy some puts and calls for july 12. interesting. glta,</Msg><Username>leereece42</Username><Timestamp>1373833477640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373833547603-166</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's that invention patent coming along? Is Burt helping you? If Boeing was awarded the Collier Trophy in 2011 for the "lame" lighter weight 787, can your award be far behind? LOL "waynedickenson961 waynedickenson961 • Jun 24, 2013 4:31 PM Flag 1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 3 Reply Boeing barkers here is why I use the Boeing message board , because I am a stock market money maker and your BA barkers with nothing invested in Boeing .I know Boeing management and know the problems and probably will sell an invention soon that will be a giant step forward in aerospace technology, not the baby steps of lighter weight planes that is so lame . Less"</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373833547603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373833562578-167</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...The defense in this case pleaded 2nd degree murder and manslaughter.. Hey dummy- the defense pleaded zip - its the prosecution that pleaded. The defense - defendant pleaded NOT Guilty . Period</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373833562578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373833578220-168</Id><Title>No grounding no cancellazations ...buisness as usual</Title><Msg>labeled as serious is a win</Msg><Username>opele1</Username><Timestamp>1373833578220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373833584168-169</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In New York, Zimmerman would have been dead - killed by Trayvon.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1373833584168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373833609203-170</Id><Topic><Title>BOING !! $93 by WED JULY 17th AND $88 by FRIDAY JULY 19th</Title><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1373829756399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:22:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its simple forget Boeing go with TSLA or SCTY or Airbus if you want another slow moving stock only up 218% in five years bettered Boeing up 60% in five years both are doggy but if the A350 goes good then Airbus will return 100% more fast for a slow moving stock and Boeing will fall to the 70 dollar range per Tom OBrien and he called it at 107 and there about it hit the wall and crashed right! so far</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833609203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834030674-171</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when airbus uses it I will be the first to let you know about it, unlike you, spartacus9991 , I only tell you what , I want you to know , you tell me about your wife on a financial web sight what a fool, spartacus9991 how is that great fake stock IGZ that you lied about and claimed to make 144% on doing for you ha ha what a fool ! you missed apple , missed acad , lied about IGZ making 144%, the stock does not exist you just shopped for one to attempt to make my ACAD look bad ACAD went up over 12005 and I told you at 25% gain and at 67% gain your a stupid fool spartacus9991 you missed 1200% like now TSLA and SCTY your a fool spartacus9991 , you missing a huge run up and still the fool, I cant teach stupid spartacus9991</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834030674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834120333-172</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The prosecutor claims to be a mind reader !! State Attorney Angela Corey said after the verdict that she believed second-degree murder was the appropriate charge because Zimmerman's mindset "fit the bill of second-degree murder." "We charged what we believed we could prove," Corey said.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373834120333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373834432231-173</Id><Title>spartacus9991 tip on IGZ a liar is a liar is a fool</Title><Msg>waynedickenson961 • Apr 11, 2013 7:01 PM • • • IGZ • Reply so sparti you asked me to stop pointing out that your a very poor critic and I used your ignorant claim about a stock IGZ, you offered to criticize my 19 day ago 26% acad gain. ? IGZ is not a real stock you’re a fool. IGZ you thought was up 144% but it is a test symbol for working on the stock market software, not a real stock. Fool. You picked a symbol used for testing the stock market software. Spartacus9991, you know nothing about trading stock do you spartacus9991! spartacus9991 your a angry fool that is it. you think by being a antagonist since you have it in for me that is your only reason to be here . First of all sparti , you started the crapola years ago with me and now you want to cry uncle? Why would I stop , you have been dogging me for years , you could have moved on or actually made some real money off my stock suggestions at the time they were apple for 15 years , you dogged me about it for 15 years as you claim it is spirited dialog, nope your a Boeing Hack not a very good one at that. Sparti, I have been pointing out now that Airbus long term is far better than Boeing and ACAD is a great stock, did you follow ACAD or Airbus , nope your a Boeing Hack not a good one . so once more and as usual for you, spartacus9991, listen up, ACAD just made me another 67% today in just 19 trade days after you tried to slam me with a bogus stock IGZ you claimed it was up more than ACAD, nope fool, IGZ is not a stock , it is a symbol used by the stock market to test their system their system. , get it how ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834432231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834546301-174</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a civil trial Zimmerman will be required to give his account of things. He'll be creamed. I believe there will be a civil rights case as well. In other words, Zimmerman is facing years of this... and still more years after that.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373834546301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834626433-175</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's that hyro racing you told the board about on a financial web site? How's the Boeing pension and all your handshaking with top executives because you were so valuable to Boeing and they tried to keep you from retiring? You won't have to personally tell me because if it is " a giant step forward in aerospace technology" the TV news channels, NY Times, and Av Week will be reporting it as top news stories. Then we'll all know your real name and backstory. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373834626433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373834628867-176</Id><Title>Boys BA guaranteed to take out last weels low at 98.99 on it's way to 90-95</Title><Msg>there is no way in Gods green earth that after a outside day and week this stock isn't going lower even if the fire was from a coffee pot, the technicals will take the spotlight all next week. GLTA</Msg><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1373834628867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834642207-177</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't know that for certain.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373834642207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834760442-178</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 tip on IGZ a liar is a liar is a fool</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834432231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the result was ACAD continued to go up until recently where it topped at over 1200% gain for me. Now its TSLA and SCTY and as usuall spartacus9991 is losing out talk about being a loser over time spartacus9991 wise up Airbus up 2185 over 5 years Boeing up 60% over five years the A350 project is learning from the failed 787 plan all the best contractors cherry picked from Boeing the batteries will be changed from lithium to NiCad the systems are l much better than Boeing read up on it stop being my personal fool do something positive with your life</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834760442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834791602-179</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 tip on IGZ a liar is a liar is a fool</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834432231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2185 should be 218%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834791602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373834981775-180</Id><Title>Galley Fire</Title><Msg>The fire started in the crews relief quarters located in the planes rear. This version of the 787 has a small galley in the rear for use by the crew and the rear flight attendants. Crews are being advised to shut off the power to the rear galley as a safety precaution while the plane is on the ground until the exact cause is found. But at this point it appears the problem is not related to any critical aircraft system. But an exact cause of the fire has not been declared and probably will not be for several more days.</Msg><Username>logictheorist</Username><Timestamp>1373834981775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373835170779-181</Id><Topic><Title>Galley Fire</Title><Username>logictheorist</Username><Timestamp>1373834981775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...The fire started in the crews relief quarters located in the planes rear... Ethopia configuration does NOT use or have crew quarters aft - they do have a galley . . .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373835170779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373835309045-182</Id><Topic><Title>An important part of the investigation will be...............</Title><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1373825216166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:06:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...Secondly did the damage render the plane un able to fly despite all the damage? .. DUH look at the photos - it is unable to fly !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373835309045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373835427207-183</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor little Raven, always on the wrong side of every issue............getting all emotional and hysterical won't change the verdict, now run along dck weed.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1373835427207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373835459011-184</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and McDonnell Douglas and stock price and how to pick a stock</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373820931044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. I don't even know how to respond to your replies. Not even worth the effort. I don't know what your agenda is, my friend. And, I have no idea who spartacus9991 is. .</Msg><Username>russellg</Username><Timestamp>1373835459011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373835610012-185</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 tip on IGZ a liar is a liar is a fool</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834432231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what are your other "avatars" for the last 15 years since "waynedickenson961" has only been registered since August 2012? You call yourself a stock trader and don't even know what the correct trading symbol is for EADS. LOL. What a fool. P.S. You posted this morning" BOEING 787 WHICH NOW IS LATE BY 8 years" Last week you posted the 787 has been late by 4 years. Wow, that was a quick 4 years passing.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373835610012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373835684456-186</Id><Topic><Title>No grounding no cancellazations ...buisness as usual</Title><Username>opele1</Username><Timestamp>1373833578220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing has got to do better than business as usual. The news wires are reporting another 777 incident. This time its a hydrolic leak the plane return back to Tokyo for repairs.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373835684456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373835880745-187</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's like the playoffs... just need two out of three.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373835880745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373835937530-188</Id><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Msg>spartacus99991 • May 28, 2013 11:30 AM Flag • Yes, TSLA and SCTY are better stocks than BA the last month for making money for traders. Happy now? Now my statement just like apple, I could have made you spartacus9991 several thousand percent of gains all the way until Steve jobs died, and yet spartacus9991, you argued for Boeing against Apple, spartacus9999a then it was ACAD most recently, I could have make you 1200% in one year and now your still arguing with me as I make 275%on each TSLA and SCTY and I am still in both . spartacus9991 and you missed SBUX up over 90000% better than Boeing since the IPO in 1992 when I got in at 17 dollars per share, I have added on each split and on each dividend too . Now don't start telling me I am so rich, I should write a book, you have already told me that on more than one occasion. I will answer that now , since I choose to answer it now. First , since I am very poor at spelling and grammar not going to happen, and you can not teach what I know in a book , it's called thinking, like you spartacu9991 you really can not think that is the problem. the books already explain how to trade a stock , you still need to be able to discern the more important from the least important trader facts. I have done that for me . spartacus99991 the only thing you have demonstrated to me is your a critic, you know a critic is someone who can not trade or act so they become a critic get it now Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373836137142-189</Id><Topic><Title>Boys BA guaranteed to take out last weels low at 98.99 on it's way to 90-95</Title><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1373834628867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:43:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your wrong; you lose. BA stock price going back to $105 tomorrow, and new 52 week high by end of week!</Msg><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373836137142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373836396293-190</Id><Topic><Title>No grounding no cancellazations ...buisness as usual</Title><Username>opele1</Username><Timestamp>1373833578220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These types of issues occur all the time with Boeing and Airbus and all aviation companies. That is what maintenance/inspection/ground crews are for to repair these issues. You are an idiot! Your wrong, BA is going up again on Monday! You lose!</Msg><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373836396293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:13:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373836722227-191</Id><Topic><Title>busloads of Trayon Martin supporters arriving in Sanford, Florida by the hundreds.</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1373663473513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 17:11:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did they ride in the back ?</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1373836722227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:18:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837045749-192</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad your mother didn't miscarriage you #$%$ zero</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1373837045749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837115951-193</Id><Topic><Title>These Planes Are Chock Full Of Cheap Foreign Made Electrical Components......Fire On The Wing</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1373756947061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 19:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You worked harder when high, was kinder and generally more productive in society??</Msg><Username>husseindamuud</Username><Timestamp>1373837115951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837227440-194</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were a lot of mistakes made in the trial on both sides, but I agree with maramwp that the defense attorney earned his pay. What was insane was the way the police seemed initially ready to just let it go, and maybe that won't happen again. What the vast majority of Americans wanted to see was justice done, and under the terms of our legal system, it was. So 6 ladies decided if a black man charged them and pounded on their heads, whether they deserved it or not, they'd shoot. That is the test in this land. It may be too bad, but maybe a wrongful death civil suit will give the family the closure they need. Zipperman and OJ have BOTH been found not guilty. (Not innocent, just not guilty.) My personal belief is that karma can be a hassle, and it may yet hassle zippy like it did OJ. But we have to let it go. "Justice," even if you have to put it in quotes, has been done. I'm glad as he11 that it wasn't up to the right-fringe gun nuts on this board.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373837227440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837355909-195</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give it a rest, Loon. Patriots, as you claim to be, are supposed to want justice to take its course as outlined in the U.S. Constitution. It was, so your gloating about the outcome is just mental (and verbal) mast urbation.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373837355909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837587777-196</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Double jeopardy consist ONLY of being charged twice with the same crime. Let's let it go. Everyone.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373837587777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837665674-197</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The part we don't understand is the part where YOU try to explain anything to anyone, Floyd.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373837665674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837697369-198</Id><Topic><Title>An important part of the investigation will be...............</Title><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1373825216166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:06:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market (public especially) hasn't had the chance to react yet, as this happened Friday afternoon, after everyone was at the beach. Anyone tempted to hold this Monday morning....is just being foolish.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1373837697369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373837947004-199</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris, there will be a civil trial, and probably a federal civil rights trial. I think Zimmerman loses both.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373837947004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373838068135-200</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" SBUX up over 90000%" LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373838068135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373838118640-201</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven hasn't been this emotionally upset</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820689927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hadn't posted re Trevon Martin/Zipperman until a few minutes ago, you nitwit.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373838118640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373838226380-202</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 tip on IGZ a liar is a liar is a fool</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834432231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You haven't even been on this board for "15 years". Only since August 2012. What a fool. So easy to trip up.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373838226380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373838328025-203</Id><Title>MSNBC is the new BET network -- did the white community protest</Title><Msg>when O.J was given a free ticket, no there was nothing about racism, we just accepted the verdict, we didn't believe it but we accepted it. This term African- American is as racist as it gets. We are all just Americans unless you were born in another country and Trayvon Martin was born in the United States of America, that makes him just and American, the only reason that other term is used is to start hatred between the races.</Msg><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1373838328025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:45:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373838360074-204</Id><Topic><Title>REAL AMERICANS 1, DFC's 0</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820726374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Floyd is a real muricin</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1373838360074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373838571225-205</Id><Topic><Title>Main problem Monday is not related too 787, but China GDP</Title><Username>rndyjensen</Username><Timestamp>1373752307422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 17:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People keep saying that China slowing down is a non event and they have been right for quite a while. But I think you are right, eventually this will be relevant to the world economy and it could impact Boeing because a significant fraction of the backlog is from China.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1373838571225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:49:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373838698012-206</Id><Topic><Title>An important part of the investigation will be...............</Title><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1373825216166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:06:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poland government prohibited kosher slaughtering of animals.</Msg><Username>husseindamuud</Username><Timestamp>1373838698012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373838700132-207</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's just as entitled to his opinions as you are, Loon. Only superpatriots like you would deny him that.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373838700132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373838734790-208</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven hasn't been this emotionally upset</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820689927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was directed at me. :-)</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373838734790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373840114630-209</Id><Topic><Title>@waynedick: Did I read you correctly?</Title><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373823442048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:37:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ You have the correct screen ID. 1. When did you make the right TSLA call? I do not recall you being there. No response, right? that's what I thought. 2. You have a full pension from Boeing? You probably meant you had a FOOL pension. What an idiot !</Msg><Username>oldtimer2013</Username><Timestamp>1373840114630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373840187666-210</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand your point. But as for THIS verdict, it's time to let it go. Zipperman will get the future his character deserves. Maybe he will move on to something Sparty can really respect, like defending the Alamo from illegal immigrants? Well, maybe not... ;-D</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373840187666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373841091198-211</Id><Topic><Title>Race Baiting /rioting/ acquittal...ALL PLANNED to keep you distracted from the REAL criminal activity.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373816427480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:40:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ease with which Democrats and their operatives can so easily play black people is what should make America afraid. To get a race of people to riot over a case of an overzealous neighborhood watchman shooting and killing a teen who attacked him takes some doing. If you remove the race elements from this story, black people would have as much interest in this case as they would reruns of The Lawrence Welk Show. Yet here we are. The Zimmerman case front and center—a 21st Century OJ trial, except this one black people want the defendant declared guilty. Thousands of black teens have been murdered since Martin’s death, yet Liberals have chosen to fixate on Martin’s death? Black Liberals should ask themselves why they have disproportionate emotion in this case versus the thousands of others. Hadiya Pendleton Hadiya Pendleton Recall the young girl, Hadiya Pendleton who had visited with Obama at the White House, then two weeks later was unceremoniously gunned down in a drive-by shooting in Chicago? If only her murderer had been Zimmerman! However, since her killer was likely black, there were no t-shirts with her face printed on them. Nor the almost countless other nameless, faceless black youth who are now just as dead as Trayvon Martin. Do their families not grieve? Do their deaths not demand justice? Don’t expect the great uniter to showcase leadership in the Zimmerman case. Obama will allow the racist attitudes of Liberals to flourish. That is the glue that binds him to black people, a group to whom he has shown little, real concern. Luckily for him, black people only care about Obama’s blackness. It’s difficult to fathom that blacks have fought so hard against racism, only to become the most racist people in the country. Black Liberals don’t care about justice for Zimmerman, because he is the wrong color. Truth be told, if Zimmerman were black, this case would have been over a long time ago</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373841091198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373841149306-212</Id><Topic><Title>Galley Fire</Title><Username>logictheorist</Username><Timestamp>1373834981775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your wrong. I have a cabin plan of this plane (the exact same one that caught fire) provided to me by Boeing and it clearly shows the rear galley with the crew quarters in the rear. The plane has 3 galleys, one in the business class all the way forward, one in the forward section of the economy class between the forward entrance doors, and the one in the rear, the back of which contains the crew bunks. Are you trying to say that Ethiopian Airlines reconfigured this plane since they took possession of it from Boeing?</Msg><Username>logictheorist</Username><Timestamp>1373841149306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373842546587-213</Id><Topic><Title>Jim MCKay arrested for male prostititution</Title><Username>jewishamerica</Username><Timestamp>1373826398614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FORWARDED TO YAHOO!!</Msg><Username>transatlantique2013</Username><Timestamp>1373842546587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373842581958-214</Id><Topic><Title>Race Baiting /rioting/ acquittal...ALL PLANNED to keep you distracted from the REAL criminal activity.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373816427480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:40:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"To get a race of people to riot over a case of an overzealous neighborhood watchman shooting and killing a teen who attacked him takes some doing. If you remove the race elements from this story, black people would have as much interest in this case as they would reruns of The Lawrence Welk Show." Gee, and people accuse you of being prejudiced... go figure. That paragraph is littered with inaccuracies and could only come from a bigot. Many White folks are upset over this verdict... and it doesn't take "some doing" for people to be angry over a senseless tragedy like a teenager dying. And, as much as you want to believe African-Americans are robots who have no emotions, they would take an interest in this story and be saddened it regardless of the racial aspects.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373842581958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373843347822-215</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree... with everything. :-)</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373843347822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373843729779-216</Id><Topic><Title>Hello my name is Ed Snowden</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373810705223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:05:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am going to be posting herre about how Snowden is being wrongly hounded by the Obama administration until the cows come home.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373843729779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373843749974-217</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am all for profiling. It saves a lot of LE work. If you're not a bad boy, profiling will not cause you any harm. If you dress and act per a profile, expect some attention. Simple is it not?</Msg><Username>broad_and_south</Username><Timestamp>1373843749974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373844125669-218</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither you (cause you are too clueless) nor the Raven/Hooz (because they are too proud to admit they are wrong) will refute the aforementioned point</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373844125669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373844228435-219</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I notice you're not telling Hooz to give it a rest hypocrite. He is the one saying its not over...and we now have the Feds who want to get in the act with yet another court case...not to mention tort claims...</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373844228435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373844388089-220</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Zimmerman's call to police was posted on wiki" Is that the one where NBC edited out what Zimmerman really said ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373844388089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373844391171-221</Id><Topic><Title>Galley Fire</Title><Username>logictheorist</Username><Timestamp>1373834981775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where on the boeing site does it show the ethopia configuration as opposed to the ' standard' configuration ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373844391171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373844757954-222</Id><Topic><Title>Galley Fire</Title><Username>logictheorist</Username><Timestamp>1373834981775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:49:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Note the seat configuration does not show crew rest quarters- but does show galleys</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373844757954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373844855478-223</Id><Topic><Title>Race Baiting /rioting/ acquittal...ALL PLANNED to keep you distracted from the REAL criminal activity.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373816427480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:40:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is amazing how often you are out-right wrong. Latest poll When Rasmussen Reports asked some of its polling subjects to conduct an odd exercise in racial stereotyping, the results were counterintuitive, or at least counterstereotypical: "Thirty-seven percent (37%) of American Adults think most black Americans are racist, according to a new Rasmussen Reports national telephone survey. Just 15% consider most white Americans racist, while 18% say the same of most Hispanic Americans." Interestingly, Blacks thought of themselves as more racist then Whites thought of themselves as racist by over 12 percentage points.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373844855478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373844951334-224</Id><Title>The Z Man vs. the Snow Man</Title><Msg>Whats the attraction of the Z Man over the Snow Man? The Z Man's day in court is over. The Snow Man is still on the lam.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1373844951334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373845334398-225</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven hasn't been this emotionally upset</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820689927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven and the #$%$. are in rabid mongoose overdrive posting racially divisive disinformation designed to tick everyone off and balkanize the board.......exactly what the folks at the top of the food chain want...useful idiots (think of the Raven and the #$%$.) who can stoke riots while the Bankers get the UN to declare more wars that young Americans will have to fight and while the bankers rape Americans of what little money they have left</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373845334398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373845529157-226</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 tip on IGZ a liar is a liar is a fool</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834432231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparticus99991, what is your point? being critic means you missed apple acad and tsla and 4 years compared to 8 years is there a point look it up 4 years would be included in 8 years why don't you go to spelling a grammar it means just as much as this nonsense .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373845529157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:45:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373845668851-227</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Opinions are like nipples, everybody has one. Some have firm points, others are barely discernible through layers, and some are displayed at every opportunity regardless of whether the audience has stated "I am interested in your nipples" or not.” ― David Thorne, The Internet is a Playground</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373845668851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373845852655-228</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 tip on IGZ a liar is a liar is a fool</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834432231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus9991 you shifted your name so to show you how stupid that isneospart99 , I demonstrated how easy that is to prove end of another liar statement what a fool over time back to the subject you missed apple for 16 years and then missed ACAD and now are missing TSla under whatever name you want to use. I thought you said, I was dell and fred , now you seem to forget what is up with that , your still a liar !neospart99, Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373845852655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373846037531-229</Id><Title>july delivery update</Title><Msg>Not much delivered in the first two weeks. 15 planes, 20 of which were 737's; 1 767; 2 each 777 &amp; 787. Should see a flurry of deliveries next week starting Tuesday,</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1373846037531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373846042283-230</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any proof spartacus99991 that I am wrong, nope your a liar Spartacus use yahoo finance chart, enter SBUX and mouse to max, , mouse to compare enter BA , mouse to ok and then read the over 90000% on the comparison chart your so lazy and just a fool and a liar</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373846042283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373846070246-231</Id><Topic><Title>Changing Sparty's Focus</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373823690896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:41:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like ole sparty's been deleting more o my posts while I've been away, I no I tried to change sparty's focus least one other time on the same thread. sparty, how bout those boys who hammered (literally) that man and threw him out of his car to steal it in the same FL county, last i heard the man was still on life support...remember that one? you wouldn't if you were dependent on the lap dogs. bet he wishes he had a gun. this may come as a surprise to you, but in addition to recreation, hunting, n such, guns can be used to protect us from bad people. much the way OUR soldiers have used guns to protect us.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373846070246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373846182965-232</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The right to be heard does not automatically include the right to be taken seriously." - Hubert Humphrey</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373846182965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373846401896-233</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, You are correct and neither could Zimmerman have known the life or death outcome of his bloodied head being pounded on the concrete by the young (though 95% of a full grown) man. And that was the point. And apparently that is what the jury also believed. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1373846401896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373846619920-234</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, you sure you don't exist to promote yourself, i mean your other IDs? Sparty uses IDs in the same manner to bump his old posts and pimp more pearls of disinformation/BS. Sparty is parasite, just like his masters.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373846619920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373846742971-235</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bulky bob agrees with hooz, err himself...imagine that. enemy friendly dumb parasites think alike, err as one.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373846742971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373846887037-236</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 since you said that TSLA was better on may 28 than Boeing I looked it up after the 15 day 100% gain I called on may 3 to buy TSLA it had already made a 1005 gain prior to may 28 and went up a lot more but lets make a point here . Using your statement and going only from may28, , to Friday the last trade day7/12/2013 , tesla is up another 16.92% from closing on May 28 to Friday TSLA it went from $110.33 to $129 that is a gain of another 16.92% spartacus99991 your arguing with me , just like with ACAD now, spartacus99991, your still a fool and can't trade Boeing is not a good stock since may 28 Boeing has gone from 100.11 to Friday 101.87 a gain of only 1.18% now since the reason I told you Boeing is a bad stock is they have a MD style business plan , that has already been proven to end in bankruptcy, you worked for MD that is your problem and might be why you hate me . Md -Boeing it will never be any good, the whole stock run upfor Boeing in the last 4 months is based on the 4 month grounding and stock buyback and that can only go on so long, eventually like MD- Boeing is going to go bankrupt. Why because like the MD management , the 747 fix, it failed the 737 MAX based on MD business plan will fail and the 777 X will fail for the same reason you can't think right spartacus99991 , so you will never get it Hart- Smith was right and it applies to all Boeing planes not just the 787.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373846887037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373847027146-237</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1005 should be 100%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373847027146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373847358385-238</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored50 your are a Boeing barker yourself, so clean up your crapola before you toss stones eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373847358385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373847629507-239</Id><Title>Undervalued BA Partner Ready to Soar Higher</Title><Msg>Major consolidation is taking place in the pay-TV industry and rumors are now circulating that the #2 U.S. cable TV operator Time Warner Cable (TWC) may acquire the #5 operator Cablevision, in order to catch up to #1 Comcast's subscriber base. Cable TV operators are now competing with telco TV operators like Verizon and OTT video plays like Netflix. Cable TV operators are beginning to invest heavily into offering their subscribers new innovative technologies in order to stay ahead. There is a low market cap, undiscovered and extremely undervalued stock that pioneered video on demand (VOD) with TWC in 2000 and is now pioneering the next technology to revolutionize cable TV, Network DVR (nDVR). The company is Concurrent (CCUR) and it looks ready to explode to new 52-week highs this week. CCUR was the first company to bring VOD to the market in 2000 when they deployed it for TWC and today, VOD is the fastest growing alternative TV viewing platform in the world - with CCUR's VOD delivery technology reaching 50 million households for a 30% market share. 1/2 of all U.S. TV households now have a DVR, but CCUR is about to make today's DVR technology obsolete with new cloud-based nDVRs. CCUR already deployed a form of its nDVR technology for TWC, which is powering TWC's extremely popular start-over/look-back services. Soon CCUR will begin deploying fully featured nDVR services for its pay-TV clients. CCUR's nDVR technology will allow anybody to record infinite television programs over the cloud, without a DVR box - and be played back on any device - including smartphones and tablets. CCUR closed last week at only $7.88 with a market cap of $68.98 million, cash of $22.37 million, and an enterprise value of $46.61 million or just 0.74X revenues and 6.54X operating cash flow. CCUR's main rival SEAC is about to hit a new 52-week high and is trading for 1.78X revenues and 15.92X operating cash flow. SEAC's valuation ratios would value CCUR between $15.41 and $15.52!</Msg><Username>ttvhbn42</Username><Timestamp>1373847629507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373847730455-240</Id><Title>Airbus deliveries looking better than Boeing this month stock price up 218% in 5 years better than BA only 60% gain</Title><Msg>Boosted by a wave of orders announced and signed at the Paris Air Show, Airbus surpassed the 5,000-aircraft backlog milestone – the first time an aircraft manufacturer has ever attained a backlog of this magnitude. Airbus’ 241 jetliners booked during the month increased its overall backlog to 5,109 aircraft, representing more than seven years of sustained production. This performance also brought total Airbus orders over the 13,000 aircraft mark, of which more than 9,600 are for the single-aisle A320 Family. Highlights of the month included the 65 additional orders for Airbus’ latest product – the A350 XWB – bringing combined total bookings for this next-generation extra widebody jetliner to 678 in the month when the aircraft performed its maiden flight. Acquisitions announced in June were Singapore Airlines’ agreement for 30 A350-900s; the Air France-KLM Group’s booking for 25 A350-900s; and 10 A350-1000s for United Airlines. The widebody A330 also continued to build up its order volume with SriLankan Airlines’ signing for six A330-300s. In new business involving Airbus’ A320 product line, Lufthansa acquired 30 A320ceo, 35 A320neo and 35 A321neo versions; 50 A320neo jetliners were booked by ILFC; and Spirit Airlines ordered 20 A321ceo aircraft. With the volume added in June, and taking cancellations into account, Airbus’ total net orders logged during the first six months of 2013 reached 722. Airbus delivered 48 jetliners during the month, composed of 38 A320 Family aircraft, eight A330s and two A380s – bringing the total provided so far in 2013 to 295, which were received by 73 customers.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373847730455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373847924688-241</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bulky bob agrees with hooz, err himself...imagine that. enemy friendly dumb parasites think alike, err as one." censored, the fact that you are allowed to vote... drive a car... are not institutionalized... are truly something to marvel. Only in America could these things happen.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373847924688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373847963900-242</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"censored50 your are a Boeing barker yourself, so clean up your crapola before you toss stones eh !" Nice thought... but don't hold your breath.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373847963900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373847997470-243</Id><Title>deliveries which is better 48 for Airbus or 16 for Boeing ?</Title><Msg>if you own Boeing stock your bettered by Airbus up 218% in 5 years to 60 % for Boeing !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373847997470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373848045570-244</Id><Topic><Title>Elon Musk on BOEING'S 787 battery, &amp; BOEING MANAGEMENT DID NOT FOLLOW MR MUSK'S SUGGESTION !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373733225063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:33:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad Boeing did a band aid (adding considerable weight) to save time and money instead of doing the right thing and redesigning the battery. I hope this doesn't come back to haunt them. I can understand how the original bunch of managers would make a mistake like that but am disappointed that the new, engineering oriented, bunch took the MBA solution.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1373848045570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373848197261-245</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you tell your aliases to "let it go"? Because "they" are still hanging on like a fly on a warm wet turd..........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373848197261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373848291041-246</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven hasn't been this emotionally upset</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820689927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever seen the Kent Raven this rabid???</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373848291041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373849170035-247</Id><Topic><Title>To what standards do you build something new and innovative like the 787 (learning experiences)</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1373741981525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can tell your not in the aerospace business. Everything is made per print or per spec. The quality assurance people do their thing, reliablity engineers etc. All have approved soldering or whatever specifications that they are inspected to. ATPs are run usually at the supplier and at Boeing at that level and then as the next major assembly is added. There is a specification for everything and that is what recieving inspection inspects too. This is not news. Mfgs been doing it this way for 40 years or more</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373849170035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373849352262-248</Id><Topic><Title>To what standards do you build something new and innovative like the 787 (learning experiences)</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1373741981525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lie alot. They don't change workmanship standards to catch up with deliveries. Nothing at all to do with how fast your building something!!!!</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373849352262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373849470323-249</Id><Topic><Title>On Sunday, all Airlines stated they gave 100% Confidence in the Safety of Boeing's Dreamliner!</Title><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373812434236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:33:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They would say the truth. You feel they would risk life for profits!!! ARe you ok??</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1373849470323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:51:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373849563843-250</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are talking about OJ getting away with two savage murders, aren't you? Poor Nichol was stabbed multiple times and had her head almost sliced off. Trayvon got off easy. Poor Nichole Simpson and Ron Goldman.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1373849563843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:52:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373849573924-251</Id><Topic><Title>To what standards do you build something new and innovative like the 787 (learning experiences)</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1373741981525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too much junk were put into an airplane. That beats the purpose of the airplane, after all, in a few hours flying, why need so much junk &amp; luxeries ? That only create more problems and unknown factors. BA should build the planes as simple as possible, will be safe that way for flying passengers. Glad I sold my shares last thursday, wait &amp; see, may buy back when dust settled.</Msg><Username>arthates</Username><Timestamp>1373849573924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373849712811-252</Id><Topic><Title>On Sunday, all Airlines stated they gave 100% Confidence in the Safety of Boeing's Dreamliner!</Title><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373812434236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:33:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chouse, I rather wait &amp; see, sold all my shares last thursday. May buy back when dust settled. GLTA.</Msg><Username>arthates</Username><Timestamp>1373849712811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373849872464-253</Id><Topic><Title>To what standards do you build something new and innovative like the 787 (learning experiences)</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1373741981525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets not forget the B-47, B-52, and the bet the farm 747 which was designed, factory built, and flew in less time than the delays after rollout of the the 787. That was before Catia, DCAC-MRM - and the McDummy Klan. Of course there was the lunar rover- saturn V- apollo, LEM, and other trival things like moon landing, Apollo 13, etc</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373849872464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373850609860-254</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I no.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373850609860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373850857271-255</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That might indicate to a NORMAL person that those aliases are not me, Nitwit.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373850857271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373850958878-256</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots... he scores!!!</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373850958878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373851040509-257</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven hasn't been this emotionally upset</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820689927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what are you doing? Raving insane as usual</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373851040509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373851544699-258</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Ron Goldman was a waiter at a fancy restaurant and said he would walk Mrs. Simpson home, being the good samaritan that he was. He just happen to be there by accident! Poor Ron was butchered any way just for being in the wrong place at the wrong time. Either OJ or OJ's son was the butcher. From the new information that is out there it very well could have been the son that murdered the two.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1373851544699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373851636976-259</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on waynes calls on TSLA and SCTY the truth nothing but spartacus9991 statement wow !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373835937530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, not only are you spelling challenged, but now we have to add math challenged. Better check that yahoo chart again it say "9K%", thst's 9000 not 90,000. Geesshh, now I have to teach you how to read numbers.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373851636976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373851801066-260</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone on this board knows you are mad as a hatter, crazy as a loon, and just plain clinically insane, Spart. There is no need to prove it to us. Perhaps your should brush up your reading skills on these 3 posts of mine this afternoon (I've added some asterisks for emphasis): ---------------------------------------------- Reply to "This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice" by hoozdik_hertz_557 •13 hours ago . chris_genna2 • 3 hours ago I understand your point. But as for THIS verdict, ***it's time to let it go.*** Zipperman will get the future his character deserves. Maybe he will move on to something Sparty can really respect, like defending the Alamo from illegal immigrants? Well, maybe not... ;-D ------------------------------------------------------------------- Reply to "This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice" by hoozdik_hertz_557 •13 hours ago . chris_genna2 • 3 hours ago Double jeopardy consist ONLY of being charged twice with the same crime. ***Let's let it go. Everyone*** ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Reply to "This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice" by hoozdik_hertz_557 •13 hours ago . chris_genna2 • 3 hours ago There were a lot of mistakes made in the trial on both sides, but I agree with maramwp that the defense attorney earned his pay. What was insane was the way the police seemed initially ready to just let it go, and maybe that won't happen again. What the vast majority of Americans wanted to see was justice done, and under the terms of our legal system, it was. So 6 ladies decided if a black man charged them and pounded on their heads, whether they deserved it or not, they'd shoot. That is the test in this land. It may be too bad, but maybe a wrongful death civil suit will give the family the closure they need. Zipperman and OJ have BOTH been found not guilty. (Not innocent, just not guilty.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373851801066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:30:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373852464822-261</Id><Title>No worries Mate! Probable cause Ethiopian Airways maintenance mistake!</Title><Msg>Former federal safety officials said that so far they were not picking up the kind of urgent alarms about the Heathrow fire from current safety officials as they did after the Boston battery fire. Aviation consultants said the airlines were also not quite sure what to make of the problem, in part because Ethiopian Airlines workers could have made a mistake in doing maintenance on the plane.</Msg><Username>chouse263</Username><Timestamp>1373852464822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373852482281-262</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, and ron goldman was killed by being slashed/stabbed to death, whereas that man in cobb county ga was killed July 1st when he was knocked unconscious by four YOUTHS and left in the middle of the street, another marine from the same area died a year earlier after suffering blunt force trauma to the back on the head. Remember the WWII vet who succumbed to injuries after his wife was raped and murdered, both beaten, in oklahoma...all kinds of crimes. Amazing what the lap dogs our willing to overlook in the pursuit of injustice.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373852482281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373852594753-263</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I accept in advance your apology, you whacked-out, super-patriotic looney tune. And I also note that you seem to acknowledge that hooz and I are different posters, even though every time the board nitwit posts that we are, you weight in in support of his obfuscatory cap. (Oops, I left out the "R")</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1373852594753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373852632430-264</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so spartacus99991 I said 9000% read above , and some how you now say, I said or have a typo and listed the Starbucks gain at 90 thousand, the title said it all, and is is correct. if you found a typo that does not match the title block on another user comment what is your point? you missed 9000% on Starbucks arguing with me as a critic that makes you no money . Spartacus9991, if your a retired MD employee hate for me is based on how MD went bankrupt and now MD is taking Boeing into bankruptcy then that is called displacement. Spartacus99991, displacement is used by you as a means of -distortion, involving a shift of emphasis from important to unimportant elements. A typo is so lame an excuse to be a critic. you have emotional problems seek help.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373852632430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373852794942-265</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus9991 tip on IGZ a liar is a liar is a fool</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373834432231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, are you dell and fred? BTW, The 787 was launched in 2005 and you're implying it should have flown and been delivered the next day so now it's 8 years late? What a fool. And still doesn't know that "9K%" is NOT 90,000%.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373852794942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:46:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373852825514-266</Id><Topic><Title>"This verdict represents a tragic miscarriage of justice"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1373803547723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:05:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry ahkmed, i mean chrissie/spart, you gotta post something of substance, if you're going to cover my posts, here's mine, afterward you can try again, or i'm gonna be dumping all over you...yep, and ron goldman was killed by being slashed/stabbed to death, whereas that man in cobb county ga was killed July 1st when he was knocked unconscious by four YOUTHS and left in the middle of the street, another marine from the same area died a year earlier after suffering blunt force trauma to the back on the head. Remember the WWII vet who succumbed to injuries after his wife was raped and murdered, both beaten, in oklahoma...all kinds of crimes. Amazing what the lap dogs our willing to overlook in the pursuit of injustice</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373852825514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:47:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373852977680-267</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus99991 attempts to draw me ingot a off topic discussion, spartacus99991, not going to happen, you said, How's that hyro racing you told the board about on a financial web site? How's the Boeing pension and all your handshaking with top executives because you were so valuable to Boeing and they tried to keep you from retiring so now , spartacus99991 your doing what then ? how is that related to a gain of 9000% on Starbucks compared to Boeing ? How does this help you as a critic , did it make you 9000% gain ? nope you only know how to be a troll and a very poor critic</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373852977680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373852979106-268</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try at spinning, but I wasn't replying to this thread. You said 90000% several times in other threads. Get over it. You don't know how to interpret "9K%". LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373852979106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373853003054-269</Id><Title>RAMPAGE GALORE....</Title><Msg>DICKWAYNEDICK ON BOARD.... POSTS BY THE BUNDLES... NONSENSE INTACT.. ITS WAYNEDICK THE FEB... BOEING $ 110 + BY EARNINGS $ 122+++ BY YEAREND...</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1373853003054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373853124846-270</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think I'm a very good critic when fools post nonsense.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373853124846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373853196926-271</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991, maybe ask your wife about my hydro racing, perhaps she can tell you more a guess ? but Starbucks is still 9000% better than Boeing and currently pays a dividend of 1.205% ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373853196926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373853225290-272</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think you're a moore-on, just like wayne</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373853225290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373853505116-273</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's related to dell and fred, at the least.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1373853505116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:58:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373854162697-274</Id><Title>Trevon' death tragic, I get it...but</Title><Msg>Why is most of the country focused on a picture of Trevon (provided by CNN) when he was 12 yr's old? acually he was 17 yrs old and about 6 ft tall. He was no kid but seems like many groups are showing his 12 year old photo on posters. Dissinformation to cause another Rodney King riot?</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1373854162697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373854370791-275</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991, you have made many false statements about me, under several of your AKA names! I was fired, I have no friends , I use drugs, I need medication, I am gay , the fact is , you do not know me and have no information to back up your false liar claims. Now you may have made those claims to Fred or Dell as Sparti or neospart99 or many of your other user names but your a liar and a very poor critic My guess is your a retired MD employee who just hates me because I am right about the MD run Boeing company that is not longer Boeing, nor based in Seattle , it is MD based in Chicago , run by a fraternity jock , James Mcnerney, who has failed at every job he had. he was overpaid to come to Boeing by a guy with temporary Chairman status, Lewis Platt who had no aero experience , and that was in 1997 the end of Boeing . any time the CEO is also the Chairman of the Board of Directors for all those years the company is dead unless run by a winner. As jack Welch said to james mcnerney, get out your not good enough to run GE and Mr Welch was right on . Or as Smith-Hart said the only thing Boeing now, is the Logo on the planes the management is in failure . going out of business per Hart-Smith it applies to the 787, and the fixed 747 ha ha and will apply to the 737MAX and the 777X no Boeing employees are left to do the work right end of the company in 9 more years . As always your a fool to waste your time being my personal critic that is called displacement- which is an emotional response in your mind . Spartacus99991, you are substituting some kind of critical problem in your persona for some deep emotional problem. I do not have to be a psychologist to see this, because you argue stupid things. I said Starbucks is 9000% better over time than Boeing that is 100% true somehow all you got was I made a typo , not that Starbucks is 9000% better investment than BA over time that shows me your not right in the head.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373854370791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373854505858-276</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals Wrong Again !</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1373770576231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:56:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hairy Weed and Chrissy now playing back seat Philadelphia lawer . Hilarious . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1373854505858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373854568259-277</Id><Topic><Title>Trevon' death tragic, I get it...but</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1373854162697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bingo !!!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1373854568259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373854754638-278</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven hasn't been this emotionally upset</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1373820689927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissy, like most Liberals, can't handle being proven wrong . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1373854754638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373855211477-279</Id><Topic><Title>SBUX up 9000% compared to Boeing been in since IPO ,and why not you ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373833065765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991, still your not up 9000% on SBUX, nor up like I made on APPL, nor up the 1200% I made on ACAD, nor up the 275% I am up on TSLA and am still in it now , and spartacus99991 just like ACAD while you argue and critique about me you once again just like ACAD are missing out, you just missed the 16.92% on the further gain on TSLA since you agreed that on may 28that TSLA beat Boeing so spartacus99991, be a critic and I will make the money, it works for me ha ha Wayne PS while your coping my style, and it is the highest form of flattery neospart99-spartacus99991, and all AKA's, at least try to come up with your own term, I called you a fool first, so lack of creativity on your part, fool or plagiarism ha ha spartacus99991 , you have a very good ability to look at yourself as ok that is most of your problem , take off those rose colored glasses and get out of that ivory tower and actually walk around the real world .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373855211477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373855319047-280</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries which is better 48 for Airbus or 16 for Boeing ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373847997470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the facts 100% copy from actual report</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373855319047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373855456173-281</Id><Topic><Title>Trevon' death tragic, I get it...but</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1373854162697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSM doing what they do/ Delivering the narrative that their masters ahve instructed them to. Only crime committed that night was felony battery by TM.</Msg><Username>g8trgr8t</Username><Timestamp>1373855456173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373855457089-282</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus deliveries looking better than Boeing this month stock price up 218% in 5 years better than BA only 60% gain</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373847730455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:22:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is word for word exactly as the report stated</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373855457089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373855948474-283</Id><Topic><Title>Elon Musk on BOEING'S 787 battery, &amp; BOEING MANAGEMENT DID NOT FOLLOW MR MUSK'S SUGGESTION !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373733225063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:33:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>techpath your right , read up on RONA and how Md does business it is not Boeing company now , it is MD covered in a Boeing logo now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373855948474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373856078405-284</Id><Topic><Title>Elon Musk on BOEING'S 787 battery, &amp; BOEING MANAGEMENT DID NOT FOLLOW MR MUSK'S SUGGESTION !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373733225063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:33:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that is why TSLA is up 275% in a short time TSLA got it right and Boeing got it wrong and MD managed BA did not listen to Elon Musk, big mistake</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373856078405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:41:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373856242471-285</Id><Title>Boeing Better Announce Problem Today</Title><Msg>I find it very difficult to believe that with all the inspectors and engineers Boeing doesn't have a good idea of what caused the fire. As equally important is the fact the fire quickly burned a hole in the composite fuselage of the airplane. Is this an issue? Can the composite deteriorate or burn faster than aluminium? Can the airplane be fixed? Boeing's inability to define the problems quickly to the public is killing the 787 . That airplane is on life support and soon could join the ranks of the Convair 880 and 990.</Msg><Username>stkmrkts</Username><Timestamp>1373856242471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373856308880-286</Id><Title>China GDP in line with expectations - DOW FUTURES UP +33</Title><Msg>Jul 14, 2013 9:14 PM CT (Bloomberg) -- China’s economy expanded 7.5 percent in the three months to June 30, matching forecasts in a Bloomberg survey of economists. Asian stocks and the Australian dollar held gains after China’s economy grew in line with forecasts and the government opened markets wider to foreign investors. http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2013-07-14/aussie-gains-before-china-gdp-as-futures-mixed-oil-falls.html</Msg><Username>mcivor</Username><Timestamp>1373856308880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373856611338-287</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus deliveries looking better than Boeing this month stock price up 218% in 5 years better than BA only 60% gain</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373847730455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:22:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>somebody is getting so desperate. looks like u are going to lose big money tomorrow. Ba going to 106 tomorrow.</Msg><Username>private.nguyen</Username><Timestamp>1373856611338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373857385213-288</Id><Title>Crooked Dumb Senators vote to subjugate American Sovereignty to Useless Nations</Title><Msg>Vote No 91; Date: March 23, 2013, Inhofe Amdt. No. 139; To uphold Second Amendment rights and prevent the United States from entering into the United Nations Arms Trade Treaty. Thankfully it passed by narrow margin 53-46 without the help of the following senators. NAYs ---46 Baldwin (D-WI) Baucus (D-MT) Bennet (D-CO) Blumenthal (D-CT) Boxer (D-CA) Brown (D-OH) Cantwell (D-WA) Cardin (D-MD) Carper (D-DE) Casey (D-PA) #$%$ (D-DE) Cowan (D-MA) Durbin (D-IL) Feinstein (D-CA) Franken (D-MN) Gillibrand (D-NY) Harkin (D-IA) Hirono (D-HI) Johnson (D-SD) Kaine (D-VA) King (I-ME) Klobuchar (D-MN) Landrieu (D-LA) Leahy (D-VT) Levin (D-MI) McCaskill (D-MO) Menendez (D-NJ) Merkley (D-OR) Mikulski (D-MD) Murphy (D-CT) Murray (D-WA) Nelson (D-FL) Reed (D-RI) Reid (D-NV) Rockefeller (D-WV) Sanders (I-VT) Schatz (D-HI) Schumer (D-NY) Shaheen (D-NH) Stabenow (D-MI) Udall (D-CO) Udall (D-NM) Warner (D-VA) Warren (D-MA) Whitehouse (D-RI) Wyden (D-OR) Not Voting - 1 Lautenberg (D-NJ)</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1373857385213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373857678977-289</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus deliveries looking better than Boeing this month stock price up 218% in 5 years better than BA only 60% gain</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1373847730455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:22:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are aware that Boeing has delivered 326 commerical aircraft so far in this fine year of 2013. I don't know word for word the report you are quoting, but I can tell you this, there are over 103 orders that were sales and commitments for the 787-10, something you fail to mention on the Boeing board. Face it, you are an Airbus person, but if you are going to talk about airbus, you owe it to us to speak of Boeing in a positive manner, and stop being the idiot you truely are! By the way as of July 9th, Boeing has received 859 commerical orders, minus the 105 orders that were cancelled for a total of 754 net orders in 2013. So, where's the beef?</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1373857678977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373857856588-290</Id><Topic><Title>Trevon' death tragic, I get it...but</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1373854162697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All 50 states now allow for concealed carry. Before you decide to beat someone up, you should REALLY consider/evaluate whether or not the person you want to pound on might be armed.</Msg><Username>discus_183</Username><Timestamp>1373857856588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373858003151-291</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Better Announce Problem Today</Title><Username>stkmrkts</Username><Timestamp>1373856242471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:44:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right now it is not in the hands of Boeing, it is in the hands of the British Government. They already said the the fire is not related to the batteries. So shut-up!</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1373858003151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373859388549-292</Id><Topic><Title>Z man found not guilty ..</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373790124567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well you are big on the voice of the people (as long as it is not a Jury that is) getting their way as a lifelong Democrat...so perhaps you will take seriously the latest Rasmussan poll which (you guess it) shows how wrong you are about the how Americans view the nexus and origin of racism in America...READ IT AND WEEP Thirty-seven percent (37%) of American Adults think most black Americans are racist, according to a new Rasmussen Reports national telephone survey. Just 15% consider most white Americans racist, while 18% say the same of most Hispanic Americans. (To see survey question wording, click here.) There is a huge ideological difference on this topic. Among conservative Americans, 49% consider most blacks racist, and only 12% see most whites that way. Among liberal voters, 27% see most white Americans as racist, and 21% say the same about black Americans. From a partisan perspective, 49% of Republicans see most black Americans as racist, along with 36% of unaffiliated adults and 29% of Democrats. ***Among black Americans, 31% think most blacks are racist, while 24% consider most whites racist and 15% view most Hispanics that way.*** ...in other words Blacks think Blacks are more racist then blacks think whites are racist....buy a clue and come back later</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1373859388549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>