<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376625622103-1</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik Hertz Helps Define Racism</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376624053732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 23:34:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, I do not get this inordinate pre-occupation with racism. Oprah goes to Switzerland and has some sort of unknown interaction with a clerk in a store where she wanted to look at a $40K purse. Whatever was said or done, Oprah invokes the racism card. Then, mysteriously, she apologizes for making a big deal out of whatever happened. Maybe she discovered that, in Switzerland, they do not have a local Al Sharpton rable rouser to call upon to carry forward her faux issue. She should have done her $40K purse shopping in the United States where the people are more sympathetic to her plight. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376625622103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376625858638-2</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, Why not post the link, and show the MB your knowledge, step up, as to your betting, wow , a gambler eh! Don, many Boeing employee's have been terminated for less . d Boeing does not need any reason to Terminate VN, its called employee at will, all I have to do is have a FBI and it is a done deal. Don. post your NLRB finding. I will do what I know how to do . Lets watch then shall we Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376625858638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:04:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376626024631-3</Id><Topic><Title>Wiped away all of yesterdays profits..</Title><Username>trujrnyfan</Username><Timestamp>1376512900681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-14 16:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about that 3 day run on HL and AUY when the stock market pulls back gold and silver go up but do not try this unless your a skilled day trader very dangerous for rookies</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376626024631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376626074553-4</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The writing of nearly half of the New Testament is hardly hyperbole, but the issue does not merit much energy in debate. As to the effect of celibacy and the promotion of Christianity, people are not "born again" physically into Christ, but spiritually (Jesus made that very clear to Nicodemus in John, chapter 3). Even if every Christian for the last two thousand years were to not have any children, there would still be new Christians.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376626074553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376626091286-5</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik Hertz Helps Define Racism</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376624053732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 23:34:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The irony, or perhaps hypocrisy, was you had PETA's 2008 Person of the Year wanting to buy a crocodile skin bag.</Msg><Username>juanruiz1330</Username><Timestamp>1376626091286</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376626264989-6</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are talking about the first generation of converts. But actually you are right, Christianity would have survived, it just not have been that of Paul's theology.</Msg><Username>juanruiz1330</Username><Timestamp>1376626264989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376627134454-7</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.. its called employee at will.. BS, pure BS. 40 nights is a engineer- Union contract does contain an employee at will provision-just the opposite. As to the NLRB filing - as you know- links cannot be posted on yahoo. You made the charge as to what YOU can do, and what 40 nights cannot do Put up or shut up !! case number is 19-CA-088157 the answer was dated March 12,2013 And the real guts is in an advice memorandum dated Feb 28,2013 Bottom line- as usual you are wrong- wrong -wrong- The real explanation as to how and why is actually contained in some footnotes in the advice memo See id. Cf. Costco Wholesale Corp., 358 NLRB No. 106, slip op. at 1–2 (Sept. 7, 2012) (finding employer’s policy prohibiting employees from making statements “thatdamage the Company, defame any individual or damage a person’s reputation” to be unlawful because the rule had no “accompanying language that would tend to restrict its application” to legitimate business concerns); Knauz BMW, 358 NLRB No. 164, slip op. at 1 (Sept. 28, 2012) (finding employer’s “courtesy rule,” which prohibited “disrespectful” conduct and “language which injures the image or reputation” of the employer, to be unlawful, because nothing in the rule or elsewhere in the employee handbook “would reasonably suggest . . . that employee communications protected by Section 7. . . are excluded from the rule’s broad reach”).</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1376627134454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376627316263-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik Hertz Helps Define Racism</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376624053732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 23:34:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately Liberal members of racial minority groups in America often play the race card, just as they've been taught to do, in order to hide their own bad behavior . It is unfortunate, mainly for them, but also for society as a whole, because they tend to start to believe their own B.S. which of course means they will not self correct . In order to correct yourself, you must first see your own faults, Liberals have no faults, just ask them . Libs sure can find faults in others though, and if they don't, they'll assign some . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376627316263</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376627492039-9</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik Hertz Helps Define Racism</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376624053732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 23:34:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PETA- People Enjoying Tasty Animals ???</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1376627492039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376628600427-10</Id><Topic><Title>Iraqi Airlines thrives, Takes Delivery</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376446966440</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-13 22:22:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will you be making more sense in the morning, or more farts ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376628600427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376628739653-11</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, You can copy and paste from any link. 2. the ethics policy is legal or the policy would be removed by law. Don, your talking about represented collective bargaining rights to be free from intimidation, nothing more. The employee conduct is a employment at will doctrine. If a company no longer wants a man(VN) to be employed even with a labor contract they can be terminated without any reason Harry Stonecipher, a CEO of Boeing was terminated he had a employment contract better than you or I did . Don, he was representing Boeing and had a inside Boeing affair, no party was harmed . Yet Boeing decided to terminate his job. This guy your representing (VN) has violated company conduct policy while an active Boeing employee and can be terminated for any reason or no reason. As a retired, but experienced Labor Relations Manger for a very large top 10 prime contractor, I know the difference between a negotiated collective bargaining right and a company policy that can be enforced Don , you lose on this one. Wayne .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376628739653</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376628839935-12</Id><Topic><Title>which is better Airbus stock gains over 51% yeaer to date or boeing 36% and How about dividends</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376617187869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 21:39:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good to read for investors !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376628839935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 00:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376630111917-13</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>juanruiz, I would have loved to have been able to ask Apostle Paul about some of his opinions. For example, he talked about long hair as a "shame" for a man. (1 Cor 11:13-16). In the 1970's, the Christian churches, responding to the "long hair" revolution, were abuzz on the subject - often quoting these verses. But, they did not really emphasize verse 16, where Paul admits, "If anyone wants to be contentious about this, we have no other practice—nor do the churches of God." Aha! In other words, he was giving his (considered and well respected) opinion - nevertheless, an opinion. He was a spiritual leader for the time, encouraging Christians to set themselves apart for Christ - even to be celibate to lessen the distraction of family from being able to do all that could be done for the cause. I am sure that he was aware that Sampson had long uncut hair - by direction of the Lord. OK, maybe a special case. On Paul's clearly theological discussions, I find no fault, and they are timeless. Some casual ("only on rare holidays") readers of the Bible may not be able to distinguish between opinion and theology. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376630111917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 01:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376631299931-14</Id><Title>Bush's last golf game</Title><Msg>The last golf game GWB played as commander in chief was Oct 13th 2003, he said "I don't want some mom whose son may have recently died to see the commander in chief playing golf. I feel I owe it to the families to be in solidarity. And I think playing golf during a war just sends the wrong signal." And he got beat up in the press for this. Obama who played cards with boyfriend Reggie Love during Osama raid is on golf game 134 and doesn't care what some mom whose son recently died thinks. See obama golf counter website for list of games vs casualties since last game.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1376631299931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 01:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376632746163-15</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, I think we are done now ! I have watched your efforts with the company and the union, for years, and smiled to myself, knowing what results you would have. . I have suggest to another board member, more than once , that he should stay with engineering and not try to compete with me on stocks .Don, you are an engineer , that is your skill set. Don, you are not a skilled Labor Relations Manager or a stock market trader. Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376632746163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 01:59:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376632980872-16</Id><Topic><Title>BA closed below its 50 day MA for the first time since January</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1376611231008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 20:00:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>foxgang good , you used a chart , way to go. I do not trade this stock and have not looked at a chart for Boeing. but , I have watched the volume go down from 5.7m to 3.7m as the stock price declines . It is not a short as very small short interest about 1%, is my guess I did not look it up . The 787 is scaring investors away from Boeing more than anything.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376632980872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376633852096-17</Id><Topic><Title>Did You Know the Deficit Is Shrinking?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376610542686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 19:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you or could you please tell me what all those percentage figures stated mean in real term dollars. All I'm reading is a bunch of duke and juke statistics from your post. From what I ascertain from your post is that the deficit is not shirking. What can be interpreted from the statistics you give is that there is a decrease in the rate of increase of the deficit since 2009 and 2013. In other words, the increase in the deficit is rising but at a slower pace. So, please quit with the hocus-pocus and just tell me what the deficit was in 2009 what it was in at the beginning of 2013 and what it is today..........if you can. Then I'll know if the deficit is indeed decreasing. Thank-you.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376633852096</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376635082340-18</Id><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Msg>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier - WSJ • Fri Aug 16, 2013 1:47am EDT Aug 16 (Reuters) - Boeing Co has traced the incorrectly assembled engine fire extinguishers on 787 Dreamliners to the manufacturing of bottles at a supplier's facility(outsourcing) while saying there were no risks to flight safety( sure you bettya), the Wall Street Journal reported. On Wednesday, Japanese airline ANA Holdings said it had found an electrical wiring problem in the fire extinguishers of the engines of three of its Boeing Dreamliner jets. The problem was first discovered during pre-flight maintenance of a jet at Tokyo airport. Boeing said in a written statement to the Wall Street Journal that the improper assembly, which has been confirmed to have been found on three ANA jets in Japan, "does not present a safety of flight issue because the bottles are not the only means of fire extinguishing for engines( oh good, Boeing, then let’s take one of the fire extinguishing features not working as a no problem then, that is called enablement) and there are multiple redundancies within the fire extinguishing system. "THE PILOT CAN PUT THE 787 INTO A DIVE, THAT WILL THRILL THE PASSENGERS ! A Boeing spokeswoman told the newspaper that activating the 787's engine fire extinguishing system "does not disable or impact [the engine's] performance." WOW IT MIGHT BE GOOD FOR THE JET ENGINE NOW RIGHT "Regardless, improperly configured components are not acceptable and this issue is being addressed promptly( just like all the other past 787 issues , the 787 grounding and the several late delivery issues to fix all those cheap outsourcing issues and still the problems exist ). Boeing will follow standard disciplined procedures to understand how this discrepancy occurred and ensure it is not repeated,"</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376636629639-19</Id><Topic><Title>Did You Know the Deficit Is Shrinking?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376610542686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 19:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROFLMAO ..... The Deficit is shrinking...Good one...you had me going too...for a minute I thought you were serious</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376636629639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 03:03:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376637163494-20</Id><Topic><Title>Did You Know the Deficit Is Shrinking?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376610542686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 19:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think a lot of people confuse the words "deficit", which is yearly, with total "debt" which is the accumulation of all yearly deficits. Debt is going up, yearly deficits have been comng down recently.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376637163494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 03:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376637353116-21</Id><Title>Obama’s Economic Approval Slips to 35%</Title><Msg>Lydia Saad Gallup August 15, 2013 Despite President Barack Obama’s renewed focus on the nation’s economy this summer, he scores worse with Americans on the economy than he did in June. His approval rating on the issue, now 35%, is down seven percentage points, and his ratings on taxes and the federal budget deficit are each down five points. During the same period, his overall approval rating is down three points.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376637353116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 03:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376637442620-22</Id><Topic><Title>Did You Know the Deficit Is Shrinking?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376610542686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 19:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correct</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376637442620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 03:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376640260527-23</Id><Topic><Title>Did You Know the Deficit Is Shrinking?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376610542686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 19:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You guys cut it out. You're going to give bumper a headache.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376640260527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 04:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376651108010-24</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's last golf game</Title><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1376631299931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 01:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush was chastised for one Golf Game and subsequently quit...Obama has 134 Golf games and the wars and the deaths of our troops continues. Any criticism of this is racism quite naturally</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376651108010</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 07:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376651222911-25</Id><Topic><Title>The Gov't Cry's Wolf</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376303310768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-12 06:28:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have to destroy Freedom in order to save it</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376651222911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 07:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376653738265-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will not stop supporting terrorists</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376619897359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 22:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama IS a terrorist....."community organizer"</Msg><Username>angusomy</Username><Timestamp>1376653738265</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 07:48:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376653910829-27</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik Hertz Helps Define Racism</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376624053732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 23:34:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Close enough.</Msg><Username>juanruiz1330</Username><Timestamp>1376653910829</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 07:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376657834034-28</Id><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Msg>It didn't appear that he was housing any poor needy families in his mansion and he is definitely living life with the 1%. What is hard to imagine is what the good reverend was thinking when he said, "God dam_ America" because it sure looks like America provided him with a windfall of wealth and life of luxury. From what I saw I don't think Reverend Wright will leave this country that is so horrible and racist anytime soon.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376658752657-29</Id><Title>Russia selling airbus stake</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - Russian state development bank Vnesheconombank, or VEB, is continuing to sell down its 5.02 percent stake in Airbus's parent EADS (EAD.PA) with the proceeds destined for local plane maker Sukhoi, Vedomosti newspaper said on Friday. In a July 26 filing in the Netherlands, where EADS is registered, VEB had already reported a reduction in its stake to 2.88 percent, the paper said</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376658752657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376658781483-30</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He offed his wife and kids too. Yeah, a real decent guy.</Msg><Username>juanruiz1330</Username><Timestamp>1376658781483</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376659197484-31</Id><Topic><Title>787 issues</Title><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1376572103594</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 09:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Considering all the cost cutting and short cuts implemented by Boeing management, the company ought to make a ton of money on the 787 project, if it survives all the malfunctions.</Msg><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1376659197484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:19:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376659584101-32</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul's authority comes from...Paul. He's no different than Mohammed, Joseph Smith, or Sun Myung Moon. "Believe because I say so, since I am in direct contact with God. Those who see him as valid, fine.</Msg><Username>juanruiz1330</Username><Timestamp>1376659584101</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376659817042-33</Id><Topic><Title>Russia selling airbus stake</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376658752657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Investors are running away from airbust.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376659817042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376659907363-34</Id><Topic><Title>AIRBUST DIVEDEND</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376523410210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-14 19:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear wayne,you have nothing to say? Mom take your computer?</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376659907363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376661129081-35</Id><Title>crash darn you crash buy low</Title><Msg>sell high is my motto. This industry will be safer then most.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376661129081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376661206901-36</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual you are f ull - and as usual YOU cannot back up your ravings. Check both state law and contract law in this state- plus actual contract. Hairy s resigned BTW- he was not technically fired- nor was Phil- look it up ! IF you were a labor relations manager - you were way over your head. Which conduct policy did VN violate ? BE specific and post the link or copy of the appropriate procedure or ethics policy involved. Failure to do so will be proof that your eyeballs are brown indicating totallly full</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1376661206901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376661907330-37</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>first God teaches love, then go to Gal 5:22 The Fruits of the Spirit. 10 Commandments is good too. I have worked with homos and lesbians all good people. While a young boy an old woman use to expose herself to me, after homosexuality was an option but I finally got over the abuse. I love women. The Bible also teaches Only God is judge so in the meantime I will love homos and lesbians. What I have noticed these people have gained a lot of influence being only 2% of the population. Legislation and this influence over me and my family has become a strain. Legislation is now moving thru Congress that would put this lifestyle in our sex education classes. I feel this lifestyle should not be legalized. As long as this nation pursues this and other actions this country will continue to lose God's blessings. Even our friends and neighbor countries are aghast at the influence of just 2%.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376661907330</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376662313965-38</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He's no different than ..." The kicker here is that the Bible says of itself, "All scripture is given by inspiration of God..." (2 Tim 3:16-17, written by Apostle Paul), which forces one into a more clearly defined position of support or opposition to itself. Even Paul's exhortations (or seeming opinions) are God inspired. Anything that then disagrees with the Bible, such as the Koran, cannot be inspired by God (of the Bible) as God is perfect and cannot be the author of confusion (1 Cor 14:33). It does not allow ambivalence, but requires a decision (Revelation 3:16-20). And, even though we reject Him, He pursues us (Romans 5:8). One must be careful not to think that turning to God is an "end of life" decision as we do not know what the next day will bring (James 4:14). And, instead, Solomon and Isaiah wrote, "Seek the Lord while He may be found" (Ecclesiastes 12:1, Isaiah 55:6-7)</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376662313965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376663554438-39</Id><Topic><Title>crash darn you crash buy low</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376661129081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 09:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am just saying a huge position but I got a ton of $ on the sidelines if this drops below 100</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376663554438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376663820650-40</Id><Title>ABBY looks like it could see $1+ in the near future</Title><Msg>Checked out ABBY yet? Looks like it is ready to go. All of the technical indicators are showing signs of a bull run.</Msg><Username>warrenl465</Username><Timestamp>1376663820650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376664292634-41</Id><Title>amazing times when a president uses races and homosexuality as talking points</Title><Msg>this talk has insight Moslems who are totally intolerant. Biden running to Norfolk to tell blacks a vote for GOP is a vote to put you back in chains. The Liberals following Obama's race card lead. 20 years with Rev Wright and this is what we get. My pastor is a black man and he has never seen so much hate and rage coming out of a black man. Considering Carter handing Reagan a $1T debt which caused 18% mortgage and interest rates what is Obama's $21T going to cause? Black surgeon Ben Carson MD lectured Obama on it at the National Prayer breakfast to no avail. Once Obama claimed to be bi-partisan but he is none of that. He insights hate and rage and uses the gov to hammer Conservatives the IRS investigating the Billy Graham non profit twice in 6 months. This president is thuggery</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376664292634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:44:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376664782669-42</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You haven't figured it out yet ? Dem 1% good , Rep 1% bad. Dem war/ drone strikes good, Rep war illegal w/ war crimes bad. Dem Guantnamo good, Rep Guantanamo bad. Dem NSA spying on citizens good, Rep NSA spying bad. Dem Bush mask good, Rep Obama mask racist....etc</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1376664782669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376665223332-43</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The New Testament was created centuries after the texts were written, by men. They left out scores of other texts now called the Apocrypha. The NT texts themselves are copies of copies etc. Comparing manuscripts of the same texts, there are many changes, additions, deletions, and the like. In other words, you are not reading what the original authors wrote. Moreover, unless you read Greek, you are reading a translator/editor's interpretation of what the texts says.</Msg><Username>juanruiz1330</Username><Timestamp>1376665223332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376665622636-44</Id><Title>@@@ MUST READ @@@</Title><Msg>I signed up for the free service and got some great tips. The service worked out perfect. I got a pick and it went up 140%. All I had to do was Text the word “ALERT” without quotes to 5,5,5,8,8,8 to join</Msg><Username>warrenl465</Username><Timestamp>1376665622636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376665954817-45</Id><Title>EMARSS milestone</Title><Msg>FAIRFAX, Va., Aug. 15, 2013 – Two Boeing [NYSE: BA] Enhanced Medium Altitude Reconnaissance and Surveillance System (EMARSS) aircraft have arrived at Aberdeen Proving Ground in Maryland for airborne tests of the target-tracking capabilities they will provide to the U.S. Army. The extensively modified Beechcraft King Air 350 ER aircraft will undergo mission systems calibration and testing to certify them prior to delivery. “It’s gratifying to see this innovative program reach the next stage of development, one step closer to delivering to our customer,” said Mark Stephenson, EMARSS program manager for Boeing. “The flights to Aberdeen from Kansas were an achievement themselves, and they paved the way for airborne evaluation and testing against a range of targets.” EMARSS aircraft are designed to detect, locate, identify and track surface targets, day or night, in almost any weather conditions. They will provide soldiers with intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance capabilities as well as communications and targeting. Boeing’s Engineering, Manufacturing and Development contract with the Army calls for four development aircraft as well as logistics services.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376665954817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376666627923-46</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being in the business, there are not many suppliers out their that manufacture fire bottle systems. I am sure that Airbus buys from the same supplier and that many of the airliners they built may carry the same defects that were found in the 787. Why don't you tell Airbus to warn their customers instaed of putting your immature comments in the article. No one is really cares about what you have to add anyways.</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1376666627923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376666851413-47</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crybaby!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376666851413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376667063144-48</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@jjovaz Yes I'm aware of the double standard but my post more importantly illustrates that their is huge money that can be made in the industry of racial divisiveness. There is a large element of low IQ victims who fall prey to the neuro-linguistic programming of people like Wright and Obonzo and happily become useful idiots in accusing everyone who makes fun of Obonzo or criticizes Obonzo, of being racists. These low IQ useful idiots are programmed to believe in men who present themselves as 'Black Prophets' when in reality they are con artists selling racial division and who are all about 'Black Profits' namely their own. There is huge money and political power to be made in race pimping and the politics of racial division, and Obonzo learned from a exceedingly successful master of the art of racial division and who is now living La Dolche Vita in his 10,400 sq/ft mansion far far far away from the low IQ useful idiots that helped make him rich.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376667063144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:31:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376667109607-49</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Billy Grahams has been IRS audited twice in the last 6 months. Any word on Rev. Wrights audits? Franklin Graham sent Obama a letter asking him to STOP. In addition the letter covers the IRS agents ruthless and abusive take over of the facilities during the audits. We have scandals we have IRS, we have FEC and other actions threatening people who support conservatives no link to the top. NSA and phone calls but no link to the top. Americans grow weary of this guy, but for free healthcare and gov giveaway he is in for a second term as the debt mounts.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376667109607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376667255535-50</Id><Topic><Title>amazing times when a president uses races and homosexuality as talking points</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376664292634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we know all that. Unfortunately the truth about O is much much worse than that. Three years from now we will be picking up the pieces</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1376667255535</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376667310257-51</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>according to Larry Sinclair, Rev Wrights church was a staging for Obama's #$%$sexual lovers. One was killed to stop the story from leaking. Obama tried to stop Larry's book in the courts but lost. Media just walked away. The book was published...Obama is a #$%$. So I say so what....be proud and Come out instead of this coward we have to see song and dance every day.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376667310257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:35:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376667720132-52</Id><Topic><Title>Racism Helps Define The Tea Party</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376611878826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 20:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's more accurate to say racism defines progressives. They seem to revel in racist talk and ideas.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1376667720132</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376667732851-53</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only spiritual people that I've paid any attention to in my life, have all been dirt poor and never had to worry about audits. Again I understand the point of a double standard in Obonzo attacking someone like Graham and protecting/supporting racial flame throwers like Jesse Jackson and Al Sharpton.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376667732851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:42:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376667974618-54</Id><Topic><Title>Racism Helps Define The Tea Party</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376611878826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 20:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is a great example of the neuro-linguistic programmed low IQ useful idiots that become pawns for the Black profiteers of racial division that I spoke of in my Reverend Wright post.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376667974618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376668675969-55</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you realize every time you open your yap you are foolishly, sophomorically, unwittingly, doofusingly, goonishly campaigning for Hillary?</Msg><Username>jumboyjetski</Username><Timestamp>1376668675969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 11:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376669059210-56</Id><Title>BA suppliers are f---- up aand they know it!!!</Title><Msg>Boeing has determined why the fire extinguisher nozzles were routed to the wrong engines: The engine-fire extinguishers were improperly assembled at a supplier’s facility.</Msg><Username>stevhitler</Username><Timestamp>1376669059210</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 12:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376669796994-57</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>◾Bland was murdered execution-style on November 17, 2007; ◾Young was murdered execution-style on December 24, 2007; ◾Spencer reportedly died of septicemia, pneumonia, and HIV on December 26, 2007. (Death certificates of Bland and Young, HERE.) Now, Young’s elderly mother is speaking out about her suspicions that her son was murdered to protect Obama’s reputation and assure his political future as President. ______________________________ Did you see the mother of Donald young all over the news channels when her son was murdered? Where were Jackson and Sharpton and why weren't they organizing protests for justice for Donald? Why did none of the national news outlets cover the story or care about justice for Donald or his mother Norma Jean Young? Help me here because I can't recall any outrage or concern when this happpened.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376669796994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 12:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376669910373-58</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>juanruiz, There is much debate out there on this subject. While the Bible "canons" (Catholic and non-Catholic) were formed and agreed upon about 1600 AD, the content (at least common content) selected is authentic and proven to be original. Literally tens of thousands of whole and fragmented copies, some dating back to within the first 100 years of Jesus' death and resurrection, are available and warehoused in universities around the globe. Google it. Various versions of translations, in addition to separate target languages, range in consistency to the original Greek and Hebrew from outright fraud (adding to and taking away) to reasonable and pure in intent and faithfulness to the original text. You can look at the original Greek and Hebrew at the "biblos" website. At some point, one might ask, "why am I here and what is my purpose?" Given that a God is One Who created the entire universe and is perfect in purpose and holiness, it is reasonable to argue or believe that such a Person would have shepherded His message to man, His creation of love, with equal purpose and perfection - versus not knowing until after death, when it is too late. It is a matter of faith and no amount of straining of the lungs in debate will lead anyone to their own conclusion. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376669910373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 12:18:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376670149280-59</Id><Title>Oh Shut Up</Title><Msg>You bunch of idiots</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1376670149280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 12:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376670157699-60</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where was an angry indignant Obonzo standing before the press demanding that the killers of his friends be brought to justice? Heck, OJ Simpson showed more interest in finding Nichole Simpson and Ron Goldman's murderer than Obonzo showed in finding the killers of his Trinity Church pals. It seems very odd that Obonzo would let it all be swept under the rug, doesn't it?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376670157699</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 12:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376671129894-61</Id><Topic><Title>Racism Helps Define The Tea Party</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376611878826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 20:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is no different tthan barack hussein, bill ayers, jessie jackson, and twana Sharpton? Which "he" are you referencing?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376671129894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 12:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376671817704-62</Id><Topic><Title>Racism Helps Define The Tea Party</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376611878826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 20:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Racism is synonymous with NAACP. Or did you know that?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376671817704</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 12:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376672323015-63</Id><Title>787 activity</Title><Msg>Air India 787 l/n 90 was delivered yesterday (8/15). Thompson 787 was delivered today (8/16). Aeromexico 787 l/n 115 was delivered today. British air L/N 114 had its first flight. China Southern l/n 100 painted at forth worth and flown back to Charleston.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376672323015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 12:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376673269202-64</Id><Topic><Title>amazing times when a president uses races and homosexuality as talking points</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376664292634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey greg is Obama`s race the reason you need to inject race into 90% of the post you make? you folks are so hypocritically stupid it`s sad.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376673269202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376673954469-65</Id><Topic><Title>Did You Know the Deficit Is Shrinking?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376610542686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 19:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are correct and I stand corrected. I should have said is we have a decreasing rate of increase in our debt. Still, the fact remains that we are still bleeding profusely and hooz's is just putting lipstick on a pig. Whoopi.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376673954469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376674429852-66</Id><Topic><Title>amazing times when a president uses races and homosexuality as talking points</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376664292634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama "insights hate and rage" eh? Don't tell me. You get all your political "incite" from the radio, eh?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376674429852</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376674499365-67</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>morisretired, you statement that both Boeing and Airbus may use the same supplier means that Airbus may inspect their supplier install at the Airbus factory, or at their suppliers prior to the acceptance or at Airbus receiving shops, prior to transport tot he assembly line, right !!Airbus and makes sure they are working right, Boeing does not do that if your guess is right then! That is why Airbus stock is up 51.3% today up from 51.2% yesterday year to date and Boeing stock is up below the 42% it was a few weeks ago now up 37% no way to be a investor! Remember if your invested in BA move to the better airplane maker Airbus or make up excuses for the Boeing fire extinguisher failure and keep losing share price value to Airbus</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376674499365</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376674699494-68</Id><Topic><Title>amazing times when a president uses races and homosexuality as talking points</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376664292634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why isn't your question and comment directed at hooz?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376674699494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376674790044-69</Id><Title>Only in Texas.....</Title><Msg>Texas Police Raid Farming Commune After Mistaking Tomato Plants For Marijuana (Disinformation website) By Jacob Sloan on August 15, 2013 Perhaps to be on the safe side, we should prohibit growing plants in general. NBC 5 Dallas–Fort Worth reports: A small organic farm in South Arlington is demanding an apology from police who raided the property in early August. Officers raided the Garden of Eden, a 3.5-acre farm, searching for marijuana in the gardens, according to search warrants. Police did not any drugs. Quinn Eaker, a resident, told NBC 5 that the six adults who live at the farm were handcuffed when SWAT officers from the Arlington Police Department came to their home with weapons drawn. According to a statement posted on the Garden of Eden’s website, the raid of the farm lasted for an estimated 10 hours. Code compliance officers mowed the grass on the property and removed wild, cultivated plants including blackberries and okra. Eaker said that the plants police mistook to be marijuana were likely tomatoes: “They can’t even tell the difference between tomato plants and a marijuana drug cartel.”</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1376674790044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376674869007-70</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update for The Boeing Company. **MUST SEE**</Title><Username>mcwhirter.felton</Username><Timestamp>1376673422430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It continues to drop</Msg><Username>tomsrobert55</Username><Timestamp>1376674869007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376675762888-71</Id><Topic><Title>FMH on Dividends BAcompared AB and actual money and rolled in stock gains on a 200K investmnet</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376545258185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 01:40:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this Boeing barker (unposter76) is thinking I did not respond to his dividend question, too much barking to actually stop and read the answer , he is pumping his question, not smart enough to realize I answered on my own post " here is what a Boeing Barker looks like! unposter76, still has not figured it out! I answered his question over a DAY AGO HA HA, unposter76 has 9 thumbs down so far, for being too lame brain to figure it out about his question comparing Airbus dividends to Boeing Airbus wins that one to especially over 5 years if you reinvest your dividend Airbus stock is up then 268% compared to Boeing only 163%. Or with just stock increase, no reinvest of the dividend ,( taking the money ) So if you keep your dividend to spend , for year to date as of two days ago calculation, Boeing cash pre tax is $3341 compared to Airbus $2616 after 15% tax per international rules Here is unposter76 still asking the questing( he apparently thinks I am hiding from his dumb question. It is dumb because if he knew the answer first he should have never asked ) unposter76 question and answer, it makes Boeing even less of a stock to own compared to Airbus , so UNPOSTER76 this post is for YOU , unposter76, you said, "unposter76 • 4 hours ago Flag 1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 9 Reply . Dear wayne,you have nothing to say? Mom take your computer?" attention, unposter76 maybe your mom should talk to you about this post ha ha Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675762888</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376675963346-72</Id><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Msg>Airbus just got a 20 billion dollar Airplane order this week. Boeing did not , Boeing still has got more problems with the 787 , airbus did not .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376676028789-73</Id><Title>Breaking News : 787 Taxis To Maintenance Facility...No Fire</Title><Msg>In an amazing show of quality and dependability, a Boeing 787 taxied to a maintenance facility under its own power without catching on fire. Boeing ceo mcninny was overcome with joy and said " Where's my bonus."</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1376676028789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376676228062-74</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Airbus uses Maggit plc fire suppresson systems. Not sure who boeing uses.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376676228062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376676290367-75</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goebbels......... there were some people who believed what he said.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376676290367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376676308724-76</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's get this straight: A man was killed to keep the secret from getting out, but the secret is out anyway in a book written by a perverted felon? That doesn't even pass the straight-face test. Or the IQ above 40 test either, for that matter.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376676308724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376676329661-77</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good job, foulmoouthharbor your stating a fact</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376676329661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376676573282-78</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bible doesn't claim anything of it self -- its a bunch of paper sheets, not a being. So the writer wants you to know it's not him talking, but God? Even Grisham and Dan Brown don't try to claim that.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376676573282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376676680369-79</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FMH since you did a good job , here is some more. Airbus fire suppression information---- I do not like the Boeing pumpers like morisretired , too lazy to do any research," Meggitt, the international aerospace, defense and electronics group, has enhanced its position as a major fire protection systems supplier to Airbus, winning the fire detection, control and APU and engine extinguishing systems for the A320neo programme. The award follows the integration of Meggitt’s established fire detection and control capability with the fire suppression equipment of recently-acquired Pacific Scientific Aerospace business, HTL. Dennis Hutton, President of Meggitt Safety Systems, explained: “The ability for suppliers to offer complete ATA Chapter 26 fire protection systems has become increasingly important as aircraft manufacturers continue to simplify procurement and logistics. In some cases, bids will only be accepted from suppliers who have the complete capability under one roof. “The APU/engine fire extinguishing system on the existing A320 family is shared between two suppliers. Backed by longstanding relationships with this customer and our excellent reputation for on-time delivery and quality, this integration has enabled us to compete for and win a sole source position on this exciting programme .” wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376676680369</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376676964371-80</Id><Topic><Title>Did You Know the Deficit Is Shrinking?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376610542686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 19:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If anyone can be confused about it, non-loony sparty, the LOONY sparty will be!!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376676964371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376677012728-81</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>morisretired, Given the same fire suppression contractor, so why did Boeing have the problem and Airbus did not have the problem? That would be proper QA( at supplier oversight,) at receiving at Airbus, proper install by mechanic and review by Airbus QA assembly line and then proper flight line review and customer QA is good at Airbus , not so with Boeing now right ! , install and management was better at Airbus then right !From Wayne, another guy in the business . Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376677012728</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376677279345-82</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>morisretired , are you moris from 767? Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376677279345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376677833945-83</Id><Title>Boeing Outsources 787 Maintenance to Zimbabwe Poison Dart &amp; Plane Fixer Uppers, Inc.</Title><Msg>Zimbabwe Poison Dart &amp; Plane Fixer Uppers, or ZPDPFU has been awarded a 50 year contract to perform 787 maintenance based on their extensive knowledge of airborne projectile sciences. Boeing ceo mcninny said " I remember in those Tarzan movies those poison darts almost never caught fire. " ZPDPFU ceo Chief Mugombi Kooboloogoo said " Arulu boogoobu chapoomoo zamoomoo airplanebooboo fix oo-oo. Financial details are sketchy but rumored to be in 5 to 10 billion banana bunch range. In a related story, Boeing ceo mcninny reported lower operational expenses and said " where's my bonus ".</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1376677833945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376677852075-84</Id><Topic><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there a difference between an order and an option?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376677852075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:30:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376678151975-85</Id><Title>DICKWAYNEDICK-FEB.......</Title><Msg>Who caaarrrrreeeeeeeees about airbust in boeing boards.......are u senile.. Man!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376678151975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376678413618-86</Id><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Msg>Boeing should have caught this problem with on site BA QA inspection at the supplier, next at boeign receiving, next at assembly with install mechanic and QA, then at the flight line test, and finally at actual flight testing. Instead Boeing wants their plane inspected by customer workers with a cheat sheet on how to do it. This is the best way Boeing can demonstrate their outsourcing business model does not work, any better than the company they got the idea from MD , a bankrupted outsource company, read JOHN HART-SMITH Japan’s All Nippon Airways Co. (ANA) has found another problem on the 787 Dreamliner from Boeing Co. (BA). On Wednesday, a flight from Tokyo to Frankfurt was delayed due to faulty wiring in a fire suppression system for one of the plane’s engines. According to reports, the system may activate a fire extinguisher on the wrong engine in the event of a fire on one of the 787’s two engines. Boeing’s solution is to ask airlines to check their own 787s using an instruction sheet the aircraft maker will supply. Boeing is blaming the problem on the supplier, Kidde, a division of United Technologies Inc. (UTX), which said it is working to resolve the issue. BOEING SELECTED THEIR SUPPLIER AND IS RESPONSIBLE TO ASSURE THE QUALITY OF THE PRODUCT WORKS PER PLAN QA SHOULD BE ABLE TO DETECT ANY VENDOR PROBLEM AT VENDOR SHOP, THEN AT BOEING RECEIVING, THEN ON THE PLANE AT INSTALL OR REVIEW OF THE VENDOR PART AS INSTALLED WHEN IT ARRIVES AT THE BOEING FACTORY, THEN ON FLIGHT LINE ON A STATIC TEST AND FINALLY AFTER A CUSTOMER QA REVIEW AND FINAL TEST FLIGHT BEFORE THE 787 LEAVE THE FACTORY TO THE CUSTOMER BOEING SHOULD CHECK AND VERIFY THEIR OWN PRODUCT IS GOOD NOT WAIT UNTIL ANOTHER TEETHING PROBLEM COMES UP AND BLAME SOMEONE ELSE FOR BOEINGS LACK OF MANAGEMENT ABILITY</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376679177810-87</Id><Title>DOMER HAS A LOVE AFFAIR , CLOUDS HIS VISION, WE UNDERSTAND DOMER</Title><Msg>domerrrrr45 • Aug 3, 2013 9:55 AM Flag 2 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 1 Reply . Bottom line dickwayne...i love boeing....even if u sell your mother to me....i will love boeing! ..case closed...no matter what you puke here in boeing boards.... No one cares!.. Dickydickywayne! Lol!.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376679177810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376680687915-88</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STUPID MESSAGE FROM STUPID WAYNEDICK!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376680687915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376681715164-89</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An FAA audit of Boeing's supplier control procedures was part of the production certificate for the 787. Mistakes can happen, but something like this should have been discovered during a functional test for the plane. August 26, 2011 EVERETT, WA – Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) Administrator Randy Babbitt today announced that the FAA has approved production of the Boeing 787 Dreamliner. At an event at Boeing’s facility in Everett, Washington, Administrator Babbitt presented Boeing executives with two certificates for the design and production of the Boeing 787 Dreamliner with Rolls-Royce engines. The first, a Type Certificate, is for the FAA’s approval of the airplane’s design. The second, a Production Certificate, allows Boeing to manufacture the 787 following a rigorous review by FAA inspectors of Boeing’s quality system, production tooling, manufacturing processes and controls, inspection methods, and supplier control procedures.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1376681715164</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376681989627-90</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe if Airbus had traced faulty fire extinguishers to suppliers in the A300 that had the fatal crash in Alabama the A300 wouldn't have crashed---what do you think waynedickensen??</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376681989627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376682593533-91</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must read the BIBLE in context, you are trying to put your own meaning to what the BIBLE is saying. remember when reading the BIBLE it's context, context, context, if taken out of context all you have is a pretext.</Msg><Username>redhook_2</Username><Timestamp>1376682593533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:49:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376682758216-92</Id><Title>how to spot a boeing Barker like father -Z aka wstlefanms it is easy , just read his post</Title><Msg>1 Reply . wstlefanms aka Father z you said ,( liar!) stop harassing me father, go back to Paul Allen and ask his advice LOL "Maybe if Airbus had traced faulty fire extinguishers to suppliers in the A300 that had the fatal crash in Alabama the A300 wouldn't have crashed---what do you think waynedickensen??" but the NSTB said this "The NTSB will hold a briefing in Birmingham at 5:00 p.m. EDT (2100 GMT) on Friday. Preliminary results from the agency's investigation, which is still in its early stages, have shown no evidence of engine fire, and the pilots did not issue a distress call.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376682758216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376683032562-93</Id><Topic><Title>how to spot a boeing Barker like father -Z aka wstlefanms it is easy , just read his post</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376682758216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:52:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and from whstle, his friend "whsteffanms... I was wondering your IP address shows as Everett and you have 4528 update(6039)posts, with almost all of them containing slams and HAR HAR HAR and nothing of any value to anyone, how is it that you get along so well with Paul Allen? eh! whsteffanms on his posts and MSFT, eh! 18-Jun-11 01:42 pm Re: Microsoft Shows First Look at Windows 8 Interface VIDEO Whsteffanms said”( aka father Z) wayne my address may be Everett, but my mansion is actually located over on Widbey( spelling for you home ?) Island( Wayne said, sure it is LOL ) and I get back and forth with my yacht(Wayne said, " the full size scale model?")- I tie up next to Paul Allen a lot( Wayne said,"a lot, like never !") down in Elliott bay and confer( Wayne said," wow") with him quite a lot-- how do you like that eh (Wayne said," Father Z,/whstle this is just like all your other emails,, har, har , har" ) Rating :</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376683032562</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376683236195-94</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing traces faulty fire extinguishers to supplier WSJ- OUTSOURCING ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376635082340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 02:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father_zosima aka whsteffanms I answered your post see it above on you special title called how to spot a Boeing barker , you go bouy</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376683236195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376683398832-95</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did paul allen help you with this user comment domerrrrr45 or did you talk directly to father z or whstle first LOL</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376683398832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376683536246-96</Id><Topic><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is there any doubt Airbus got both, Boeing got neither ! LOL give it up MD retired bankruptcy guy</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376683536246</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376683566124-97</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he's friends with Burt Rutan too.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376683566124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376683680561-98</Id><Topic><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But they don't have the $20B yet either.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376683680561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376683892855-99</Id><Title>Kiddie Fire Supression System</Title><Msg>Not sure if Airbus uses any of their hardware, but it appears at a minimum they do use their training. Kidde Fire Trainers, Inc. has delivered the world's first CAT 10 Aircraft FIRETRAINER® (A-380 Type) Simulator. The system was completed for the SERCO International Fire Training Centre in Durham Tees Valley, United Kingdom, in October 2007 and features 17 distinct fires. The "crashed aircraft" configuration simulates a major fuselage split. Aircraft FIRETRAINER® Systems can be fueled by multiple fuels, including LPG, Kerosene, and Carbonaceous.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1376683892855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376683996737-100</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Boeing does not need any reason to Terminate VN ..." Wanna bet? My peers and I are represented by a union (SPEEA). All of the terms and conditions of our employment are guaranteed by a legally-binding contract between Boeing and that union and in that contract is language that prevents Boeing from terminating us "at will" (i.e. on a whim, for no other reason than it's what they want to do). We can only be terminated "for cause", which basically means for committing a gross violation of company rules and/or policies or repeated instances of lesser violations. I have committed neither and you are essentially threatening me with an empty bag. Yeah, good luck with that. "... its called employee at will, ..." Wrong. It's called "employment at will" and neither I nor any of my peers are employed in that fashion. If you had ever worked for Boeing you'd know all of this stuff cold, but as usual you don't know jack. Nice try. Wanna try again?</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376683996737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:13:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376684097813-101</Id><Topic><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not a comeback at all , Boeing definitely will not have 20 billion ever on this deal, while Airbus has a deal, once more your argument makes no sense you know Airbus stock over time is up over 51.5% ytd and Boeing is not 37% and it worse over 5 years for Boeing the reason is Airbus got a 20 billion dollar order , slice it up any way you want the 787 is in trouble and the Airbus company is better at delivery and working planes sot he stock price is higher, your a Boeing pumper I am a stock market guy I win you lose the stock price is the only winner , get over it mr MD bankruptcy engineer</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376684097813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376684138027-102</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ja, Ich habe. Danke.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376684138027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376684246347-103</Id><Topic><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Contrary to what you think BA delivered more planes (and received more orders) than Airbus in 2012. Just facts, not spin.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376684246347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376684271552-104</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better, Joseph Goebbels or Wayne Dickley?</Title><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376595744862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 15:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>recorded</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376684271552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376684668632-105</Id><Topic><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, MDC never filed bankruptcy. Don't you remember, we bought Boeing with Boeing's money and then installed all of our managers into all the top Boeing positions (even though most are now retired or dead, but that's never been an impediment to those who want to play the blame game).</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376684668632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376685034839-106</Id><Topic><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its not he plane delivery its the working planes and the not creative bookkeeping allowed in the USA and not France, the stock gain is better for Airbus , a real profit margin on the Airbus planes is why, once more, the stock price of Airbus over 51% ytd compared to 37% for BA is bettering Boeing. That explains it all to the winner investors its airbus , slice it again, if you want ! Airbus stock up over 51% ytd and Boeing is not 37% the 787 does not work as promised , the 747-8 is not selling while the Airbus worst plane , the a380 is working and all the other Airbus planes work both companies have plane crashes when the first 787 crashes it will be a catastrophic event for Boeing shareholders, and for Boeing as the troubled 787 is in the public view much more than any other plane in recent history, no indication that it will not crash more than one fire, and different causes, fires, oil leaks, emergency landings , have already occurred and the fire suppression system for the Boeing 787 jet engines is flawed not a good sign , If you want to slice it up into smaller pieces to swallow, that is fine with me, you still have to eat it don't you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376685034839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376685317777-107</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem would have been discovered if the QA process was the same as it was before all the cost cutting moves were implemented.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1376685317777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376685403141-108</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spatsi, that message was for father z not me, maybe you need to check out who you are attempting to snub, or are you ganging up on Father z to help me out? if so, I do not need your help with father and his many avatars his posts speak for themselves</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376685403141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376685412610-109</Id><Topic><Title>how to spot a boeing Barker like father -Z aka wstlefanms it is easy , just read his post</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376682758216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:52:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you had better give it up due to your senility Dell George- witnesses said the A300 was a ball of fire prior to the crash- probably some design mistake - maybe like building jetliners without pitot tube heaters which aircraft then fall out of the sky because the pilots who are on instruments haven't got a clue what their airspeed is because the pitot tubes are frozen up</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376685412610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376685507124-110</Id><Topic><Title>how to spot a boeing Barker like father -Z aka wstlefanms it is easy , just read his post</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376682758216</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 15:52:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father z let me take a page from your most intelligent post ever har , har har har har har</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376685507124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376685634517-111</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oldbuck56 you are 100% correct,</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376685634517</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376685927281-112</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the FAA , cbx, just checking, were they(FAA) the ones that made an exception for Boeing and no other American plane to use the lithium ion battery, if I recall correctly can you remind me on that ?If so that mistake was more like FAA in Bed with Boeing against passenger safety of flight. " At the same time the government certified Boeing’s 787 Dreamliners as safe, federal rules barred the type of batteries used to power the airliner’s electrical systems from being carried as cargo on passenger planes because of the fire risk. Now the situation is reversed. "</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376685927281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376686102710-113</Id><Topic><Title>August stock stock comparison year to date Airbus stock up 51.3% Boeing not so good 37%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376675963346</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 13:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparti and we are done, had enough for now then, any more logic you want me to correct , just let me know, I am here for you Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376686102710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376686320744-114</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Djumboysca* bski err spaz err censored brain damage err spazmo</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1376686320744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:52:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376686717868-115</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It be the power or prayer! Druid</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1376686717868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 16:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376689858114-116</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not certain if the FAA reviews were on the "Boeing supplier control procedures" or directly at the suppliers on their internal controls. Hard to tell the way the article is written. I would have to believe it applies to both</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1376689858114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 17:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376690436965-117</Id><Title>UTX admits to BA 787 error</Title><Msg>A unit of United Technologies Corp. said Friday it is responsible for assembly errors in engine-fire extinguishing systems supplied for Boeing Co. 787 jets. Improperly assembled extinguisher bottles were found on three All Nippon Holdings Inc. 787s in Japan on Wednesday, spurring a round of Boeing-recommended inspections by operators ."An assembly error in our service center impacted a limited number of refurbished fire extinguisher bottles," said a spokesman for United Technologies in an emailed statement. The parts were manufactured at the company's Kidde Aerospace unit. The company said that the "error has been corrected and we are working with Boeing and the airlines to complete the necessary inspections, which we expect will be completed over the next few days."</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376690436965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376690633614-118</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing is scaring the 787 Flying public, blames Fire suppresion supplier , not BA - QA! and want Airlines to inspect</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376678413618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sarcasm seems to be lost on this board, eh Wayne? P.S. Has Burt given you any help with your invention yet?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376690633614</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:03:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376690983783-119</Id><Topic><Title>UTX admits to BA 787 error</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376690436965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone know how many bottles are in each engine compartment? Was the miswiring just between the multiple(?) bottles on one engine or was it that the switch to discharge a bottle on one engine would actually discharge a bottle on the other engine?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376690983783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376691792529-120</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rev. Wright attracted a large Black membership by preaching racism, and hate towards Whites. One of his members was Obama, and he learned well from Rev. Wright.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1376691792529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376691939627-121</Id><Title>El Al Plane Makes Special Stop for Cancer Patient</Title><Msg>There you have it, a good airplane news item. Even has a 747 in it.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1376691939627</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376693423579-122</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama isn't the #$%$ you make him out to be. While he may have been seating in the congregation, he was learning from the enemies feelings, plans and thoughts about America. Obama can be qouted as saying "keep your friends close and your enemies closer.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1376693423579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376695238595-123</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? Seems pretty unequivocal to me. Of course, if you are going to use the context argument to say it really doesn't mean what it says you need to do the same for the Leviticus quote on homosexuality QED it's really OK you just need to put it in context.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1376695238595</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 19:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376696837231-124</Id><Topic><Title>What does the Bible say about homosexuality?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1376589894248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 14:04:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imbecile, if you hate #$%$ so much why don't you move to Russia, and join Putins circle jerk for wayward traders.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1376696837231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 19:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376700706299-125</Id><Topic><Title>AIRBUST DIVEDEND</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376523410210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-14 19:36:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cmon dipstick admit it BA pays a better divedend</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376700706299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 20:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376701239998-126</Id><Topic><Title>UTX admits to BA 787 error</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376690436965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not much factual detail out there.One news release said: "According to reports, the system may activate a fire extinguisher on the wrong engine in the event of a fire on one of the 787’s two engines."</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376701239998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 21:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376702679608-127</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wright is one good hustler.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376702679608</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 21:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376702956990-128</Id><Topic><Title>UTX admits to BA 787 error</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376690436965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is one bottle per engine. The fire supression system is set up where it can cross feed each engine.</Msg><Username>morisretired</Username><Timestamp>1376702956990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 21:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376702996896-129</Id><Topic><Title>amazing times when a president uses races and homosexuality as talking points</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376664292634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 10:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may be assuming that we will be able to pick up the pieces.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376702996896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 21:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376708719933-130</Id><Title>Boeing should be admitting that Boeing failed 100% with quality assurance of their vendor, not UTX is responsible</Title><Msg>The Boeing pumpers say the contractor admitted to Boeing they made the product wrong, instead of pointing out Boeing is responsible to assure the quality of all parts and build per FAA flight certificate granting the Boeing Company the privilege to sell the 787, as it is certified safe to fly. These Boeing pumpers spartacus99991,, domerrrr45,,foulmouthharbor,father Z ,VN, morisretired,and others most Boeing workers or evil trolls, all use hate for any users who explain that the vendor works for Boeing per specifications that were accepted by the FAA in order to certify the 787 to build and sell as flight worthy. . ,BOEING is responsible to assure THEIR vendors product is made and delivered in working condition, not the other way around, as this other user attempts to claim.. these people, the Boeing pumpers ,are not what the flying public need to rely upon. The Boeing Company is responsible for every part of the plane and the certificate to fly the plane is Boeings responsibility . Where was the BOEING quality assurance? it should have been spotted at the vendor , next at Boeing receiving, than on assembly or at delivery of part assembled on the section of the plane, then at final assembly , and then functional test, and finally at flight test. For the airline customer to discover the problem THIS IS A MAJOR FAILURE OF BOEING NOT THE VENDOR IT is a BOEING failure and scary for the flying public</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376708719933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 23:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376709620987-131</Id><Topic><Title>I went past Reverend Wright's 10,400 sq/ft mansion the other day at Odessey Country Club</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1376657834034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 08:57:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hatred of whites coming from Chicago blacks. Been there.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1376709620987</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 23:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376711411033-132</Id><Title>Liberals Upset Over Welfare Drug Testing</Title><Msg>By Travis Melvin on August 16, 2013 chicago_housing_authority It has been standard policy for years that for anyone living in government-subsidized housing in Chicago must undergo annual drug testing. The rationale is that taxpayers don’t want to hand out their hard-earned money to support a person’s drug habit. In many other areas of welfare, people are also asked to be tested before given handouts. Now, liberals are saying this goes too far. The ACLU has filed a lawsuit in US District Court claiming that the practice is “humiliating and invasive” and that for people asking for the hand out it “stigmatizes (them) as a presumptive criminal and drug user.” They point out that most subsidized housing around the country does not require a drug test and call the practice “very rare”. The Chicago Housing Authority put this in place due to the rampant drug use and narcotic sales going on in its public housing. During the 80s and 90s, they were seen as a national symbol for failed public housing. The public housing buildings, especially in the area known as Cabrini Green, which is the area that is specifically under scrutiny in this law suit, had record high crime numbers and a shocking level of violence. It got so bad that the large buildings were demolished and smaller units were built to make policing the area more manageable. The numbers show this policy has been effective and the crime rate in that area has declined since the drug testing policy went into effect. Liberals, of course, disagree and would prefer taxpayer money to be handed out without any controls. whoring themselves for the vote. These people would kill a baby for the vote, but I think they do via abortions.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376711411033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-16 23:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>