<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369022588553-1</Id><Topic><Title>Even Piers Morgan is now saying the Governments actions border on Tyranny</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368878541738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:02:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What, you'd rather have Mrs. Moore?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369022588553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:03:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369023025148-2</Id><Title>Boeing Ships 6th Wideband Global SATCOM Satellite for Launch</Title><Msg>Boeing [NYSE: BA] is progressing with the expansion of the U.S Defense Department's highest capacity communications satellite constellation, recently shipping its sixth Wideband Global SATCOM (WGS) satellite, pictured here in the company's El Segundo facility, for a scheduled launch from Cape Canaveral, Fla., later this year.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369023025148</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369023255769-3</Id><Topic><Title>Chinook is Boeing’s longest continuously running production program</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1368878651638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:04:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sept. 10, 2001, BA was at 43.46. Today. 98.92. September 11 was very good for Chinook sales.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369023255769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369023901108-4</Id><Topic><Title>Chinook is Boeing’s longest continuously running production program</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1368878651638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:04:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats one of the sickest things I have ever seen written about the tradegy of 9/11. How crazy are you to say that. 9/11 was good for nothing. I hope a family memeber of one of the killed people of that day doesn't see that 3,000 dead Americans is good for Boeing business. Seek help. Somebody on the street I grew up in died that day as a Police Officer trying to get everyone out. They named a park after him. He was a great guy. Hope everyone see's your sick post!!</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369023901108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369024731747-5</Id><Topic><Title>instead of economy economy its scandle scandle and there all Obama's doing</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368895154427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure- when pigs fly and the pope has twins</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369024731747</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369027933094-6</Id><Topic><Title>instead of economy economy its scandle scandle and there all Obama's doing</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368895154427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republicans wanted Obama in the WH 'cause they knew he was toothless. The Dems were too dumb to know the Republicans wanted Obama in place to do nothing and take the blame for everything. Martin Luther King would be ashamed of the war criminal Obama.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369027933094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 01:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369034682965-7</Id><Title>Emirates Planning Major 777X Order Helps Boeing Market Aircraft</Title><Msg>Emirates has 175 Boeing 777s in its fleet that will start retiring from 2017, many of which will replaced by the successor-model dubbed the 777X. “We’re not saying we’re going to buy 175, but we’re looking to replace a large chunk of them with the 777X,” . Note to all---thats just the first airline-----good news for sure</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369034682965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 03:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369040439093-8</Id><Title>George Soros is Buying These Stocks in 2013</Title><Msg>Soros proved he’s not finished with the manufacturing sector, as he bought shares of Boeing (NYSE:BA) for the first time. The company’s recent maneuvering through the Dreamliner problems — not to mention its increased production pace — have been attracting investors from all sides. Viking Global recently bought over 12 million shares of Boeing.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369040439093</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 05:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369040857039-9</Id><Title>Boeing Showcases BBJ 3(Business Jet) for the First Time at EBACE 2013</Title><Msg>Boeing Business Jets (BBJ) is displaying a BBJ 3 for the first time. The airplane, based on the 737-900ER, was outfitted with its custom VIP interiors at Jet Aviation in Basel, Switzerland. The range of the BBJ 3 exceeds that of other business jets in its class. It can fly 4,900 nautical miles; more than 1,500 nautical miles (3 hours) farther than its direct competitor. Thats something to write home about. Great that if can go 3 HOURS further then the competion is big.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369040857039</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 05:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369046537242-10</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz will post a poll sponsored by Insurance companies that show Obamacare is cheaper for America...when the opposite is true</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369046537242</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369046645178-11</Id><Topic><Title>Even Piers Morgan is now saying the Governments actions border on Tyranny</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368878541738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:02:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His ratings are about half of what they used to be ...CNN is a ghost of its former self. The people are hip to the propaganda</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369046645178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369046812739-12</Id><Topic><Title>HOOZDIKs post on obstruction of Obamacare is one big LIE !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368967069760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:37:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How true</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369046812739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369046865833-13</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz Chi Minh, the board DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369046865833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:47:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369047402685-14</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>99% say your nuts. What does that prove? Your still here. Besides, the President was justified in holding off and not interfering with the investigations until concluded to avoid making any hasty decisions not grounded on facts. No impeachment will happen. Its the Republicans making political hay with investigations instead of dealing with the really important problems facing the nation.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369047402685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369048290415-15</Id><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Msg>The Beghazi attack by I slamic terrorists would have failed if the US Embassy and its personnel would have been reinforced as they requested. The Republicans are as much to blame for not preventing the attack as the Obama Administration. If the Republicans had given the President all the budget requests the President asked with no looming sequestors, the President would have enough money to deal with any problems, including reinforcements at Benghazi. It is the Republican penny pinching that has forced all government departments to cut back all around on expenses.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369048411630-16</Id><Title>New Poll Shows Obama Approval UP Despite Hokey Repub "Scandals"</Title><Msg>So all the gnashing of teeth, wailing, and renting of garments garnered the baggers nothing. It's back to RubeRadio for the next cooked up "scandal" by their favorite lying repub propagandist.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369048411630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369048503104-17</Id><Topic><Title>Maher: GOP has moved beyond obstruction to treason</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1368966110214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:21:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Treasonous baggers deserve detention in Gitmo.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369048503104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369048806340-18</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Money was not an issue and the money was available according to testimony provided in the first Congressional hearings on Benghazi. This tactic was already tried by Dems who presented the same nonsense as you at the whistleblower hearings and it blew up in their face on rebuttals from informed people and the Dems looked like fools.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369048806340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369049150921-19</Id><Title>Obama-Backed FSA Rebels Name Their Brigade “Osama Bin Laden”</Title><Msg>Obama-Backed FSA Rebels Name Their Brigade “Osama Bin Laden” Paul Joseph Watson May 20, 2013 Underlining once again how the White House is openly seeking to arm terrorists in Syria, video has emerged of one of the FSA rebel groups referring to their unit as the “Osama Bin Laden” brigade. The clip shows one of the militants proclaim how he is part of “The Osama bin Laden brigade of the Souqour Dimashq (Hawks of Damascus) Battalion…..Allahu Akbar!” as the insurgents prepare to attack a Syrian Army checkpoint. “Western countries have been claiming that the FSA is comprised of somewhat “secular” people and that jihadists have only joined the fight but they are not part of the FSA. Well, you cannot get more al-Qaeda’ish than calling a brigade “Osama bin Laden,” states the description accompanying the video.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369049150921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369049737682-20</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its the Repubs who looked liked fools, in that Obama won a resounding victory with a second term and will likely remain strong through the midterm elections no matter how much smoke and mirrors the Repubs make in the hearings.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369049737682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369050529311-21</Id><Title>The Tea Party Folks think they are clever</Title><Msg>The Tea Party folks think they are clever but they don't fool me. They are upset they are audited and required to pay proper taxes like all Americans should. They blame the IRS for targeting them. If there taxes werefully in order they have nothing to hide and should feel at home with an audit as proof they pay their just taxes. Instead they are cooking a scheme with Repub help to avoid future audits by targeting folks at the IRS as the bad guy. They want an easy pass out of the eyes of the IRS. Its the old criminal defense ploy of blaming the police for misconduct as a way to get acquited for murder.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369050529311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369053908614-22</Id><Title>Obama's Chief Lawyer Knew About IRS Targeting Weeks Ago</Title><Msg>The IRS scandal keeps getting closer and closer to the top of the White House food chain as Obama officials desperately try to spin their way out of mounting evidence and foul play. The Wall Street Journal is reporting President Obama's top attorney knew about the IRS targeting weeks ago before news broke, but of course, Obama still didn't know about it until he learned about it "from the news." The White House's chief lawyer learned weeks ago that an audit of the Internal Revenue Service likely would show that agency employees inappropriately targeted conservative groups, a senior White House official said Sunday. That disclosure has prompted a debate over whether the president should have been notified at that time. In the week of April 22, the Office of the White House Counsel and its head, Kathryn Ruemmler, were told by Treasury Department attorneys that an inspector general's report was nearing completion, the White House official said. In that conversation, Ms. Ruemmler learned that "a small number of line IRS employees had improperly scrutinized certain…organizations by using words like 'tea party' and 'patriot,' " the official said. President Barack Obama said last week he learned about the controversy at the same time as the public, on May 10, when an IRS official revealed it to a conference of lawyers. The main question since this whole thing broke on May 10th is whether President Obama ordered the targeting, knew of targeting, or encouraged the targeting through his statements. Did this thing come from the top? Kim Strassel says of course it did.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369053908614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369054628177-23</Id><Title>God Bless The TEA Party</Title><Msg>Without them people sane people wouldn't know how utterly corrupt the Democrat Party has become since the Communist Party USA took control of it..</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369054628177</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369055373970-24</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing made 5.5% in just ten days gain in stock price and then there was TSLA, AMD, DDD and JRCC</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369019850594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 23:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JRCC up over 14% in premarket, must be sad to own Boeing compared to the stocks I usgggested just 10 days ago , you could have locked in more profit in 10 days than Boeing will make you in 5 years " this morning on JRCC"Iberia Capital upgraded James River Coal from Sector Perform to Outperform with a price target of $5.00. For an analyst ratings summary and ratings history on James River Coal click here. Shares of James River Coal</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369055373970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369055512908-25</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Democrats did very well in 1998 amid the "scandal" of President Clinton. They will do even better in 2014.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369055512908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369055633094-26</Id><Title>Quotes of the Day</Title><Msg>Love this woman: “Oprah was demoted from her first job as a news anchor. Now she doesn’t even need a last name,” she said. “And then there’s this guy Barack Obama. … I could take up a whole afternoon talking about his failures, but he lost his first race for Congress, and now he gets to call himself my husband." Michelle Obama</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369055633094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369056284353-27</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll Shows Obama Approval UP Despite Hokey Repub "Scandals"</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369048411630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:13:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369056284353</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369056550184-28</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll Shows Obama Approval UP Despite Hokey Repub "Scandals"</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369048411630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:13:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It that supposed to be some kind of victory for ignorance and the explosion of organizations polling low information voters?</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369056550184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369056846963-29</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll Shows Obama Approval UP Despite Hokey Repub "Scandals"</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369048411630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:13:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all where you take the poll. Get the tabulator out on a big inner city street, and stop the young person with the long hair with the ring in his nose who smells like Yul Gibbons after spending 6 mo.'s in the woods, and it will favor Obama. Small town USA whose folks have a decent set of values, family oriented folks that live drug free, decent lives can't stand our fascist Pres.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369056846963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369057135555-30</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Present the scenario to 3rd graders as to what to do. Tell them 6 mo's before the attack other agencies in the area were attacked by Al Queda. Tell them email, after email, was sent to Hillary, and Obama telling them of the dangerous situation they were in, the likelihood they would be attacked, and they needed security. at the US Embassy. Obama nor Hillary responded. They didn't want the voters to know there was a threat of Al Queda. They had lied prior to the election saying their policy had removed the threat of Al Queda around the world. They were willing to sacrifice those 4 American lives to make voters believe there was no threat. I think I know what 3rd graders would have done.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369057135555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369058454499-31</Id><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Msg>bloomberg has a reporter flying to BA in Chicago today on a 787. He will be recording on the flight and at Boeing and showing it later today on Bloomberg TV.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058565500-32</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P hantom says 'it was the GOP that looked like fools"...and that is always the leftist strategy to policies this Regime' supports. They are unsupportable so the attack dogs go on the attack discrediting the fact finders with the support of the mainstream media. The evidence is overwhelming. The pinkos just try to discredit, and so far it has worked on all fronts regarding this corrupt Regime'</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369058565500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369058930231-33</Id><Title>New Poll: Amercians Hate Obamacare</Title><Msg>(UTI Natiuonal) A poll take of people who are among the 51% of Americans that actually pay federal income tax show 92.4% want Obamacare repealed.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369058930231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369059390807-34</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH BULL PUCKY .. C lamb testified under oath in October on the $$ issue- claimed $$ were NOT a problem or ISSUE.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369059390807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:16:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369059562292-35</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>United Flight 1 is scheduled to depart Houston at 11 a.m. local time en route to Chicago, where the airline and Boeing both have their headquarters. The passengers will include Boeing Chief Executive Officer Jim McNerney and Jeff Smisek, CEO of United parent United Continental Holdings Inc. (UAL)</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369059562292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060003211-36</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll Shows Obama Approval UP Despite Hokey Repub "Scandals"</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1369048411630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:13:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep! That's the same poll taker who predicted President Romney's win.. He polls only small town rubes.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1369060003211</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369060574900-37</Id><Title>WayneDickensen ON SUICIDE WATCH!!</Title><Msg>Wayne's entire life savings and fortune was tied up in a 100 share BA account which he had shorted at $80!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060574900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060598900-38</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a solid example of what a tanning bed and alcohol can do to a person</Msg><Username>duybaisanutcase</Username><Timestamp>1369060598900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369060742572-39</Id><Title>God Bless The Tea Party douchebaggers</Title><Msg>Without them people sane people wouldn't know how utterly corrupt the Democrat Party has become since the Communist Party USA took control of it.. (we have a place for all of them in the hottest circle of hell) signed --Beelzibub</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060742572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:39:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060785606-40</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comics is a huge step up from WND. WND has even less credibility than you or Sparty. Wow, less than zero!</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1369060785606</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:39:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369060846277-41</Id><Title>Keep Gitmo!</Title><Msg>There are reports of trillions of dollars hidden in offshore tax havens. The CIA and FBI should be deployed to ferret out the Romney-like scofflaws possessing these accounts. They should be detained in Gitmo until they cough up what's due.</Msg><Username>agent0977</Username><Timestamp>1369060846277</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369060976094-42</Id><Title>New Poll: Americans Love Obamacare</Title><Msg>(UTI Natiuonal) A poll taken of people who are among the 51% of Americans that actually pay federal income tax show 92.4% want Obamacare implemented.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060976094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061063680-43</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing made 5.5% in just ten days gain in stock price and then there was TSLA, AMD, DDD and JRCC</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369019850594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 23:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JASO will most likely keep going up all day, it popped on smaller loss than expected, up 21% this morning. If you must follow Boeing and go with stock buyback as rigged reason for your very poor stock gain, then at least use other worthless stocks and make more money in a few hours than Boeing does in months . When Airbus comes online with their 787 buster, and if on time and on budget, then Airbus will take more market share away from the 787 Boeing . Even the Airbus failure on the A380 , a very late late and over budget A380, like the 787 Boeing plane has an adverse result for Boeing! Airbus is taking huge market share from the 747 line. Why? there is only room in the super jumbo market for one super jumbo and the market has already chose Airbus 380, How do I know this as a fact, look at the orders and deliveries each year, and Boeing cuts the cycle time on the poor selling 747. Why do I know this, there is only room enough for one super jumbo an old Boeing 1969 plane with a new wing or a new larger capacity Airbus 380? figure it out Boeing shareholders look at the orders from Airbus on the A380 compare this number to the 747 . Guess what , Boeing has lost that super-jumbo market . . Airbus has better management and Boeing worse management This is what is killing off Boeing the MD management style a proven failure it put MD into bankruptcy</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369061063680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061743125-44</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing made 5.5% in just ten days gain in stock price and then there was TSLA, AMD, DDD and JRCC</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369019850594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 23:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JASO that was fast, just went over 45% up this morning , might be time to take some profits how is Boeing doing this morning eh ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369061743125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369062973746-45</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing made 5.5% in just ten days gain in stock price and then there was TSLA, AMD, DDD and JRCC</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369019850594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 23:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>notice the time stamp I said might be time to take profits on JASO it was then $.840 , now its $8.08, that is how you read a stock chart learn to do that and you too can move on and leave Boeing crapola trolls and Boeing Hacks in the dust</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369062973746</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369063400716-46</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would have to get fk drunk and take some prozac before going on this flight</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1369063400716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369063822037-47</Id><Title>Boeing CEO on CNBC just now going flying on the 787 today</Title><Msg>The Boeing Chairman interview just now on CNBC wow and bark for Jim. Jim looked real scared on TV just now, his hair was in disarray and he was unable to make eye contact with the reporter. Perhaps what flies in the Corporate Board Room and catches on fire in the real world worries Jim more than he is letting on! Don't worry be happy the firestarter 787 now has a box to contain the, " sometimes we don't know what we don't know" about how the lithium batterycatches on fire . Wow and bark the container and the battery now weigh more than a safe nicad battery but it would have taken longer to redesign and fix the problem that build a heavy battery box with breather tubes what a failure of a plane the 787 all the hopes of Boeing shareholders are riding on a failed 787 going forward with a 747 not selling well the 777x and the 737 max no longer a Boeing upgraded design spells more trouble for Boeing shareholders</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369063822037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369065524542-48</Id><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Msg>Obama and the IRS: The Smoking Gun? It looks like its a certainty. Article on drudge.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369065998548-49</Id><Topic><Title>WayneDickensen ON SUICIDE WATCH!!</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060574900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:36:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>surely some twist of fate will save this Boeing scourge in time to bash Boeing yet again</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369065998548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369066107802-50</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't go thru life believing your own Bool sh.t and you will get by a lt better</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369066107802</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369066315727-51</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The IRS scandle originates in the minds of the evil Tdouchebaggers who are desperate to depose Obama before his AG prosecutes them for Tax Evasion. All the groups like TParty Patriots, Americans For Prosperity, Freedom Works, TParty Express and Tparty Nation will lose dozens of their upper management personnel as they are prosecuted by AG Holder and convicted and sent to jail.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369066315727</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:11:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369066569520-52</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima is stupid beyond believe.....makes you wonder who tell him to breath......and why.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369066569520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369066733149-53</Id><Title>PRICE TARGET $105!!</Title><Msg>STILL BUYTIME</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1369066733149</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369066871057-54</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing made 5.5% in just ten days gain in stock price and then there was TSLA, AMD, DDD and JRCC</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369019850594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 23:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JASO after making about 50% so far on a run up this morning, , now I am day trading JASO from 8,08 to 8.40 that is another slightly over 3% to the almost 50% I made on the initial run up this morning on better than expected reports its all a stock makret game if you know the rules you make money this stock is worthless like Boeing but I will take 50% in a few hours any day the money is real in my trade account hope to do it a couple more times today. going to the store now back in a few minutes could just set a buy at 8.08 but will wait . Now you trolls remember this "is someone who posts inflammatory, extraneous, or off-topic messages in an online community, such as a forum, chat room, or blog, with the primary intent of provoking readers into an emotional response or of otherwise disrupting normal on-topic discussion. and for traders it sure is nice to make 50% in a day trade meanwhile Boeing hacks report the CEO is flying on the 4 year late and 30 billion dollar overpriced 787 and they are up 1/10th of 1 percent not the 50% that I have booked this morning or the 302% i am up for 1 month and 10 days . Looks like tsla may be done maybe, but so what , I am up 123% in 1 month and 10 days nice for me</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369066871057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369067188620-55</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well if it isn't our old friend Marx-- tell me Marx has the grand jury met to define and begin your prosecution for treason yet- I bet they are laying in a supply of rope at Leavenworth these days- they are going to need it for the Tbaggers</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369067188620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369067330622-56</Id><Topic><Title>PRICE TARGET $105!!</Title><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1369066733149</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOO LOW...TACK ON ANOTHER $ 20 -25</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369067330622</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369067399841-57</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take your prozac for other reasons...u need it bad!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369067399841</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369068078864-58</Id><Title>Wall Street article covering the IRS history of going after Conservitive donors. That guy in Idaho was audited 4 times, ofcourse the media</Title><Msg>keeps a lid on most of this but coming from Idaho we learned of it. Americans want to believe but in light of the facts enablers. Like the family member we want to believe but when truth comes out. Blacks got this guy elected thinking benes in the mail. Food Stamps yes but even Mexican living in Mexico get that, free medical, the promise of freebees, but looking at the numbers 19+% unemployment for blacks paints a different story. This president is about Social Change not job growth as Bernanke has statted. Obama's policies do not support a recovery. He promised transparancy and change but the change we see is Marist thuggery. Many want to give him credit for the Markets but Bernanke says otherwise, CEOs get the credit here but I can assure you they got thier fingers on the layoff button if red pops up.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369068078864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:41:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369068314377-59</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UAL1 is airborne. Just left Huston' GWB airport.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369068314377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369068756223-60</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>41000 feet, 526 knots</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369068756223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369068954816-61</Id><Topic><Title>Wall Street article covering the IRS history of going after Conservitive donors. That guy in Idaho was audited 4 times, ofcourse the media</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369068078864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:41:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greg we are in a recovery what kind of mumbo jumbo are you spewing about now?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369068954816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369068990039-62</Id><Title>All Conservitive donors be warned, Obama just might send the IRS after you for audits like he has done</Title><Msg>even before this last election and even now. Oh yes he is Angered that he got caught, but I don't think he really cares except for this next midterm election. He has the next 4 years all sewed up. Thuggery and mayhem or the duration. AP CEO is expected to take the Government to court breaking the 1st Amendment, but nobody cares about that right?</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369068990039</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369069317393-63</Id><Title>Democrats Guilty of Suppressing the votes of Conservatives</Title><Msg>Their Use of the IRS to intimidate fund raising efforts of conservative groups is nothing more than voter suppression.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369069317393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369069381700-64</Id><Topic><Title>Chinook is Boeing’s longest continuously running production program</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1368878651638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 08:04:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9/11 was very good for the Military-Industerial-Complex and the National Security State. In fact, it was just the "New Pearl Harbor" that the neocons wanted to smooth the way for their agenda of military buildup in peacetime. 9/11 was very very good for BA, GE, NOC, LMT, RTN, GD. Just look at the charts. Open your eyes.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369069381700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369069681498-65</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Guilty of Suppressing the votes of Conservatives</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369069317393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:01:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>collect emails from the AP goes right after the First Amendment. Liberals do not care they want a one party system, over throwing the gov from within. All Obama needs now is the military to overthrow the gov as the #$%$ cheer.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369069681498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369070081070-66</Id><Title>Terrible mistake in not letting the Old South to secede</Title><Msg>Lincoln got it exactly wrong. Plain and simple. But, it's not too late. All states wanting to leave the United States, please, please make your exit now. Sane, rational blue state citizens need and want a chance to move forward. Tea party types and other wing nut freaks are disallowing and hindering my right to pursue happiness and fulfillment. We won't stand in your way. Again, please leave and create your own "homeland" where you can have an infinite number of guns (including machine guns, missiles, whatever you want) no taxes, (or roads or water or fire departments, etc) and no evil governmental structure of any sort. You can blissfully live in anarchy and chaos until nature takes it course and your collective gene pool goes by the wayside. Anyone need help packing up???</Msg><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369070081070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369070640354-67</Id><Topic><Title>the first 16 days of May</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1368807431059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 12:17:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you see what JP Morgan came out with a misly $1.06 should be at $150.00 all in due time I guess$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1369070640354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369070641001-68</Id><Topic><Title>All Conservitive donors be warned, Obama just might send the IRS after you for audits like he has done</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369068990039</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:56:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mumbo jumbo</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1369070641001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369071036622-69</Id><Topic><Title>Terrible mistake in not letting the Old South to secede</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369070081070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:14:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even if the South had been allowed to seceed, we would have eventually gone to war over claims on the western territories (slave vs free). "Kansas Bloody Kansas" would have just been a warmup. On the other hand, times have changed and if disunion could be done PEACEABLY it sounds pretty compelling.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1369071036622</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369071782234-70</Id><Title>Anti Americans Gleeful</Title><Msg>The more it becomes clear the Obama Administration is engaged in using the power of government institutions to commit voter intimidation and suppression the more gleeful ignorant democrats become. Somehow they are ignorant enough to think they will escape the tyranny of people who abuse government power. We know from history these people will eat their own and in time they will turn on the useful id iots who enabled them.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369071782234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369072393246-71</Id><Title>REPORT: DOJ Leaked Docs to Smear Fast &amp; Furious Whistleblower...</Title><Msg>The Department of Justice (DOJ) Inspector General published a new report Monday that confirms former U.S. Attorney for Arizona Dennis Burke leaked a document intended to smear Operation Fast and Furious scandal whistleblower John Dodson. The DOJ IG said it found “Burke’s conduct in disclosing the Dodson memorandum to be inappropriate for a Department employee and wholly unbefitting a U.S. Attorney.” “We are referring to OPR our finding that Burke violated Department policy in disclosing the Dodson memorandum to a member of the media for a determination of whether Burke’s conduct violated the Rules of Professional Conduct for the state bars in which Burke is a member,” the IG wrote. Burke resigned from his post as U.S. Attorney over the incident in August 2011, the first major Department of Justice official to leave his or her post in the Fast and Furious scandal. He said after the fact, in interviews with congressional investigators, that he now views leaking the document as a “mistake.” In addition to Burke’s involvement in leaking the document, emails the IG uncovered show senior officials at the Department of Justice discussed smearing Dodson. One of those was Tracy Schmaler, the Director of the Department’s Office of Public Affairs, who resigned her position at the DOI after emails uncovered through a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request showed that she worked with leftwing advocacy group Media Matters for America to smear whistleblowers and members of Congress and the media who sought to investigate DOJ scandals under Attorney General Eric Holder.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369072393246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:53:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369072833473-72</Id><Title>The Impeachment Option</Title><Msg>Representative Jason Chaffetz, a Utah Republican, says President Barack Obama may face impeachment over his administration’s response to the Benghazi attack. “They purposefully and willfully misled the American people, and that’s unacceptable,” Chaffetz tells me. “It’s part of a pattern of deception.” Behind the scenes, he says, House Republicans are frustrated by the White House’s evasiveness, and the calls for impeachment will likely increase. Chaffetz acknowledges that House speaker John Boehner is wary of moving too swiftly against the president, but the brash, 46-year-old conservative is tired of waiting for answers. He’s ready to issue subpoenas and schedule more hearings. His chief concern is that the White House, which he says is staffed by “self-preservationists,” seems to be hiding documents related to the attack and the president’s decisions, in order to protect the administration from scrutiny. “They’ve released 100 emails, but there are thousands of documents that we still need to see,” he says. “The truth gets colder as time goes on, so we need to stay vigilant.” “Now, the speaker has more patience than I do,” Chaffetz says. “He has told me to be patient, that the truth will eventually surface. But I’m not a patient person, and if this administration makes us do this the hard way, that’s what we’ll do.”</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369072833473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369073050056-73</Id><Title>Have Democrats Admitted they Can't Win an Election Without Cheating</Title><Msg>......or is it such a natural part of what they are they can't resit it?</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369073050056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369073224259-74</Id><Title>More IRS gotchas</Title><Msg>Big brother is out of date . . . A healthcare provider has sued the Internal Revenue Service and 15 of its agents, charging they wrongfully seized 60 million medical records from 10 million Americans. The name of the provider is not yet known, United Press International said. But Courthouse News Service said the suit claims the agency violated the Fourth Amendment in 2011, when agents executed a search warrant for financial data on one employee – and that led to the seizure of information on 10 million, including state judges. The search warrant did not specify that the IRS could take medical information, UPI said. And information technology officials warned the IRS about the potential to violate medical privacy laws before agents executed the warrant, the complaint said, as reported by UPI. “Despite knowing that these medical records were not within the scope of the warrant, defendants threatened to ‘rip’ the servers containing the medical data out of the building if IT personnel would not voluntarily hand them over,” the complaint states, UPI reported. The suit also says IRS agents seized workers’ phones and telephone data – more violations of the warrant, UPI reported. The complaint alleges the IRS was “invasive and unlawful” and stole access to intimate medical records that included patients’ treatment plans and therapies, UPI said. The suit seeks $25,000 in compensatory damages, per violation. The records’ seizure could impact up to one in 25 Americans, UPI said. washingtontimes..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369073224259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369073464910-75</Id><Topic><Title>Have Democrats Admitted they Can't Win an Election Without Cheating</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369073050056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:04:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy after GHW Bushe's idiot child cheated both times to gain the presidency I guess bagger criminals just naturally assume that everybody cheats to gain the throne</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369073464910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369073561420-76</Id><Title>Organizations that Preferred a One Party Government</Title><Msg>Communists in the USSR, Cuba, North Korea, China, Islamic Republic Party of Iran, the Democrat Party of the USA, absolute monarchies in a number of countries.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369073561420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369073628006-77</Id><Topic><Title>More IRS gotchas</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369073224259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>boy the minute the IRS prosecutes tax crooks its like viewing an exorcism where Beelzibub starts to scream and holler and do all kinds of awful things the minute he begins to feel himself being exorcised</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369073628006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369073827139-78</Id><Topic><Title>Organizations that Preferred a One Party Government</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369073561420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:12:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marx Bouncer and the dregs of humanity always wanted a fuhrer type of govt like his former sweetheart installed in Germany about 1934</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369073827139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369073827753-79</Id><Title>'Richard Milhous Obama'...</Title><Msg>.....it's the cover up that will get him.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369073827753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369073968133-80</Id><Topic><Title>More IRS gotchas</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369073224259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fascists at work. Anyone with 1/2 a brain, and a decent sense of right and wrong that eliminates liberals from any intelligent debate knows that Obama, and the left are after a one payer system. They know they will eliminate any competition for healthcare that holds down the cost, and the corruption.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369073968133</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:19:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369073977253-81</Id><Topic><Title>Terrible mistake in not letting the Old South to secede</Title><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369070081070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:14:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We can eject the Southern States if we want to- sez so in the constitution right next to the right to bear arms!!!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369073977253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:19:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074098386-82</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flight landed and is headed for the gate</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369074098386</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074151520-83</Id><Topic><Title>Organizations that Preferred a One Party Government</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1369073561420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:12:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at Obama's background. He even says he favored his Father's desire for communist rule. That says it all. Obama, and the pinkos that understand what his Regime' is after, know he wants to eliminate any form of competition that competes with his fascist approach to governing. Look at his followers on this thread. They attack anyone that questions what he supports.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369074151520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074327454-84</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Americans Love Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060976094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We desperately need Obamacare to creat jobs if nothing else- just think in addition to providing insurance to those 40 million who were formerly uninsured we will be able to see the level of healthcare for these people rise by several magnitudes and as the need for more care is addressed we will have to hire many more health service personnel- its like killing two birds with one stone- something no bagger is capable of ever understanding</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369074327454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074745681-85</Id><Topic><Title>HOOZDIKs post on obstruction of Obamacare is one big LIE !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368967069760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:37:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you guys sure are desperate RWNJs across the planet are feeling the heat now and that includes you spartacs... We can sure expect the number and magnitude of the anti Obamacare entities' lies to increase and multiply as the date for complete implementation nears. BTW The Washingon Examiner has no credibility whatsoever considering it ties to the TParty</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369074745681</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369074925833-86</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO on CNBC just now going flying on the 787 today</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369063822037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey wayne don't you know we have already built 100 787's and only have 700 to go- we will finish in about 4 years if no new orders arrive- most likely the orders will keep coming forever</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369074925833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369075086473-87</Id><Topic><Title>HOOZDIKs post on obstruction of Obamacare is one big LIE !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368967069760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:37:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey Floyd did you ever get that last mouthful swallowed?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369075086473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:38:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369075258752-88</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"stupid beyond believe (sic).....who tell (sic) him to breath (sic)" Anybody else see mass irony right there in Harpo's post?</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1369075258752</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369075414156-89</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You went off on a tangent from original comment and not one Democrat in the original hearings made the lack of money issue stick. The key witnesses from the state department were asked about budgets and their answer to questions regarding budgets was that money was available if needed. I'm pointing out that you are wrong in thinking the sequester had any bearing on Benghazi.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369075414156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369075538315-90</Id><Title>Boeing or JASO which is better today ?</Title><Msg>Attention Boeing investors, , today I called JASO it is up 57%, that is in less than a day, so in one day you could have made more than Boeing has made in five years . Airbus is up 40% YTD Boeing up 31 % YTD, for 5 years BA up 16% , Airbus up 121% todays CEO flying on UAL did nothing for the Boeing stock , Why , simple, Boeing787 is flying 4 years late and 30 billion over cost and the stock is going no place fast. You need to learn how to trade stocks and get off the dog and pony show . Next up, the Airbus 787- competition plane will take market share away from the 787. Just watch and learn</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369075538315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369075857851-91</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the First Amendment is under attack, we will hear misinformation out of the gov. hoping the scandle will go away. Even the CEO at AP is considering a suite. The media has kept quite so far but now reporters can't do thier work. Any negative out of the media can expect IRS or the Attorney General to get involved. That donor in Idaha was audited 4 times. Just wondering of the many other donors that we never heard about. I expect the media to push and shove for truth at this point.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369075857851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369076141400-92</Id><Title>Y'all Quit Be leav'n anything bad bout Ma President.</Title><Msg>As sister Sheila Jackson Lee says, as former slaves we deserve to be able to take advantage of control'n the government and doing what we want wid the govement's money. After all they gots all that money by stealing it from us former slaves.</Msg><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369076141400</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369076502624-93</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing or JASO which is better today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369075538315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne go sell your AVON products somewhere else!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1369076502624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369076824299-94</Id><Title>Obama is one of us</Title><Msg>He's black, grew up without a daddy, his momma lived on welfare, he used a lot of drugs and delt some and in spit of all dis, he got a fine education without paying for it because of firmative action. He's getting us free medical care, pay'n our men for disabilites and increas'n our wellfare befits. Now I axe you, does it matter if he had to tell you a few lies and use the gubment to punish people that tried to keep him from distribut'n money to us former slaves? He know's wat it's like to be Black and have yer gramdma raise you.....hees one of us.</Msg><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369076824299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369077677715-95</Id><Title>787 fleet battry retrofit almost done.</Title><Msg>45 of the 50 delivered 787's have completed the battery retrofit.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369077677715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369077743428-96</Id><Title>Brother Al Sharpton Says ConServatives Trying to Lynch Obama</Title><Msg>Rev. Al says Obama should be held accountable for any of the stuff he administration has been doing......he said Obama was out on the golf course when most of the stuff was being done so don't blame him.</Msg><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369077743428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369077967370-97</Id><Title>Sister Maxine Waters Says Obama Has the Right to use the IRS.......</Title><Msg>.....any way he wants to......he won the lection.</Msg><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369077967370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369078061676-98</Id><Title>LOL!!!!!! Guy goes on the flight with camera and asking people</Title><Msg>if you are nervous just min beofre takeoff ?? WOW!!!!!! idiots !!!</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1369078061676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369078487387-99</Id><Topic><Title>Sister Maxine Waters Says Obama Has the Right to use the IRS.......</Title><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369077967370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:26:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Maxine Waters comes from the same thinking mode of how to govern as Karl Marx....and that is a fact.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369078487387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369078516084-100</Id><Topic><Title>More IRS gotchas</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369073224259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One employee they are after so they get 60 million healthcare records on 10 million people Must be ObUma math !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369078516084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369078531169-101</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing or JASO which is better today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369075538315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about that JASO up over 66% today and Boeing stock is a gain of nothing as usual 0.00 now remember a troll is is someone who posts inflammatory extraneous, or off-topic messages in an online community, such as a forum, chat room, or blog, with the primary intent of provoking readers into an emotional response or of otherwise disrupting normal on-topic discussion. So once agains I called JASO and you could have made a gain of more today than Boeing has made in 5 years ony up 16% in five years wow and barkand ouch for Boeing shareholders and the Boeing Hacks nothing at all to say now too ! well bark and ouch for them too. Time to move on with this weeks gainers [</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369078531169</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369078902465-102</Id><Title>Flying on the 787 today especially wow what a thought</Title><Msg>As Fly through space, one thought kept crossing my mind - every part of this 787 fire starter airplane was supplied by the lowest bidder. The man on the plane today is the CEO James M. , another thought crossed my mind, the Boeing CEO is not only deranged MD style leader and millionaire.he is doing his best to fleece the Boeing shareholders and become a deranged billionaire. He is one of the highest paid CEOs in America while Boeing stock has gone in a flat spin for 5 years up only 16% while Airbus stock is up over 121%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369078902465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:41:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369079081454-103</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing CEO on CNBC just now going flying on the 787 today</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369063822037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well the CEO flying on the 787 did nothing for the stock today while JASO is up 66% today on a one day trade , humm maybe learn how to trade stocks, instead of listening to Boeing hacks then eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369079081454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369079444056-104</Id><Topic><Title>Flying on the 787 today especially wow what a thought</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369078902465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another bs post by waynedick......triple digits this week wdick! Got it?</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369079444056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369079938759-105</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing or JASO which is better today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369075538315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That man wdick is an absolute whacko! We will hear about 100 stocks by the end of the month in boeing boards...such a sad case!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1369079938759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369081010617-106</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is one of us</Title><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369076824299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's one of the 1%.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369081010617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:16:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369081957156-107</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is one of us</Title><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369076824299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He travelled the world without any money. Who footed that bill? His real daddy was a communist, and that impressed BO, and he favored communism. He got a socialist education at Harvard, and why he probably has hidden his college records.... went on to work as a community organizer with that Jerrett gal who is a close advisor of his now...worked in Chicago, and got millions of dollars in federal monies to rebuild the Black slum neighborhoods, and nothing to show for it. Where the money went no one but Jarrett, and BO knows it appears.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369081957156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369082540220-108</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing or JASO which is better today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369075538315</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 14:45:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you repost your JASON call from yesterday, I didn't see it, that would give you credibility if it is there It's easy to pick/post them after market close right from the Yahoo Finance site. % Gainers % Gainers Name Price Change % Chg AQ 12.73 +6.77 +113.59% Acquity Group Limited MEAD 3.41 +1.74 +104.19% Meade Instruments Corp. ZVV 340.00 +170.00 +100.00% ZVV JASO 9.56 +3.95 +70.37% JA Solar Holdings Co., Ltd. RSOL 6.08 +2.05 +50.87%</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369082540220</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369082953218-109</Id><Title>Yuse Gots ta Admit the Smartest People in Congress are......</Title><Msg>.....all members of the congressional black caucus.</Msg><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369082953218</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369083796923-110</Id><Title>Black Cildren Alll over America are Starting to get Anxious</Title><Msg>...they does this every year bout this time. They know pretty soon it's goan be father's day and since most of em don't have a clue who they daddy is they start think'n they goan be miss'n out on something. I always tell my chill'n the ain't goan miss out on nothing because Obama is president and he goan make shor that the gubmit is goan be their daddy and the good thang bout that is you doan even have to buy the guberment a present fer being their daddy. Obama understands black chillen bacause he was in the same condition when he was their age.</Msg><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369083796923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369084459192-111</Id><Title>I foud out the best place to Hide my food stamps is.....</Title><Msg>....is under my boyfriend's work boots.</Msg><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369084459192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369084491893-112</Id><Topic><Title>Black Cildren Alll over America are Starting to get Anxious</Title><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369083796923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your racist cr@p not is funny.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369084491893</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369084602111-113</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is one of us</Title><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369076824299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:07:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's good reason to suspect that the CIA footed that bill. Obama's first job after college was in a CIA front. At least one of his mentors was a very spooked-up guy. Joseph Cannon has done some good work in this.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369084602111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369085098760-114</Id><Title>You know these Tornadas Are Wores on Black People and Mexicans Than Other Peolpe</Title><Msg>It's True.......In Shawnee Oklahoma there was a 3 story apartment building with 1 apartment on each floor. A white family lived on the top floor. A Mexican family lived on the second floor. A black family lived on the bottom floor. At 2:00 PM in the afternoon a terrible tornado hit the building, totally destroying it. You know which family didn't even get hurt? Yea, it was the White family, because both parents were at work and the kids were in school. It jist doan seem fair.</Msg><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369085098760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369085504722-115</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Telling me that money was not an issue, is like telling me the Repubs don't want to cut medicare or social security from seniors. Yeah right next you'll be selling me shares of the Brooklyn Bridge.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369085504722</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369085570797-116</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing that when I posted news this morning and mentioned Bloomberg, or Alpha mine got censored. Nothing against you I just wonder if my acct. is compromised</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369085570797</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369085779304-117</Id><Title>Bombshell news that the Oval Office knew about IRS targeting and lied about it</Title><Msg>Jay Carney admitted today that Obama's top staffer's knew about IRS targeting problem. This isn't going away anytime soon.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369085779304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369086027130-118</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Telling you the truth revealed in open televised testimony is the same as telling my cat, except that my cat has a greater potential to comprehend.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369086027130</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369086991510-119</Id><Title>United feels 787 best aircraft in sky today</Title><Msg>Thats good to hear from their US launce customer</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369086991510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369087287402-120</Id><Topic><Title>United feels 787 best aircraft in sky today</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369086991510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is that censored. No mention of source and is plain vanilla post. How are others on board able to do it like I did with no particulars. Have I been hacked or censored by Yahoo for what? Please respond Yahoo. Don't know how to post anymore, following all rules yet in less than 2 minutes taken off board</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369087287402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369087799885-121</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Total lie....the GOP has proven beyond a doubt that there was plenty of money to protect the embassy. Requests were denied because the REGIME' did not want voters to think Al Queda was any problem given the REGIME' had portrayed the world as getting much safer under Obama's policy of APPEASEMENT towards Al Queda. So they flatout allowed the 4 Americans to be murdered...and that is a fact.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369087799885</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369087899697-122</Id><Title>DOJ Secretly Monitored and Criminalized Three Fox News Reporters</Title><Msg>Earlier today the Washington Post reported that Fox News' James Rosen had been secretly monitored by the Department of Justice. DOJ monitored his work and personal emails, read his work and personal emails, monitored his phones, monitored his movements and even named him as a criminal conspirator. Now, we know Rosen wasn't the only Fox News reporter targeted. Reporter William LaJeunesse, who extensively covered Operation Fast and Furious and national-security senior producer Mike Levine. Fox News executive Michael Clemente is vowing to stand by reporters and slammed the administration for their intimidation tactics and assault on the First Amendment. “We are outraged to learn today that James Rosen was named a criminal co-conspirator for simply doing his job as a reporter. In fact, it is downright chilling. We will unequivocally defend his right to operate as a member of what up until now has always been a free press.” White House Press Secretary Jay Carney refused to comment on the secret monitoring of Fox News reporters and continued to say President Obama believes in a balance between free speech and national security during his press briefing Monday. "I can't address an ongoing criminal investigation," Carney said. "The president believes strongly in the need for reporters to pursue investigative journalism." The Department of Justice is justifying its actions and saying the Department followed the law and all regulations in relation to tapping communications of the press.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1369087899697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369088313897-123</Id><Topic><Title>United feels 787 best aircraft in sky today</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369086991510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo please send a message to me. what is wrong with this post. Says nothing with no sources listed like you like. Others still are quoting MarketWatch and other sites and there posts remain--hate discriminatory acts.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369088313897</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369088373799-124</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a paid shill your propaganda isn't working any more.....get a new job and get some self respect</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369088373799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369088474904-125</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Attack Would Have Failed</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1369048290415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:11:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you drunk?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369088474904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369088615432-126</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you suggesting that anyone with any credibility isn't a believer anymore?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369088615432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369088643189-127</Id><Title>Obonzo regime continues Jihad against 1st and 4th ammendments</Title><Msg>Now they have been caught accessing personal medical records.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369088643189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369088753009-128</Id><Topic><Title>Flying on the 787 today especially wow what a thought</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369078902465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and remember for all the trolls yu are simply put, someone who posts inflammatory,] extraneous, or off-topic messages in an online community, such as a forum, chat room, or blog, with the primary intent of provoking readers into an emotional response] or of otherwise disrupting normal on-topic discussion.[</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369088753009</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369088958949-129</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Americans Love Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060976094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a very funny and fascistly fat, little Not-See.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369088958949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:29:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369089074024-130</Id><Title>IRS Agent: "What do you expect when you target the President" ?</Title><Msg>What do you expect when you target the President?” This is what an Internal Revenue Service (IRS) agent allegedly said to the head of a conservative organization that was being audited after calling for the impeachment of then-President Clinton. Recent revelations that IRS agents gave “special scrutiny” to organizations opposed to the current administration’s policies suggest that many in the IRS still believe harassing the President’s opponents is part of their job. As troubling as these recent reports are, it would be a grave mistake to think that IRS harassment of opponents of the incumbent President is a modern, or a partisan, phenomenon. As scholar Burton Folsom pointed out in his book New Deal or Raw Deal, IRS agents in the 1930s where essentially “hit squads” against opponents of the New Deal. It is well-known that the administrations of John F. Kennedy and Lyndon Johnson used the IRS to silence their critics. One of the articles of impeachment drawn up against Richard Nixon dealt with his use of the IRS to harass his political enemies. Allegations of IRS abuses were common during the Clinton administration, and just this week some of the current administration’s defenders recalled that antiwar and progressive groups alleged harassment by the IRS during the Bush presidency. The bipartisan tradition of using the IRS as a tool to harass political opponents suggests that the problem is deeper than just a few “rogue” IRS agents—or even corruption within one, two, three or many administrations. Instead, the problem lays in the extraordinary power the tax system grants the IRS. The IRS routinely obtains information about how we earn a living, what investments we make, what we spend on ourselves and our families, and even what charitable and religious organizations we support. Starting next year, the IRS will be collecting personally identifiable health insurance information in order to ensure we are complying with Obamacare’s mandates. The current tax laws even giv</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369089074024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369089117055-131</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Americans Love Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060976094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get off my board you piece of trash</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369089117055</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369089327155-132</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People arnt buying Obama is a man of peace cause he got a Nobel Prize People arnt buying he "didn't know" about the IRS scandal People aren't buying Obama is open and honest after NEVER releasing any of his records People arnt buying that we should give up our guns when he gives them to Mexican Drug lords. People arnt buying that we should be afraid of Alqaeda when he supplies Alqaeda with guns in Libya and Syria. Our President is a cleverly crafted Hoax.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369089327155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369089369760-133</Id><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Msg>for the investors remember my earlier user comment on how to trade , you know what to do if you read them. Two of the 4 stocks that I made over 123% in 10 days got on the short list to drop today on the trade principal I mentioned for the beginner, This is the remedial training for the Boeing investors and troll users who need to learn how to make money in the stock market , instead of making gibberish user comments . Once you learn how to craw, l then I can teach you more trade skills . Eventually, you will be able to make more than 17 per cent on a stock in 5 years like what you have made on Boeing, remember if its a 787 then its a fire starter with a box, because sometimes Boeing does not know what they do not know about why the batteries catch fire. Remember a battery In a box, if a fire occurs, that is still a mandatory emergency landing. So how smart was building a box instead of changing to safer nicad batteries hummmm! the stock closed up another 3 percent in after market trading so tomorrow will be the stock trader test read my user comment to learn how to trade stocks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369089509878-134</Id><Title>PPS</Title><Msg>Bracing for $100 this week</Msg><Username>moanawai</Username><Timestamp>1369089509878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369090404799-135</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody that is interested in fact finding, and not a leftist more interested in promoting socialism, and a leftist agenda can get the facts of Drudge. Drudge's reputation is based on getting it right, and relying on reliable sources of information period. There is no more reliabe source of accurate info then Drudge.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369090404799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369090519288-136</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Americans Love Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060976094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOUR board? This is a loon-free zone!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369090519288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369090764318-137</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Orly. You're making much more sense than is even normal for you!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369090764318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369090917412-138</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll: Americans Love Obamacare</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369060976094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Loon free"? Who is the decider? You? Uncle Ho? Or Heinrich? You are a funny one.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369090917412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369090984059-139</Id><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Msg>This week President Obama's disapproval rating in the polls was higher than his approval rating. And some are already speculating that the Democrats' biggest obstacle to take over the House in 2014 is the President. Obviously those speculators are forgetting that polls show a much larger disapproval of Congress. And Americans, so say the polls, dislike the Republicans more than the Democrats. They also blame the GOP for the sequestration. These speculators must have forgotten the election results this past November, when Democrats gained seats in both the House and the Senate. This is the president's second term. Historically, unless there is some big political Hail Mary event, Americans seem less enthusiastic about president's the second time around. It is pretty well known in Washington that the president wants a Democratic controlled House in the next election, making it easier for him to get legislation passed that he has promised the American people. Looking at the new face (literally) of the voting population (Hispanics, African-Americans and women), I don't think Democrats have anything or anyone in their way to take over the House in 2014. Now certainly the seats that are up for grabs are in very red Republican conservative territory, but the American people are clear: work together and get something done Congress or we'll vote you out. Another reason I see the Democrats being able to capture the 17 seats they need to have a majority in the House? The Republican Party. It's badly divided. It lacks leadership. And I'm not sure the GOP knows who they want to be when they grow up. And if you factor in two Republican governors, Chris Christie of New Jersey and Rick Scott of Florida, who were very outspoken against the president's Affordable Care Act, and who are now gladly embracing the Medicaid extension and happily taking the federal government's cash: This shows that the president's "agenda" thus far has been successful. Repeal and replace what? So the president is not in the Democrats' way. And I'm not worried about a few polls that show a dip in the president's approval rating. Because from where I sit, the road to a Democratic takeover of the House looks pretty clear right now.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369090984059</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369091001491-140</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandle originates in the Oval Office</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369065524542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talking to your aliases all day long is kind of funny, in a psychotic sort of way...............</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369091001491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369091146770-141</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369090984059</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven continues his propaganda mission that Ho, Mao and Goebbels, would marvel at................</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1369091146770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:05:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369091154133-142</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a joke, what a joke. A more realistic poll result is 100% of sane people (progressives) believe Sparty is even too whacko even for the tinfoil hat crowd.</Msg><Username>greatolbigun</Username><Timestamp>1369091154133</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369091801872-143</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another way to look at it, if you invested in JASO 5 years ago, you would be down 95%. That would mean you you were 112% better off by being in Boeing.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369091801872</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369092355590-144</Id><Title>The 21st Republican Tea Party: No Bottom to Their Abyss</Title><Msg>Remember the good old days when Republican-Tea Partyers' political attack ads placed rifle scope crosshairs over their Democratic Party opponents' congressional districts? Sarah Palin urged Tea Party candidates to "reload" and "aim" for Democrats. Republican U.S. Senate candidate Sharron Angle urged her voter base in 2010 to resort to "Second Amendment Remedies." Arizona congressional candidate Jesse Kelly who opposed Gabriel Giffords put out political ads inviting his supporters to a rally to "Get on Target for Victory in November. Help remove Gabrielle Giffords from office. Shoot a fully automatic M16 with Jesse Kelly." During the frenzy of gun rhetoric Allen West's chief of staff, screech radio host Joyce Kaufman, shrieked, "If ballots don't work bullets will." That incendiary statement caused Florida's Broward County to immediately close schools and send 250,000 schoolchildren home because of the fears of escalating gun violence. Allen West was defeated in his reelection bid in 2012 but he recently joined his like-minded cohorts on Fox News who are presently on a Benghazi Obama impeachment crusade which is devolving more into a risible Sisyphean parody. Rush Limbaugh spouted, "I tell people don't kill all the liberals, leave enough around so we can have two on every campus; living fossils, so we will never forget what these people stood for." Ted Nugent raged, "Obama, he's a piece of #$%$. I told him to suck on my machine gun. Hey Hillary [Clinton], you might want to ride one of these into the sunset, you worthless #$%$." Yes, those were the old days when Republicans made Violence a political strategy and Hate their guiding principle that they plan to carry right into 2014 and 2016. But, they have now upped their game, or should we say, lowered the depth of the cavity, into which they keep sinking. Enter the Republican Party's malignant, more violent, more threatening and more abominable version, Hate radio host, Pete Santilli. Santilli has been recruited as their latest depraved Republican attack dog with his indirect threats on the life of the President Barack Obama and direct threats on the life of possible 2016 presidential candidate, Hillary Clinton. "I want to shoot her [Clinton] right in the vagina and I don't want her to die right away; I want her to feel the pain and I want to look her in the eyes and I want to say, on behalf of all Americans that you've killed, on behalf of the Navy SEALS, the families of Navy SEAL Team Six who were involved in the fake hunt down of this Obama, Obama bin Laden thing, that whole fake scenario, because these Navy SEALS know the truth, they killed them all. On behalf of all of those people, I'm supporting our troops by saying we need to try, convict, and shoot Hillary Clinton in the vagina." Santilli added, "Barack Obama needs to be tried, convicted, and shot for crimes against the United States of America." "And if anybody has a problem with that, then you are an enemy of our state." We should never make the mistake that this guy's comments are an aberration. They are not. They are the summation and distillation of the past 4 years of Republicans' boiling anger and intense, palpable hatred of Barack Obama. That seething resentment and acrimony were a large part of the Tea Party emergence in 2010 in the aftermath of their violent gun rhetoric that catapulted so many of them to office on a media-fed belief that they represented a groundswell of support. That support has collapsed as the Rasmussen poll taken earlier this year which shows only 8% of voters now identify with the subversive Tea Party and their surrogates like Pete Santilli. Rush Limbaugh, Michael Savage, Ted Nugent, Ann Coulter and other bilge have made millions off of spreading racist, hateful attacks against the President from Day One when he first took the oath of office on January 20, 2009. Incivility has become the Republicans' modus operandi. It is a well-practiced strategy and political doctrine in their ongoing venom-filled attacks that they have committed to pursue between now and 2016 regardless of the outcome in the midterm 2014 elections. Santilli exemplifies the vile metastasizing of a Republican-Tea Party descent into an ever deeper sulfurous abyss. He is the next vile phase of their vitriol and an escalation of their undisguised, unapologetic use of gun threats against political opponents. He defines the entire Republican-Tea Partyers' deviant, rotted ideology. This is who they are and what they have become in the 21st Century.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369092355590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369092463931-145</Id><Topic><Title>The 21st Republican Tea Party: No Bottom to Their Abyss</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369092355590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Jigs up.....the tipping point is past...everyone knows Barry is a fraud and a criminal</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369092463931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369093236244-146</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you numbers work? Boeing was at 65 back in April 2008, now 98.72. (98.72-65)/65= up 52%</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369093236244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369093302714-147</Id><Topic><Title>Black Cildren Alll over America are Starting to get Anxious</Title><Username>biggovmomma</Username><Timestamp>1369083796923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a republican. What do you expect besides vile, disgusting, virulent, nasty, hateful, fetid, stinking racism.</Msg><Username>jumboyjetski</Username><Timestamp>1369093302714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:41:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369093398895-148</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty and his brainwashers also believe that the tornados in OK were orchestrated by the NWO, via their chemtrails.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1369093398895</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:43:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369093599611-149</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost forgot the BA dividend. 2% compounded for 5 years is another 12.6% gain over JASO's zero dividend. 124.6% better off with Boeing over the last 5 years if you include the dividend?</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369093599611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369093710365-150</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is Obama supporting AlQaeda in Libya and Syria ? Google it</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369093710365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:48:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369093782324-151</Id><Title>Enabling Greed Makes US Sick</Title><Msg>At the end of a week that reminds us to be ever vigilant about the dangers of government overreaching its authority, whether by the long arm of the IRS or the Justice Department, we should pause to think about another threat — from too much private power obnoxiously intruding into public life. An investigator looks over a destroyed fertilizer plant in West, Texas, Thursday, May 2, 2013. (AP Photo/LM Otero, Pool)All too often, instead of acting as a brake on runaway corporate power and greed, government becomes their enabler, undermining the very rules and regulations intended to keep us safe. Think of inadequate inspections of food and the food-related infections which kill 3,000 Americans each year and make 48 million sick. A new study from Johns Hopkins shows elevated levels of arsenic — known to increase a person’s risk of cancer — in chicken meat. According to the university’s Center for a Livable Future, “Arsenic-based drugs have been used for decades to make poultry grow faster and improve the pigmentation of the meat. The drugs are also approved to treat and prevent parasites in poultry… Currently in the U.S., there is no federal law prohibiting the sale or use of arsenic-based drugs in poultry feed.” And here’s a story in The Washington Post about toxic, bacteria-killing chemicals used in poultry plants to clean more chickens more quickly to meet increased demand and make more money. According to Amanda Hitt, director of the Government Accountability Project’s Food Integrity Campaign, “They are mixing chemicals together in these plants, and it’s making people sick. Does it work better at killing off pathogens? Yes, but it also can send someone into respiratory arrest.” So far, the government has done next to nothing. No research into the possible side effects, no comprehensive record-keeping on illnesses. “Instead,” the Post reports, “they review data provided by chemical manufacturers.” What’s more, the Department of Agriculture is about to allow the production lines to move even faster, by as much as 25 percent, which means more chemicals, more exposure, more sickness. Think of that and think of the 85,000 industrial chemicals available today – only a handful have been tested for safety. Ian Urbina writes in The New York Times, “Hazardous chemicals have become so ubiquitous that scientists now talk about babies being born pre-polluted, sometimes with hundred s of synthetic chemicals showing up in their blood.” Think, too, of that horrific explosion of ammonium nitrate in the Texas fertilizer plant. Fifteen people were killed and their little town devastated. The magazine Mother Jones noted, “Inspections are virtually non-existent; regulatory agencies don’t talk to each other; and there’s no such thing as a buffer zone when it comes to constructing plants and storage facilities in populated areas.” For years, the Fertilizer Institute, described as “the nation’s leading lobbying organization of the chemical and agricultural industries,” resisted regulation and legislators went along. People can lose their lives when federal or state government winks at bad corporate practices — 4,500 workplace deaths annually at a cost to America of nearly half a trillion dollars. As Salon’s columnist and author David Sirota observes, “If all this data was about a terrorist threat, the reaction would be swift — negligent federal agencies would be roundly criticized and the specific state’s lax attitude toward security would be lambasted. Yet, after the fertilizer plant explosion, there has been no proactive reaction at all, other than Texas Republican Gov. Rick Perry boasting about his state’s ‘comfort with the amount of oversight’ that already exists.” Finally, consider this story from ProPublica’s investigative reporter Abrahm Lustgarten about a uranium company that wanted a mining project in Texas that threatened to pollute drinking water. The EPA resisted — until the company hired as its lobbyist the Democratic fundraiser and fixer Heather Podesta, a favorite of the White House. Her firm was paid $400,000, she pulled the strings, and presto, the EPA changed its mind and said yes, go ahead and do your dirty work. In fact, ProPublica found that “the agency has used a little-known provision in the federal Safe Drinking Water Act to issue more than 1,500 exemptions allowing energy and mining companies to pollute aquifers, including many in the driest parts of the country.” Of course, in a free society we’ll always be debating the role of government and its agencies. What are the limits, when is government oversight necessary and when is it best deterred? But it’s not only government that can go too far. As long as there are insufficient checks and balances on big business and its powerful lobbies, we are at their mercy. Their ability to buy off public officials is an assault on democracy and a threat to our lives and health. When an entire political system persists in producing such gross injustice, it is making inevitable wholesale defiance.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369093782324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369093869216-152</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369090984059</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I expected a reply such as that. However, the number of syllables you were able to bang out did surprise me.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369093869216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369094008323-153</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, spartacus, how many young people will be euthanized? Will you tell us? You posted a reader comment. Do you think that person was objective?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369094008323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369094634580-154</Id><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Msg>Impeachment will never happen... despite the best efforts of the racists in this country. Obama is a winner, and a survivor. As for me, I've got my: Toes in the water #$%$ in the sand Not a worry in the world A cold beer in my hand Life is good today Life is good today Obama will win again Listening to McCartney's greatest hits All 3,000 of them Tomorrow's forecast? Good Day, Sunshine!</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369094634580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369094837199-155</Id><Topic><Title>Enabling Greed Makes US Sick</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369093782324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:49:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor hooz doing his sub-par best to defend the greediest most power mad president in quite some time, a president who has been exposed for using his power by targeting citizens for abuse and punishment, and punishing citizens who stand up to defend the 1st, 2nd and 4th ammendments against Barry's jihad.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369094837199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369095216464-156</Id><Topic><Title>instead of economy economy its scandle scandle and there all Obama's doing</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368895154427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting. Anybody else notice that two posters spell the word scandle the same way? Wrong, that is.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1369095216464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369095868112-157</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx^cylinder, I use cnn money and then type in BA and then use their stock chart it is set up from today going back 1 days 5 days 30 days 3 monts ytd and 3 and 5 years. I am a swing trader and so if the cnn chart is not adding any dividend i can not tell you one way or the other. One thing is sure if you look at my 4 trades from April 3 to today AMD, JRCC,tsla, ddd and today jaso I am way ahead of any boeing investor. Remember i move to the hot stock. Today it was easy I get up at 6 am and read the news jaso had better than expected earnings Actually losses and so I looked at the previous day close that was a get in for me today the open was much higher. It is basic technical stock market procedure. cbx6cylinder I made without any dividend 302% since april3 to Friday. If you can tell me since 2008 until today somehow Boeing is a better deal than I will eat my hat. I also made a few other day trades and posted one. I decided to do this 10 day deal to shut up one of the doubting Thomas guy I have done it to him before then he waited several years to try to bring it back as some kind of forever trade .the funny thing was two o f the stocks I suggested years ago are still beating Boeing real bad. anyway my numbers are real and I am making that money. I am not a troll or a Boeing Hack. I quit Boeing because I had the minimum number of age years,50 to get out and have not looked back I make a lot of money and cant go anywhere for the day trades so i sit here and enjoy the Boeing hack and the trolls try to spin their story. if you read me you, should already know what my plan is for jaso and the 4 stocks I have . I made it very simple to the readers how to play a stock on a swing trade. A swing trade is anything from a few minutes to a few months. A day trade can be several in and out trades over a day and a long term investment is what you are talking about. i accept your reinvestment and any other adds but they do not add up to 302%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369095868112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096274707-158</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sdolar? Is Obama putting more hard workin folks' tax money into those failed Solar companies still? Must be a big contributor heading up JA Solar that will take home the cash when JA Solar folds up, and screws the investors.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369096274707</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096775002-159</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx6cylinder so remember my gain is in one moth and 11 days now 302% is my gain, are you in your comparison going from 2008 to 2013 and I can guarantee I will be making this kind of gain every month . I have only held apple until steve jobs died and starbux since I boughtit at the ipo every stock I do now is a swing trade wasy too much money to stay with any one stock . As far as paying tax I do that once per quarter if in a taxable account and for my ira it is all tax deferred .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369096775002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369096893735-160</Id><Topic><Title>instead of economy economy its scandle scandle and there all Obama's doing</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1368895154427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 12:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do people forget that Obama flatout said he wanted to see $5 a gal gasoline? Support for high energy prices is worse than what Al Queda can do. It crushes our economy. How many times does Obama have to violate the constitution before he gets pegged as a constitution violator? He even said it was "a failed document."</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369096893735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369097190913-161</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369094634580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:03:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just grabbing another cold one. Still winning.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369097190913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369097282628-162</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx, once more you need to read all my user comment I am not being paid to teach you to trade stocks if you want to learn then you need to pay attention and be quiet . If your attempting to put a spin on your hogwash about comparing Being from 2008 to my stock over one month and 11 dasy then you need to add the same gain for each month from 2008 to today for my trades , your assumptions are squed in your favor . You sir are engaging me in a game of yoru statistics dont lie but you do I willhave nothing more to do with you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369097282628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369097427419-163</Id><Topic><Title>Flying on the 787 today especially wow what a thought</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369078902465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks that is 7 thumbs up for me and minus 6 thumbs for the troll !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369097427419</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369098582678-164</Id><Topic><Title>Flying on the 787 today especially wow what a thought</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369078902465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry but that doesn't detract anything from what he stated in his initial post. He does have a point on BA's quality issues. The criticisms of the CEO is also valid.</Msg><Username>conservative_influence</Username><Timestamp>1369098582678</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369099035959-165</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>falmouthharbor I want to first say your one of the better posters I have read, but I need to ask you how you do something I can't. The above write-up list flights, names of passengers,etc. IF I PUT THAT I AM CENSORED AND MY COMMENTS REMOVED IN LESS THAN 10 SECONDS. How do you do it. I never post anything I havent verified through released offical info. I am a Boeing lover and hate when you can do something I can't?? Nothing against you at all. Yahoo allow me to post like others please. I have good info, not lies. Spreading false stock info is a no no big time. So listing sources and giving them credit is like a footnote in a book. TRY READING MY POSTS---IF YOU DID YOU WOULD REALIZE I AM AN ASSET TO THE BOARD. I NOW DONT LIST NAMES OR NOTHING JUST HERE SAY LIKE THEY WANT AND I AM STILL CENSORED. ANY THOUGHTS. NEED A MANAGER INVOLVED TO ASK CENOR WHY THEY REMOVED MY PLAIN VANILLA POSTS. They actually removed when i said I heard the 787 is best in the sky and lets passengers arrive refreshed with the better air.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369099035959</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369099911081-166</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight to BA in Chicago today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369058454499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at another plain vanilla doesn't break one rule from posting board comments, but was censored??? Why??? "Things occurring to Boeing and Airbus planes are normal for any commercial or military plane. Don't get so alarmed at what is normal for people in the industry. Planes go through normal learning curves, upgrades, updates, obsolesense issues, matienance issues etc etc etc. Normal." WHY WAS THIS CENSORED. ITS A TRUE STATEMENT OF A NORMAL PLANES DEVELOPMENT. if you can help, it would be great. So much good stuff to report that keeps getting censored.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369099911081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369100776951-167</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If anyone's "brain" needs to washed, it's Sparty's</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1369100776951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369100980388-168</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not trying to put you down, but the statement in your origional post leads me to believe you were saying Boeing only went up 17% in 5 years and were comparing it to JASO ""Eventually, you will be able to make more than 17 per cent on a stock in 5 years like what you have made on Boeing, " It was up over 17% in that time period, that was the reason for my post.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369100980388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 21:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369102038354-169</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sane progressives? HAHAHA Sane folks don't support communists having a major influence in governing America. Sane folks don't support ACORN, or have an anti-American as their minister for 20 years.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1369102038354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369103384418-170</Id><Title>United to put all 787's in air this week</Title><Msg>Thing seem to be going fine IMHO. Can't wait to fly on one.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369103384418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369103552788-171</Id><Topic><Title>PPS</Title><Username>moanawai</Username><Timestamp>1369089509878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:38:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That should be the real break-out IMHO</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369103552788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369104000278-172</Id><Topic><Title>United to put all 787's in air this week</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369103384418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:29:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How in the world can this be censored too. HELP. No links listed. No names of source. So what is wrong with this post to. MANAGER OR SUPERVISOR PLEASE HELP</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369104000278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369104216494-173</Id><Topic><Title>United to put all 787's in air this week</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369103384418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:29:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>try to NOT post names of passengers or any private person NOT already in public dont know what you are trying to post- but THINK - read the Fine rules ...</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1369104216494</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:43:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369104334656-174</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven lunatic: "If anyone's "brain" needs to washed, it's Sparty's" Your dozens of IDs and your unrelenting propaganda are trying Bagdad Bob...but failing miserably</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369104334656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:45:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369104629169-175</Id><Topic><Title>HOOZDIKs post on obstruction of Obamacare is one big LIE !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1368967069760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 08:37:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go back to the Commune ..... Barrys Great Leap forward into National Bankruptcy...a 5 year plan of one disaster after another....Barrys "Cultural Revolution" of despotism.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369104629169</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369104817521-176</Id><Title>Report: DOJ Leaked Docs to Smear Fast &amp; Furious Whistleblower, Says IG</Title><Msg>Matthew Boyle Breitbart May 20, 2013 United States Attorney for the District of Arizona, Dennis K. Burke. The Department of Justice (DOJ) Inspector General published a new report Monday that confirms former U.S. Attorney for Arizona Dennis Burke leaked a document intended to smear Operation Fast and Furious scandal whistleblower John Dodson. The DOJ IG said it found “Burke’s conduct in disclosing the Dodson memorandum to be inappropriate for a Department employee and wholly unbefitting a U.S. Attorney.” “We are referring to OPR our finding that Burke violated Department policy in disclosing the Dodson memorandum to a member of the media for a determination of whether Burke’s conduct violated the Rules of Professional Conduct for the state bars in which Burke is a member,” the IG wrote</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369104817521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369105620032-177</Id><Topic><Title>JA Solar Earnings Send Stock Up 73% much better than Boeing in one day too</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369089369760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 18:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx , I will answer this leads me to believe statement , once more if yoru going to comment on my users statement then please read me , I have repeatedly stated i use a world recognized chart system that is free CNN money , I do not know if CNN money adds in dividends or any of your additions for all I know it is computed into the CNN stock chart, Do you know different ? Once more do me the courtesy of following me if your going to make a point . At least read up on me. It sound like you are studing me so do a complete job . My statments are 100% true and factual unless I make an honest mistake. I am always making this kind of return because I AM A SWING TRADER AND I HAVE OVER 30 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE. READ UP ON HART SMITH , READ UP ON WHY md WENT BANKRUPT, READ UP ON WHAT HAPPENED WHEN THE bOEING ceo SAID THE CUSTOMER WOULD WAIT FOR THE 737MAX, THE MAKE WORK SOCIALIST air Bus COMPANY IS BEATING BOEING FOR 11 YEARS NOW AND BOEING PRIOR TO BUYING MD WAS THE CLEAR LEADER IN THE WORLD ITS ALL ABOUT THE m BUSINESS PLAN APPLIED TO BOEING IT WILL AND IS FAILING THE 787 IS THE FIRST EXAMPLE LATE BY 4 YEARS OVER BUDGET BY 30 BILLION AND NO CONTROL OVER THE ENGINEERING WILL ONLY LEAD TO MORE PROBLEMS I AM PRETTY SURE OF THIS WAIT AND WATCH THIS FAILURE IS NOT DONE YET</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369105620032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369106668362-178</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt that your adversary has ever used WND, Breitbart, Orly Taitz,, or "Google it" as an attempt to transform something into fact. Therefore, the failure is 100% yours without any question.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1369106668362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369107300890-179</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369094634580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:03:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember when you used to rail against the crimes of Bush. Now you celebrate the crimes of Obama. He's turned you into a hypocrite. Mission accomplished.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369107300890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369107426824-180</Id><Topic><Title>New poll reveals half of Americans wants Obama impeached</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1369012709636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because that means continued growth for the military-industrial-complex and the National Security State?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1369107426824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>