<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366099239740-1</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats are also taxing generations un-born by borrowing staggeringly huge sums of money to support out of control spending, thus taxing them with out representation, thus enslaving them since they had no say in the matter either personally, or by legal representation . This is the evil of large, long term public debt . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366099239740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 04:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366108508125-2</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=Bush kept us safe for 8 years, = Only a completely ignorant moron could come up with something like that.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1366108508125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 06:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366109862958-3</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Believe Gun Registration Will Result in Confiscation</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365616330577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 13:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it bump it bump it bump it bump it bump it bump it bump it</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366109862958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 06:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366109956033-4</Id><Topic><Title>Africa: The Growing Campaign to Revoke Obama’s Nobel Peace Prize</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365379617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 20:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5th year of peace ? Is that why Barry Soetoro is responsible for TWICE the deaths in Afganistan then under George Bush ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366109956033</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 06:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366114748117-5</Id><Title>Obama 'Only' Reads New York Times, Former Adviser Says</Title><Msg>President Obama's media diet has been of interest to journalists since he entered office in 2008. The president has previously discussed perusing major newspapers including New York Times, Washington Post and Wall Street Journal. But according to a new piece in The New Republic Monday, the president has only one publication on his mind. "There’s only one paper the president reads, that’s The New York Times," a former Obama adviser was quoted as saying in Noam Scheiber's article titled, "Get Rich or Deny Trying: How to make millions off Obama." -The Huffington Post- ___________________________________________ One of the things that Barry didn't lie about was the fact that he is lazy. He admitted he was a lazy person and this is further confirmation of his true nature. Reading only the NYT is akin to living in a mental bunker, a merry-go-round of bias reinforcement, a world of limited perspective. Barry has far more in common with W than I thought and I joked that Barry was Bush 44. It's not such a joke after all.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366114748117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366116519766-6</Id><Title>good news for Boeing (BA)</Title><Msg>A bit of good news for Boeing (BA) on a day when the FAA orders 737 tail plane inspections: U.S.... Monday, April 15, 4:41 PM ET A bit of good news for Boeing (BA) on a day when the FAA orders 737 tail plane inspections: U.S. Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood, who previously called the company's battery fix "a good plan," says a decision on getting the 787 Dreamliner back into service will come "soon."</Msg><Username>cnarntz</Username><Timestamp>1366116519766</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366116735269-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 'Only' Reads New York Times, Former Adviser Says</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366114748117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should be no surprise. And all the while he has his henchmen out trying to censor responsible journalism.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366116735269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366117116962-8</Id><Title>Jeeferies says $116.00 stock price raised$$$$</Title><Msg>Go Boeing now get that 787 up in the Air$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366117116962</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366117198472-9</Id><Topic><Title>good news for Boeing (BA)</Title><Username>cnarntz</Username><Timestamp>1366116519766</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:48:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also Jefferies raised the price target to $116.00 a share$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366117198472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366117800149-10</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Believe Gun Registration Will Result in Confiscation</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365616330577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 13:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the result of Canadian gun registration and enforcement is that there are less than 1/3 the gun deaths per capita Canadian gun deaths vs American gun deaths</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366117800149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366117899311-11</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Believe Gun Registration Will Result in Confiscation</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365616330577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 13:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny-- Airplanes are registered-- has the gummint confiscated the airplanes? Cars are registered- has the gummint confiscated the cars Trucks are registered- has the gummint confiscated the cars HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366117899311</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366118041150-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 'Only' Reads New York Times, Former Adviser Says</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366114748117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Considering that Barry had about 3 times as many brains as W you had better reconsider your reconsideration</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366118041150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366118131769-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 'Only' Reads New York Times, Former Adviser Says</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366114748117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why dont you cite just one example of the gummint trying to censor journalism- lies are lies even if yours is the result of your mild retardation and paranoid schizophrenia</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366118131769</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366118593868-14</Id><Topic><Title>Buy the Dips boys$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366040322701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>screwed did you time the bottom yesterday??</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366118593868</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:23:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366118770491-15</Id><Title>How will Barry Blame Bush for the Bombing?</Title><Msg>Democrats think Barry is infallible, socialism is good, trillion dollar deficits are really just stimulus-es and 40 million Americans out of work is a great economy.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366118770491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366120542084-16</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOOK AT AT ALL THE LAME CONSERVATIVES POINTING FINGERS AND PASSING BLAME YOU`RE ALL A BUNCH OF LOSERS AND LIARS. at a time when the country should be coming together you AS#h0les have to be more negative than ever GET THE Fok out of this country you little p r icks.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366120542084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 09:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366120884672-17</Id><Title>An Abortionist's Unglamorous Victims</Title><Msg>He’s allegedly killed more people than Jeffrey Dahmer and John Wayne Gacy combined, but most Americans have never heard of him. Two years ago, Philadelphia authorities raided Kermit Gosnell’s inner-city abortion clinic on suspicion he was dealing prescription drugs. What they found there was unimaginably worse: bloodstained medical equipment, semi-conscious patients, cat feces, and dismembered fetal body parts in jars. Gosnell is now standing trial for the murders of one woman and seven infants, who allegedly had their spinal cords slit with scissors after being born alive. Former employees say he killed hundreds more. It’s all the stuff of a horror movie—and a media feeding frenzy. Instead, the mainstream media refused to cover the story until last week, and then only thanks to relentless pressure from pro-life activists. Why? Pro-lifers have speculated that journalists, being mostly liberal and pro-choice, were reluctant to shed any negative light on abortion in America—even illegal abortions performed by a sadistic, greedy “doctor.” There’s certainly plenty of that going on. Megan McArdle of The Daily Beast admitted it, writing, “I understand why my readers suspect me, and other pro-choice mainstream journalists, of being selective—of not wanting to cover the story because it showcased the ugliest possibilities of abortion rights. The truth is that most of us tend to be less inte It’s not hard to understand why viewers would avoid the Gosnell story. For starters, it exposes the gruesomeness of late-term abortions, which involve killing and dismembering fetuses in a much more brutal procedure (euphemistically called “dilation and evacuation”) than Gosnell’s method. Half of America voted for a president who supports late-term abortions, and voted against the Born Alive Infants Protection Act on the grounds that it would undermine abortion rights. Who wants to turn on CNN and confront such a reality? No, we prefer stories that titillate and entertain. We have wall-to-wall coverage of Jodi Arias, a lone nut who admits to killing her boyfriend in Arizona, but a blackout on Kermit Gosnell. And why wouldn’t we? The Arias trial involves nude pictures, kinky sex, and an attractive woman.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366120884672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366120975541-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make us you punk</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366120975541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366121037907-19</Id><Topic><Title>An Abortionist's Unglamorous Victims</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366120884672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:01:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You`re sick and a little weasel typical for conservatives these days.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366121037907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366121096708-20</Id><Topic><Title>Buy the Dips boys$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366040322701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. I'm waiting.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366121096708</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366121271226-21</Id><Topic><Title>63 % of Americans Doubt Michele Obama is part Gorilla</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1365178143567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She isn't as intelligent as most gorillas.....could be a baboon.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1366121271226</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366121410780-22</Id><Topic><Title>An Abortionist's Unglamorous Victims</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366120884672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:01:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you call him sick for reporting what a liberal paper wrote about what Democrats and the president have encouraged?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1366121410780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366121851430-23</Id><Title>The Gosnell trial and Democrat's Compassionate care for Women</Title><Msg>The Gosnell trial involves women seeking abortions in an inner-city chop shop. Karnamaya Mongar, the woman Gosnell killed during an abortion, was a 41-year-old Nepalese immigrant from one of Philadelphia’s worst neighborhoods. The vast majority of his patients were desperately poor women of color. (Former employees claim that when Gosnell received the rare white, middle-class patient, he’d bring her into a separate waiting room so she wouldn’t see the real condition of the clinic.) In short: this story took so long to break because no one cared about these women. “Sparse coverage shouldn't surprise us, despite the sensationalistic details of the Gosnell case, because horrific things happen to poor black people in urban areas all the time, and the press ignores them,” wrote Conor Friedersdorf of The Atlantic. As for Gosnell’s other victims, we have trouble seeing them as humans at all. “Truth be told, I don’t think these people consider abortion survivors as real people—or Gosnell a mass murderer,” pro-life blogger Jill Stanek wrote. “Calling Gosnell a ‘mass murderer’ for completing abortions outside the uterus brings them too close to pro-lifers who call abortionists mass murderers for completing abortions just a few inches the other way.” Before we condemn the “liberal media” for burying the story, we should ask ourselves if we really wanted to see it. In this case, the bias isn’t just the media’s—it’s ours.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366121851430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:17:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366122045379-24</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please remember the crash from a Boeing 737 Turkish Airlines in the Netherlands being quite similar.</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1366122045379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366122174427-25</Id><Topic><Title>An Abortionist's Unglamorous Victims</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366120884672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:01:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pay4ity All the facts you present are suspect- grossly inaccurate or out right evil viscous lies and you are one of the worst of the liars. Take a good look at yourself- see if there is anything worth saving and if there is get down on your knees and beg your God for forgiveness and find a way to make restitution for your evil ways before you arrive at the day of judgment</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366122174427</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366122248186-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 'Only' Reads New York Times, Former Adviser Says</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366114748117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be a clone of hooz as you don't know anything either and only offer made up nonsense. lol ______________________________________________________ According to a study W's IQ is 124.9 which is pretty close to Barry's IQ of 130 Presidential IQ, Openness, Intellectual Brilliance, and Leadership: Estimates and Correlations for 42 U.S. Chief Executives Author(s): Dean Keith Simonton Source: Political Psychology, Vol. 27, No. 4 (Aug., 2006), pp. 511-526 Published by: International Society of Political Psychology Accessed: 04/03/2010 02:53</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366122248186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366122467080-27</Id><Topic><Title>I know a person that saw Hillary without makeup</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366074386469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:06:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Bill, He is such a nice guy!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1366122467080</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366122931645-28</Id><Title>Despotic Marxist Regime</Title><Msg>returns bust of Churchill then snubs funeral for Margaret Thatcher, sending no one to pay respects.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366122931645</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366123119053-29</Id><Topic><Title>An Abortionist's Unglamorous Victims</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366120884672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:01:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because you`re sick #$%$ that do nothing but repeat negativity and create division, you`re liars , cheats and by far the biggest losers this country have.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366123119053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366123162224-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we may have to someday !</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366123162224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366123280134-31</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahkmed, whats the President gonna call this one...sporting event violence?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366123280134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:41:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366123375774-32</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we know he's a phony and a marxist, but is he African or American?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366123375774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366123543152-33</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Conservative being honest , did hell freeze over ?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366123543152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366123574122-34</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a racist would criticize Obama -- is that what you are saying? Keep it up -- most people in the country are beyond fed up with libs pulling out the race card ad nauseum to cover up failed policies</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1366123574122</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366123794775-35</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One lib lies, and another swears by it...too funny. Has nothing to do with racism. There are Black Champions in the GOP. But they are Pro-American, free market capitalists that want health and prosperity for all Amiericans, self determining Americans not the crony capitlaism under Obama that just rewards his rich, liberal supporters, and traps the poor into feeding at the big govt liberal trough.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366123794775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366123965123-36</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The weakest kid on the block has no qualms about t aking on Obama. Obama doesn't even have the backbone to call our enemies by name, radical jiihadist Muslims.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366123965123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366124070365-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 'Only' Reads New York Times, Former Adviser Says</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366114748117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama himself has spoken out against the evil being perpetrated by Fox News, and Rush L. Usually he speaks with forked tongue, and then has his thugs do the dirty work.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366124070365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366124587062-38</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please! A guy like you should never use the word honest. You are just a modern day NASI.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1366124587062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366125110826-39</Id><Title>Why are White Liberals such Racist</Title><Msg>It's obvious white liberals don't think people of color should or can think for themselves. Look at the way they treat a black conservative. They view them as runaway slaves that need to be punished for not being in lock step with the rest of the plantation votes. But when conservative white people treat people of color no differently than they would a white person.....it's the white liberals who want to play the race card.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366125110826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366125374317-40</Id><Title>Axelrod: Obama Thinks Boston Bombings Could Be Related to 'Tax Day'</Title><Msg>In explaining why President Obama didn't call the Boston bombings a "terrorist attack," former adviser David Axelrod said, "I'm sure what was going through the president's mind is -- we really don't know who did this -- it was tax day": The Blog Axelrod: Obama Thinks Boston Bombings Could Be Related to 'Tax Day' 10:01 AM, Apr 16, 2013 • By DANIEL HALPER Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts In explaining why President Obama didn't call the Boston bombings a "terrorist attack," former adviser David Axelrod said, "I'm sure what was going through the president's mind is -- we really don't know who did this -- it was tax day": "The word has taken on a different meaning since 9/11," Axelrod said of the phrase "terrorist attack." "You use those words and it means something very specific in people's mind. And I'm sure what was going through the president's mind is -- we really don't know who did this -- it was tax day. Was it someone who was pro--you know, you just don't know. And so I think his attitude is, let's not put any inference into this, let's just make clear that we're going to get the people responsible."</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366125374317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366125376555-41</Id><Topic><Title>Why are White Liberals such Racist</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366125110826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The most obvious racists in this country are Blacks. Not all for sure, as many are now Republicans. If they are democrats, and get into politics, they are generally racists. They make no bones about being racists. Their NAACP organization is full of racist hate mongering.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366125376555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:16:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366126069128-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why are White Liberals such Racist</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366125110826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The first reaction of the guilty racist or criminal is for the perp to project his guilt on the innocent as well as the population at large. that would be you hope4 .. keep in mind you crooks dont fool anybody</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366126069128</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366126185006-43</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are the people who admire Ben Carson but criticize Barry, racists? Are the people who praise Barry but attack Ben Carson racists? Hooz will you ever grow up or are you content being an immature fanatical turd polisher idolizing a phony and imagining everyone is a racist because they aren't on their knees for Barry like you are?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366126185006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366126381476-44</Id><Title>Morality of Taxation</Title><Msg>Let me start off by referring to the U.S. Constitution, or what I prefer to call the citizen's rule book. To say something meaningful about taxation one must also say something about expenditures. I know that nowadays one risks being labeled an extremist if he looks to the Constitution for guidance about what the federal government should be doing, but I will happily accept that risk. Article I, Section 8 of our Constitution is very relevant to today's discussion. Article I, Section 8 begins by granting Congress authority to lay and collect taxes. In the passages that follow, it enumerates a broad category of activities (namely nineteen) for which Congress has spending authority for which it can use its taxing authority. Among those activities, for those who have not bothered to inspect, are common defense, coinage of money, establish of post offices and courts. I have not done the numbers but I am guessing that the amount of money necessary for Congress to pay for these constitutionally, and by the way moral, authorized functions of the federal government would come to no more than $400 billion or so at the most. Obviously, that amount differs significantly from today's expenditure level of $1.6 trillion. Even that expenditure figure does not capture total spending because we have an underground government - the so-called "off-budget" expenditures as well as government-mandated spending by its citizens - such as ADA, OSHA, EPA dictates. I do not believe that we can restore government to its proper role in a free society by focusing our energies on the revenue side of the equation. In saying this, I in no way wish to demean the yeoman-like efforts of all those who worked to come up with a better method of taxation. I do not mind being corrected, if I am totally off base, but I see the debate between the flat tax, national sales tax and our current tax code as essentially one of which is the best way for government to subjugate its citizens? That is, of course, not a totally meaningless question because, given that we are going to accept subjugation, there are, I suppose, preferable methods to be subjugated. The debate over the form of taxation we should have legitimates the level of government spending. It is spending, not taxation, that is the true measure of the burden of government. After all there is no necessary reason why government has to tax in the first place. At one extreme Congress could acquire all the resources it needs simply by printing currency. Or Congress could borrow and require citizens and other entities to hold a portion of their holdings in government securities. Of course there would be severe problems associated with either of those methods but the point is that government spending, not taxation, is the proper measure of the burden of government activity. That is the major problem that needs to be addressed. Throughout most of our nation's history, up to the beginning of the twentieth century, the federal government spent no more than three or four percent of the nation's output except during war times. During that interval, it did not make much of a difference what form of taxation supported federal government activity. In fact, excise taxes carried the burden. But even if we had today's income tax code, there would not have been much of a problem. In other words, if federal spending is only three or four percent of the GNP, almost any kind of a tax system is not going to impose that much of a burden. And I am sure, were that the case, we would not be gathered here today to discuss substituting a flat tax for the current code. Some might ask what congressional spending should be cut so that we would not have to worry about the form of taxation. A French philosopher, Frederic Bastiat, gave us the best guide, in a little book titled, The Law, wherein he suggested a way of identifying legal plunder saying, "See if the law takes from some persons what belongs to them, and gives it to other persons to whom it does not belong. See if the law benefits one citizen at the expense of another by doing what the citizen himself cannot do without committing a crime." Clearly, at least two-thirds of all federal spending fits Bastiat's description of legal plunder or what I call legalized theft. So if we eliminated legal plunder from the scope of congressional activity, the form of taxation could easily be a non-issue. Some may wish to quarrel with my description of Congress' business as legal plunder. If you do so, just ask yourselves how does Congress get money for, say, farm subsidy programs, S&amp;L bailouts or foodstamp programs. It uses intimidation, threats and coercion to take what rightfully belongs to one citizen and gives it to another to whom it does not belong. The mission of virtually every cabinet department is to distribute the loot. There is neither moral or constitutional authority for Congress to commit plunder As evidenced my remarks, I am a purist or what the news media and maybe even some of you might call an extremist. But I am not so much of a purist that I cannot see that a flat tax is a major improvement over the status quo. But if there is a flat tax enacted, there should be a supermajority vote required to increase the rate, say, four fifths of both houses and a simple majority to decrease the rate. My reason is quite simple. Like the Framers of our constitution, I do not trust Congress. With the current complex tax code, there are numerous legal ways to hide our money from the revenuers. With a simple flat tax, those hideaways would be eliminated. Then, if Congress raised taxes we would be up that proverbial creek without a paddle. Walter E. Williams</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126381476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366126608689-45</Id><Topic><Title>Why are White Liberals such Racist</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366125110826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zosima....how many days old were you when your momma dropped you on your head......from a second story window?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126608689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366126748422-46</Id><Topic><Title>Morality of Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126381476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The biggest lack of responsibility from bureaucrats, especially liberals like Obama, is they view your hardworking tax dollars as theirs with no thought of spending it wisely, and not wasting it.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366126748422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366126806969-47</Id><Topic><Title>Despotic Marxist Regime</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366122931645</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumper err despotic err censored err prevaricating again err Thatcher err wicked witch is dead err spaz</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1366126806969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366126989621-48</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair vindicated, Robert Braddock Jr. Sinclair lie detector administrator indicted, Obama is a switch hitter Michelle let Fraud out</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366125786902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are polygraph tests normally admitted in court?</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1366126989621</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366127063748-49</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This changes everything. Big crowds in small places. Always in the back of your mind.</Msg><Username>catiaguy</Username><Timestamp>1366127063748</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366127151791-50</Id><Topic><Title>I Made An Offer</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366124538256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Let's add that to the charges and help veterans!" What charge? Felony gay?</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1366127151791</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366127543725-51</Id><Title>Hyphenated Americans are the Best Americans</Title><Msg>Dumb ole Unhyphenated Americans are always racist and stuff.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1366127543725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366127820322-52</Id><Topic><Title>Why are White Liberals such Racist</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366125110826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whatsamatta ignorant racist #$%$ ? does the truth have a little sting for you</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366127820322</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366128569992-53</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In mine too.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1366128569992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366128627983-54</Id><Title>If I move to South America, Will I be An American-American</Title><Msg>I really want to be A Hyphenated American .....They're so good ...and everything. But I was born an unhyphenated-American...If I put the word" Unhyphenated "in front of the word " American " and put a hyphen between them, and refer to myself as such, does that qualify me to be a hyphenated American .....All Unhyphenated Americans hate hyphenated Americans.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1366128627983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366128701286-55</Id><Topic><Title>Morality of Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126381476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldnt have thought less of you hope4- a maximum effort to debase taxation and weasel out of your responsibility as a citizen to pay your taxes and leave everyone else support you. You might as well be a welfare bum living off the dole. If you are really serious about taxes there are still two or three places in Africa where you wouldnt have to pay taxes- we would buy you a free ticket to travel and immigrate- one way of course</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366128701286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:11:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366129003774-56</Id><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Msg>Mentions for the Boston Bombers. Islamic extremist, Right wing extremist, Conspiracy theorist, Lone wolf extremist. Doesn't mention Left wing extremist such as Ayers and Dorn, or the Chicago bunch etc. Yes its very strange.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366129057259-57</Id><Title>Remember Tax Avoidance is Legal, Tax Evasion is Criminal</Title><Msg>When liberals, Democrats and other anti-Americans criticize anyone for avoiding paying higher taxes, what they they really are saying is, "you have not right to equal protection under the law."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366129057259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366129898046-58</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair vindicated, Robert Braddock Jr. Sinclair lie detector administrator indicted, Obama is a switch hitter Michelle let Fraud out</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366125786902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He won't "get" that. (Good point, though :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366129898046</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366131197511-59</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair vindicated, Robert Braddock Jr. Sinclair lie detector administrator indicted, Obama is a switch hitter Michelle let Fraud out</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366125786902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Won't matter a bit to gregjane. He simply has some weird erotic fantasy about the President and enjoys reading this stuff. I wonder what Google search phrase he used?</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1366131197511</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366131411761-60</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't Hillary involved with that left wing extremist group?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366131411761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366131718118-61</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair vindicated, Robert Braddock Jr. Sinclair lie detector administrator indicted, Obama is a switch hitter Michelle let Fraud out</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366125786902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It surely is admissible in the court of public opinion. Barry's fanatics accepted Larry's failed polygraph exam as evidence that he lied about his affair with Barry. I say good for Larry. He is lucky not to be taking a dirt nap like the Trinity gay members that rolled with Barry before he ran for president. This indictment damages the credibility of the polygraph examiner and helps Larry's story. Sinclair has beaten Axelrod and Obama in every attempt by them to silence him. They couldn't stop the book and they couldn't stop the videos detailing Barry's involvement in #$%$ and drugs. Eventually Obama's past will catch up with him. Barry is far more flawed than Bush and Barry is spending millions to try to conceal all his skeletons.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366131718118</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366131746015-62</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe because it has been over 40 years since the groups you want mentioned have done anything like that, while the other groups have all used bombs in fairly recent memory. Moron</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1366131746015</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366131812527-63</Id><Title>Taxes of $14 on last Year's Income Seem a lot for a minimum wage job</Title><Msg>A Cayman Island corporation that manages 3 cayman Island trusts that have extensive income producing assets in the U.S. A. pays someone a minimum wage salary, requires him to live in and care for a 14,000 sf home on 3,200 acres of farm land with oil and gas wells on and manage two other ranches in a neighboring state and two large medical clinics. It's a lot of responsibility for minimum wages but having all expense paid and an unlimited expense account helps ease the pain. Of course there are some taxes on the income produced by the U.S assets and business activity but that is greatly reduced by depletion allowances, depreciation and management fees paid to a Cayman Island corporation. However, passive income from assets owned by one of the trusts in not subject to any income tax even though that income was 9 figures +. Makes one almost thankful for good Democrats like the Kennedy family who made all this possible. "The Kennedy fortune is locked into a complex series of family trusts based in Fiji, first started by the patriarch, Joe Kennedy. The labyrinth of trusts, which dole out only a small amount of money annually to the large Kennedy clan, are invested conservatively and run by financial experts whose goal is to maintain the principal." And just thank, we never have to worry about inheritance tax because trusts don't die. Legally avoiding taxes is something most wealthy Democrats regard as a sport. So wealthy conservatives like myself might as well join in and play the game with them. And don't forget you can still qualify for food stamps in the process.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366131812527</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366131819155-64</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course- and so was Barry Sortero- and also the current Executive Director of SPEEA- who published a marxist newsletter and was proud of the Battle in Seattle !! Google his name and marxist and battle of seattle for the doubters !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1366131819155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132132463-65</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it's a right wing nut job....it will be condemned by conservatives. If it's a left wing lunatic or a mu slum, Democrats will defend, support him and scream, "it's George Bush's fault."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366132132463</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:08:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132429193-66</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>911 didn't count. It was Georgies "have it to do over again", aka, a Texas Mulligan. After all this C- gradgiate was only in office for a mere 7 months and 22 days. If some country would have nuked the USA during Georgie's first 7 months and 22 days would have been entitled another "do over again" or Texas Mulligan. Georgie was to busy teach kids how to spell 'potatoe'. "Now chillian's fur definication that can also be knowed as a 'poh tated toe', and you don't want to git that kinda disceese". "I be Mr. Presedent."</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1366132429193</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132432219-67</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Inteeresting - how long will it be before the lamestream media and some dimocrat congresscritters blame bush, teaparty etc- answer Rep king already blamed the right wing- and bernie s is using the event to say/push no cutting taxes and need bigger government. Obvioulslym the tea party bit will take a few minutes longer Question- who has the best record for causing such events ? Answer- Bill ayers and his ilk- all well documented and admitted read rules for radicals !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1366132432219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132690897-68</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for your typically useless diatribe. You and Sparty must be on the same hallucinogenic drugs.Or maybe, you are both just idiots and fools.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1366132690897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:18:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132728810-69</Id><Topic><Title>I Made An Offer</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366124538256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Felony gay?" stop it, your'e kill'in us here! rots ah raffs over that one.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1366132728810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132738808-70</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a funny DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366132738808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132767584-71</Id><Topic><Title>I Made An Offer</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366124538256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, one very funny DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366132767584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366132849957-72</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're just a bunch of high school kids with active imaginations.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1366132849957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366133075847-73</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give'em a break. As soon as they imagined what they would have accomplished going down swinging, they quickly decided to capitulate, unlike the IAM.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1366133075847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366133104441-74</Id><Title>John Kerry takes Global Hoax Conference to China</Title><Msg>priorities priorities CHICOMs are in agreement, destroy the USA</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366133104441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366133231058-75</Id><Title>Obamas and Bids Avoid paying their Fair Share</Title><Msg>Well, they don’t voluntarily. Today, the Obama’s and Biden’s tax returns were released by the White House. The President and First Lady earned over $600 thousand, while the Vice President and wife earned over $385 thousand. The irony or hypocrisy (whichever way you want to call it) was that the Obama’s only paid a 18.4% tax rate (federal), and the Biden’s a 22.8% rate. Obama tried to use this opportunity to push for higher taxes, so that “he would pay more in taxes while ensuring we cut taxes for the middle class and those trying to get in it.” Wait, what? Where in the world was he required to pay the 18.4% or Biden the 22.8%? They voluntarily chose to accept all those deductions our massive tax code allows.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133231058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366133798268-76</Id><Topic><Title>Despotic Marxist Regime</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366122931645</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:35:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump for the communists, their dear leader is showing his true colors even chavez got state sponsored travelers</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366133798268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366133917657-77</Id><Topic><Title>Morality of Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126381476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"welfare bum living off the dole" that would be genna.....zosima you're very confused as usual.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133917657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366134190133-78</Id><Topic><Title>Lest We Forget – Hillary’s $100K Cattle Scam</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133741204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>far as i can tell there is no threshold for impropriety / crime which dumbocrats won't forgive, even elevate, fellow dumbocrats</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366134190133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366134437212-79</Id><Topic><Title>Lest We Forget – Hillary’s $100K Cattle Scam</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133741204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must really be desperate to have to reach back almost 20 years to find some fodder for your smear campaign. Nothing says "loser" like your desperate attempts to try and point a finger.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1366134437212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366134467783-80</Id><Title>Has Anyone Noticed the more Corrupt, Dishonest and Immoral a Politician is......</Title><Msg>the more popular they are with Democrats......Clintons, Kennedy and Obama come to mind.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366134467783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366134606842-81</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry takes Global Hoax Conference to China</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366133104441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kerry has nothing substantive with respect to reducing GHG emissions. It's all smoke and mirrors to make it seem as if Kerry is actually accomplishing something. The Chinese are happy to play Kerry for the fool that he is and they will try to get more technology secrets out of him like they were able to get from Gore. Listening to Kerry it is clear to me he is 15 years behind on his understanding of climate science and he sounds like the folk tale character "Chicken Little" in his silly comments.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366134606842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366134948649-82</Id><Topic><Title>Lest We Forget – Hillary’s $100K Cattle Scam</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133741204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps you don't remember how Democrats and other ant-Americans reached back more than 20 years to use a DUI against George Bush or how they reached back 20 years and fabricated a fraudulent letter about his NG service. At least it got Dan Blather fired.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366134948649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366135156724-83</Id><Topic><Title>John Kerry takes Global Hoax Conference to China</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366133104441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:25:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Embarrassing to have liberals representing us. China meanwhile will soon pass the USA in GDP growth, and improve the health and welfare of the Chinese, as they become capitalists while we continue to decline...sad.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366135156724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366135558232-84</Id><Topic><Title>Why are White Liberals such Racist</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366125110826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White liberals can't engage in truthful or logical dialog so, the easiest weapon they have is pulling the race card. The know it's an admission of intellectual bankruptcy but they also know their message plays well to low information and low IQ voters.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366135558232</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366135849862-85</Id><Topic><Title>Morality of Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126381476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Morality and the Constitution are two things the the Democrats prefer to ignore in their quest to "fundamentally transform" the USA into a socialist/fascist state.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366135849862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366136161084-86</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Noticed the more Corrupt, Dishonest and Immoral a Politician is......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366134467783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:47:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup.....Marion Barry, Ray Nagin and cold Cash Jefferson were all re-elected in spite of their corruption and incompetence which was evident at the time of their re-election.......or maybe it was just the result of playing the race card.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366136161084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366136409594-87</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Noticed the more Corrupt, Dishonest and Immoral a Politician is......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366134467783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:47:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its Mir i`m a #$%$ k head morgons spewing his hate, lies and propaganda and wishing he sold his gold earlier. lmao</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366136409594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366136532510-88</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the Nelson Mandela syndrome. Once Mandela was let out of prison an entire movement died. Paul could end this once and for all, but never did because for that reason. But it didn't help his side win.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1366136532510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:22:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366136631321-89</Id><Topic><Title>Why are White Liberals such Racist</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366125110826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hopey dopey is a programed fool he probably does not even understand or comprehend most of the pre programed propaganda he spews he just repeats the top GOP talking/hating points of the day.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366136631321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366137213927-90</Id><Topic><Title>Okay, So It's Pure Racism Against An African-American President</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366123133697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the only one assuming that the hate for Obama is based on racism. The "he'snot an American" slant can be based solely on Barry's actions in showing contempt for the constitution and to sane people it doesn't have to be based on racism. You are the only one displaying racist tendencies in this thread as you are the one projecting racist motives onto others with not one shred of evidence and based only on your paranoia as a fanatic trying to protect your boy Barry. You are incapable of rational objective assessment of Barry's actions, like my brothers new schnauzer pup, but at least the schnauzer doesn't see everyone else as a racist like you do when they criticize Barry. You are loony tunes on this racist nonsense Hooz.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366137213927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366137640698-91</Id><Topic><Title>Lest We Forget – Hillary’s $100K Cattle Scam</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133741204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you are telling me your standard for acceptable behavior is a 3rd grade "he did it too!"? Nothing says more about your lack of character than your own posts.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1366137640698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366138136822-92</Id><Topic><Title>Lest We Forget – Hillary’s $100K Cattle Scam</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133741204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying it was acceptable for Democrats to lie and cheat if it was 20 years ago. There is a difference between someone like Bush who admitted he was wrong and needed to change and did and someone like the the Clintons who maintain denial or only admit they're wrong when exposed to the point they have no choice.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366138136822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366138421839-93</Id><Topic><Title>Lest We Forget – Hillary’s $100K Cattle Scam</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133741204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=Nothing says more about your lack of character than your own posts.= So very true of mirde [sic].</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1366138421839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366138772478-94</Id><Title>Cattle Futures, Vince Foster, Rose Law Firm Records and Benghazi</Title><Msg>.....Prove several things but most importantly that Hillary has been a liar and a conniver all her life and people getting killed because of it has never phased her. Benghazi proves it's not a 20 year old thing and some animals never change their stripes. In Hillary's case she should be wearing stripes....literally.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366138772478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366139309590-95</Id><Title>HILLARY CLINTON STORIES</Title><Msg>FIRST FIRST LADY to come under criminal investigation FIRST FIRST LADY to almost be indicted according to one of the special prosecutors NUMBER of Hillary Clinton fundraisers convicted of, or pleading no contest to, crime: 5 NUMBER OF TIMES that Hillary Clinton, providing testimony to Congress, said that she didn't remember, didn't know, or something similar: 250 NUMBER OF CLOSE BUSINESS partners of Hillary Clinton who ended up in prison: 3. The Clintons' two partners in Whitewater wereconvicted of 24 counts of fraud and conspiracy. Hillary Clinton's partner and mentor at the Rose law firm, Webster Hubbell, pleaded guilty to federal mail fraud and tax evasion charges, including defrauding former clients and former partners out of more than $480,000. Hillary Clinton was mentioned 35 times in the indictment. IN THE 1980s, Hillary Clinton made a $44,000 profit on a $2,000 investment in a cellular phone franchise deal took advantage of the FCC's preference for locals, minorities and women. The franchise was almost immediately flipped to the cellular giant, McCaw. HILLARY CLINTON AND HER HUSBAND set up a resort land scam known as Whitewater in which the unwitting bought third rate property 50 miles from the nearest grocery store and, thanks to the sleazy financing, about half the purchasers, many of them seniors, lost their property. IN 1993 HILLARY CLINTON and David Watkins moved to oust the White House travel office in favor of World Wide Travel, Clinton's source of $1 million in fly-now-pay-later campaign trips that essentially financed the last stages of the campaign without the bother of reporting a de facto contribution. The White House fired seven long-term employees for alleged mismanagement and kickbacks. The director, Billy Dale, charged with embezzlement, was acquitted in less than two hours by the jury.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366139309590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366139646457-96</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY CLINTON STORIES</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366139309590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the Democrats want her to run for President! What in the world is the country coming to, first Obama then Hillary.......</Msg><Username>sayuthink</Username><Timestamp>1366139646457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366139720891-97</Id><Title>Why do Democrats Hate Children So Much?</Title><Msg>They're either trying to kill them before they're born or they're trying to spend them into a future of debt slavery.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366139720891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366140539624-98</Id><Topic><Title>Lest We Forget – Hillary’s $100K Cattle Scam</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1366133741204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 13:35:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you claiming to be a DFC?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366140539624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366141746923-99</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY CLINTON STORIES</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366139309590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what about Beghazi?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366141746923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366142152425-100</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY CLINTON STORIES</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366139309590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, Baby!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366142152425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366142275827-101</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>search for article {{Who's behind the Boston Marathon bombings? }} Mentions bombing the Federal Bldg in OKC as linking Timothy McVeigh as a right wing extremist. Timothy McVeigh would better be described as the lone wolf. He fit the left wing nuts just as well as the right wing nuts. So more liberal press blather.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366142275827</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366142316808-102</Id><Topic><Title>Cattle Futures, Vince Foster, Rose Law Firm Records and Benghazi</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366138772478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vince Foster? H. Clinton must have you right-fringers quaking in fear, unable to hold on to your bodily excretions. We can all have a big laugh, knowing how successful your hand-wringing was in the last election.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366142316808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366142370863-103</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY CLINTON STORIES</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366139309590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could be much worse, could be Bush II, Palin, Romney, Santorum, Perry, Bachmann, or Cain. The GOP is so screwed up they won't even seriously consider Huntsman because he doesn't pass their "Ideology" test (and he has too much brains). The Republiban won't tolerate any veering from their dogma. That is why we laugh at you.</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1366142370863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366142556130-104</Id><Topic><Title>Morality of Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126381476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm living off money I invested long ago in the U.S. Social Security Administration. For such a hotshot capitalist, you seem to have a lot of difficulty understaning this simple investment principle. Putz.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366142556130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:02:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366142830985-105</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair vindicated, Robert Braddock Jr. Sinclair lie detector administrator indicted, Obama is a switch hitter Michelle let Fraud out</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366125786902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the court of public opinion didn't have grave doubts about polygraphs, then they would be admissible in court. The jurors are supposed to be representative of public opinion. The lawyers struggle to achieve that. That's how we get free trials in this country. Why do you hate the Constitution?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366142830985</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366143334574-106</Id><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Msg>If not, how would you define involuntary servitude?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366143822229-107</Id><Topic><Title>Larry Sinclair vindicated, Robert Braddock Jr. Sinclair lie detector administrator indicted, Obama is a switch hitter Michelle let Fraud out</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366125786902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= Why do you hate the Constitution? = Touché.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366143822229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366144433335-108</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MIght be the only thing the 2nd Amendment is good for...</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366144433335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366144499525-109</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you get more bazzaro everyday there mir</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144499525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366144713894-110</Id><Title>The day after 911</Title><Msg>This country stood together and supported the President of the Untied States in his efforts to find the culprits and bring them to justice , today we have conservatives spewing hate and lies with lots of pre programed finger pointing conspiracy theory`s they have become a pathetic vocal minority in this country slowly fading away not fast enough.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366144724392-111</Id><Topic><Title>4 Theories , strange very strange</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1366129003774</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 12:16:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs jumped all over the bombing from the time the bombs went off politicizing the bombing as caused by right wingers. All kinds of speculation as to what right winger, or right wing group did it, and why. These folks definitely follow the preachings of their guru, Saul Alinsky.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366144724392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366145059978-112</Id><Title>Neo#$%$ and Fascist Right Wingers</Title><Msg>Timothy McVeigh is their hero.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1366145059978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366145675976-113</Id><Topic><Title>Morality of Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126381476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if gold keeps dropping Mir might have to ask for a hand out someday lmao</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366145675976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366145874697-114</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well.....c'mon libtards.....take a stab at it.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366145874697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366145913472-115</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speak for yourself, cowardly wuss.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1366145913472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366146625148-116</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They'll call you names, insult you and the really dumb ones will tell you it's a stupid question.......but they won't dare answer you.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1366146625148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366146802267-117</Id><Topic><Title>HILLARY CLINTON STORIES</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366139309590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:08:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Huntsman instead of a Democrat?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1366146802267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366147992688-118</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The silence is obviously an admission. But it makes one wonder if it's an admission of being cluless or fearful of exposing what they stand for.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366147992688</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366148209893-119</Id><Topic><Title>Morality of Taxation</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366126381476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many people have invested in socialism but few have gotten as rich as the politicians who sold the investment.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366148209893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366148238765-120</Id><Topic><Title>I Made An Offer</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366124538256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 11:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you living in 1952?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1366148238765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366148447748-121</Id><Topic><Title>Cattle Futures, Vince Foster, Rose Law Firm Records and Benghazi</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366138772478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoozdik.....how long has your nose been transplanted in chrissie's rectum?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366148447748</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366148503195-122</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They'll call you names, insult you" You must be used to that by now.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1366148503195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366148655804-123</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You certainly belong in the clueless category.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366148655804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366149024872-124</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You were already there.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1366149024872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366149179555-125</Id><Topic><Title>Cattle Futures, Vince Foster, Rose Law Firm Records and Benghazi</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366138772478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 14:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We can always tell when you trip-wire right-fringers run out of good temper, arguments, logic, and patience. You fall back on language that reflects tour perverted sens of sexuality, your fear of a manhood deficit. You call people gay, stupid, and refer to anatomical parts in controted positions. All in all, it sounds homoerotic. Do you dream of doing that to your boyfriend?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366149179555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366149300292-126</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The absence of an answer to loaded questions doesn't mean either of those thinhgs. It means we regard life as too valuable to waste on your river of tears. Elsewhere in the world, there are people reall suffering real mistreatment.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366149300292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 17:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366149722670-127</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK......that's one in the clueless category and one in the "fear of being exposed" category. Actually, Chrissie belongs in both categories.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366149722670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366149912515-128</Id><Title>Boeing stock goes noplace fast the 737 needs 1000 planes fixed and the 787 is not certified</Title><Msg>FAA said today no rush to help Boeing get the 787 into certification why does that guy keep letting the message board know the plane continues to fly without certification? That seems like pointing out a bad deal, not to mention Boeing stock has gone up less than five percent in five years while Airbus stock is up more than one hundred and five percent. With one thousand horizontal tails to remove and replace fasteners on the 737 line, that seems like a once great profit center is now less than ideal. Wow in the lst month arcadia is up more than seventy five percent and silver on a short sale is better than fifty percent gain. Why do these management enablers think that anything they do or say will help Boeing stock , IF Boeign can recommend that the Cessna airplane change from lithium to NiCad you would think Boeing would take the same remedy. The 787 is a instaflash lemon designed by foreign engineers .</Msg><Username>billboeing198</Username><Timestamp>1366149912515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366150007859-129</Id><Title>Democrats Obviously Still Believe in involuntary Servitude</Title><Msg>.......they're just not honest enough to say so.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150007859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366150278998-130</Id><Title>Chrissie is Hillarious wnen Confronted with Questions He Can't Answer</Title><Msg>His dodgyness is transparent and his attempts to save-face comical.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150278998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366150678227-131</Id><Topic><Title>Buy the Dips boys$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366040322701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking to reporters after the hearing, Huerta said the FAA is not currently considering granting the 787 approval to fly extended missions beyond 180 minutes. The jet had that level when it was grounded in January, and Boeing had been seeking approval for 330 minutes, allowing the plane to make the long-range missions over remote areas that it was designed to fly. Approval is pretty much a given to resume flying 180 minute legs and I believe is already priced into the stock. There may be a little bump but that will probably evaporate intra day. The institutional investors will quietly and slowly take there profits, short the stock and then start talking about the financial impact of the grounding will have on the bottom line to drive their play. At $79-80 bucks they will buy back in and issue upgrades to drive the price higher. Barring anymore battery issues this will be a $100 stock in the next twelve months. My entry will be as close to $80 as I can get. Earnings may be a squeaker with no 787 deliveries for the quarter and costs associated with the grounding so I don't see a big bump there either. At least they can pump out some aircraft during the next quarter.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366150678227</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366151078200-132</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait till all the facts are in before making judgements on what happened in Boston</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366151078200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366151560914-133</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock goes noplace fast the 737 needs 1000 planes fixed and the 787 is not certified</Title><Username>billboeing198</Username><Timestamp>1366149912515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell are you out to grant us the boone of your great aerospace knowledge yet again HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR ARHA RHAR HAR HAR AHR HARA HRA</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366151560914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366152088201-134</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Obviously Still Believe in involuntary Servitude</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150007859</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:06:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paying your taxes -- and probably paying far more taxes than you are paying now -- is not involuntary servitude, bozo. (You can always move.) Paying those taxes is meeting your MINIMUM obligations of living in the greatest, richest, and militarily strongest nation in the world. And believe, me, you'll only do the minimum.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366152088201</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366152411568-135</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must have bitten your tongue off to not launch off on some new "false flag" conspiracy fantasy (I refuse to call them "theories" anymore because that implies a level of sophistication NONE of them have, :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366152411568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366152624953-136</Id><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Msg>Boeing has proven by successfully completing flight tests with the redesigned lithium-ion battery that the 787 is flightworthy. But the FAA is delaying its approval to lift the ban on the 787. The FAA knows that every additional day delay is costing Boeing millions of dollars. There is no legitimate reason to keep the Dreamliner from flying. It a matter of the FAA wanting to stick it to Boeing.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366152835355-137</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I said...all the facts are not in. False Flag attacks have a pattern that blames a patsy early on in the OP.... because most of the population is almost as dumb and gullible as you are. For example. Lee Harvey Oswald was blamed for the murder of JFK WHILE he was STILL IN THE MOVIE THEATRE....Bin Ladin was blamed for the Twin Towers falling within MINUTES of the attacks.... ...that way the New World Order can control the narrative as early as possible...standard cointel PSYOP procedures.... I at least WAIT until most of the facts are in...there are some disturbing early trends but I will wait a week or so..</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366152835355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366152924940-138</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie is Hillarious wnen Confronted with Questions He Can't Answer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150278998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gennas M.O. is to protect his fragile Ego at all costs...no matter HOW ridiculous his arguments</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366152924940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366153180844-139</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie is Hillarious wnen Confronted with Questions He Can't Answer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150278998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you're a committed far leftist you have to learn to rope a dope. You bob and weave, fake low blows, play deaf and dumb which is real easy to do....anything to turn the attention away from you who can not support anything you support.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366153180844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366153764768-140</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Catiaguy (I used to know what CATIA stood for; then I retired and jettisoned that info to make room for things like the grandkids favorite colors :-) The U.S. went through a wave of sidewalk bombings in the 1920s. Then it was anarchists (and Italian-Americans!). Now the boogeyman is "mis lums." The FBI cracked down pretty quickly and the threat all but vanished until the late 1960s, then now. They did it without the Patriot Act and a police state, but I'm sure there was a lot less concern about suspect/perp rights in those days. After all, Ferdinando Sacco and Bartolomeo Vanzetti were executed, probably wrongly, for two murders in (gasp) Massachusettes -- but mostly for being anarchists. I do not like the Patriot Act -- it is power that no branch of our government will ever give up because it is so handy, and it passed only because we lacked the faith we need to have in our systems. (Like the ones that nailed the 1920s bombers.) But as restive as I am about the Patriot Act, I have to say that with it, the people who did this haven'g got a snowflake's chance in he11 of getting away with it. My bet is that they will be caught so quickly that Sparatacus will start howling it was a put-up job. Remember Timothy McVeigh. Of course, there will be others, but law enforcement will weed them out too. By the way, I haven't heard Wayn (K) e (R) Lapierre claim that citizens on the sidewalk with guns could have prevented the Boston bombings. That's disappointing! :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366153764768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366153969515-141</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie is Hillarious wnen Confronted with Questions He Can't Answer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150278998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366153969515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:12:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366154148135-142</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You posted this while I was writing a response to catiaguy. All I can say is, I called it! Or as YOU would say, "I shoot ... I score!" This perp/these perps will be caught faster than McVeigh was, because they're getting better and better at it, Spart -- that should be a lesson you should take to heart! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366154148135</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366154323612-143</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie is Hillarious wnen Confronted with Questions He Can't Answer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150278998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoozdik....are you Chrissie's crotch sniffer? When he makes a sharp turn to the left does your nose hurt?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1366154323612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366154770661-144</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a lot of data to review, including procedure for manufacturing and implementing the fix. Just because the planes flew doesn't mean the process is complete. There is no deliberate foot dragging going on.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366154770661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366154893702-145</Id><Topic><Title>Neo#$%$ and Fascist Right Wingers</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1366145059978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes perfect sense. McVeigh was a conservative, right wing, Republican NRA member.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1366154893702</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366154933900-146</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock goes noplace fast the 737 needs 1000 planes fixed and the 787 is not certified</Title><Username>billboeing198</Username><Timestamp>1366149912515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He can never change the sound of his voice.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366154933900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366155090195-147</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the problem? It's not a trick question.....it's a straight up simple question. I don't mind answering it. Yes, it is. According to wikipedia: Involuntary servitude is a United States legal and constitutional term for a person laboring against that person's will to benefit another, under some form of coercion other than the worker's financial needs. According to the Legal dictionary: Slavery; the condition of an individual who works for another individual against his or her will as a result of force, coercion, or imprisonment, regardless of whether the individual is paid for the labor. The term involuntary servitude is used in reference to any type of slavery, peonage, or compulsory labor for the satisfaction of debts. Two essential elements of involuntary servitude are involuntariness, which is compulsion to act against one's will, and servitude, which is some form of labor for another. Imprisonment without forced labor is not involuntary servitude, nor is unpleasant labor when the only direct penalty for not performing it is the withholding of money or the loss of a job.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1366155090195</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366155145284-148</Id><Topic><Title>Neo#$%$ and Fascist Right Wingers</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1366145059978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Unabomber was a left wing liberal nut like yourselves.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1366155145284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366155470330-149</Id><Title>Why are Democrats so Fearful of Answering Questions?</Title><Msg>Are they afraid answering simple question will expose the illegality of their left-wing dogma?</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1366155470330</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366155642768-150</Id><Title>Liberal Terrorist</Title><Msg>sends letter addressed to Republican Senator Roger Wicker of Mississippi tested positive for the poison ricin. This only shows you that Republicans are doing something right! Actions taken against them by the Leftist Radicals has every sign of Occupy Wall Street Anarchists! Never turn your back on a Leftist!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1366155642768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:40:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366155815580-151</Id><Title>Chrissie's Crotch Sniffer has a Love Affair with a Blow-up Doll</Title><Msg>.....the worst part is it's a male doll he calls Sir Paul.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1366155815580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366155901676-152</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The country stood together? Bull @#!@, I seem to recall that many liberals were blaming the Bush administration for orchestrating 9/11.</Msg><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1366155901676</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366157036459-153</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" All I can say is, I called it!" ... Called What ? The fact that you're short stroking your ego again ? You spurted ...you missed ...however in order to protect your fragile Ego...feel free to log in as the #$%$ and tell us all what a wonderful guy you are.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366157036459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366157556510-154</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boe5 made two more flights today at San Bernardino. The more they make, the more likely they will have enought data to satisfy the FAA. I suspect we will have news on granting flight staus to the 787 at teh earnings announcement.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366157556510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366158181608-155</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I called that you would start to scream about conspiracuies if they catch the perp/s too soo, and you were already laying the groundwork. Thanks for acknowledging how wonderful you think I am, but I don't kneed to have an alias like vendetta or jackripper to say it when I have you. What a loon! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366158181608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366158336372-156</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie is Hillarious wnen Confronted with Questions He Can't Answer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150278998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the dope we rope is the guy on the far far right, such as you.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366158336372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366158377707-157</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" called that you would start to scream about conspiracuies " The only problem with YOUR conspiracy is I never started one myself. I said WAIT TILL ALL THE FACTS ARE IN before rushing to judgement. To repeat my EALIER point...we need to WAIT ...the GOVERNMENT and the MSM rushes to judgement..hence my earlier comment... "For example. Lee Harvey Oswald was blamed for the murder of JFK WHILE he was STILL IN THE MOVIE THEATRE....Bin Ladin was blamed for the Twin Towers falling within MINUTES of the attacks.... ...that way the New World Order can control the narrative as early as possible...standard cointel PSYOP procedures"</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366158377707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366158487711-158</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie is Hillarious wnen Confronted with Questions He Can't Answer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150278998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and no matter HOW many times Genna logs in under the #$%$'s moniker....and AS USUAL...Hoozdik is hee when Genna is online...So predictable its pathetic</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366158487711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366158499429-159</Id><Topic><Title>Does Forcing One Man to Serve the Needs of another man = Involuntary Servitude?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366143334574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't mind aswering it either: Hahahahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366158499429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366158587555-160</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. You're just part of the lunatic echo chamber.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366158587555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366158774901-161</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: "... if they catch the perp/s too SOON,..."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366158774901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366159029513-162</Id><Topic><Title>The day after 911</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366144713894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>first you say I am showing restraint for NOT talking about Conspiracies...and then saying in the next post that I AM predicting a conspiracy over the BOston Marathon..all within Minutes. You are so driven by rage by getting your prodisious #$%$ handed to you that you cant think straight. ...You can have the last word loser...Im off to make love to my wife.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366159029513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366160558355-163</Id><Title>Is it wrong to Call a gay guy a Gay Guy?</Title><Msg>I don't think so.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1366160558355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366161248589-164</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We're on our own timetable in terms of completing the analysis," Huerta told reporters. "Once we're ready to move and make a determination, we will." He also told the committee the FAA was considering separately whether to certify Boeing's 787 for extended-range operations, known as ETOPS. The plane was approved for flights over remote areas of up to 180 minutes when it was grounded for two battery meltdowns in January. Before the grounding, Boeing had requested an upgrade to 330 minutes, but Huerta told reporters the agency was "not considering any expansion beyond that (180) at this time."</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1366161248589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366161706190-165</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie is Hillarious wnen Confronted with Questions He Can't Answer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1366150278998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz Chi Minh is running a one man psyop using multiple aliases. What a sick DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366161706190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366161751298-166</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Crotch Sniffer has a Love Affair with a Blow-up Doll</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1366155815580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:43:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366161751298</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366161836998-167</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am convinced the FAA and NTSB have no clue and do not possess the technical competence to make a decision on what is a real safety issue. The NTSB should be focusing their attention on automobile accidents that kill 35000 people per year. When was the last death caused by a airplane accident? Did anyone even get a scratch out of this battery issue? This is simply a political cya by bureaucrats so incompetent they cannot see the forest thru the trees.</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1366161836998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:23:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366162035430-168</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Terrorist</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1366155642768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:40:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals are DFC's.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366162035430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366163017669-169</Id><Topic><Title>Is it wrong to Call a gay guy a Gay Guy?</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1366160558355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have to say anything any more. Just stick your limp fingers near your mouth and flick them up and down to signify gaydom.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1366163017669</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366163142040-170</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of brain in butt, here is an all-time world record classic from gregjanetommax: gregjanetommax • Apr 14, 2013 "9/11 was another Democrats failure to take action to kill Bin Laden who was also responsible for the Subprime Lending legislation that eventually wrecked our economy...."</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1366163142040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366165151425-171</Id><Title>ETOP 180 DEN-NRT</Title><Msg>Is the route within the 180 ETOP? Thanks to those who understand these things.</Msg><Username>jmcbride383</Username><Timestamp>1366165151425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 22:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366166704217-172</Id><Topic><Title>One of the ironies of human nature is that it often has a way of rejecting the best and accepting the worst. Obama over Romney</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366163299063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:48:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vile Racist.</Msg><Username>charlesg50</Username><Timestamp>1366166704217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 22:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366167722837-173</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing has proven it does not know what caused the battery to catch fire and made a containment box nothing more safety last</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366167722837</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366167816428-174</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would that be two more flights of a 4 year late uncertified, 33 billion dollar over cost plane , how is that a good deal for the shareholder BA for 5 years gains less than 5% and Airbus in five years returns over 105% bark and ouch</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366167816428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366168122712-175</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are right the FAA already got burnt by going along with Boeing on the special conditions of using a lithium battery, something that was forbidden to be carried on any airplane in the cargo area due to more than one ignition and crash, so how is a another several days, weeks or months going to change anything? the self igniter in a box is still a danger to the flying public, it is odd that Boeing helped Cessna to decide to change out its firestarter sparky plane that switched from lithium batteries to NiCad and yet Boeing can not get it that way for their own plane, ouch and wow talk about denial .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366168122712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366168261465-176</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Sticking it to Boeing</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366152624953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow you just put down not one , but two agencies that oversee the aerospace industry and have been doing a good job for decades , I am convinced you do not know what your talking about</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366168261465</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366168369900-177</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock goes noplace fast the 737 needs 1000 planes fixed and the 787 is not certified</Title><Username>billboeing198</Username><Timestamp>1366149912515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now this guy Bill Boeing really knows what he is talking about ! spot on comment, very insightful</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366168369900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:12:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366168441423-178</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock goes noplace fast the 737 needs 1000 planes fixed and the 787 is not certified</Title><Username>billboeing198</Username><Timestamp>1366149912515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father wstleffanms I get it you don't know anything but Paul Allen , ",</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366168441423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366168571242-179</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock goes noplace fast the 737 needs 1000 planes fixed and the 787 is not certified</Title><Username>billboeing198</Username><Timestamp>1366149912515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>right back at you, if Boeing is still almost 4 years late on the 787 and almost 33 billion over cost and has a decertified plane and the stock price has gone up less than 5% in five years. well that is the truth and I can't help you with the facts.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366168571242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366170104965-180</Id><Topic><Title>One of the ironies of human nature is that it often has a way of rejecting the best and accepting the worst. Obama over Romney</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366163299063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 21:48:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Race is not a factor. What is a factor is that Obama punked us and Mitt would be doing much better.</Msg><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1366170104965</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366170938186-181</Id><Title>Boeing CEO made the list of the top 20 paid CEOs, but the shareholders have made less than 5% in 5 years ouch , bark</Title><Msg>James McNerney is the 16th highest paid CEO in the Nation , his return on shareholder investment for the last five years for his stockholders is less than 5%! The Airbus CEO made considerably less money and he has returned over 105% for their investors . bark and ouch for Boeing investors. Maybe Boeing investors should look for a better return on investment. The Dreamliner plane that Mcnerney is responsible for , the 787 is almost 4 years late, still not certified , and is 33 billion dollars over the original cost budget. Mr. Mcnerney was asked to leave his last job with GE as the GE CEO said he was not good enough. Mr. McNerney did much worst at 3M than the CEO that took over for him . bark and ouch Mr McNerney can not take any credit for the old 737 but can be credited with the newest version that need 1000 plane call backs to replace the fasteners on his watch. The man can also take credit for the extended 747 which is two year late and 2 billion over budget and not selling as predicted. The 777 was Phil Condit and Allan Mulallys plane and until Mr. McNerney messes with it , it will continue to be a winner. So until Mr. Mcnerney and his hand picked enabler Board of Directors are gone stay away from Boeing stock . Company: Boeing (BA) Cash compensation: $13.6 million Stock and options: $7.5 million Change in total pay (1 year): 15%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366170938186</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 23:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>