<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378183814916-1</Id><Title>Why Do You Guys Like King Obama So Much?</Title><Msg>It really makes no sense. King Obama is speeding up the decline of this nation. It must be a lack of education on the thumbs down guys. For full disclosure, Bush didn't do everything right either however, King Obama has been in office for over 4 years now.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378183814916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 00:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378186771396-2</Id><Title>Obama shuts down another business</Title><Msg>The boy king says same $ex marriage is good and if you don't think the same he gonna shut you down. From KGW website: GRESHAM, Ore. – A Gresham bakery that refused to make a wedding cake for a same-sex couple, prompting a state investigation, shut its doors. On Sunday, KGW stopped by Sweet Cakes by Melissa and found the bakery completely empty. All counter tops, display cases and decorations were gone. Hanging in the window was a sign from the Oregon Family Council that read "Religious freedom is under attack in Gresham." They should have claimed they were Islamic, then obama would proclaim let them make cake.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1378186771396</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 01:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378198598300-3</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Obonzo, Hitler gave a lot of speeches filled with lies and propaganda and like the loyal useful idiots that fell for Hitler's propaganda you remain blind and loyal to Obonzo. History is full of such repetition by useful idiots. Obermayer was a historian/witness who wrote several books and papers on Hitler and he documented how Hitler disarmed the people who he deemed his enemy like the 6 million he eventually to eradicate. Obama doesn't believe citizens should have guns and he lies about it in speeches when he says he doesn't want to take away peoples second amendment rights. Only useful idiots believe Obonzo's propaganda and lies and remain blind to all his scandals and his actions intended to reduce the freedom and privacy of Americans. You just keep chewing and digesting those Obonzo turds and burping them up like the useful idiot that you are Zo. It is very entertaining. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378198598300</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 04:56:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378201214506-4</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick,and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378140236115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 12:43:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, what a little pansy he is...........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378201214506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 05:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378201383800-5</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Buchanan: "This thing Reeks of a False Flag"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378177611270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 23:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good analysis.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378201383800</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 05:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378201577609-6</Id><Topic><Title>"I'm SANE...I'm Sane...I'm Sane....I'm Sane"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378169154968</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 20:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual, they are too ignorant to understand anything beyond 3 to 4 word talking points that are on a third grade level.............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378201577609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 05:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378203424038-7</Id><Topic><Title>"I'm SANE...I'm Sane...I'm Sane....I'm Sane"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378169154968</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 20:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi there Anal, some idiots never change, eh?</Msg><Username>analgonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1378203424038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 06:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378207272587-8</Id><Topic><Title>How Reagan Armed Saddam with Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378167348264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 20:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>‘Now Obama Can Start a War the Next President Will be Stuck With’ David Letterman</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378207272587</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 07:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378211288250-9</Id><Topic><Title>How Reagan Armed Saddam with Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378167348264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 20:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm all for encouraging Syrian factions to use as many chemical weapons as they want on each other. That would be less for them to use on other countries and less for us to eventually destroy. Your propaganda has several flaws of logic though. 1980 was completely different than today. The threat of oil being cut off to the USA under Reagan was enormous as imports from the Middle East were much much higher. The US dependence on Middle East necessitated our efforts to protect American interests there. What American interest is Obonzo protecting in 2013? There isn't any. Obonzo is doing all he can to prevent the USA from being energy independent and as far as I can tell from the $500,000.00 in jewels that Hillary Clinton got from the Saudi king, current Dems are all about getting $$$$ while they sit by and watch US diplomats get killed and creating false flags. So let the Syrians gas each other and let All ah sort it out. Obonzo needs to focus on energy independence,, jobs, debt, etc. and we need to focus on Obonzo'x scandals and hold him accountable for his numerous failures.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378211288250</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 08:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378212795733-10</Id><Title>All of the tech indicators are pointing to a bull run in INOL</Title><Msg>INOL looks like it is ready to pop. Have been doing some research on it for the past few weeks. Start your DD on INOL</Msg><Username>hudsone934</Username><Timestamp>1378212795733</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 08:53:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378214289894-11</Id><Topic><Title>How Reagan Armed Saddam with Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378167348264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 20:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound as incoherent as Zosima with the above post. I welcome your corrections to my posts since you seem to want too defend Obonzo involving the USA involvement in Syria but I don't think it is in the US strategic interest. If you disagree with mmy analysis, then offer evidence to show I'm wrong. I don't think your smarter than father zosima though when you post stupidity like above.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378214289894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378214307948-12</Id><Title>Presidents who can do no wrong</Title><Msg>President Nixon had one Watergate break-in resulting in his resignation. Under President Obama the NSA formally known before Snowden as No Such Agency has had thousands of break-ins gathering information from Americans emails and internet and other communication records that had nothing to do going after terrorism, in violation of the US Constitution and all is forgiven. ( except for Snowden) Why, because Obama has such a strong constituency that place him on a pedestal with the likes of Lincoln and Washington. Whatever decision Obama makes or will make war or no war, the majority of the public will go along with because President Obama can do no wrong.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378214307948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378214727271-13</Id><Topic><Title>Presidents who can do no wrong</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378214307948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:18:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS - 90% of the public are against US involvement in Syria and Obonzo's job approval is taking a dive as Unions are working with Republicans to shoot down Obonzocare and moderates are jumping the Obonzo ship. I just watched several of the Illinois Dems on the morning news here hedge on any support for Syrian involvement.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378214727271</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378215112585-14</Id><Topic><Title>How Reagan Armed Saddam with Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378167348264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 20:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does this have to do with my post. I didn't post that I agreed with Hoodz_weiner's belief that the US supplied chemical weapons. I posted strictly to address the rationale of Reagan supporting Iraq during its war with Iran. Try to read more carefully and post the above information as a response to show that Hoodz_weiner is moron.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378215112585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378215543783-15</Id><Topic><Title>Presidents who can do no wrong</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378214307948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:18:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You miss my point. Of course the public is against US involvement in Syria and does not like Obamacare, or much else of Obama decisions. Nonetheless, the public is so smitten by Obama's aura they will accept whatever he says. My word, look what Obama has gotten away with up to now including reelection.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378215543783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378216237717-16</Id><Topic><Title>How Sparty Lies about the USA arming Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378213460331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:04:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are a liberal you have to lie to forward you agenda. Liberalism sure can not stand on its merits.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378216237717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378216315360-17</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"took their guns from them" I cant believe you said that- even you havent appeared to be this skrewey in the past- what happend did your old lady up the lead content of your oatmeal to make you dumber still and easier to bump off??????? -----------talk about stooopid gawd- oh and BTW Hitler made it clear in 1935 that he was indifferent to the German people having gun ownership---------making ali infestid one of the crookedest liars on this planet</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378216315360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378216689689-18</Id><Topic><Title>How Sparty Lies about the USA arming Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378213460331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:04:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At the start of the Iraq War to unseat Saddam Hussain, the TV news showed huge convoys of Iraqi trucks traveling into Syria. I still hold that these trucks were transporting the WMD that the US was unsuccessful in finding in Iraq. The WMD transported are the chemical weapons now being used in Syria.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378216689689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378216709230-19</Id><Topic><Title>Presidents who can do no wrong</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378214307948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:18:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry I missed your point and in rereading your post I see that I DID indeed miss your point. I agree that for some unknown reason the public has allowed Obonzo to continue to fail in leadership and continue to be susceptible to his propaganda rather than judge his actions and examine his sub par performance on the economy.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378216709230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378216897590-20</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is documrnted in books you refuse to read so you stay stupid and just keep worshipping your totalitarian Obonzo and his totalitarian dreams.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378216897590</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 10:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378217040900-21</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SNOPES --This purported quote from Adolf Hitler about the disarming of citizens being essential to "conquering a nation" is frequently cited in discussions about gun control in the United States, but as far as we know no one has ever turned up a source documenting that Adolf Hitler literally said this (or something similar). GOOOGLE IT !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378217040900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 10:04:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378217381351-22</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How braindead is the father? lol! Hundreds of examples in hindsight, and he's too blank between the ears to get it. Socialism.......strives for equality by restraint, and servitude.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378217381351</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 10:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378221852813-23</Id><Title>How times change</Title><Msg>Ten years ago Republicans would say spying on Americans is just fine if you have nothing to hide no worriers, now that they don`t have a man in the white house and feel the only way for them to succeed is for the President and America to fail they will fully support a Traitor. I say they are pathetic little weasels everyone of them! and no I don`t support spying but it`s been going on since before the Hoover admin. and we are at war with animals that would love to do this country harm. we can`t just sit there and do nothing to stop them.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378222492024-24</Id><Topic><Title>How Reagan Armed Saddam with Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378167348264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 20:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even in the '70's and '80's middle east oil was more important to our allies, and non allied, than to the US. After all, Venezuela is next door.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378222492024</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378223196701-25</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snopes? You think Snopes doesn't have a left wing bias and are objective experts in German history? You and other idiots here keep depending on left wing propagandist for your idiotic views and then try to pass it off as fact to those of us who actually read history and look at expert sources who base their research on actual events and witnesses who had their guns confiscated. I am aware of the laws that were put in place in 1935 to allow German's to possess weapons. That has nothing to do with Hitler's secret efforts to disarm the 6 million people that were on Hitler's enemies list and that he eventually exterminated. Obonzo has an enemies list too, which is another trait that he shares with Hitler. Obonzo is using the IRS NSA DEA, etc,. for the purpose of going after his enemies. Yes this is more subtle than Hitler who established a secret police to do his dirty work but Obonzo's play book is exactly the same. Obonzo pretends to be pro second amendment when he is doing everything he can to weaken and destroy it. Are you as dense as you appear? I provided a new Harvard study last week based on the most extensive accumulation of international data on gun control that clearly shows that gun control doesn't work. Yet Obama wants to infringe on law abiding citizens and impose more gun control. Those patriots who stand up to Obonzo's attempts to infringe on the constitutional rights of Americans are viciously attacked and labeled as enemies of the Obonzo Reich.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378223196701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378223853294-26</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Jewish people of that time should not be confused with the Jewish people of today. Back then they were peaceful to a fault. The were not armed to begin with. It was the Hitler regime that changed their creed.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378223853294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378224718667-27</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Buchanan: "This thing Reeks of a False Flag"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378177611270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 23:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like it made no sense that Hitler gasses Jews: In a March 17, 1990, syndicated column, Buchanan wrote that it would have been impossible for Jews to die in the gas chambers of the Treblinka death camp, and referred to a "so-called Holocaust survivor syndrome," which he described as involving "group fantasies of martyrdom and heroics."</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1378224718667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 12:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378225229748-28</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You could just point out the flaw in the statement, and disregard who made the statement.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378225229748</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 12:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378227372317-29</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ = #$%$ in the above post.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378227372317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 12:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378227698891-30</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreams Of My Father" = Hitler's "Mein Kampfh"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378102624403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-02 02:17:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently you can't make heads or tails of it, because I don't hate Jews. I was pointing out that the force to be reckoned with in Israel is a result of the actions of Hitler. They knew after what happened in Europe their peaceful creed could allow them to be wiped from the earth, so they took up the creed of self defense. Not sure how you got from my comment that I hated them. Quite the opposite.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378227698891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378227869202-31</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not that slaughter is not happening around the world, it is the manner in which it is happening in Syria.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378227869202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378227914174-32</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vice versa to your ten years ago rant.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1378227914174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378228244647-33</Id><Title>40,000 Union Members Leave AFL-CIO Over Obamacare</Title><Msg>AFL-CIO President Richard Trumka received some tough news on Labor Day: his union just lost 40,000 members over his support for Obamacare. The International Longshore and Warehouse Union officially decided to cut ties over the legislation, but it isn't for the reasons you may think. "It is with regret but resolve that we have come to the point where the International Longshore and Warehouse Union must cut formal ties with the AFL-CIO," ILWU International President Robert McEllrath wrote in a letter to Trumka. McEllrath expressed disappointment in Trumka for "going along to get along" and in the failure for the AFL-CIO to secure a government run single-payer healthcare system for its members.That's right, Obamacare just isn't liberal enough. McEllrath also ripped Trumka for his support of Obama's 40 percent Cadillac healthcare plan tax. "President Obama ran on a platform that he would not tax medical plans and at the 2009 AFL-CIO convention, you stated that Labor would not stand for a tax on our benefits," the letter states. "The ILWU has also become increasingly frustrated with the Federation's moderate, overly compromising policy positions on such important matters as immigration, labor law reform, healthcare reform, and international labor issues." Labor unions and President Obama have been taking beatings over Obamacare from all sides. Labor union leaders supported Obamacare before really knowing what was in it, resulting in massive taxes, layoffs and fewer working hours for the workers they represent. In July, labor union leaders from the Teamsters, UNITE-HERE and UFCW sent a letter to Congress saying, "We have a problem; you need to fix it." Last week, Trumka finally openly admitted Obamacare needed to be tweaked and that mistakes were made in the legislation. The reality is, an expensive government run single-payer will only result in higher taxes for workers and subpar medical care. If the Longshoreman are going to complain about a 40 percent Cadillac tax on medical plans, they better get realistic about the cost of a single-payer system.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378228244647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378228685121-34</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Democrats need to get it through your thick heads that there are a lot of people in this country that are neither Democrat of Republicans. There are almost as many of us as in either of those two political parties. The Democrats are by far the worst of the lot and are the most anti-freedom/anti American of all. They used to be a credible party but now have become the voice for those who want to fundamentally transform America into the Socialist Republic of America.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378228685121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378228762742-35</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Assad was not kicking butt. He was losing, even without our help. He was not winning, even with the considerable help of Russia.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378228762742</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378229012825-36</Id><Topic><Title>40,000 Union Members Leave AFL-CIO Over Obamacare</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378228244647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:10:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unions change affiliations as often as sovereign nations change allies, and for just as many reasons.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378229012825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378229450626-37</Id><Topic><Title>Presidents who can do no wrong</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378214307948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:18:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nixon wasn't forced to resign because of a simple breakin at the Watergate. It was the purpose of the breakin; to help insure the perpetual reelection of Nixon, insuring his aids' jobs indefinitely, enabling them to continue their projects.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378229450626</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:30:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378229456334-38</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You left out a few important distinctions. Republicans were only supportive of monitoring communications that were coming to the USA from known terrorist areas and I don't think that has changed at all. What they are against now is Obonzo's totalitarian spying on not just those receiving calls from known terrorist areas, but Obonz's expansion and misuse of the Patriot Act to spying on all Americans and then using information for his war against American patriots/citizens. Obonzo and Nixon are the only presidents that have been caught spying on US citizens for personal political gain. No one I know ever knowingly wanted any president spying on them and they certainly want Obonzo to stop spying on them now. Do you want Obonzo to stop spying on you or are you a terrorist suspect that is fine with Obonzo's continued spying on you? Obonzo has crossed the line where his cure for terrorism is worse than terrrorism and you are the only weasel here for not being able to discern the differences and then misrepresenting the thoughts, distinctions and correct reasoning of others.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378229456334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378229592970-39</Id><Topic><Title>Two Things Alwayd Dominate and Motivatare Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378229198054</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>x6xxx still pretending that the World doesnt have a need for taxes to pay for public expenses. x6xxx you are ever the slacker and ever willing to let somebody else carry the load for you-- just how are you different from the common welfare bum?? you certainly are a POS</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378229592970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378229876458-40</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we knew where the chemical weapons were located we should have made the strike right away. But now that we have given them time to relocate military assets and chemical weapons a strike is very risky. And taking out the Syrian Governments ability to battle the rebels risks putting the chemical weapons into the hands of the islamic extremists and may cause high civilian casualties if the potential targets have been filled with civilians by the Syrian government.. It is highly likely that an attack will not end well.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1378229876458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378230271732-41</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh bull. The Repugnantcon party has been hijacked by religious zealots and those so conservative socially that they want to deny women access to any health care, not just health care choices (After all, there are plenty women, more than half the population, so the guys will be all right) want to restrict voter registration and hours and polling places in an effort to limit the right of minorities to vote, want to gerrymander state legislative districts so a majority of Democrats in a state like, oh, say either Carolina will only EVER elect 1/3 of a state legislature. They want less intrusive government -- unless you want an abortion, want your own city council and mayor to run your city instead of am "emergency manager" appointed by the governor, or what to try some new position in your bedroom. They want smaller government but they want to force your children to learn that the earth is only 12,000 years old and popped into existence in one swell foop lasting 6 days, and that all science is lies straight from the pit of hell. The day is coming when only terrified middle-aged white men will vote GOP, and those folks will blame Democrat Party scams for that fact. Oh, and they want gold to be the only lawful currency so that those who work for a living will be serfs to the corporate CEOs.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378230271732</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378230576741-42</Id><Title>Zosima Sentenced - Has new Job.</Title><Msg>CLEVELAND (AP) -- A man who threatened officers in Cleveland is making a court-ordered public apology by standing near a police station with a sign describing himself as an idiot. A judge had ordered 58-year-old Richard Dameron to stand outside a local police station with a sign bearing an apology. He began the vigil Monday and must stand outside for three hours each day for the rest of the week. Dameron was convicted of threatening officers in 911 calls. His public shaming isn't the first of its kind in the city. The Cleveland judge who sentenced Dameron previously made a woman wear an "idiot" sign in public for driving around a school bus.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378230576741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378230838833-43</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"deny women access to any health care" ????? What woman has ever been denied access to health care? What Republican has propose denying a woman access to health care??? Chrissie.....on what planet do you live?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378230838833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378231010407-44</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A missile strike against Syria would be intended to make a political statement, not wipe out Syria's chemical weapons or capabilities, as I understand it. I don't know hoe effective it would be, but I don't attribute false expectations to it.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378231010407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378231112857-45</Id><Topic><Title>Two Things Alwayd Dominate and Motivatare Democrat Politicians</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378229198054</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To offte4n our taxes don't go to pay for necessities required to run the government but they do go to reward political donors and left wing social engineering programs that often are pay-offs for support.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231112857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378231203697-46</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting rid of chemical weapons is a bit complex - cant just bomb em ( unless using a n u ) read about Umitilla depot in oregon The Umatilla Chemical Agent Disposal Facility is designed for the destruction of the chemical weapons stored at the Umatilla Chemical Depot. The facility was completed in 2001. The Army began weapons disposal on September 8, 2004 and completed disposal on October 25, 2011.[1] Destruction is a requirement under the Chemical Weapons Convention and monitored by the OPCW. The facility destroyed 220,604 munitions and containers containing 3,717 tons of GB, HD and VX via high-temperature incineration, representing 100 percent of the base's stockpile.[2] While destroying 50% of its stockpile took six years (until August 2010), the processing of the second 50% was expected to take only two years. The process is simplified by having only ton-containers of HD remaining to be processed while multiple kinds of individual munitions containing several agents were destroyed early in the campaign. An emphasis on risk reduction prioritized destruction of the most modern and dangerous compounds (VX and GB) and destruction of smaller containers, which had greater risk of theft, explosion, and leakage.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1378231203697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378231384606-47</Id><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Msg>.....or an abortion doctor?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378231634532-48</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is strange that Censored parroted what I already wrote and then dismissed what I wrote in oorder to maintain his belief that everyone here except him is Sparty. Is it deranged paranoia that Censored suffers from? I notice that he gets the most deranged when I call out Hoodz_weiner on his progressive idiocy. Censored I am against going into Syria, what is your position?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378231634532</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378231752841-49</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The one where religious zealots believe everything that humans should or does reflect God's will. YOUR planet Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378231752841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378231812835-50</Id><Title>Why is Hilary Distancing Herself from Obama?</Title><Msg>.....is she afraid the tide is turning? Does she think Americans are finally waking up? If so, she better start praying they go back to sleep.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231812835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378232066752-51</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is that different from atheistic zealots that believe that all political subjects should reflect the will of Karl Marx?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378232066752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:14:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378232372895-52</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the strike is not designed to take out Syria's military assets or chemical weapons, what good is it? A political statement? We have already heard the statement. Any strike not hitting Military assets is a waste of time and effort and simply fans the flames of war.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1378232372895</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378232412237-53</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's the over-generalization of one of those terrified middle-aged white men I was talking about. It's designed to terrify and age us all. It just won't work because too many people can hear your voice being muffled by your hat. One day, reasonable people will realize that Marx advocated that all factories, all farms and all "means or production" whould be owned by the mass of people, in common (that's where the word comes from, eeniac.) And no one with any authority in the United States of America has advocated that. You've been reading too much Ayn Rand (from BEFORE she was drawing Social Security.) Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378232412237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378232523345-54</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I notice you have no rejoinder to any of my other accusations.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378232523345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378232817945-55</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must think I was expressing an opinion counter to you opinion. I was stating facts counter to your opinion. Such a strike probably WOULD be no more effective that throwing 4,000 American lives away for "regime change" in Iraq. Bet you were all for that one. Look at it this way: All those crews missiles will have to be replaced. Your stock will go up.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378232817945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:26:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233049701-56</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully- at the minimum- a strike **might** seriously degrade the military ability to deliver chemical weapons on target. And **might** take out significant airfields, command and control, power, etc around military installations. But if a lot of capability is on moving targets, trucks, launchers, etc. then what ?? IMO- there is NO such thing as a surgical strike- and an outcome is at best a choice between bad, worse, and disaster. At the same time - we are not in a position to NOW ignore Assad. In any case- it will be either bush faulstm or boehner fault . And Putin is snickering. Moneky with a grenade comes to mind .. .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1378233049701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233138546-57</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Baloney. Spy-rooms at the ATT facilitates hoovered up all the emails under Bush and, AFAIK, still are. Look up the EFF. Bush admitted on national TV that he was doing wiretaps that were totally illegal, without FISA authorization, and the Republicans didn't say boo. The line where the cure for terrorism is worse than terrrorism was crossed a long time ago, under Bush. Obama has exacerbated the situation, it's true, by validating, continuing, and augmenting Bush's dictatorial toolkit, but Obama didn't start it.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378233138546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:32:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378233181317-58</Id><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Msg>Genna says Republican have denied Women access to health care but he can't name any instances where this occurred and they certainly have have had just as much access to healthcare as people do to a grocery store or restaurant.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233371409-59</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it any worse than the Progressive's religious like zealotry in worshipping Obonzo as a savior and blindly supporting his will?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378233371409</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233452890-60</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why offer more rejoinders when you refuse to even attempt to substantiate the ridiculous and utterly false accusation you made when brought to your attention?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233452890</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233498668-61</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Censored are you in favor of bombing Syria? Yes or no? Simpple question even your simple mind should be able to deal with.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378233498668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:38:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233690086-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Hilary Distancing Herself from Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231812835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you suppose it has something to do with Obama's 44% approvals?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378233690086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233794474-63</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The issue with chemicals is that they are indiscriminate. Chemicals are more indiscriminate than bullets, which are more indiscriminate than abortion.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378233794474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233905332-64</Id><Topic><Title>Presidents who can do no wrong</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378214307948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 09:18:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't the crime, it was the coverup--that's what they said at the time.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378233905332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378233968830-65</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a huge difference between a pro-American President that wants to spy on our enemies to protect American citizens, and do it in a limited way, and to have an anti-capitalist, a socialist, a supporter of our terrorist enemies wanting to spy on an extensive number of Americans, and then lie about doing so. And one who has a history of lying to the folks a great deal.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378233968830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378234063212-66</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It sounds like Genna embraces cradle to grave entitlements and may be upset that Chelsea Manning may have to pay for her own sex change.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378234063212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378234294506-67</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A person who would use chemicals of mass destruction has about the same moral character as a President who would say that the use of chemicals of mass destruction especially on innocent children crossed his red line, and he would not tolerate it, and needed no congressional approval to take action against.....then decided he could wait a week till congress convened, and ask for their approval. Both have no sense of values.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378234294506</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378234306841-68</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He sounds very confused about access to something and the power to force someone else to pay for what you'd like to have.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378234306841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378234428884-69</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378234428884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378234452501-70</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot comes of this: mostly bad. Congress gets on board and supports the President. Why? Partly because a statement does need to be make regarding the use of chemical agents as a military weapon. Another reason is, it helps to close the door on Iraq and Afghanistan-two thorns in the side of most Republicans. It also redirects the light onto this subject and away from budget, immigration, and ACA. Why do we need to make a statement in this matter? Every government on earth has pockets of people they wish would go away. If the precedent is allowed to stand, how useful will your AR-15 be against an oppressive government? Oh, very good recap of the munitions depot in Boardman, Shupe.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378234452501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:54:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378234849704-71</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bombing stockpiles of chemical weapons is poor practice. Have you forgotten Gulf War Syndrome?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378234849704</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378234889887-72</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chemicals will make you twitch!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1378234889887</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:01:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378235030910-73</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Power corrupts. That's why powers are limited by the Constitution. Politicians inevitably come to consider maintenance of their own image and suppression of the opposition to be national security issues.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378235030910</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378235095750-74</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has already been acknowledged that actually hitting the chemicals is a bad idea and that they would not be the targets.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378235095750</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378235226915-75</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another reason chemical warfare was outlawed is that survivors of chemical attacks were often left with scarred lung tissue and blindness, causing lifelong debilitation.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378235226915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:07:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378235320784-76</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yippie for the War President, is that what you're saying? Gee, where did I hear that one before? And I bet you weren't so happy about it then, you freakin hypocrite.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378235320784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378235595721-77</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have to substantiate my opinion. Trust me; I have it. Your opinion is that I hold one opinion erroneously. You said nothing about my other opinions. I assume then those other opinions are correct. But it makes little difference because they are ALL my opinions. Hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378235595721</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378235621233-78</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who has told you they do that?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378235621233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378235752770-79</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How bout Sandra (sp?) Fluke not being even allowed to testify before a cabal of terrified middle-aged white men about the need for private insurance companies (not taxpayers) to cover birth control pills?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378235752770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378236321635-80</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For decades women had access to things like Thalidamide, valium (sp) and diet pills, but not access to things that would help in their own reproductive maintainance. Why? Because men wanted them to have access to anti hysteria and diet meds. Not the other.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378236321635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378236601783-81</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bush admitted on national TV that he was doing wiretaps that were totally illegal, without FISA authorization, and the Republicans didn't say boo." PDB This what was reported by CNN in 2006 on Bush admitting to wire taps. "Democratic and Republican senators on Sunday expressed support for congressional hearings to review the program, which President Bush secretly authorized shortly after the September 11 attacks. It allows the National Security Agency to intercept domestic communications without a warrant, as long as one party is outside the United States." So It was not BS when I said the monitoring involved an overseas party and in fact you are wrong as Republicans did say boo and joined Dems in support of hearings into Bush's program as reported by CNN. The Obonzo leak OTOH indicates that he is monitoring all domestic communication even when communication does not involve an out of the country party. I could be wrong but I don't ever recall any Republican supporting spying on domestic communication where no overseas party was involved in that communication. If there was such support then I am fine with going after Republicans who supported such a program. But it seems odd that Republicans want hearings on the NSA, the IRS, the DEA, etc., if they were the ones expanding spying at the domestic level. Either way I am for more public hearings to get to the bottom of domestic spying and breach of privacy by our government and too put an end to it. PS I did like the EFF site and will use it as a source going forward, so thanks for that.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378236601783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:30:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378236780606-82</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sandra Fluke had access to to birth control pills.....no middle-aged white men were advocating denying her that access.......what she wanted was someone else to pay for them.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378236780606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378236920753-83</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We don't have anything like that happening with IEDs do we? ......Get real!</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378236920753</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378237091924-84</Id><Title>Rangel: 'I Love Obama' But Red Line 'Embarassing'...</Title><Msg>Rep. Charlie Rangel (D-N.Y) on Monday called it “embarrassing” that President Barack Obama has drawn a “red line” on Syria, and the congressman does not see “anything urgent about it.” “I love Obama, and you’ll never find a truer Democrat than me, but this whole idea of any president of the United States drawing lines saying that if any country does something, that he considers wrong, that the nation is going to war, it’s unheard of–drawing a red line. So, of course, it’s embarrassing. I wish it didn’t happen,” Rangel said.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378237091924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378237231204-85</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep; like those same private insurance companies pay for terrified middle-aged white men's Viagra so they can impregnate any woman who will let them (and rape victims, but let's not go there, since a Texas lawmaker ASSURES us that medical "rape kits" prevent pregnancy by cleaning the victim out.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378237231204</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378237244639-86</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about Sandra go Fluke herself and find a part job to pat $2.00/month for her own pills or refuse to have sex with men who don't use condoms? Next nitwits like her will be demanding free batteries for their vibratos or Monica Lewinsky/Bill Clinton endorsed cigars as master bating is a health issue for women too. ROTFL</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378237244639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:40:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378237754338-87</Id><Title>Book: State Department Knew Benghazi Raid Was Terrorist Attack Within Minutes</Title><Msg>A new book contains additional confirmation of what we already know about the Obama administration's response to the Benghazi attacks. Namely, that pretty much everyone up and down the chain of command understood the raid to be a terrorist attack almost immediately: Just minutes after 35 jihadists crashed through the U.S. diplomatic compound in Benghazi, Libya, nearly one year ago, the facility got word to the State Department, FBI and Pentagon that terrorists were attacking, according to a forthcoming book that provides the fullest review of the assault to date. In “Under Fire, the Untold Story of the Attack in Benghazi,” it is revealed that an unidentified security official in the Benghazi compound protecting Ambassador J. Christopher Stevens messaged the U.S. embassy in Tripoli: “Benghazi under fire, terrorist attack.” Stevens and three others died that night. Twenty-five minutes after it began, the operation center at State received an electronic cable announcing the attack, according to authors Fred Burton, a former State Diplomatic Security agent and Samuel Katz, an author and expert on international special operations and counterterrorism. Their findings in "Under Fire," based on exclusive interviews of those in the battle, refute days of claims by the administration that the attack was sparked by Muslim anger at a U.S.-made anti-Muslim film, and raise new questions as President Obama eyes military action in Syria that U.S. diplomatic posts in the region are properly protected. The authors note that at the time of the attack in Benghazi there were riots against U.S. embassies in Cairo, Tunis and elsewhere related to the film, “Innocence of Muslims.” That could have been the cause of initial confusion about the attackers, but the eyewitness accounts by State and CIA agents in the battle — backed by live video feeds from drones — should have erased any doubt.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378237754338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378238087089-88</Id><Topic><Title>Book: State Department Knew Benghazi Raid Was Terrorist Attack Within Minutes</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378237754338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:49:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bengazzi the little hill of sh.t compared to the mountain of sh.t called Iraq invasion with its 4000 KIA hope4 you SUCK as a human being</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378238087089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378238124088-89</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one forced anyone to buy insurance that didn't provide what the buyer wanted......until Democrats passed Obamacare. Do you really know anyone who took Viagra and ran out and raped someone?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378238124088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378238752703-90</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Generally people distinguish between explosives and chemical weapons.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378238752703</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:05:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378239097933-91</Id><Topic><Title>Book: State Department Knew Benghazi Raid Was Terrorist Attack Within Minutes</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378237754338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:49:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even the Huffington Post highly endorses reading this book.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378239097933</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378239124297-92</Id><Topic><Title>40,000 Union Members Leave AFL-CIO Over Obamacare</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378228244647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 13:10:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You bought the Fox News half truth, sucker. Try reading from a credible source for the real story. Chump.</Msg><Username>eggs_acklee</Username><Timestamp>1378239124297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378239680509-93</Id><Title>EXCLUSIVE: Explosive new book sets out case for impeaching Barack Obama over Benghazi, health care reform, immigration and spying scandals</Title><Msg>Another new book about BHO failure and criminality announced by the Daily Mail in the UK (the UK didn't support Obonzo's efforts to drag them into the Syrian war and this won't help). lol ____________________________________________ Book from best-selling conservative authors lays out 'a blueprint for drafting articles of impeachment' *They claim the Benghazi outpost was involved in illegal arms transfers to Syrian rebels, akin to the Iran-Contra scandal *Obamacare may be constitutional, they say, but the president's men have steamrolled Congress by rewriting portions on their own *'Executive amnesties' of illegal immigrants, write Aaron Klein and Brenda Elliott, may be impeachable end-runs around legislators *The Florida-based National Black Republican Association released a list of proposed Articles of Impeachment on Tuesday (nice to see minority involvement in impeaching Obonzo. In a lengthy indictment of President Barack Obama, two best-selling authors argue in a forthcoming book that the current occupant of the White House has committed numerous 'high crimes and misdemeanors' that could justify his impeachment and removal from office. 'Consider this book to be ... a blueprint for drafting articles of impeachment,' author Aaron Klein told MailOnline, which exclusively reviewed a copy of his 'Impeachable Offenses,' a book co-authored with Brenda Elliott and due out August 27. 'It is up to the public and ultimately up to their elected representatives,' he said, 'to decide what to do next.' Obama's actions, the authors write, include sanctioning an alleged 'arms-to-jihadist-rebels scheme' in Benghazi, Libya that 'aided an Islamist revolution and armed our most dangerous al-Qaeda enemies,' Those terror groups include al-Qaeda militants fighting alongside Syrian rebels trying to topple dictator Bashar al-Assad.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378239680509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378239819929-94</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you had listened to Fluke, you would have known she was defending birth control pills needed got medical reasons -- not birth control. (And anyone who thinks condoms are the most reliable form of birth control is a Neanderthal.) (And anyone who thinks the cost of birth control pills increases with frequency of sex is thinking with his little head.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378239819929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378239821200-95</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush signed the order in 2002. Your article is in 2006. Supporting hearings is easy to do--especially if you can be confident they aren't going to happen or will be toothless. As a whole, the Republicans didn't say boo about the wiretapping. They were fine with it, just as hypocrite Obots like hooz are fine with it as long as it's Obama that's doing it. Here's what EFF has to say about it: In 2005, after the New York Times broke the story of the surveillance program, the President publicly admitted one portion of it—warrantless surveillance of Americans believed to be communicating with people connected with terrorism suspects—Senior Bush Administration officials later confirmed that the President’s authorization went beyond the surveillance of terrorists and conceded that the program did not comply with the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act (FISA). The President, invoking a theory of limitless executive power to disregard the mandates of Congress, reauthorized this warrantless surveillance more than thirty times, including after the Department of Justice found the program to violate criminal laws. President Obama has continued the program, but with differing secret legal justifications. . . . Shortly after the initial revelations, a whistleblower named . . . specific AT&amp;T facilities . . . where the handoff of customer communications is occurring. Mr. Klein's evidence confirmed what was already indicated by numerous newspaper reports and Congressional admissions—that the NSA is intercepting and analyzing millions of ordinary Americans' communications off of the fiber optic cables that carry our communications, with the help of the country's largest phone and Internet companies. EFF has brought two lawsuits to stop this illegal surveillance. In 2012, three NSA whistleblowers came forward to confirm Mr. Klein’s evidence, as well as other information about the warrantless surveillance. Today, the warrantless surveillance program started under Bush remains largely intact under the Obama administration, and, in June 2013, reports in the Guardian and Washington Post confirmed key facts alleged in our cases, and provided supporting documents.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378239821200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378240889364-96</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Deny Women Access to Ruth's Chris Steak House</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378233181317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh please. You guys argue like puppies chasing their tails. Condoms are reasonably effective in preventing sexually transmitted diseases. This entire thread has dragged on from sublime to ridiculous when you consider the Fluke came up when I was asked for ONE EXAMPLE of women being denied health care. Your weak attempts to baffle us with DS rather than dazzle us with brilliance has gone on far past long enough. Just one more example of why I feel the day will come when only terrified middle-aged white men wilkl vote GOP -- you can't disprove it by acting just like it.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378240889364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378241043389-97</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you stated "not wipe out Syria's chemical weapons or capabilities". My point is then why do it? Why send a cruise missile to just blow up a sand dune? But the greater risk is that they have probably moved assets to civilian areas and targets may bring more harm than good. The stated purpose from Secretary Kerry is to punish the Syrian government. How would a non destructive tomahawk attack accomplish that? And, by the way, do it with only a couple of impotent countries backing the action.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1378241043389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378241208617-98</Id><Topic><Title>Book: State Department Knew Benghazi Raid Was Terrorist Attack Within Minutes</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1378237754338</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:49:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mediocre is it possible that 4000 Iraq KIA is not as bad as 4 KIA in Bengazi--- just how GD dumb are you------let us all know</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378241208617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378241519159-99</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Much of what the EFF writes is their opinion and not fact and we will see what happens with their law suit. I am weary of the fact that they only intend to sue Bush and not wait for Obonzo to lose immunity from prosecution. It smacks of partisan politics, so I am leary. I don't have time to research this but I will as I respect you and your willingness for honest discussion. If this law suit leads the courts to demand that the government reign in its domestic spying I will be the first to celebrate.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378241519159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378241797556-100</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haven't you figured it out yet? Tyranny is a bi-partisan agenda.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1378241797556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:56:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378242021322-101</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You ignore all the books coming out which show that this is a contrived war by Obonzo. I think the real winners will be those who don't support war expansion because Americans don't want to expand US wars. Look for Rand Paul or Christy to capitalize as the Arab Spring is going down in flames.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378242021322</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378242210412-102</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has a health care plan that he is afraid to implement whiile he is in office and that nobody including unions and government workers want, his Arab Spring has blown up in his face and the economy is running on 5 of eight cylinders and Hoodz thinks that is winning.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378242210412</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378242331529-103</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A magnificent success compared to Bushstink. Even a low-information, low I.Q. voter like Chemical_Ali_Infested should understand this.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1378242331529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378242624376-104</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being named after the place between a vagina and a pooper really suits you taint. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378242624376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378242819882-105</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, that's what I stated. But if you think that leaves only sand dunes for high-value targets, you don't know Syria or the Pentagon very well. Look, don't try to put me in the position of defending a U.S. strike I am not in support of. I simply wanted to disabuse you of the notion that such a strike would be intended to target Syria's chemical warfare capability. I don't have to support an act of our government to read enough to understand what supporters are saying for it. That should not be rocket science.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378242819882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378242914117-106</Id><Topic><Title>Boehner On Board</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378222829638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:40:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't think they intend for the strike to be non destructive. They will intend for it to hit an oil depot or a palace or what passes for government building, or where their fighters are parked, but not what is thought to be a chemical weapons facility.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378242914117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378242979503-107</Id><Topic><Title>How times change</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378221852813</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 11:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not naïve PDB and I am not partisan as I live in a state, Illinois, where there is the same ratio of Repubs in jail as there is Dems, and both parties are corrupt. I will research your information and I do hope that this law suit and other challenges to domestic spying lead to its reversal and reigns in government power and intrusion into the rights and privacy of US citizens.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1378242979503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378243000121-108</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Books are already written about Assad's use of chemical weapons?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378243000121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:16:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378243107500-109</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guys have taints, too.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378243107500</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378244000796-110</Id><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Msg>He is all giddy over another war because he doesn't have to go.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378244229185-111</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think its started when some incredibly smart poster called Orly Taitz "Oily Taint" at the height of her birth certificate grandstanding.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378244229185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378245285990-112</Id><Topic><Title>Report: Hillary Clinton Received $500K in Jewelry from Saudi King</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378239661820</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 16:21:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary Clinton received $100,000 of investors money. Money that was invested in the Chicago commodities market. A free gift from her corrupt supporters, or supporter. And that is a fact. She should have done time for that one.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378245285990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378246294711-113</Id><Topic><Title>Why did Obama and Hillary Lie about Benghazi?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378245695184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 18:01:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They lied because they thought Obama would lose the upcoming election if the folks really knew that Obama's foreign policy against terror was a total failure, and that Al Queda was greatly expanding their presence, not on the decline, and on the run like Obama was lying about. He sacrificed the 4 American lives, and told the blatant lie about the movie causing the attack, and not because of his failed foreign policy. Very easy to see, and substantiate, but protected by the liberal press, and the corrupt administration.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378246294711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 18:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378246790966-114</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama likes to throw his power around the world stage as much as Republican leaders McCain and Graham. Notice those with the most power gave free license to the NSA to do whatever the hell it pleases. Obama is no different than GW Bush, having power he likes to show off American might by being a war hawk.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1378246790966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 18:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378247190872-115</Id><Topic><Title>A Politically Brilliant Move By Barack Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378235162344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 15:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the hell is the UN doing on this matter besides playing with themselves? What the hell is the UN good for besides shipping wheat to Cuba? Obama could really make a difference on the world scene right now if he was to have a coming out party. Everybody already suspects he's a limp wristed president with his finger on the doomsday button!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1378247190872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 18:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378247586442-116</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Hilary Distancing Herself from Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231812835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For 3 months Hillary has been absent from human contact. Where the hell is this socialist mongoloid hiding? NO! Don't tell me? She's getting ready to have a coming out party,too?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1378247586442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 18:33:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378248012428-117</Id><Title>Recall Recall</Title><Msg>I think Obama made fools of the Nobel Prize Laureates. Liberals will believe anything they tell themselves. It's time to force our illegal immigrant president to return his Nobel Peace Prize to Norway.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1378248012428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 18:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378249644701-118</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Hilary Distancing Herself from Obama?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231812835</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:10:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary is just as complicit here as when Al Gore vaporized during the gulf oil spill situation.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378249644701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 19:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378251349545-119</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great New Word....Hippo-Chrissy ... sums up the Ravens prodigious girth and sloth like entitlement attitude coupled with his constant and unrelenting Hypocrisy regarding everything from the Constitution to the illegal wars in the Middle East !!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378251349545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 19:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378251404425-120</Id><Title>KERRY AND OBFUSCATION</Title><Msg>...""Let's shut the door now," Kerry said. "The answer is, whatever prohibition clarifies it to Congress or the American people, there will not be American boots on the ground with respect to the civil war." RIIGHT - No boots on ground re civil war ( in syria)... but door open re Alqueda, IRAN, Chem weapons protection- removal, training, defense of embassy in lebanon, iraq, and whatever other red-pink- yellow line comes to mind as we get close to election or need to cover up IRS, debit- budget, benghazi, or 'oooopssie ""</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1378251404425</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 19:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378251577150-121</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roger that Bongo 52. Sabre 06.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378251577150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 19:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378251736598-122</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all know you're nuts, Spart, There is no need to keep proving it.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378251736598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 19:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378252788878-123</Id><Topic><Title>Pew: Americans against Syria strike, 48%-29%, fear backlash</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378250863872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 19:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it! Huge Mistake !</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1378252788878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 19:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378253495782-124</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bomb Syria-sooner or later you can get both</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1378253495782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378253502928-125</Id><Topic><Title>Pew: Americans against Syria strike, 48%-29%, fear backlash</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1378250863872</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 19:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right now, and after a highly credible source reported that the Obama administration was in cahoots with the Muslim Brotherhood, and they are the ones that used the lethal chemicals on their own people, I wouldn't vote to attack. I sure wouldn't put it past Obama. It is all about BO saving face, and blaming the GOP for not attacking if they vote against it. nWe do know BO is in bed with the radical Muslim Brotherhood.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378253502928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378253937824-126</Id><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Msg>Conservative radio talk show host Rush Limbaugh acknowledges building evidence that the chemical weapons attack in Syria was staged to frame President Bashar al-Assad. On Tuesday’s broadcast of the Rush Limbaugh show, the talk show host acknowledged reports from the Associated Press that the admitted intelligence on Syria’s chemical weapons attack was “no slam dunk.” He also announced he believes Obama may have been “complicit” in the attack and possibly helped plan it. Limbaugh expressed doubt over allegations Assad used chemical weapons against his own people. Limbaugh asked if the allegations are true, what does Assad have to gain? On Saturday morning, the talk show host received a note from a friend who spent time in the Middle East. In the note, Limbaugh’s friend vouched for Assad, claiming there’s “nothing in it for him,” and “he’s not that kind of guy,” describing the note as “almost a personal reference for Bashar.” Limbaugh initially dismissed the claim and filed the note away stating “everybody wants to do my job” and “everybody wants to influence what I say.” “Anybody can write me anything and say anything, says Limbaugh. I have to be very careful. “I just can’t accept what somebody sends me in an email and run with it. So, I ran the theory by a couple of people whose opinion on these things I respect over the years. They both said ‘Na, na, na, that’s a little crazy.’” However, Limbaugh changed his mind when he discovered another piece making similar accusations by a journalist named Yossef Bodansky. In the article Bodansky argues the “deception playing out in Syria is a deception similar to the one used in Sarajevo in 1995 to provoke air strikes against the Serbs for the benefit of the Bosnian Muslims.” According to Limbaugh, “If this is true, this is the setup of all time.” The article alleges the “US had intel involvement dating a week before the alleged chemical weapons attack in meetings that were anticipating a war changing event.”</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378253972323-127</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“We could be looking at a frame job. Pretty big setup,” says Limbaugh. “The rebels nerve gassed themselves in order to engineer a response that takes out Bashar, putting the US on the side of Al-Qaeda,” alleges Mr. Bodansky. Limbaugh’s skepticism of the White House narrative regarding the chemical weapons attack in Syria adds him to a growing list of people who believe the attack to be a staged false flag provocation. The talk radio icon joins a long list of credible experts including Pat Buchanan, Ron Paul, Rand Paul and Jerome Corsi, who see evidence the Obama administration helped staged the chemical weapons attack in Syria with Al-Qaeda to frame the Assad regime.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253972323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378253986138-128</Id><Topic><Title>Is A Person Killed by Chemicals More Dead than One Killed By Bullets?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1378231384606</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 14:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that was with the mustard gas (chlorine). Now there are a lot of poisons, including nerve agents.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378253986138</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:19:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378254164257-129</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all know you're a sloth like, slack jawed hypocrite Raven...There is no need to keep proving it.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378254164257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378254358010-130</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There you have it: all the evidence from all the experts.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1378254358010</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378255252430-131</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you know that? The voices in your head?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378255252430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378255426709-132</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He probably is slack-jawed, since it means dropping the mouth open and leaving it open for a time period in astonishment or amazement. We are all astonished or amazed at the depth of your hatred for people who question your rants.</Msg><Username>wellsaid_1234</Username><Timestamp>1378255426709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378255469305-133</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378255469305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378256390752-134</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has the Raven explained why he supports AQ?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378256390752</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378257314616-135</Id><Topic><Title>The hypochrissy of the Kent Raven</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378244000796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How long did it take you to log in as a new user and pretend you have support Hippo ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378257314616</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378257552344-136</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Experts ? ... As opposed to Moral pillars such as Hillary, John Kerry and Barry Soetoro ? False Flag is now becoming a topic on everyones lips ....and the opposition to this war via ALL polls prove it ..... blow it out your rectal cavity !</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378257552344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378258133267-137</Id><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Msg>Someone wants to get the United States into a war with Syria very, very badly. Cui bono is an old Latin phrase that is still commonly used, and it roughly means "to whose benefit?" The key to figuring out who is really behind the push for war is to look at who will benefit from that war. If a full-blown war erupts between the United States and Syria, it will not be good for the United States, it will not be good for Israel, it will not be good for Syria, it will not be good for Iran and it will not be good for Hezbollah. The party that stands to benefit the most is Saudi Arabia, and they won't even be doing any of the fighting. They have been pouring billions of dollars into the conflict in Syria, but so far they have not been successful in their attempts to overthrow the Assad regime. Now the Saudis are trying to play their trump card - the U.S. military. If the Saudis are successful, they will get to pit the two greatest long-term strategic enemies of Sunni Islam against each other - the U.S. and Israel on one side and Shia Islam on the other. In such a scenario, the more damage that both sides do to each other the happier the Sunnis will be. There would be other winners from a U.S. war with Syria as well. For example, it is well-known that Qatar wants to run a natural gas pipeline out of the Persian Gulf, through Syria and into Europe. That is why Qatar has also been pouring billions of dollars into the civil war in Syria. So if it is really Saudi Arabia and Qatar that want to overthrow the Assad regime, why does the United States have to do the fighting? Someone should ask Barack Obama why it is necessary for the U.S. military to do the dirty work of his Sunni Muslim friends. Obama is promising that the upcoming attack will only be a "limited military strike" and that we will not be getting into a full-blown war with Syria. The only way that will work is if Syria, Hezbollah and Iran all sit on their hands and do nothing to respond to the upcoming U.S.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378258199234-138</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>attack. Could that happen? Maybe. Let's hope so. But if there is a response, and a U.S. naval vessel gets hit, or American blood is spilled, or rockets start raining down on Tel Aviv, the U.S. will then be engaged in a full-blown war. That is about the last thing that we need right now.” See also: Attack on Syria: The worst and least-bad scenarios “Western military strikes on Syria present a complex set of possible outcomes, and all of them make problems for energy markets to one degree or another. But some scenarios are worse than others. Despite an abundance of oil supplies—and the fact that Syria is a minor oil producer, at best—the global market for crude has been dominated for a week by worries about the Middle Eastern country. U.S. oil hit a two-year high above $112 on Wednesday, after closing below $104 on Aug. 21, the day that the Syrian military is believed to have used chemical weapons against rebels fighting the regime of President Bashar Assad. Hundreds of civilians died in the attacks. Since then the United States has intensified its naval presence in the region, and increasingly hostile rhetoric has spilled from allied capitals, including Washington, London, Paris and Ankara, Turkey. Given Syria's geographical location and the multitude of countries and non-national actors with interests in Syria's brutal 2½-year-old civil war, market watchers and others are asking themselves, where is this conflict headed?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258199234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378258467193-139</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Third Republicans are so blinded by irrational rage that they can't even keep their stories straight. The President re-established the CIA outfit specifically tasked with locating bin Laden (said office had been suspended by W), made the tough call to go after bin Laden, and killed him. So the Republicans have no credibility in any foreign policy affairs, having been reduced to comic strip character participants, are simply blinded. No expectation of sanity or even adult behavior. They would be screeching with equal spittle, vomit, and venom if either total war or nothing happened. Whatever the President does, they automatically oppose. (Equally like their blind opposition to Obamacare, which was actually originally a Republican plan.)</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1378258467193</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378258627241-140</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post of the day! Using "Jerome Corsi" and "credible" in the same month!!</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1378258627241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:37:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378259151133-141</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmmmm.....then again 90 pct of the American people are opposed to a Syrian attack...I WONDER WHY genius ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378259151133</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378260710886-142</Id><Title>Flash Flood Warning for 20 million residents</Title><Msg>Spartacus, An odd thing is happening down here in Southern California. Some thunderstorms dump rain in Riverside and, EVERY SINGLE DAY for the past two weeks, the emergency broadcast system, which has to date been collecting dust, warns all residents across 36K sq miles of five So Cal counties that there are flash flood potentials in Riverside - often 50 to 200 miles away from other population centers. EVERY television station is interrupted for five minutes to tell all 20 million residents about this emergency. The EBS is based in San Diego. I went to NOAA's National Weather Service just now and they did not have any weather warning for Riverside County. I went to the Weather Channel and they did not have anything for Riverside. Any thoughts as to what they are up to? Preparation? Practice for future events? BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1378260710886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378261025398-143</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The greatest deception of all time was Bush ordering the toppling of the twin towers and a missile hitting the pentagon ..... so say the Lefties on this board. Can't beat that one!</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1378261025398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378261177522-144</Id><Topic><Title>Flash Flood Warning for 20 million residents</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1378260710886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Living in Northern California myself they have occasional flash flooding so I grow used to it ... On the other hand, there is NO DOUBT that the powers that be are getting ready for something big over the next few years....and are in the process of training us like Dogs to accept Government Emergency help....with 1.2 billion rounds of ammo going to Government agencies, armoured vehicles by the hundreds used for Domestic use and EBS that is used incessantly I would say the Feds are thinking of either an economic meltdown coupled with civil unrest or some environmental calamity (we are at Solar maximums over the next year or so)......Any one scenario is unlikely...HOWEVER...given all possible emergency scenarios over the next 10-15 years ..a monumental cataclysm approachs a certainty Bob.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378261177522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:19:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378261475765-145</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus, Hooz posted a brief statement about Obama's brilliance on working this issue with Congress. One point was about throwing the issue back in the Congress' lap after they had complained about being bypassed. Of course, the warmonger McCain is drooling over the possibility of spitting a few bombs out. But the presence of the Republican House leadership at the White House provided support to the President - including Boehner and Cantor. Pelosi was there. But where was Reid? Even Rand Paul conceded that the President will get his way. Now, the real question is: what is Obama up to? Despite Hooz' undying devotion to election of Democrats, it is not clear that Obama and the Democrats are making a good showing to the people. What if Obama concocted a war which the Republicans provided the leadership to approve and then it turned out to be a major disaster? Obama does not have a re-election concern. The Pres elections are three years away, but the congressional elections are next year. One way to create instant campaign issues for Democrats is for them to say, "see, we told you so? Republicans are warmongers!" Obama did not see fit to press for supporting the Syrian opposition, despite 120K deaths, until about 1400 poisonings. Dead is dead. and 120K is two orders of magnitude more then 1.4K. I guess if Obama had been an engineer, he would have seen that a difference of two orders of magnitude is pretty much a big deal. It is my opinion that we have no business doing anything in Syria. Not much good can come of what we are about to do. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1378261475765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378262064523-146</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure that some politicians can manipulate events like Mid Term Elections etc.....I have never given it a thought since things of a more prescient nature could occur such as events spinning out of control into World War III which is a very real possibility with Russia giving material support to Assad in the form of things like Anti Ship missles....My God Barry Soetoro is arrogant beyond belief...and giving this war criminal a Peace Prize shows the moral depravity of the days we live in...Bob ... I am positive you can come up with a Biblical quote that covers the times we live in...then again they may be unprecedented ...</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378262064523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378263306224-147</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can we count on your support at the anti-war rallies to be held this week end? Bushbots who swallowed Bush's WMD lies without questions are especially invited!</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1378263306224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378263619831-148</Id><Topic><Title>Limbaugh suspects Obama conspired with AlQaeda to Frame Assad</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378253937824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 20:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! The Big Idiot's list doesn't even include Bush, Cheney, and Rumsfeld. No wonder you are so skeptical.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1378263619831</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 23:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378264079473-149</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I strongly suspect you have not been on this board very long...I shouted to the Heavens that Bush was a war criminal over 9 years ago...and rightly so....BUT....what is absolutely amazing is that the background singers who criticized Bush for War crimes just as loudly as I did...NOW think War and mass murder is just fine under Barry Soetoro.....hence my denunciation of the Hypocrites infesting this board.....God does not forgive a Democrat for war crimes any easier then a Republican just because he has a D after his name !!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378264079473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 23:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378265491059-150</Id><Topic><Title>Flash Flood Warning for 20 million residents</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1378260710886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 22:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>* It's the "Monkeys &amp; Buttons" paragraph of Murphy's Law in operation . * Blue states are especially susceptible . * * * Y.T. Jumbojetski *</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1378265491059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 23:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378266939740-151</Id><Topic><Title>Who REALLY benefits from a War between the U.S. and Syria ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378258133267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mark 13, Matthew 24, Luke 21 (chapters)</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1378266939740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-03 23:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>