<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366604832761-1</Id><Title>She say why do u only have 4 toes not 3 or 5</Title><Msg>you call that a toe ? we call it it useless but tasty ? I could be wrong but then what would frosh H.S. be like without toes.... same aqs what hger fasces - queen of sometyhing and if a single RWNJ believes that... he she or it must post here</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366604832761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 00:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366605639834-2</Id><Topic><Title>She say why do u only have 4 toes not 3 or 5</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366604832761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 00:27:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or cat-sup, natural sutures, the five-string tatter-tots, outta the park</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366605639834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 00:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366607075709-3</Id><Topic><Title>Me, IAM, and SPEAA</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366595391357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 21:49:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>name them U turn me on 3000 degrees</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366607075709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366607483621-4</Id><Topic><Title>Me, IAM, and SPEAA</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366595391357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 21:49:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3000 degrees is for itty-bitty kitty self-immoliators let us jump the degrees to 3500 and see which RWNJ isn't from Hell</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366607483621</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366608137385-5</Id><Topic><Title>Will Boeing's Stock Soar Thanks to a New Battery?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366570738036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>greg, in three years Airbus has made 190% I use the CNN money stock chart and the symbol for Airbus is EADSY . Boeing in 5 years has made only 5.9% gain and that is now after a 15% run up so if your in Boeing , that is your choice. I would stay clear of Boeing until the BOD and the CEO are replaced or retired. Also, The grounding has cost Boeing an estimated $600 million, so how is the cheap outsourcing working for you So far the 787 is 4 years late , decertifed, and it was 33 billion over expected cheap outsourcing make that 33 billion and 600 million or just round up to 34 billion as we are not done with 787 failure . so there is a break even point above 1000 planes and Airbus has had 4 years to carefully get their 787 buster online. This has been a disaster for Boeing. If the plane had worked , cost 5 to 10 billion and was on time it would have been a huge success, that did not happen. Airbus has studied Boeing failures, they have employed the best contractors that Boeing trained and worked with for free to Airbus, Airbus learned on the lithium battery and switched to nicadfor the answer to the 787. That is how Airbus is winning, they let Boeing make the mistakes on new plane's and technology and learn or take apart their better older planes like the 777 and study them first.Airbus is getting a free ride on Boeing , no 33 b illion to invest on the 787, take the good and shove the bad back. Airbus has a great business plan to run Boeing into the ground In ten years Boeing will be a niche player at best, China and Airbus will rule the sky for passenger planes . . It is like a long foot race to win you stay just behind the guy in front and out kick him at the end, it works almost every time .In this case Boeing ran out too fast and every runner is passing Boeing now, even Cessna has replaced lithium with nicad. Only Boeing is so arrogant as to go thelithium battery , they said is a," sometimes we dont know what we dontd know battery .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366608137385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366609014250-6</Id><Topic><Title>I ONLY BUY ILLEGAL GUNS FROM THE INSANE WITH FELON RECORDS</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366584502743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>five dings and a splat they semeed tohave stop;p[rd thbe brand new3 t corvette and ar discusing what tro do mebbe yu know them mebbe yu do no0t if thery catch me beat into a pulp tell them to buff it out in shop</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366609014250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366609402570-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Islam is a very populous religion. Mathematically there are probably more Muslims who do nothing wrong than there are Christians who do nothing wrong.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366609402570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366609836572-8</Id><Title>BROKERS are ALL Buying SHORT SHARES......huge downturn this week.</Title><Msg>up early for this HUGE DOWN.</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366609836572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:50:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366612181850-9</Id><Topic><Title>林志玲林志 EACH American owe me $80,000 now and growing daily...Bwhahahahahaha!</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366611046894</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:10:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>newbies are alawys welcolme 2B fleecee3ced how may way to skin a cat in your land no noodles or in the words of ottrers bug -off my wave no noodles</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366612181850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366612992199-10</Id><Title>In Jedda they make me Dean of School or no dice</Title><Msg>theynhad their chpoicee i wish i knew whast that ,meant In any case...</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366612992199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366614608325-11</Id><Topic><Title>In Jedda they make me Dean of School or no dice</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366612992199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 02:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hairy dice were talking 1000x the black forrest big dark and hairy or no dice photos of pluto 2 should anyone e-show up on my cloud let me e-chew this tasty offfer it taste like a st. bernard chewing a field-mouse until all it;s bones were crunched lucvky fellla drop0 itw2hatever youi are chewiong on leave some four me goodby</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1366614608325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 03:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366625934888-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come MSNBC wants to keep saying the Perpetrators were right wing gun toting John Deere Hat wearing terrorists ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366625934888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 06:18:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366630573317-13</Id><Title>“I have never done it , they set me up” This is the claim by the Boston Bomber suspect</Title><Msg>“I have never done it , they set me up”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366630573317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366631839769-14</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366582876616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:21:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did he write for Pravda?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366631839769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366634335968-15</Id><Title>☛☛☛Electrical "TIMEBOMB"...The Boeing 787, a steel box, new gases vent,+ same u battery</Title><Msg>needs complete rewiring...guaranteed</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366634335968</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 08:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366635393236-16</Id><Title>JAL &amp; ANA likely couldnt read english directions on how to chargethe batterys</Title><Msg>and were to stoooopid to learn- either that or they deliberately sabotaged the batterys. Boeing flew these batterys for 2 years in 5 different airplanes without a mishap- Now Boeing has had to engineer around ignorant Asians who cant or wont learn how to operate the airplane HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366635393236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 08:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366635857807-17</Id><Topic><Title>***HEY BOEING..a steel box and a vent...6 months? Bwhahahaha ..I'll NEVER fly on one787 !</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366602500162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 23:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gggggggggggg</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366635857807</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366635900501-18</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P Report....APRIL 13, 2013....12 month price target $82...BOEING is a SELL boys !!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366415792963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sell.........timebomb this is.....</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366635900501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366636344909-19</Id><Title>ANOTHER Billion lost for TEST flights thru JUNE in Japan ! ..ridiculous......</Title><Msg>really</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366636344909</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366636833183-20</Id><Title>WaynesWorld</Title><Msg>I wonder if Wayne's (multi-id) jihad against Boeing, is part of Sparty's larger disinformation jihad... financed courtesy of our dumb reps by way of taxpayers and new debt a billion, err thousand million, dollars to spread disinformation on a thousand or so heavily trafficked msg boards is a drop in the bucket relative to the thousands of billions wasted.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366636833183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366637683696-21</Id><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Msg>The AP reports that the men who detonated explosives to kill innocents at the Boston Marathons and later engaged in a shoot-out with police (after shooting an MIT security guard execution-style) didn't have gun permits, according to Massachusetts state police. But wait a minute. I thought a rigorous system for regulating gun permits was supposed to prevent gun violence (that's what Massachusetts state officials insisted upon passing the nation's toughest gun laws back in 1998). It's almost as if the Tsarnaev brothers -- terrorists, murderers, carjackers -- had no respect for the (gun) laws . . .</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366639445801-22</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>x6xxx234 why don't you go take a look at some coutrys that have strong gun control- Canada, Japan, Germany etc- then tell me strong gun control doesn't work- ignorant rednecks like you are too stooooopid to know that these countrys even exist</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366639445801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:04:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366640222848-23</Id><Topic><Title>“I have never done it , they set me up” This is the claim by the Boston Bomber suspect</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366630573317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, Sparty wants to believe this because it fuels another in a long series of wacko conspiracy theories. In Sparty's (insane) world, everything is a conspiracy. No wonder you got booted out of the military on a medical discharge.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1366640222848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366640369848-24</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another big day / week for our disaster n chief.... "The president, along with First Lady Michelle Obama, will be in Texas two days this week, heading to Dallas Wednesday for a Democratic National Committee fundraiser and then remaining in the city overnight. On Thursday, he is scheduled to attend the dedication ceremony for the George W. Bush Presidential Center in Dallas. But he may be on a tight schedule as he is supposed to attend the Planned Parenthood Gala in Washington Thursday evening." Looks like Today, Monday, is another day of rest/scheming... 10:45 AM The President and the Vice President receive the Presidential Daily Briefing 12:00 PM Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jay Carney 1:35 PM The President views science fair projects 2:25 PM The President delivers remarks at the White House Science Fair</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366640369848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:19:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366642390319-25</Id><Topic><Title>“I have never done it , they set me up” This is the claim by the Boston Bomber suspect</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366630573317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My favorite Sparty theory is that the earth is flat.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366642390319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366643016182-26</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The countryside is flooded, inundated, with guns of all types. Anyone can get one, or more than one. A nine year old can get a gun. If he doesn't take the one from his Dad's dresser he can get one from his friend's brother. Manufacturers don't care what their product does, they just want to sell more to generate more revenue. They are the first to mouth the platitudes that guns don't kill, people do, or to parrot the 2nd amendment. They are exactly like the cigarette manufacturers, defending their product despite piles of evidence proving the destruction to society and national health. It will take the same lawsuits and coordinated efforts to clean up this mess that had to be done regarding cigarettes. It's true, in a roundabout way that guns don't kill, people do, but, six year olds seldom kill anyone any other way but with a gun. My question is: Why are people despising these bomber brothers more than they despise the school shooter? And using the Islam angle for the excuse to despise them more? Is three dead with a relationship to a twisted form of Islam worse than twelve dead due to a twisted psyche?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366643016182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366643263510-27</Id><Title>This is the institutional holders slow selloff starting</Title><Msg>then the short position, start talking about how worried they are about the cost of this grounding followed by selling their short and riding it back up all to start over again in the vicious cycle. Eventually this will be a fine stock at or near $100</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366643263510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366643704536-28</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What an ignorant, pacifist fool you are....certainly a victim in waiting. Anyone that is not willing to defend themselves, deserves what they get. Are you really stupid enough to believe our government is going to protect you 24 / 7 ????? I mean, it only took 1000 " heroes " of 10 different law entities five days to find a kid they identified on the first day. I have no problem with the law and how they handled the capture of the Boston , but had this lunatic tried to take an armed Bostonian hostage, that Friday night band standing episode would most likely not have been necessary . As a matter of fact, I find it interesting that he didn't take a hostage......maybe he was thinking he just might roll up on the wrong dude and get his head blow off. On the other hand, if no citizens were allow to have arms, he would certainly been free to enter any establishment, take hostages, and probably result in more deaths than occurred on race day. To be completely honest I don't know if I could shoot some one, but if confronted in the middle of the night with some doped up punk looking for drug money or some nut job looking to make a political statement, I certainly reserve the right to defend myself .</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1366643704536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366643839891-29</Id><Title>Let me see now</Title><Msg>We started in Italy with the tube problems and had to send Boeing folks to straighten it out. Then came the WIingbox problem in Japan and we did the same thing. Now it is the batteries and the charging system and we are at it again. Is there anything else that we subed out that needs Boeing Engineering before go forward. And how much money has good ole Jimmy Mac saved shareholders doing this?</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1366643839891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366644290805-30</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366582876616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:21:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty's all time classic was the Alamo screed.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1366644290805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:24:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366644437598-31</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never once did I say that no citizen should be able to own arms or defend himself. Cigarette smokers can still smoke, they just aren't allowed to force it on the rest of us in theatres and restaurants. By the way, I own guns and know how to use them, but no one else knows I own them. I don't pack them around or show them to people. I go everywhere all the time and never have trouble with other people. I have been very fortunate, but part of self defense is a person's demeanor, that tells others they are not an easy victim, not the gun in their pocket.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366644437598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366645077787-32</Id><Topic><Title>WaynesWorld</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366636833183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:20:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another earth day ahkmed, just like may day</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366645077787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366645892809-33</Id><Title>Charleston 787 flights start</Title><Msg>B787-8 Hainan First Flight is airborne. Scheduled for a 2 hour flight. It is the 6th Charleston built aircraft. BOE431 on flightradar24/flightaware.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366645892809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366645943526-34</Id><Title>All Cooking Utensil Must Be Banned...I Want To Feel Safe</Title><Msg>Ron Popeil and Chef Tony sell those WMD on infomercials. Not to mention the "Magic Bullet."</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1366645943526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366646800619-35</Id><Topic><Title>All Cooking Utensil Must Be Banned...I Want To Feel Safe</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1366645943526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope all gun nuts get so busy making cute jokes about pressure cookers that they are overcome with mirth and forget about unyielding opposition to reasonable gun regulation. Hey, have you heard the one about the guy who killed his neigbor with a glue gun? Hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366646800619</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366646824636-36</Id><Title>BA supplier activity</Title><Msg>Hexcel (HEX) uo on RBC upgrade. Earnings after the bell today. (Carbon Fiber) BE Aerospace (BEAV), earnings announcement before the bell today. (Cabin interiors) Spirit Aerosystems (SPR) earnings to be announced on May 2nd.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366646824636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366646849515-37</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not the author of the rant I posted. I try to be careful not to lump Muslims as terrorists and I think I do a much better job than Chris Matthews who lumped Americans on the right as domestic terrorists when he said: “Normally, domestic terrorist people tend to be on the far right, although that’s not a good category,” Matthews said on Monday’s show. “Extremists, let’s call them that. Do they advertise after they do something like that? Do they try to get credit as a group or do they just hate America so much, or its politics, or its government, that they just want to do the damage – that they don’t care if they get public credit if you will.” Can you ever imagine Matthews ever saying, "“Normally, terrorist bombers tend to be Muslim, although that’s not a good category”? I can't either yet it is easy for him to do so with Americans on the right.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366646849515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366646857767-38</Id><Topic><Title>Charleston 787 flights start</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366645892809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:51:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was quick.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366646857767</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647172446-39</Id><Topic><Title>This is the institutional holders slow selloff starting</Title><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366643263510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:07:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dont think so. More like lower then expected housing numbers and lower numbers from CAT are making investors nervous. BA share price may wind up positive today.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366647172446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647312889-40</Id><Topic><Title>Charleston 787 flights start</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366645892809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:51:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Modification of production units at both plants seems to be underway. Should see the number of flights increasing each day.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366647312889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647326890-41</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't stop with gun manufacturers. Go after fertizer manufacturers too. Look up accidental disasters caused feriilzer explosions most notably Texas City, Texas. Then do a little research on the deaths caused by fertilzer exposure and the environmental damage caused by fertilzers. Then look up the cause of the Oklahoma City bombing the second worst terrorists act in U.S, history. Then after you're done shutting down the fertilizer industry go after the oil/gas companies. If there was no gas the worst terrorist attack in U.S. history, 9/11 wouldn't have happened.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1366647326890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:15:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647364413-42</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so right, alb. At a recent gathering of Ghost Riders, some of the gun-nuttier GRs were hazing me about my "fear of guns." I took out my concealed weapons permit and showed it around. The three guys who were police officers (and more or less felt as I did) just laughed at the way that shut the crazies up. It seems nothing is quite as shocking as when other individuals don't seem to fit in one's neat little stereotypes. And keep in mind these guys were all ex-helicopter pilots, all decorated, all men with balls I know and trust. Guys I flew with, drank with, played poker with, faced enemy fire with. If they didn't know that about me, what can idiots on a message board know about me? They are victims -- victims of their own narrow thinking.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366647364413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647487439-43</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeep you are a contributor to the 30,000 gun deaths that occur in the US every year- you should be proud of that right?? you should also be proud of your towering ignorance of the world around you- with people like you part of the US population I can see why the scientists are predicting that the USA will be extinct in a century or two</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366647487439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647554098-44</Id><Topic><Title>“I have never done it , they set me up” This is the claim by the Boston Bomber suspect</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366630573317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty would rather nbelieve the worst about our nation and its government and its servants thanm believe anything good about any of those things. In his mind, that's being a patriot, and oath-keeper.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366647554098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647774240-45</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366582876616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:21:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure Spart, sure. We can trust a guy like you to know ALL about me, when he thinks that two dozen other people are ALSO me! You can't buy humor like that Sparty provides. Harharharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366647774240</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647817515-46</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who makes this stuff up for you, Sparty? We know you aren't lucid enough to do it yourself.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366647817515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:23:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366648012418-47</Id><Topic><Title>BROKERS are ALL Buying SHORT SHARES......huge downturn this week.</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366609836572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 01:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a call purple man. BA is right now at $87.00. My cost basis is $36.04 per share. If you weren't trying to make the mythical "killing" by day trading in the range of a couple of pannies, but had been a long-term investor in a great company, you might see things in the correct perspective.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366648012418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366648271610-48</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will be lucky if you hear the mainstream media identify the bombers for who they are...radical Muslim jiihadists. The Regime feels it offends Muslims. What the Regime had better understand is that if these Muslim Jiiihadists are not louldy rejected by Muslims as extremists they are willing to identify as extremists, then Muslims are going to feel the brunt of the criticism.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366648271610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366648940934-49</Id><Topic><Title>“I have never done it , they set me up” This is the claim by the Boston Bomber suspect</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366630573317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes he is. For a guy who complains about those slopping at the public trough, he slops his share. Ask him about his 20% disability for but t problems. Then TRY to confine yourself to facts.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366648940934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366648986669-50</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I already addressed this once before in that if you remove gun murders committed by Blacks and Latinos, US per capita murder rates would drop drastically according to FBI data. How many Blacks and Latinos are there in Japan where 98.5% of the population is ethnic Japanese? Far far less than 1%. How about Canada? Also both less than 1%.How about Germany where 92% of the population is ethnic German? again less than 1%. What you need to do to compare apples to apples is to look at murder rates for predominately White communities. If you do you will see that homogeneous White communities have per capita murder rates similar to homogeneous countries like Canada Germany and Japan.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366648986669</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366649261418-51</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go look at the number of Christians killed in Africa by Muslin factions. You are in deep denial and in need of facts for your made up assertion.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366649261418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366649331682-52</Id><Topic><Title>“I have never done it , they set me up” This is the claim by the Boston Bomber suspect</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366630573317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it was a setup, huh spazticus, perpetrated by boston, the lamestream media, our schools, and mobros (who've taken advantage of uncle teddy's third world immigration preference to grow their numbers by 9000% since 1970, from 100K to near 9 million today).</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366649331682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366649359698-53</Id><Topic><Title>“I have never done it , they set me up” This is the claim by the Boston Bomber suspect</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366630573317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They give you a pension in the Air Force for being an A $ $ H 0 L E?</Msg><Username>marxmoronic</Username><Timestamp>1366649359698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366649449784-54</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>infested you cant provide substantiation for your lunatic idea- you cant cite the text from an FBI report and you cant cite the keywords necessary to find it and you don't have a URL. In other words you are using the old tried and true Tbagger trick- you are lying thru your teeth</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366649449784</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366649557511-55</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Idea- Tim McVeigh thot it was also and used a fertilizer bomb in OK City to kill 175 people</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366649557511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366649698581-56</Id><Title>Boeing and Airbus and ACAD and Boeing Hacks too ACAD up over 10% today again</Title><Msg>Today's numbers; Boeing is down today 1.1% on news the 787 is approved to fix and fly. That is because the 787 is still the 4 year late 33.5 billion over cost plane! Get it now ? , ACAD, a stock I pointed out this year is (once more again ) up today 10%. ACAD has made Boeing hacks look very incompetent this year. So once more Boeing Hacks the facts, This ACAD is a swing trade for me. ACAD up 10% today,up 187% YTD, 1 year up 806%, 3 years up 694%, and while I would not long term play this stock it is up 50% in 5 years this is a swing trade stock today it peaked again I just love it when I suggest a stock then keep quiet about it until I am out , over and over I make more money that Boeing Hacks . BA, YTD it is still 15%, and Airbus up( still) 30%,and for long term buy and hold Boeing Hacks still 5% gain compared to 120% gain for Airbus today Boeing is down 1.1% Conclusion learn how to read a stock chart and make some money or be a loser critic all your life or watch 787 planes fly and really be a Boeing Hack that will get you a lose of 1.1% today. I like the 10.1% gain for me today on ACAD and out it is at resistance now , your too late again. Told yah</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366649698581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366649720220-57</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a little help to get you started. In Sudan, it is estimated that over 1.5 million Christians have been killed by the Janjaweed, the Arab Muslim militia, and even suspected Islamists in northern Sudan since 1984.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366649720220</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366649737476-58</Id><Topic><Title>“I have never done it , they set me up” This is the claim by the Boston Bomber suspect</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366630573317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 07:36:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you overuse your but t by sitting on it too much, the Air Force has discovered it can cause debilitating injuries. All joking aside, I thanked Spart for his service to his country a long long time ago, before he made it clear he thinks the service of nut-case conspiracy theorists is more valuable than the service of citizen soldiers who did their part and then got out before they could be a burden on the system.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366649737476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366650172232-59</Id><Topic><Title>This is the institutional holders slow selloff starting</Title><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366643263510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:07:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>har har har wow denial, if BA ends up higher then BA stock buy back is on today, Boeing is not tied to CAT or ACAD which is up over 10% today, and up 187% for YTD or 806% for 1 year. BA is tied to a tractor really har har har har har BA is tied to a 4 year late , 33.6 billion dollar over cost program that was grounded and customers and passengers and the stock holders do not trust Boeing to do what they claim they are going to do. It is a insult to the average investor that you post the plane is flying today like that is news, The 787 should have been flying with passengers 4 years ago guy, get a clew</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366650172232</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366650687735-60</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER Billion lost for TEST flights thru JUNE in Japan ! ..ridiculous......</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366636344909</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>add the 600 million to the grounded shareholder bill for the 787, so the 787 is 4 year late, over cost by 33.6 billion and the 787 beater from Airbus is now not far from launch if done right Boeing's early potential lead is done. But wait it gets worse for only BA investors are saddled with a 33.6 billion development bill and a break even point above 1000 planes , usually Boeing has a break even in the few hundred airplanes and this plane is still not fixed, it is now flying with a, " sometimes we don't know what we don't know" battery fix , Airbus has switched to nicad , Cessna has switched to nicad Boeing has used the very skilled IAM workers to make a fire box for old sparky, Terrible non fix, just another example of poor Chicago Mismanagement wow denial is a terrible thing for the shareholders</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366650687735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366650759243-61</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the body count for Shia, Sunni and Sufi killing each other during the late 20th Century and early 21st Century, over religious differences? Most of the other millions of human non world war killing has been provided by atheists and communists not by Christians.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366650759243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:12:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366650762021-62</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing and Airbus and ACAD and Boeing Hacks too ACAD up over 10% today again</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366649698581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:54:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the Boeing hacks say ?????? they seem less and less willing to open their mouths , wonder why, ? hummm the truth hurts but it is still he truth</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366650762021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366651015424-63</Id><Topic><Title>Will Boeing's Stock Soar Thanks to a New Battery?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366570738036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing down today 1.02%, I guess not then ! or as foulmoutharbor thinks , really ? bark and ouch Boeing is being held back by CAT, denial is a terrible thing foulmoutharbor, Boeing is alos not being pulled up by ACAD up over 10% today wow foulmoutharbor is the 787 really flying today ? is that important ? or is the 787 program being 33.6 billion over cost and 4 year late more significant ? bark and ouch for FMH</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366651015424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366651245808-64</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER Billion lost for TEST flights thru JUNE in Japan ! ..ridiculous......</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1366636344909</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet another idiot appears. WTG purple worm!</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1366651245808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366651811961-65</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only difference from a Right wing radical nut case and a Muslim radical nut case is their shoe size`s</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366651811961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366651964138-66</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't need to look those things up because the ones that are true I already know. That fertilizer plant in West, Texas was in violation of regulations and laws 7 ways from Sunday. You can bet it will generate a different way of oversight for that industry. They had stockpiled 270 times the amount they had declared. It is just like the firearms regulations: it doesn't matter what laws and regulations are on the books if they are not enforced. There is no trust without verify. And there are reasons, safety reasons for those regulations. They are not just there to annoy.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366651964138</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366652490940-67</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a stereotype that needs to be made braindead because all of terrorist atacks have been made by them. Can you think of an exception? They get trained in terrorist, Radical Muslim training camps to kill Americans.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366652490940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366653237816-68</Id><Title>Hope for the Boeing shareholder</Title><Msg>stay clear of Boeing until the BOD and the CEO are replaced or retired. Also, The 787 grounding has cost Boeing an estimated $600 million, so how is the cheap outsourcing working for you? So far the 787 is 4 years late , decertifed, and it was 33 billion over expected cheap outsourcing Boeing investors make that 33 billion and 600 million over expected cost or just round up to 34 billion . With the 787 failure, as we are not yet done with 787 problems. . Boeing claims a breakeven point above 1000 planes, that will be extended, usually Boeing breaks even in a few hundred planes like with the 777. Next, Airbus has had 4 extra free years to carefully get their 787 buster online, due to the massive lead and then failure of the 787 to launch and work as promised and as expected. . . This has been a disaster for Boeing shareholders. If the plane had worked on time, cost 5 to 10 billion as projected, it would have been a huge success, that did not happen. Airbus has studied Boeing failures, they have employed the best contractors that Boeing trained and worked with for free to Airbus, Airbus learned on the lithium battery 787 failure and switched to nicad for the answer plane to the 787.. That is how Airbus is winning. Airbus management let’s Boeing management make the mistakes on the 787 and takes the new 787 plane's technology and learn for free from Boeing shareholders massive cost of mistakes. . Airbus business plan is to study Boeing old school planes like the 777 and study them first then build a better or at least competitive new plane. It is not that Airbus management is good, look at the A380,, it is that Boeing Management is worse. Even the A380 is now cutting into the 747 orders . How can I tell the production cycle for the 747 just was slowed down, as the 747 production has been cut back, get a clue Boeing investors. .Airbus is getting a free ride on Boeing, shareholders who have paid 33.6 billion extra to make the 787.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366653237816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366653336658-69</Id><Topic><Title>Hope for the Boeing shareholder</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366653237816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haha, you must be a disgruntled laid off union worker. So sorry dude but they cut the fat and the stock is flying. Get lost mor0n.</Msg><Username>tallicat9300</Username><Timestamp>1366653336658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366653341727-70</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google 'FBI Uniform Crime Reports" that is where the base information is contained. Here is how you get the further breakout of non-Hispanic Whites and the .32/100,000 per capita rate which is close to many other countries like Spain, Germany and the UK. Hispanic firearms homicide rate According to the Bureau of Justice Statistics, the 20-year gun homicide rate is 41.9% "white" and 56.4% black. The "white" rate is lower than reported by the FBI for 2010, which, if I am correct, reduces the known black share from 56.4% to 49% due to the rising Hispanic population. But since there are plenty of cases that are unknown, we will use the 20-year rate in order to avoid the possibility of a single year outlier while considering the 9,146 gun homicides concerned. We will assume, for the sake of argument, that Hispanic victims are synonymous with Hispanic killers. The BJS supports this assumption, reporting that from 1976 to 2005, 86% of white victims were killed by whites and 94% of black victims were killed by black. A CDC report states: "Homicide rates in 2010 among non-Hispanic, African-American males 10-24 years of age (51.5 per 100,000) exceeded those of Hispanic males (13.5 per 100,000) and non-Hispanic, White males in the same age group (2.9 per 100,000)." What interests us is how the remaining 4,116 gun homicides are divided between whites and Hispanics. The distribution indicated by the CDC report shows that 3,388 were Hispanic and only 728 were white. This may be a little skewed by the focus on young males, but nevertheless provides a very credible estimate of 6.8 per 100k population, which would put the US-Latin firearms homicide rate in between Nicaragua at 5.9 and Paraguay at 7.4. It would also indicate that the US-White homicide rate is 0.32 per 100k population, a per capita rate</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366653341727</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366653453857-71</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Z I know you prefer emotional fanaticism to data but try your bset to look at data. Let me know if it is too hard for you and I will help.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366653453857</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366653870135-72</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals are going to get this terrorist out of prison in 5 years with a PHd</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366417059193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so true, its a liberal creed, criticize the grammer when the facts can't be disputed. At the expense of truth and all that is good in the world.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366653870135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366654454748-73</Id><Topic><Title>S&amp;P Report....APRIL 13, 2013....12 month price target $82...BOEING is a SELL boys !!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1366415792963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:56:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA stock price is down today and the 787 is approved by the FAA !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366654454748</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:14:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366654641499-74</Id><Topic><Title>***HEY BOEING..a steel box and a vent...6 months? Bwhahahaha ..I'll NEVER fly on one787 !</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366602500162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 23:48:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing stock price is down and the box is approved by the FAA humm and a 787 is flying hummm oh wait foulmoutharbor says it is because CAT is holding Boeing stock price down or maybe it is my stock ACAD up 10% being bought today , no more private funds to invest in a lowser company like BA only up 5% in 5 years Airbus up 120% in 5 years foulmoutharbor when are you going to learn limited money so you go where the money can make more not nothing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366654641499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366654729258-75</Id><Topic><Title>TOO HIGH EXPECTATION, SOMETIMES IS LOWER SIGN</Title><Username>kaoginger</Username><Timestamp>1366573805032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 15:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well expectations or not Boeing stock price is down on good news the FAA approved the battry box wow maybe the public does not like that fix eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366654729258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366654961681-76</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we are to accept these assumptions, then why are so many people so afraid of other races? And, does homicide include accidental and negligent deaths among households?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366654961681</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:22:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366655022713-77</Id><Topic><Title>Hope for the Boeing shareholder</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366653237816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 13:53:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow foulmoutharbor said after all his posting that the 787 is flying, With Boeing stock price foulmoutharbor has another point to make, now it is CAT stock price, a tractor company holding Boeing stock price down today. well ouch and bark for that excuse. actually foulmoutharbor the BA stock price has been bad for 5 years only up 5% so today is just like the past 5 years pretty much nothing. unless Boeing buys their own stocks after a 15% gain in the last month BA on Boeing stock buyback, Boeing stock is now up a pathetic 5% gain for five years get it now ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366655022713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366655048750-78</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were 32,885 car crash deaths in 2010. Blacks have a 20 year average homicide offender rate of 12.5/100,000 compared to non-Hispanic Whites with an average of 0.32/100,000 which equates to about 1,008 total gun related homicides in 2010 based on census data. Why do you insist on punishing and invading the privacy of those that have been accountable and responsible just because you have a hard on for guns for some strange reason? Can you see why White gun owners feel targeted when they average homicides rates similar to countries with gun bans? If you want to take away guns from Blacks and Hispanics who are responsible for 9 out of 10 gun deaths per capita that's acceptable to me as they are not being responsible like Whites are..</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366655048750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366655259699-79</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The very first place I looked shows the gross difference between one of the countrys with strong gun control (United Kingdom) and the USA This information is available on a lot of web sites- this particular entry was from endotwikipediadotorg In the United Kingdom, firearms are very tightly controlled by law, and while shooting organisations provide some minor opposition to existing legislation [1] there is little wider political debate on the subject as UK public opinion heavily favours strong control.[2] These laws are much less restrictive in Northern Ireland than in the rest of the UK. In 2012 the British Shooting Sports Council believed that the law needed to be consolidated, but did not call for a review.[3] The United Kingdom has one of the lowest rates of gun homicides in the world. There were 0.07 recorded intentional homicides committed with a firearm per 100,000 inhabitants in 2010, compared to the 3.0 in the United States (over 40 times higher) and 0.21 in Germany (15x higher).[4] you and your ilk only interpret or find #$%$ that bolsters your evil murderous gun slinger ideology-- once again you contribute to the 30,000 gun deats in the USA-- boy is that ever something to be proud of</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366655259699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366655355297-80</Id><Topic><Title>Will Boeing's Stock Soar Thanks to a New Battery?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366570738036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apparently not , oh wait , wait that bad old other stock CAT is now the excuse for BA stock going down, lets blame my stock ACAD up 10% today for holding Boeing stock price down, you see foulmouth harbor with all the buyers of ACAD there is less money to waste on Boeing stock, get it now .faoulmoutharbor in order for CAT to hold Boeing stock price down, stock investors would have to be buying CAT instead. You are reading too many stock market crapola stuff and do not know how the stock market works or you would not be a Boeing Hack, it is simple, that is how the stock market works, learn to read a stock chart. Boeing is a dead cat bounce stock 5% gain in 5 years says so !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366655355297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366657358431-81</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Homicide rates per 100,000 with knives is higher as well as blunt objects. 'In the UK – population 56.1 million (4) – there were an estimated 550 murders in 2011-12 (5), a rate of about 1.4 per 100,000. Of these 39 were carried out with a firearm (6).' So while there are only 39 homicides with a firearm non-Hispanic White Brits are strangling, beating and bashing there victims to death at rates similar to non-Hispanic Whites in the USA. The mix is different and the US non-Hispanic Whites use guns rather than strangling and bludgeoning victims to death like Brits. Isn't it more humane shooting someone rather than strangling them or smashing their skull in? Coincidentally other violent crime like robberies, rapes and home invasions rose dramatically after the gun ban in Britain. You still lose the debate Z because the gun ban only shifted the methodology of homicides but it never actually lowered homicides and it led to a rapid increase of other violent crimes. You didn't do your homework and still suffer confirmation bias.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366657358431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 15:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366659070451-82</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing becomes #21 MOST SHORTED STOCK !! replaces GE !!! **STRONG SELL</Title><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1366436243886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 01:37:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Boeing company makes great heritage planes , it is everything the Boeing management now touches that goes to crapola, the 747 ws touched now the cycle is slowing down due to lack of orders even the airbus failure the A380 is cutting into the once great 747, the 777 so far is great , but jsut wait unitl the Chicago management makes a change it will fail too, the 787 is a all new chicago MD outsource business plan 33.6 billion over cheap price 4 years late while the Airbus plane got an extra 4 years to close the gap, it it comes online on time and on budget Boeing shareholders will go form dead cat bounce to negative. BA in five years is up only 5% that is a dad cat bounce. I am retired BA and spent 5 of my years on the old school 737, really amazing a plane so old that the wheel well do not have a enclosed lid and yet the 737 is the best profit center for Boeing but wait the 737 max and Chicago management will destroy that too, right now the 737 NG has 1000 plane recall on the new version for fasteners IF Chicago touched it the plane will fail the airbus planes according to Boeing management and Airbus says the same for Boeing planes so it is the management not the plane that makes the difference . Comfort is important but safety of the plane is most important and a box to cover the we don't know what we don't know is not a fix it is another disaster fix</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366659070451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 15:31:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366659111283-83</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>none of your feeble arguments about bare hands, automobiles or knives holds up. You can murder more people with guns than all of the above and at a much faster rate and from a longer distance. The fact that you cant stop homicide is no reason not to try to stop the deadliest form of homicide. The other items- knives, automobiles etc are needed on a much wider scale than guns. Your real argument is that you are #$%$ for guns- and you are unmoved by their murderous power. Boy that says something about you. You also seem to think that if black people are murdering themselves at a prodigious rate its ok since - wel they are black- they may be primates.but................ Yup racism and infestid and guns go together like a ............</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366659111283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 15:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366659684833-84</Id><Topic><Title>Will Boeing's Stock Soar Thanks to a New Battery?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366570738036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 14:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so foulmoutharbor said once the 787 is flying again, Boeing stock would soar like the 787 plane flying well nope foulmoutharbor it does not work that way. You forget the fundamental reason Boeing stock is flat. , Boeing is down 1.23% today on good news the FAA approved the firebox solution, so now foulmoutharbor said Boeing was being held back by a tractor company stock CAT , wow and bark I guess ACAD being up today 10% is another real reason, investors put their money to use where it will make a good return. ACAD is up 50% for 5 years BA is up 5% for five years, ACAD is up 187% YTD , Boeing is up 15% YTD and Airbus is up 30% YTD the flying 787 is 33.6 billion over original cost and 4 years late foulmoutharbor that is the issue not the plane is testing again get it now ? learn to read a stock chart ! Being a Boeing hack gets you yoru opinion nothing more ACAD on a stock chart make money</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366659684833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 15:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366661002182-85</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK...READ PLZ...</Title><Msg>Valued at $42.4 billion, EADS is at nearly two-thirds Boeing's market cap. But with only $1.6 billion in annual net income, the company pulls down less than half the $3.9 billion in annual profit of its American rival. Worse, EADS generated only about $752 million in real cash profit last year -- less than half its own net income. In contrast, Boeing's $5.8 billion in trailing free cash flow vastly exceeds the $3.9 billion that GAAP accounting standards permitted the company to report as net income. Simply put, Boeing's a cash monster, and EADS is not. At a valuation of 26.5 times earnings, and an even more altitudinous price to free cash flow, EADS shares are priced to crash and burn. For this stock, at least, investors' fear of flying seems well-founded</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1366661002182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366661293312-86</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK...READ PLZ...</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1366661002182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:03:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spot on, domerrrr45, spot on..</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366661293312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366661671689-87</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now the rationalization for too many unregulated guns is that it is a more humane way of murder? Is a widow less traumatized if her husband was shot by their infant rather than stabbed by him?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366661671689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366661825882-88</Id><Topic><Title>Charleston 787 flights start</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366645892809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:51:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder why it taked CHS twice as long to build a 787 compared to PAE.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1366661825882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366661964122-89</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366582876616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:21:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex Jones must be either getting lazy or think his readers are really dumb, Combination of both.</Msg><Username>ichbinienmachoman</Username><Timestamp>1366661964122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366661989047-90</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366582876616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:21:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>InfoWars-News for #$%$ #$%$ like you.</Msg><Username>ghm737</Username><Timestamp>1366661989047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366663777175-91</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure they all got a good laugh at your expense! You must win "the pansy of the party award" every year.....</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366663777175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366664151601-92</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look how stupid the liberals are that post here. For example, the Kent raven posts under many aliases, talking to himself all day and night, thinking that nobody can tell the difference.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366664151601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366664755922-93</Id><Title>Happy Earth Day: Anti-Fracking Activists Block Farmers From Entering Film Festival About Their Lives</Title><Msg>Police were called to the Tribeca Film Festival over the weekend as anti-fracking activists blocked farmers from seeing a film about their lives. Some farmers left their homes as early as 4:30 a.m. to attend the new film Gasland 2 in New York City, yet were denied access when they arrived. Despite holding tickets to Gasland 2 (Gasland 1 has been debunked by FrackNation, a film by Ann McElhinney and Phelim McAleer), farmers were denied entry. Why? Because they dared to ask Director Josh Fox and Yoko Ono questions when they were posing for the cameras on the red carpet. "The Tribeca Film Festival likes to position itself as edgy but wants to quash a couple of farmers and give the red carpet to Yoko Ono and millionaire anti fracking activists," McAleer wrote in an email.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366664755922</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366664816651-94</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones is phoning it in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366582876616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 18:21:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump</Msg><Username>wellsaid_1234</Username><Timestamp>1366664816651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366664837372-95</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump.</Msg><Username>wellsaid_1234</Username><Timestamp>1366664837372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366665374320-96</Id><Title>The Raven's Religion is Obviously.....</Title><Msg>.....Communism.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366665374320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366665594648-97</Id><Title>Atheists Still Trying to Prove Something can Come From Nothing.</Title><Msg>.....seems hard to believe. Believing that would take a lot of faith.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366665594648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366666256570-98</Id><Title>Jesus Loves the #$%$. but he hates Hom*ism</Title><Msg>Don't for get what he did to Sodom and Gomorrah.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366666256570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366666917556-99</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Psychologists would say this type of hazing is an early human, but unreliable, way for people to know if they can count on each other in a pinch. People think if they are like minded they can count on each other. What many don't realize is when many people disagree they remain silent. The hazer takes this as agreement, only to be dismayed later when he finds he has no backing during an unjustified bullying event. In a roundabout way, it's why Christians think they like Christians and why cowboys like cowboys. They think they know more how like minded people will behave, and can relax more around them.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366666917556</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366667042609-100</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TORONTO (AP) — Two men were arrested and charged with plotting a terrorist attack against a Canadian passenger train with support from al-Qaida "elements" in Iran, police said Monday. Chiheb Esseghaier, 30, and Raed Jaser, 35, who live in Montreal and Toronto, were planning to derail a Via Rail passenger train in Toronto but posed no immediate threat, the Royal Canadian Mounted Police said. "This is the first known al-Qaida planned attack that we've experienced in Canada," Superintendent Doug Best told a news conference. RCMP Assistant Commissioner James Malizia said the two men had "direction and guidance" from "al-Qaida elements located in Iran," though there was no reason to think the planned attacks were state-sponsored. Police said the men did not get financial support from al-Qaida, but declined to provide more details.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366667042609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366667506523-101</Id><Topic><Title>Charleston 787 flights start</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366645892809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:51:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more production lines at Everett</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366667506523</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366668647601-102</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your response is one of irationalism and emotion and ignores science and statistical evidence. Nothing offered by you, Obama, Biden and the rest of the Dems has been shown to be an effective deterrent to mass murder. Nothing offered thus far would do anything to change the outcomes in Sandy Hook Columbine,,etc. Police had more information than new regulations would provide including a written warning by a psychologist that James Holmes was planning a mass murder. Why was he able to succeed and what would have changed with any further restrictions offered by Barry? You are still basing your views on nothing more than projection and emotion. I'm not interested in losing rights just so Barry can score political points like you are. My reason for pointing out the homicide rates is that you continue to ignore the statistics of what is skewing the high homicide rates in the US. The real problem isn't White conservatives or White liberals so taking their semi automatic weapons away and limiting their magazine capacity isn't going to help reduce high homicide rates in the US. You choose to be ignorant of the real cause of high crime despite all the evidence and you don't want to accept that Blacks and Hispanics are responsible for high homicide rates in the US. You're the only racist here as you ignore that Whites in the US have homicide rates similar to other homogeneous societies like Japan and Germany where there are no Blacks and Hispanics shooting up the streets. How and when did you become such an emotional, factless, idiot hell bent on denying the rights of law abiding citizens and playing the race card?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366668647601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:10:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366669602672-103</Id><Title>Boeing Board Baggerazi</Title><Msg>The Boeing board baggerazi spend their days regurgitating republiwhoppers from RubeRadio and Foxvda. They are radicalized extremists who should be under FBI surveillance. Come to think about it , they probably are!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1366669602672</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366669874093-104</Id><Topic><Title>The Boston Terrorists were Muslims--Please Forward this to Chris Matthews</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366599120192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-21 22:52:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually Barry started the meme with his clutching bibles and guns nonsense. Chris "I'll never wash my thrilled leg" Matthews and the rest of Team Obama aka MSNBC, continue campaigning for Barry by repetitive reinforcement of the meme which seems to be effective on mindless twits still watching MSNBC (I stopped watching 5 years ago). How did you miss the meme?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366669874093</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366673866450-105</Id><Title>FBI in contact with Bomber after bombing and before fatal shooting....</Title><Msg>In a report released by Channel Four news in Britain, a reporter has revealed that the mother of the suspected Boston bombers has claimed that FBI officials contacted her eldest son after the bombing had taken place and before the shootout that claimed his life. Speaking with the suspects’ father, Anzor, reporter Nick Sturdee says that the father claims Tamerlan contacted his mother, Zubeidat Tsarnaeva, two or three days after the bombing. According to Sturdee’s report, “Tamerlan told her the FBI had just rung him and accused him of being behind the attacks, and that he had responded by saying ‘that’s your problem’”. The report states that “The FBI in Boston told Channel 4 News they currently won’t confirm or deny any claims about their involvement.” However, a further AP report states that “The FBI is strongly refuting a report by Britain’s Channel 4 News that Tamerlan Tsarnaev was contacted by federal agents last week.” “Story is false,” a spokeswoman for the agency said in an email response to a Boston Herald inquiry. Although this information will likely never be verified, it does suggest even more evidence that the FBI knowingly lied to the public when officials claimed that they did not know who the suspects were upon releasing pictures of them at the scene of the bombing. Channel Four news has clearly put its weight behind the information because it fits with everything else the suspects’ parents have said thus far. Both have claimed that their sons were framed, with the mother going into detail about how the FBI were regularly in contact with Tamerlan for three to five years. The FBI was forced to admit that it had previously had contact with Tamerlan Tsarnaev in 2011, but only after officials first denied the claims made by the mother. The change of story from the FBI came when the media, particularly RT (Russia Today), began to further investigate the matter. It also emerged that Russian officials contacted the FBI last year regarding Tamerlan’s visit, ask</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366673866450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 19:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366675056054-106</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz said, "I think Hitler once said that, too. You and Adolf think pretty much the... More" Hooz Hitler never said anything remotely similar to what I said and you are also suffering brain damage and an inability to separate reality from your imagination. But since you brought up Hitler let's see if you know who said this: pg. 403 of Mein Kampf - " as long as the government is perceived as working for the benefit of the children, the people will happily endure almost any curtailment of liberty and any deprivation." Hitler can also be seen in photos with children as a backdrop when signing his gun bans. Isn't it fascinating that Barry stepped atop the dead bodies of children to push his anti gun agenda in a manner so eerily similar to Hitler's actions? Barry believes in his heart that no Americans should own guns and he expressed those sentiments as a professor at University of Chicago to another professor. But you don't know #$%$ about Barry and you prefer an existence of willful ignorance and fanatical allegiance. All that you need now is a brown shirt Hooz.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366675056054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 19:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366675753809-107</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey dob sas your outrageously racist rhetoric is about all you have- you sure as h dont have logic-- your primary lie is that white gun homicide is similar to Britain and Japan- when in fact its not but is vastly higher. Your statments that blacks and other non whites are responsible for the high gun homicides is so racist the world would cringe if they heard it. You imply that since that is the case its ok to continue to have the high gun homicide rates because you dont think of blacks as people- so whats the difference between you and Hittler, Himmler, Heydrich and the rest of the Nazzzie butchers--put that in your nose</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366675753809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366677871929-108</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're now clearly in a drug induced state imagining that facts about race equate to racism. I clearly stated that the UK shifted from guns to other methods of homicides and that the overall homicide rates were similar. Why would the world cringe at the truth about the higher rates of homicide offenders among Blacks and Hispanics? Please explain why facts don't matter. These other countries don't have the population of Blacks and Hispanics that the US does. From a scientific standpoint you chose to compare apples and oranges and I made it more of an apples to apples comparison. That' not racist at all. I didn't say it's OK to have high rates of Black Homicides (only you did). I said further gun restrictions that you and Barry want to place on law abiding citizens wouldn't resolve mass murder or other murders. The difference between me and the Nazis is that I want law abiding citizens to enjoy their Constitutional right to own guns and not have the equivalent of the SS invading the privacy rights of Americans. You and Barry on the other hand are the ones that share Hitler's ideology in wanting to deny Constitutional rights of freedom to own guns and the right to privacy. You're a brown shirt with the same basic ideology as Hitler but you are so stupid that even as you embrace Hitler like tactics by Barry to reduce Constitutional rights of law abiding Americans, you project your brown shirt enthusiasm on others.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366677871929</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366678128323-109</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz chi Minh, a Kent Raven alias in charge of propaganda, quoting his favorite national socialist, Adolph, to try to make a point and win a debate. What a pathetic little pansy.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366678128323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366678344344-110</Id><Title>does Domerrrrr45 opinion and his statement that Boeing is a cash machine mean much? bark and ouch no</Title><Msg>Domerrrrr45, first of all you claim Airbus is priced to crash and burn, wow for 20 years that has not happened, however the Boeing 787 lithium battery has smoked and been on fire, reality check For 5 years Boeing Stock has returned only Second Domerrrrr45 your motivation is clear, you consider any truthful comment about Boeing as a personal attack , here is your other opinion "WAYNEDICK.... by domerrrrr45 • Feb 7, 2013 3:50 PM Flag Plain and simple...u bash boeing i will bash you take it to the bank... and have you noticed the stock price $ 77+? Sentiment: Strong Buy SO DOMERRRRR45, HERE IS MY REPLY TO YOUR OPINION THAT BOEING IS A CASH MACHINE AND WHY YOU ARE, AS USUAL WRONG, IF THAT WERE IMPORTANT THEN APPLE WOULD NOT BE DOWN FROM 700 TO UNDER 400, APPLE HAS 34 BILLION FREE CASH FLOW BOEING HAS 7.5 BILLION SO IN TERMS OF CASH MACHINE THAT STATISTIC IS NOT ANY GOOD, GET IT NOW DOMERRRRR45? LET ME EXPLAIN IT TO YOU THE 787 IS LATE BY 4 YEARS LIKE THE MAP DID NOT WORK FOR APPLE , ITS FAILURE TO MEET EXPECTATIONS GET IT NOW ? APPLE AND BOEING NO GOOD. Next As to your opinion about Boeing for five days Airbus is up 7% and Boeing is not Boeing is up only .20 of 1 percent, for YTD Airbus is up 30% , Boeing is not , BA is up 15% on stock buyback only, Airbus just approved 15% stock buy back and will wait until it needs to use it. for 5 years Airbus is up 120% Boeing is not infact Boeing is up a pathetic 5% in five years. Now domerrrrr45 and foulmoutharbor those are facts. CNN money stock chart is easy to sue . ACAD is up OVER 8% TODAY AND 182% YTD AND FOR ONE YEAR UP 788% THAT IS A FACT. YOU SIR, HAVE A PERSONAL PROBLEM WITH REALITY WHEN IT COMES TO INVESTING IN BOEING THAT IS YOUR PROBLEM NOT MINE! AND YES FOR 15 YEARS APPLE, UNTIL STEVE JOBS DIED WAS ALSO A MUCH BETTER STOCK THAN BOEING. CASH MACHINE IS ONLY GOOD IF IT TRANSLATED TO SHAREHOLDER STOCK PRICE INCREASE AND THAT LIKE THE 787 FLYING MEANS NOTHING APPLE FOR EXAMPLE HAS</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366678344344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366678558382-111</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another flaccid post by chemical ali infested, truly worthy of scorn. Sheesh. "more humane shooting someone rather than strangling them ...." This specifically and permanently puts chemical ali infested in the "megadoofus" crowd.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1366678558382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366678706331-112</Id><Topic><Title>does Domerrrrr45 opinion and his statement that Boeing is a cash machine mean much? bark and ouch no</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366678344344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:52:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>writing a book again waynedick?.....not my opinion...an airline analyst in motley fool! ...and he is right w/ his numbers ...no doubt about that waynedick! keep writing....</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1366678706331</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366678916619-113</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world would be a better place if chemical ali infested returned to Baghdad. Or his cave near Kirkuk.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1366678916619</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366680078206-114</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Obama calls for assault-weapons ban, background checks' David Jackson and Aamer Madhani, USA TODAY6:34 p.m. EST January 16, 2013 hooz_genna_talia -That was the headline in USA Today. Barry had every intention of banning semi-automatic rifles. Barry also expressed that Americans shouldn't be allowed to own guns when he was at U of C. You suffer from selective amnesia. Feinstein is also on record saying she would have banned all guns if she had the votes in the Senate. When are you going to stop lying to yourself and admit what everyone already knows, that Progressives want to ban all guns? It's obvious that Nazis and Progressives only want governments to have guns.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366680078206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366680225306-115</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest myths from the Boston Marathon bombing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366670331109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:38:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$..."myth" and his A_N_O_I_N_T_E_D W_O_N's ilk are ALL ABOUT "myths" whilst #$%$ are caught red handed murderin_g Americans in their profusely professed j_ihad program! And damned be an obvious truth in a little Dim mind!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1366680225306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366680396141-116</Id><Topic><Title>Senator Told Shooting Victim’s Mother He Supported Background Checks, Then Voted Against Them</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366678172183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:49:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guns for #$%$ but not for Americans #$%$? Really? You are definitely sicker than I originally thought!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1366680396141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366680514037-117</Id><Topic><Title>Former aide: Bachmann approved illegal payments</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366680219385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:23:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the ##$%$ A_N_O_I_N_T_E_D W_O_N is going to push forward with HIS "Dream"?</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1366680514037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366681239806-118</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ali, you do not just want law abiding citizens to own guns. You want anyone to own guns free from background checks, including felons and mentally ill.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366681239806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366681269595-119</Id><Title>Progressives are fine with the deaths of children due to after birth infanticide</Title><Msg>Progressives don't want to do any background checks on Planned Parenthood and they murder far more children than assault rifle owners. Why the huge double standard?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366681269595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366681885424-120</Id><Topic><Title>Senator Told Shooting Victim’s Mother He Supported Background Checks, Then Voted Against Them</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366678172183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:49:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your use of the pronoun "I" and "thought" in the same sentence would be hilarious if you had not used the qualifying adverb "originally."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366681885424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366682044706-121</Id><Topic><Title>No Gun Licenses for Marathon Bombers</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366637683696</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2010 a mass murderer killed 12 people and injured 17 more in Britain. He was gay. Should background checks screen out gay people as they have higher rates of depression, a common trait of mass murderers? Is that acceptable to you?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366682044706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 21:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366686789680-122</Id><Topic><Title>FBI in contact with Bomber after bombing and before fatal shooting....</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366673866450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 19:37:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This time Spartacus has typed a total falsehood. Doesn't even live up to Sparty's typically unbelievably low standards. Seek help, boy.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1366686789680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366687373024-123</Id><Topic><Title>does Domerrrrr45 opinion and his statement that Boeing is a cash machine mean much? bark and ouch no</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366678344344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:52:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45, so your opinion is that the airline analyst is right and therefore that is your opinion , righ ? t So your opinion is stuck in the future not now. domerrrrr45, you just said he was right , so that is your opinion. The thing about analysts , they are pimps for the stock market and usually want you to be invested in anything. They don't care if you lose or make money , they are paid on investments. Domerrr45, for example, the real estate market was fueled by prognosticators who said the real estate market would go up. But really what was happening was when a dummy - domerrrrr45, purchased a house the commission was paid up front. Domerrrr45, that is what your analyst is doing to you, if you buy Boeing, at any time long or short guess what , up front you pay a commission get it now ? , you really need to learn how to read a stock chart and form your own opinion. And once more your rotten note does not work, you still have no valid reason to think that an analyst is right about the future, looking at today and reading a stock chart is the way to figure it out. Geez you really need to learn, are you that wet behind the ears ??? Look at a stock chart , it is more accurate and you have seen the numbers. BA 5 years up 5%, Airbus five years up 120%, airbus has made more money for their shareholders in the last 5 trade days than Boeing has made for their shareholders in 5 years. Domerrrrr45, if you continue to hope and not read a stock chart your going to get exactly what you deserve, learn to make trades based upon information that means something. To think that your going on a analyst that claims to know the future is insane . You can look at their opinion but then you need to understand key statistics for yoru stock and the trend of the Boeing management meeting their promises and that is the key issue here . the CEO said 4 years ago at launch the 787 would be flying in a couple of months, now his word is mud. Same with apple</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366687373024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366687686140-124</Id><Topic><Title>FBI in contact with Bomber after bombing and before fatal shooting....</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366673866450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 19:37:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Channel 4 News in Britain: "Both have claimed that their sons were framed, with the mother going into detail about how the FBI were regularly in contact with Tamerlan for three to five years." MPT A FALSEHOOD....from the boys own parents....DEAL WITH IT SPIN DOCTOR</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366687686140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366687774382-125</Id><Topic><Title>The Raven's Religion is Obviously.....</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1366665374320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and devoutly practices</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366687774382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366687785887-126</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Board Baggerazi</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1366669602672</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With obama in the WH we are all under surveillance, unless your a fanatical Islamist - then you get a pass.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1366687785887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366688081217-127</Id><Topic><Title>Biggest myths from the Boston Marathon bombing</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366670331109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:38:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW...I predicted that you would have a Mainstreama media article that is in FULL HISTORY RECONSTRUCTION MODE...the establishment is in full underwear melt down to cover this up..Actually Beck at FIRST was calling Jones a nut job ..buit now is AGREEING WITH HIM AFTER INVESTIGATING THIS STORY TO ITS LOGICAL CONCLUSION...It just gets better and better</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366688081217</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366688195579-128</Id><Topic><Title>Bulky Bob ........................... Proof of Heaven</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366463637747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:13:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HEY IDIDOT...THE TITLE ""PROOF OF HEAVEN" is the title of the book...its on the New York Time Best seller list.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366688195579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:36:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366688879353-129</Id><Title>Seventeen UnAnswered Questions about the Boston Bombing</Title><Msg>#1 Why were runners being told that a bomb squad drill was taking place during the Boston Marathon? The following is from an article by Natural News… #2 Why did authorities deny that a bomb squad drill was being held? #3 According to The Mirror, the FBI is reportedly “hunting” a 12-strong terrorist “sleeper cell” that Tamerlan and Dzhokhar Tsarnaev were allegedly a part of… #4 CBS News is reporting that the FBI interviewed Tamerlan Tsarnaev back in 2011. The mother of the two Tsarnaev brothers insists that the FBI had been in contact with them for up to five years. At first, the FBI denied any previous contact with the two suspects. Will we ever learn the true scope of the previous relationship between the FBI and the Tsarnaev brothers? #5 Debka is reporting that the Tsarnaev brothers were “double agents” which had been “hired by US and Saudi intelligence to penetrate the Wahhabi jihadist networks which, helped by Saudi financial institutions, had spread across the restive Russian Caucasian.” Could this possibly be true? If so, will the American people be told the truth about these links? #6 According to their uncle, there were “mentors” that “radicalized” the Tsarnaev brothers. So precisely who were those “mentors”? #8 Were the Tsarnaev brothers in contact with a rebel leader named Doku Umarov who is known as “Russia’s Bin Laden #9 Did Tamerlan Tsarnaev post a video on YouTube last summer that expresses a belief that the 12th Imam, Mahdi, will soon come and that an Islamic army with black flags with arise out of a province in Iran known as Khorasan? #10 Why aren’t we being told that the “pressure cooker bombs” used in the Boston Marathon attacks are very similar to the kind of pressure cooker bombs that are commonly used in the Middle East?…</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366688879353</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:47:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366689360463-130</Id><Topic><Title>Seventeen UnAnswered Questions about the Boston Bombing</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366688879353</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:47:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More importantly, when are you going to make something of your sorry, so-called "life?" Get busy. You can be a man some day, with a little help and perhaps some lithium.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1366689360463</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>