<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366863240657-1</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imean, look at the facts, boys and girls! We already know the Bush administration was itching to go to war in Iraq, now, don't we? Yes, indeed we do, my darling ones! The Downing Street memo proves that beyond a shadow of a doubt. Then you look at the Presidential Daily Briefing of Aug. 6, 2001, the one headlined "Bin Laden Determined to Strike in U.S." Ignored! Why, children, they threw that briefing aside like used wrapping paper on Christmas morning, didn't they? And remember, sweet little ones, Bin Laden never claimed responsibility for the attacks until 2004. Do you know how many years that is, boys and girls? Something was up the government's sleeve, and I'll let you in on a little secret: It wasn't sugar plums, oh, no! No, it was the ties between the bin Laden and Bush families. They've been under the mistletoe for decades, if you catch your old pal Kris Kringle's meaning! I've checked my list twice, and it seems Arbusto Energy, a Bush business, had financial connections to Salem bin Laden, half-brother of Osama. The CIA actually helped create and fund al-Qaeda right around the time Bush Senior was the agency’s director—Now, as for the towers themselves: The type of steel they used melts at a temperature of about 2,700 degrees Fahrenheit, and as I'm sure all you smart little boys and girls know, jet fuel burns at 1,500 degrees, tops. My darlings, you'd need quite a Yule log to create that extra 1,200 degrees, wouldn't you? Oh, what a glorious sight it would be! Of course, you do know what they found in the Ground Zero debris, don't you? Would you like St. Nicholas to tell you? Well, then, hop up on his lap and I'll whisper it in your ear: traces of nano-thermite. Does that jingle any bells upstairs? Nano-thermite is an explosive compound, children, capable of making the biggest Christmas cracker you ever saw! So what in the name of Donner and Blitzen was it doing in the world's largest ba</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366863240657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366863487179-2</Id><Title>Obama to American People: "My Will...Not Yours !!"</Title><Msg>In 2009, over 70% of the American people said they did not want Obamacare, but did Obama listen to the American people? No! He pushed it through against the will of the American people and now we are all paying for it, literally. Obamacare is already costing most Americans thousands of dollars more for healthcare, when we were promised it would keep costs down. It’s also costing thousands of Americans their jobs as employers lay people off because of their increased costs. Millions of Americans are losing their employer provided healthcare benefits because of the increased costs to employers. The vast majority of Americans want our international borders secured, especially the border with Mexico. Arizona Gov. Jan Brewer asked the Obama administration to take action to secure the border and stop the flood of illegal drugs and aliens. The only action Obama took was placing road signs along Arizona highways telling them that it could be dangerous to travel in the southern portions of the state and drastically reducing the number of National Guard troops along the border. When she passed state laws to protect her state, Obama challenged them in court. Another act of Obama’s will to surpass the will of the American people is evident in the White House announcement that they are filing an amicus brief with the US Supreme Court to overturn California’s Proposition 8. In 2008, the people of California voted in favor of Prop 8 which defines marriage as one man with one woman and bans same-sex marriages. The measure went to the citizens of the state and their voices were heard at the polling booths. California is not the only state that has banned same-sex marriages. There are 37 other states with laws banning same-sex marriage. That should say a lot about the will of the people. But Obama doesn’t care about the will of the people. He only cares about</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366863487179</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366868968085-3</Id><Topic><Title>By the time battery issue is resolved., BA is at 100</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363361940809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without 787, BA almost made 1.8$... Just wait until 787 taking off,, 120. People... This is not pumping. this is truth...</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1366868968085</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 01:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366870096513-4</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Tells WA Residents to Just Shut Up and Eat Their Mercury</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366824031721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 13:20:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like those who've given this post a thumbs down. They just have too much mercury in their brains.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366870096513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 02:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366880145981-5</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Tells WA Residents to Just Shut Up and Eat Their Mercury</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366824031721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 13:20:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Chrissie alias trying to be funny, but only sounding dumbed down.........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366880145981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366880259236-6</Id><Topic><Title>Whe do Liberals hate the TEA Party so much?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366743222076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 14:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are comrades of Hooz Chi Minh, the ba board communist from Kent.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366880259236</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366880345216-7</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366856940486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:29:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't that what all Communists and Nazis have done?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366880345216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366880393970-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to American People: "My Will...Not Yours !!"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366863487179</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals love dictators.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366880393970</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 04:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366882165508-9</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you mean is listen to my uninformed rant and pretend it's facts . George Bush was asked today on Cspan, "What was the worst thing about your presidency ?" His answer, "Being a war-time President, I did not expect it, and I did not want it ." He was then asked what was the worst thing he had to do ? With-out a microseconds hesitation he answered, "Sending American troops into combat ." You see Sparty-boy, despite all your call sign pretensions, you don't have the right stuff . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366882165508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 05:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366886933701-10</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a difference between going to War because America was under attack....and going to war to increase Halliburton profits....I sure dint profit...and the boys I see regularly with blown off legs and broken psyches did not profit either.... It takes nothing for a spoiled rich kid to send troops off to war when Dubya missed his OWN war in the 70s isitting on an Alabama bar stool...so unless you believe the WMDs will be found any day now...Iraq was a total three trillion dollar waste.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366886933701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 06:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366887990448-11</Id><Title>BEFORE Boston bombing: "Stay alert..stay calm...this is all part of the drill"</Title><Msg>ALL CONFIRMED.... “At the STARTt at the event, at the Athlete’s Village, there were people on the roof looking down onto the Village at the start. There were dogs with their handlers going around sniffing for explosives, and we were told on a LOUD ANNOUNCEMENT that we shouldn’t be concerned and that it was just a drill. And maybe it was just a drill, but I’ve never seen anything like that — not at any marathon that I’ve ever been to. You know, that just concerned me that that’s the only race that I’ve seen in my life where they had dogs sniffing for explosions, and that’s the only place where there had been explosions.” INSIDE JOB</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366887990448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366888271535-12</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are Killing America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366832281958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 15:38:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Team is exactly right and you are a naïve fool. It would be nice if Barry got tough on radical Islamic jihadists and remove law abiding Americans who just want their Constitutional rights respected, from Barry's enemies list.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366888271535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366888940356-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to American People: "My Will...Not Yours !!"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366863487179</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberal is the root word or Liberty.....the ORIGINAL "liberals" were John Adams and T Jefferson...lovers of Liberty....In true Orwellian fashion liberals have ruined the word....and are NOW authoritarians and socialists....telling OTHERS how to live their lives and FORCING policies that are freedom crushing</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366888940356</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366889538730-14</Id><Topic><Title>BEFORE Boston bombing: "Stay alert..stay calm...this is all part of the drill"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366887990448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I see video of the people interviewed at the race many made comments about how odd it was that there was a "drill" in progress during race day. They had never experienced such a thing before during a marathon race and they seemed incredulous. The MSM has just rolled over and gone to sleep on the matter as usual. I have no doubt that IF it had been a "McVeigh type" incident, the MSM would have had all sorts conspiracy theories tying the terrorist act to ALL conservatives and it would have been dragged on for months. Hell they were already coming up with conservative conspiracies before there were any suspects. Now that it's radical Is lam Jihadists behind the bombing, The "in the tank for Barry" media are pushing the lone wolf meme and saying case closed. Our government and our news agencies are failing "We The People".</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366889538730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:32:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366889849985-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to American People: "My Will...Not Yours !!"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366863487179</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 00:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry was big on bragging that he would bring fundamental change to America. Who knew fundamental change would turn out to be "code" for dismantling the Constitution.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366889849985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366890153515-16</Id><Topic><Title>BEFORE Boston bombing: "Stay alert..stay calm...this is all part of the drill"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366887990448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think they got outed...and Drudge and Alex Jones FORCED them to change the narrative.....they caught on videotape 2 guiys who were part of the drill with Blackwater hats (complete with skulls and backpacks)...leaving the area without their backpacks...and had also been talking to the Russians/patsies earlier...the MSM knew they had to change the story...but it looked like a conservative Tim McVeigh type was originally being set up to take the fall.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366890153515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366890294210-17</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366856940486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:29:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roger that</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366890294210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 07:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366891470462-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Welfare State -- Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1366822495260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mobros have no qualms about taking advantage of porous borders and immigration preference to take advantage of the stupid American/Westerner welfare states, it’s another means to their end, and just like post cold war communists they’ve seized the opportunity to destroy their adversaries from within. Old news for the UK and Europe in collapse. Sparty hasn’t worked a real job since I first noticed his disinformation campaign on the BA board, has to be near a decade by now.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366891470462</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366892251478-19</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing nice jump today in stock price</Title><Username>fred.white72</Username><Timestamp>1366820844312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:27:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If not happy waynedick...u can easily go to airbus boards and talk your garbage there and drop the boeing boards...oh no.. It can't be done....you waynedick have an agenda...cause u were let go by boeing..sadly or maybe not! Is it true you made $ 28 million in apple stock? You and fred? Lol!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1366892251478</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:17:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366892357476-20</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The job of being President is too big for any man or woman. I do not fault Obama for the terrorist attack in Boston anymore than I do Bush for 9/11. In the same way I do not fault Bush for not keeping the economy safe at near the end of his Presidency. Its what the President's do when confronted with these unwanted events that rates the President, both deserve high marks.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366892357476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366892941628-21</Id><Topic><Title>Whe do Liberals hate the TEA Party so much?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366743222076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 14:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey dumbbsas how do you pay for it yourself when you have diabetes or heart disease- they wont even sell it to youl you should know this if you had ever been dropped for you mental disease you got to be the dumbest jackoff on the planet not to know these things</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366892941628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366893044272-22</Id><Topic><Title>Whe do Liberals hate the TEA Party so much?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366743222076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 14:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason mental midgets such as yourself still exist is because of the safety nets the Democrats have provided for you- otherwise if left to the Pukes you would have been allowed to die in the gutter decades ago</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366893044272</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366893192793-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Welfare State -- Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1366822495260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if the Bushites had gotten busy and deported this guy he wouldn't have been receiving welfare- conservativism is truly a mental disorder</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366893192793</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366893285136-24</Id><Title>The ignorant racist #$%$ state--Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Msg>RWNJs sold these characters their explosives without a back ground check----dumbbsases</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366893285136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366893292552-25</Id><Topic><Title>Whe do Liberals hate the TEA Party so much?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366743222076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 14:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha Ha Ha! YOU sound like an angry little perverted pansy! Ha Ha Ha!</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366893292552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366893295439-26</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does Bush get a total freaking pass on the first worst attack in US history that killed 3,000 people on his watch, especially since the 9/11 Commission concluded that 6 of the 10 major missed opportunities to prevent 9/11 occurred under Mr. Kept Us Safe's watch?...We're just supposed to give him a mulligan on that?</Msg><Username>chsacs</Username><Timestamp>1366893295439</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366893340766-27</Id><Topic><Title>The Welfare State -- Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1366822495260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sissyboy zosima, just another DFC............from Kent...........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366893340766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:35:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366893479929-28</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why did they ignore russian intel? fact IS we know he could do a MUCH better job of securing the borders and defining the ENEMY. our WORST enemy (by virtue of the office he holds and manner in which he uses it) currently occupies the white house (when he's not campaigning/fund raising or vacationing). suicide has replaced auto accidents as the no 1 cause of death in the USA (not including abortion).</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366893479929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366893739401-29</Id><Topic><Title>The Welfare State -- Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1366822495260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>davy, you related to sparty, he's quick to cover for mobros and welfare statists too</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366893739401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366893932687-30</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The teahadists have a short memory when it comes to the number of terrorist attacks during dubyah’s failed reign: 1. 9/11 2. DC Sniper Terrorist Shootings 3. Anthrax attacks 4. Shoe bomber (albeit, i failed) 5. Center for Urban Horticulture destroyed. ELF members plead guilty. 6. Tacoma, Washington abortion clinic bombing 7. Attack at LAX against El Al ticket counter 8. Hughes &amp; Dunahoe firebomb abortion clinic 9. Women’s Health Clinic bombed in Palm Beach burned 10. SUV attack at UNC 11. Seattle Jewish Federation shooting, Egyptian shoots six 12. McMenemy abortion clinic arson attempt. Not an actual clinic, he was mistaken. 13. IEDs tossed at Mexican Consulate in NYC. 14. Altman &amp; Baca arrested for the abortion clinic arson 15. Planned Parenthood arson in Virginia Beach, Virginia. 16. IED attacked attempted at women’s health clinic in Austin 17. Virginia Tech Shootings 18. Dr. Nicholas Barth right-wing terrorism in NY 19. Dr. Tiller killed at the hands of a right-wing terrorist who worshiped Fox News and O'Reilly 20. 12 embassy attacks under his watch (where is the fake Benghazi-like outrage?)</Msg><Username>chsacs</Username><Timestamp>1366893932687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366894391856-31</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>new whack job ID? still trying to find a violent tea party? has your welfare media been able to plant the image?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1366894391856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366894833570-32</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all planned during your democraptic messaih, mr. clinton............your freakin brainwashed, now go back in line for your welfare check</Msg><Username>hirtuism</Username><Timestamp>1366894833570</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366895062660-33</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The capacity of libs is an overload if it is two. Just one rattles around in a lot of empty space. GW Bush keep folks working, and unemployment regarded as FULL EMPLOYMENT (4.5% unemployed) because of his support for TAX REBATES for those that paid in fed. taxes. Fed. and state tax coffers overflowed under Bush....until the libs came up with their mortgages for flakes who couldn't pay them back, and that took down European countries as well.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366895062660</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366895273305-34</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And your memory? Why did Obama's buddy, Bill Ayers get a pass when he helped orchastrate a major New York City bombing?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366895273305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366895693217-35</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chechen terrorism was a Russian problem not a US problem since the collapse of the USSR. Chechen's want their freedom. America remained neutral. There was no reason to help one side or the other. That's why we did not take the Russian's requests seriously. What we did not know is that the two brothers had their own terrorism agenda inspired by al qeada jihadists. Information the FBI and CIA did not know.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1366895693217</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366896421772-36</Id><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Msg>love it !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366896421772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366896606683-37</Id><Topic><Title>By the time battery issue is resolved., BA is at 100</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363361940809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INDEED IT IS...</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1366896606683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366896964426-38</Id><Topic><Title>The ignorant racist #$%$ state--Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366893285136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do jihadists want to buy explosives and blow up people? All these years, 100+ million adults had the very same access to powder and no one else used it to blow people up. You want to blame law abiding Americans who are being responsible and follow the law and you ignore the REAL problem which is that our government knew these guys were radical Islamists and they didn't protect the American people.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366896964426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366898148889-39</Id><Topic><Title>I love it when I wake up in the morning and Obama is President !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366896421772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:27:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me too because with each new day I see Barry losing support, becoming more of a pariah and becoming less able to deprive law abiding Americans of the rights that our fathers, sisters and brothers fought to preserve .</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366898148889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 09:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366899031584-40</Id><Title>Poor Shorties don't know what to do!!</Title><Msg>Boeing is going to blast thru these shorts and a small squezze will raise this price up to the $94.00$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366899031584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366899142900-41</Id><Topic><Title>The ignorant racist #$%$ state--Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366893285136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zo, should we pass a law requiring background checks on all followers of Islam buying pressure cookers and anything else bombs can be made from?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366899142900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366899341434-42</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the REAL NEWS REPORTERS ASKING THE TUFF QUESTIONS ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366842342139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 18:25:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that the best you can do? I am sure in your delusional world that is considered clever. In the real world it is pathetic.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1366899341434</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366900828465-43</Id><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Msg>evidently, Tsarnaev was unarmed when arrested in boat...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366900906499-44</Id><Topic><Title>The ignorant racist #$%$ state--Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366893285136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RWNJ criminals want to sell deadly weapons to criminals and jihadists- stands to reason doesn't it the rest of the pukes just want to avoid background checks so they themselves don't get caught. These are the reasons the neocons RWNJs Baggers and pukes are soft on crime</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366900906499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366902157398-45</Id><Topic><Title>The ignorant racist #$%$ state--Financing Terrorism and Murder</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366893285136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 08:34:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to be unaware that RWNJs aren't committing mass murder. It is young people immersed in pop culture that become depressed and Islamic Jihadists doing all the killing. Did you see the poll of people in Boston who were asked if they wished that they had a gun during the manhunt for the little jihadist that escaped? 70% answered that wanted to be armed. Also of note is that observant people took note that trained professionals fired roughly 200 bullets to kill one jihadist. Trained professionals needed 200 rounds to take down one bad guy but idiots like you, I'm no Einstein Feinstein and Barry the brain damaged destroyer of Constitutional rights, think they know better and that law abiding citizens only need 3 to 7 bullets to defend their loved ones. You have it backwards Zo. Barry wants you helpless and unarmed and dependent on him for protection. It is the progressives that don't want the death penalty and are always eager to put criminals back on the street Zo. You've drumk too much hope change and forward Kool-Aid and you have become a brain dead fanatic.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366902157398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366903024021-46</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Tells WA Residents to Just Shut Up and Eat Their Mercury</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366824031721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 13:20:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Case in point....</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366903024021</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366903190904-47</Id><Topic><Title>By the time battery issue is resolved., BA is at 100</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363361940809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Osulin Its resolved lets get this flying$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366903190904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366903587333-48</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sharing with us your belief that the little jihadist is innocent is your best post yet. We need more like you for citizens to learn from your example how the mind of a fanatic can twist and mangle truth to the degree that a fanatic desires that law abiding citizens are deprived of Constitutional rights while giving jihadists the benefit of doubt that doesn't even exist. U.S.News &amp; World Report LP April 23, 2013 Tsnarnaev reportedly confessed before being read Miranda rights Dzhokhar Tsarnaev, 19, confessed Sunday to participating with his older brother Tamerlan in the April 15 Boston Marathon bomb attacks that killed three people, a law enforcement source told the Boston Globe. The Globe reports that Tsarnaev confessed before being read his Miranda rights, which in ordinary circumstances could result in the confession being thrown out of court. FBI investigcan ators chose not to read him these rights, which include the rights to remain silence and to have a lawyer, citing a "public safety exception." An explanation of the exception on the FBI's website says the U.S. Supreme Court ruled in the 1980 case New York v. Quarles that "failure to administer Miranda warnings does not, standing alone, make a confession involuntary in violation of the Constitution." ___________________________________________________________________________________---</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366903587333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366903878343-49</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing nice jump today in stock price</Title><Username>fred.white72</Username><Timestamp>1366820844312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:27:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991, so makes and means that you have hate for anyone who states the truth about boeing weather is is fred72,dell,fred j veronica wanye, and all the same people , oddly I am not fred 72 , domerrrrr45d,custerious,sparti 1-2-3-4-,uni1-2-3-4- and all the same people who apparently think that ignoring the facts about boeing and making up ficticious stories about me or other yahoo comments about users who they know nothing about changes the facts means something I guess it does to you guys not the other readers, the fact mean more and you can't stand the truth because anyone who goes to cnn money and uses the stock symbol for boeing ba or the stock symbol for airbus EADSY can verify my facts are right and yoru 150% for 4 years is total crapola btw boeing hit a statiically bottom as you know at about 55 and at 90 that is not a gain of 150% so again a and for the reading public here are the numbers , not on the airbus board which does not exist at the yahoo finance site so I use the Boeing site get it now ?????? for five days Boeing stock price is up 6.5% good for you, airbus stock up 4.3% good for them,for the yar to date boeing is up 22% good for you, airbus is up 33% better and good for them, for 3 years boing is no up 26% not so good for you, airbus is up 187% real good for airbus shareholders, for five years now boieng is up a pathetick 10.8% bad fro you and your friends and their several aka names, airbus is up 127% in five years better for them souce can money stock chart and too bad for you hat hate,hate,hate,just stew in your own hate , so now domerrrrr45 give me your rotten note and ama i writing a book and spart lie and say ba is really up 150% in 4 years instead of telling the truth ,you picked the absolut bottom to the absolut top a unreal story gain while I use a world wide stock chart that uses real numbers like 5 days ytd 3 year 5 year</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366903878343</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366904109439-50</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing nice jump today in stock price</Title><Username>fred.white72</Username><Timestamp>1366820844312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:27:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>false statement show your date and price and then your gain price and date and I will explain to the user group your false and misleading numbers sparticus I know your hate knows no bounds and you will do anything to make Boeing look good inspite of the problems with this company , you are living in a fantasy world , the newspaper reports of the grounding of the 787 and being over budget and late by 4 years are true , the stock being up only 10% in 5 years are correct , you sire are in denial</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366904109439</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366904294089-51</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me brainwashed? What a firkin pathetic excuse of a life you are. Why don't you go back in line to your Messiah Glenn Beck. hirtuism you are a Pathetic loser.</Msg><Username>chsacs</Username><Timestamp>1366904294089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366904341090-52</Id><Title>PPS</Title><Msg>Told my friends to buy this when it was 57$ I bet they would have listened to me. How could you not buy this up way back when it was only 57$ OMG</Msg><Username>williamkania</Username><Timestamp>1366904341090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366904619988-53</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing nice jump today in stock price</Title><Username>fred.white72</Username><Timestamp>1366820844312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:27:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45 and spartacus99991 wow similiar same pattern of sign on hummm well I just counted you guys with hate for wayne have 18 thumbs down so apparently the readers do not thing anything of the rrrrrrr and the 99999 and the custerious and the other boye friends personal attack and hate notes , they do like the statistics of the poor boeing performance over time so sorry BTW inviting me to go to the airbus message board, wow ouch and bark for you----- if you were a real stock trader then you would know that airbus does not have a message board here, wow another proof of incompetence by the hate wayne group----- bark and ouch for you guys again and par for the coarse Boeing up 10.8% for 5 years Airbus up 127% for 5 years and 187% for 3 years 33 % for YTD BA is up 22% ytd get it yet</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366904619988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366905782612-54</Id><Title>PPS just upgraded by Credit Susie $110. price Target!!</Title><Msg>Baby show me some WINGS$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366905782612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366905946182-55</Id><Topic><Title>PPS</Title><Username>williamkania</Username><Timestamp>1366904341090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 11:39:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smae price range I bought it back in August 2010 and some more at $70.00 last year and you hav'nt seen nothing yet, buying the dips$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366905946182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:05:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907476912-56</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing nice jump today in stock price</Title><Username>fred.white72</Username><Timestamp>1366820844312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:27:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sir waynedick....in denial everyday...everyday... With your books. You will lie everyday to make this great american icon who employs 170,000 americans except you...look bad... No reason for your daily lies and nonsense. Got it? go to airbus boards with your zillion id's!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1366907476912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366907697323-57</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing nice jump today in stock price</Title><Username>fred.white72</Username><Timestamp>1366820844312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 12:27:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, Wayne, Wayne, do we have to show you how to look up historical BA values? Go to the "historical prices" tab in BA Yahoo. Enter start dates from about Feb1, 2009 to end dates of about April 30, 2009. You will see that the bottom of 29.36 accured on March 3, 2009 for a gain of 213 percent to today's 92. My earlier post used the April 20, 2009 value of 36.48 to get the 4 year gain of about 150 percent. My math says 150 percent for 4 years is better than Airbus 127 percent gain in 5 years. It's OK to admit you make a mistake once in a while. You probably shouldn't call someone a liar until you have checked the facts.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1366907697323</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366908989571-58</Id><Title>Beltway Elites Planning to Exempt Themselves From ObamaCare</Title><Msg>It's no surprise to most people at this point that ObamaCare is a total trainwreck but apparently, it's so bad that both Republicans and Democrats working on Capitol Hill are trying to get themselves a waiver while the rest of the country scrambles to comply. Unreal: Congressional leaders in both parties are engaged in high-level, confidential talks about exempting lawmakers and Capitol Hill aides from the insurance exchanges they are mandated to join as part of President Barack Obama’s health care overhaul, sources in both parties said. The talks — which involve Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid (D-Nev.), House Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio), the Obama administration and other top lawmakers — are extraordinarily sensitive, with both sides acutely aware of the potential for political fallout from giving carve-outs from the hugely controversial law to 535 lawmakers and thousands of their aides. Discussions have stretched out for months, sources said. A source close to the talks says: “Everyone has to hold hands on this and jump, or nothing is going to get done.” Yet if Capitol Hill leaders move forward with the plan, they risk being dubbed hypocrites by their political rivals and the American public. By removing themselves from a key Obamacare component, lawmakers and aides would be held to a different standard than the people who put them in office. Let's not forget about the historic 2010 overturn of the House when the main issue was ObamaCare. You can bet that if both parties go through with this move, Republicans can expect to be primaried while Democrats can kiss their seats goodbye....again. Not to mention, if both parties see the law as this big of a disaster, they should all vote to repeal it rather than exempting themselves while the rest of the country suffers. As I've written before, the best we can hope for is that ObamaCare collapses on itself as states refuse to implement ObamaCare exchanges, small businesses lay off workers and cut hours to avoid it and as health insurance costs skyrocket as a result of government overreach into the health insurance system.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366908989571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366909409316-59</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now them namby pamby dems are trying to regulate who can buy explosives! Started with guns now this! Where will it stop. We's gots a right to bear arms!</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1366909409316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910111968-60</Id><Topic><Title>Beltway Elites Planning to Exempt Themselves From ObamaCare</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366908989571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets get serious- NOBODY is required to join an insurance exchange- this is only an ignorant #$%$ lie Everybody is required to have health insurance States preventing health chare exchanges-- cant be done they are installed by the Federal Governmant if the states refuse to set up their own exchanges- looks like another ignorant #$%$ lie Boy turn the ignorant #$%$s loose and they will lie about the sun coming up in the morning</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366910111968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910201126-61</Id><Topic><Title>Beltway Elites Planning to Exempt Themselves From ObamaCare</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366908989571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBTW #$%$= #$%$ minus every other letter</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366910201126</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910268760-62</Id><Topic><Title>Beltway Elites Planning to Exempt Themselves From ObamaCare</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366908989571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how can I say #$%$-- one who has a very red appendage between his chin and his upper torso</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366910268760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910339519-63</Id><Topic><Title>Beltway Elites Planning to Exempt Themselves From ObamaCare</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366908989571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The is a toilet paper roll of exemptions these bureaucrats make laws we have to follow that they exempt themselves from following. But a slimy liberal wants to expand their powers not rain them in.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366910339519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910380921-64</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Shorties don't know what to do!!</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366899031584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just got out of the hospital. Glad to see the stock is up. Hope it continues.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366910380921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366910562598-65</Id><Topic><Title>Beltway Elites Planning to Exempt Themselves From ObamaCare</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366908989571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 12:56:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joedopes whats your IQ? about 37?? you sure are dumb if you believe that kraap</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366910562598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366910695874-66</Id><Title>Tough Titty WayneDickensen</Title><Msg>say bye to the 90's BA is headed for $150 HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366910695874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:24:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366910780234-67</Id><Title>Lawmakers passed Obamacare but they don't want it for themselves.</Title><Msg>What does it tell you when both sides of the aisle don't want Obamacare and Nan Pelosi is handing out waivers like popcorn? If you have two functioning brain cells left it should be enough to tell you that you've been had! lol 'Lawmakers, aides may get Obamacare exemption' Congressional leaders in both parties are engaged in high-level, confidential talks about exempting lawmakers and Capitol Hill aides from the insurance exchanges they are mandated to join as part of President Barack Obama’s health care overhaul, sources in both parties said. The talks — which involve Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid (D-Nev.), House Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio), the Obama administration and other top lawmakers — are extraordinarily sensitive, with both sides acutely aware of the potential for political fallout from giving carve-outs from the hugely controversial law to 535 lawmakers and thousands of their aides. Discussions have stretched out for months, sources said.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366910780234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366910813886-68</Id><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Msg>No regulations required! The dead and injured can just sue the owners. Oh, wait, they just declared bankruptcy...... Building Collapse in Bangladesh Leaves Scores Dead By JULFIKAR ALI MANIK and JIM YARDLEY New York Times April 24, 2013</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366911114652-69</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers passed Obamacare but they don't want it for themselves.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366910780234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>infested I guess your 37 IQ is catching up with you- in the first place Obama care is little more than a requirement for everybody to have insurance. If for some reason they cant afford it the Federal Govt provides health insurance exchanges where citizens can buy insurance at a reasonable rate with no one being barred for previous uninsurable illness. Legislators already have the best insurance in the world- Opt out of Obama Care?? what kind of gibberish is that?? is that the product of someone with a 37 IQ</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366911114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366911233090-70</Id><Topic><Title>Tough Titty WayneDickensen</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366910695874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:24:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talk about funny har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har harhar har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har harhar har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har har</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366911233090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366912443745-71</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers passed Obamacare but they don't want it for themselves.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366910780234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zo for you a 37 IQ score would be a doubling of your IQ. The version of Obamacare that you offer is some propaganda meant for spoon fed consumption by Low IQ folks still supporting Barry the liar. Behind closed congressional doors they are wondering #$%$ were we thinking". No one wants the reality, everyone wants an exemption and not even the people who dumped this garbage on honest Americans want it. Go join Hooz with your head in the sand or up his wazoo whichever makes you feel more intelligent.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366912443745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366912499346-72</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers passed Obamacare but they don't want it for themselves.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366910780234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, come on now. You're are going to sit there and tell us that you have read, studied and understand the 2,864,094 pages of Obamacare and say it is, "little more than a government requirement for everybody to have insurance". Dollars to donuts you didn't even know it is a (illegal) tax until the Supreme Court told you so. Chances are you, like most people including me, don't even fully comprehend your own current medical insurance policy. Only thing I'm sure of is my medical insurance costs are skyrocketing with decreasing coverage.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1366912499346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:54:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366912835623-73</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Shorties don't know what to do!!</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366899031584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope everthing went well at the hospital its going great here Boeing getting the Ok on the787 Plus earnings was great PPS getting revised up and the Upgrades will be following soon$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366912835623</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366912906860-74</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers passed Obamacare but they don't want it for themselves.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366910780234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you just love it when zosmia slams someone's s IQ that's at least 30 points higher than his!</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366912906860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:01:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366913059021-75</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers passed Obamacare but they don't want it for themselves.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366910780234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt if you are smart enough to double any number - BTW are you even a US citizen- you sound like a communist or maybe a Taliban militant- Its like I said- you will be required to get health insurance- and you wont have to part with your life savings to get it like you have it now- You will be able to go to the local Insurance exchange to buy the insurance if Hartford or somebody still wants to charge you 50,000$ a year for insureance(I can see why they would considering your mental incapacities)</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366913059021</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366913592004-76</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers passed Obamacare but they don't want it for themselves.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366910780234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you tell us how many pages it took to implement Medicare?? Medicaid etc</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366913592004</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366913858413-77</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the verdict will be determined by a court of law... not by cowards shooting at an unarmed man !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366913858413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:17:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366914094134-78</Id><Title>Library dedication to a Chimp</Title><Msg>DALLAS (Reuters) - Former President George W. Bush returns briefly to the U.S. political stage with the dedication of his presidential library on Thursday, an event that will offer Americans a fresh look at his eight storm-tossed years in the White House.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366914094134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366914706790-79</Id><Topic><Title>Lawmakers passed Obamacare but they don't want it for themselves.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366910780234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you know what's going on behind closed congressional doors? One thing about ObamaCare is people with coverage don't have to buy more coverage. Congress has coverage. I would like to see them have to secure their own, but probably won't happen. It's true: each state will offer insurance exchanges unless they opt out, which costs them. Everyone who doesn't already have insurance is supposed to get some by the end of this year. If they still don't want to, they can pay a penalty, which may be less than the cost of insurance, but will really bite them in the #$%$ if they need serious medical attention. The exchanges will be open in October.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366914706790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366915125249-80</Id><Topic><Title>Library dedication to a Chimp</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366914094134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:21:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, paintings by chimps are in high demand these days!</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1366915125249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366915439971-81</Id><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Msg>IRS Says the cheapest approved Obamacare policy will cost a family $20,000. The regulations attached to to the 2,700 page bill now is more than 20,000 pages and growing every day Law makers want to be exempted from the bill. The guy who wrote most of the bill has decided not to run in 2014. Obamacare is a socialist's nightmare.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366915559989-82</Id><Title>ENOUGH OF THE POLITILCALLY B S !!!!!!</Title><Msg>Can we not just talk about the stock at hand.... PLEASE !!! THANKS</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1366915559989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366915720066-83</Id><Topic><Title>ENOUGH OF THE POLITILCALLY B S !!!!!!</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1366915559989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:45:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just shouting the the wind to stop.</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1366915720066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:48:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366915907880-84</Id><Topic><Title>ENOUGH OF THE POLITILCALLY B S !!!!!!</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1366915559989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:45:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The increasing costs associated with Obamacare will hurt Boeings net income and dividends. You're welcome.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1366915907880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366915912804-85</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The guy who wrote most of the bill? Who was that? Communist Van Jones played a part in it as part of the Apallo Organization, a far leftist outfit. Who else helped write it? No one seems to know not even #$%$ Pelozi who is given credit for writing a lot of it.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366915912804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:51:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366916034082-86</Id><Topic><Title>63 % of Americans Doubt Michele Obama is part Gorilla</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1365178143567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 12:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Her husband's ears make him the new WH chimp.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366916034082</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366916513846-87</Id><Title>787 production cost reduction</Title><Msg>According to the NYC787 site, The per unit cost of producing each 787 has come down 60% from LN 8 to LN 100.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366916513846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366916758219-88</Id><Topic><Title>Library dedication to a Chimp</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366914094134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:21:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be jealous of the ivory chimp as the ebony chimp will get his turn. We've reserved space in the Lincoln Park Zoo Primate House in Chicago for Barry's library. There will be interactive exhibits where people can swing from trees in an environment reconstructed to look like Kenyan forests. There will be an interactive exhibit dedicated to photoshopping and forging documents. The "Man Country" section will contain a replica of the famous bath house room Barry frequented that is affectionately now known as the "Oral Office". The highlight of the library and surely the most popular will be the "Choom Gang Room" which will host live classes on how to grow weed and get high. A wide variety of weed will be available for visitors to sample including Barry's favorites. There will also be the "Children's Death and Taxes" exhibit with a life sized replica of Barry sitting on his hands in his early years as a Chicago politician watching kids getting gunned down on Chicago streets and voting present on every bill as well as a collection of legislation as president that caused national debt to skyrocket and bury future children in debt and taxes. It will be the bestest library ever. ROTFLMAO</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366916758219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366916776550-89</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wikipedia (edited) The Triangle Shirtwaist Factory fire in New York City on March 25, 1911 was the deadliest industrial disaster in the history of the city of New York. The fire caused the deaths of 146 garment workers, who died from the fire, smoke inhalation, or falling or jumping to their deaths. Most of the victims were recent Jewish and Italian immigrant women aged 14-23. Because the managers had locked the doors to the stairwells and exits – a common practice at the time to prevent pilferage and unauthorized breaks– many of the workers who could not escape the burning building jumped from the eighth, ninth, and tenth floors to the streets below. The fire led to legislation requiring improved factory safety standards and helped spur the growth of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, which fought for better working conditions for sweatshop workers. The company's owners, Max Blanck and Isaac Harris, who survived the fire by fleeing to the building's roof when the fire began, were indicted on charges of first- and second-degree manslaughter in mid-April; the pair's trial began on December 4, 1911. Max Steuer, counsel for the defendants, managed to destroy the credibility of one of the survivors, Kate Alterman, by asking her to repeat her testimony a number of times, which she did without altering key phrases. Steuer argued to the jury that Alterman and possibly other witnesses had memorized their statements, and might even have been told what to say by the prosecutors. The defense also stressed that the prosecution had failed to prove that the owners knew the exit doors were locked at the time in question. The prosecution was sent to the scene to find the locks of the doors in question. It was found that the locks were intended to be locked during working hours based on the findings from the fire. However the defense also stressed that the prosecution had failed to prove that the owners knew the exit doors were locked at the time in question.The jury acquitted the two men, but they lost a subsequent civil suit in 1913 in which plaintiffs won compensation in the amount of $75 per deceased victim. The insurance company paid Blanck and Harris about $60,000 more than the reported losses, or about $400 per casualty. In 1913, Blanck was once again arrested for locking the door in his factory during working hours. He was fined $20. Rose Schneiderman, a prominent socialist and union activist, gave a speech at the memorial meeting held in the Metropolitan Opera House on April 2, 1911, to an audience largely made up of the members of the Women's Trade Union League. She used the fire as an argument for factory workers to organize: “I would be a traitor to these poor burned bodies if I came here to talk good fellowship. We have tried you good people of the public and we have found you wanting.... We have tried you citizens; we are trying you now, and you have a couple of dollars for the sorrowing mothers, brothers and sisters by way of a charity gift. But every time the workers come out in the only way they know to protest against conditions which are unbearable the strong hand of the law is allowed to press down heavily upon us. Public officials have only words of warning to us—warning that we must be intensely peaceable, and they have the workhouse just back of all their warnings. The strong hand of the law beats us back, when we rise, into the conditions that make life unbearable. I can't talk fellowship to you who are gathered here. Too much blood has been spilled. I know from my experience it is up to the working people to save themselves. The only way they can save themselves is by a strong working-class movement."</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366916776550</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366916861633-90</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wikipedia (edited) The Triangle Shirtwaist Factory fire in New York City on March 25, 1911 was the deadliest industrial disaster in the history of the city of New York. The fire caused the deaths of 146 garment workers, who died from the fire, smoke inhalation, or falling or jumping to their deaths. Most of the victims were recent Jewish and Italian immigrant women aged 14-23. Because the managers had locked the doors to the stairwells and exits – a common practice at the time to prevent pilferage and unauthorized breaks– many of the workers who could not escape the burning building jumped from the eighth, ninth, and tenth floors to the streets below. The fire led to legislation requiring improved factory safety standards and helped spur the growth of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, which fought for better working conditions for sweatshop workers.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366916861633</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917082811-91</Id><Topic><Title>787 production cost reduction</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366916513846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cost might have gone down, but encasing a battery in steel will make them explosive rather than inflamable---this problem will not go away with that japanese battery.</Msg><Username>allouezsup</Username><Timestamp>1366917082811</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917200296-92</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like one of those readneck families of 20 or more with about as many fathers</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366917200296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917305889-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmmmmm Van Jones- anybody ever hear of him- didn't know he was a commie- he must be just like joedopes and the mediocre 37IQ guy</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366917305889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917544013-94</Id><Topic><Title>787 production cost reduction</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366916513846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>allouezsup, guess you have'nt been keeping up with the news so just cover your shorts.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366917544013</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917580322-95</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senator Baucus and Senator Reid wrote the bill mowrawn</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366917580322</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917602690-96</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? You must be a Dzhokhar or a comedian. You believe that the baby brother jidhast was not involved in the shooting of the MIT guard, the car jacking and the police shoot out? Why that woull mean that the FBI/DHS/local police were terrorizing the community looking for an innocent kid. Where do you live so can call 911 and send help locating your missing brain. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366917602690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917614771-97</Id><Topic><Title>ENOUGH OF THE POLITILCALLY B S !!!!!!</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1366915559989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:45:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cutt they screwed up GE message board also.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366917614771</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917695093-98</Id><Topic><Title>787 production cost reduction</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366916513846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the box is of course vented but if the gas comes out of it as fast as it comes out of some of the BA message boards mouths it could indeed be explosive</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366917695093</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917989372-99</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Times Square Targeted By Boston Marathon Bombing Suspects, FBI Says' "The Huffington Post" The brothers who allegedly detonated pressure cooker bombs at the Boston Marathon had rudimentary plans of traveling to New York for an attack on Times Square, according to New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg. Dzhokhar Tsarnaev, 19, told interrogators that he and his older brother, Tamerlan, intended to set off explosives in Manhattan, according to unnamed law enforcement officials who spoke to Reuters and NBC News. "Last night we were informed by the FBI that the surviving attacker revealed that New York City was next on their list of targets," said Bloomberg at a quickly organized press conference this afternoon. "We don't know if we'd been able to [stop an attack] if the terrorists had arrived from Boston. "Thank God we didn't have to do that," Bloomberg said in City Hall. "The fact is New York City remains a prime target for those who hate America and want to kill Americans." The FBI Joint Terrorism Task Force shared information with New York officials that the Tsarnaev brothers had six bombs, including one pressure cooker explosive like the bombs that killed three and wounded more than 280 at the marathon, and five pipe bombs. The brothers allegedly made a spontaneous decision to head to New York in a stolen Mercedes SUV last Thursday after the fatal shooting of an MIT campus police officer, Kelly said. The victim of the carjacking heard them brainstorming the idea as he was held captive in his Mercedes. The victim fled the car at a gas station and called police.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366917989372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:26:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366917996026-100</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If zosima ever climbs up to a double digit IQ he'll be dangerous.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366917996026</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366918352634-101</Id><Topic><Title>ENOUGH OF THE POLITILCALLY B S !!!!!!</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1366915559989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:45:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo supplies this nifty app called "ignore" which if activated will magically make all the political posters disappear and leaving only the Boing discussion posts visible to you. You should try it. I can instruct you if you need help finding the "ignore" feature.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366918352634</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366918557056-102</Id><Topic><Title>787 production cost reduction</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366916513846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>falmouth, you didn't have to stay in hospital? good.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366918557056</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366918966744-103</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot !! what do you Not understand "..the verdict will be determined by a court of law.." you remember what is a court of law dont ya ???</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366918966744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366919207090-104</Id><Title>This is an Stock Investment Board and Politics Effect Stocks</Title><Msg>This is not an airplane board so blow it out your #%&amp;* nose.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366919207090</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366919351662-105</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have not been able to find anything that suggests anyone would have to pay $20,000 for insurance under obamacare. And who would, when a person or family can get pretty good insurance for way less than that. Only the most ill person blacklisted from most insurance companies (which will no longer be allowed) would pay that kind of premium, or the most wealthy to whom it doesn't matter.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366919351662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366919519883-106</Id><Title>Spanish Unemployment Rate Soars to Record 27.16%...</Title><Msg>AFP - Spain's unemployment rate soared to a new record of 27.16 percent of the workforce in the first quarter of 2013 as the number of those without jobs surpassed six million, official data showed on Thursday. The unemployment rate jumped from 26.02 percent in the previous quarter. The number of unemployed climbed by 237,400 people to 6.2 million, the National Statistics Institute said. What are they doing that we aren't?........oh yea, they've had socialized medicine longer than we have.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366919519883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366919602428-107</Id><Title>stick.man007, Anzor Tsarnaev &amp; Zubeidat Tsarnaev think the Boston bomber boys were innocent.</Title><Msg>At a news conference Thursday in Russia, the mother of the accused Boston Marathon bombers suggested a conspiracy in which American police captured her older son alive and murdered him. Zubeidat Tsarnaev and the boys' father, Anzor Tsarnaev, told reporters in Dagestan that their children were innocent in the attack that killed three people and wounded more than 260 others. Though they have shown sympathy for the victims, the parents refuse to accept the mainstream storyline pieced together by authorities. She said that in the days after the Boston bombing she had seen what she described as video footage on the internet appearing to show Tamerlan alive and being put into a police car, naked, apparently stripped to check for explosives. The next day, she said, she saw gruesome images of his dead body. “Killed, truly killed,” she said, describing the images. “I wanted to scream, to scream to the whole world: ‘What did you do? What have you done with my son? He was alive. Why did they need to kill him? Why not send him to Guantánamo or whatever. Why did they kill him? Why did they have to kill him? They got him alive. He was in their hands.'” In the mean time Michael Bloomberg says that the surviving jihadist has been singing like a canary and that he confessed to plans to bomb NYC too. Of course Bloomberg could be making it all up to gain the attention of the national press.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366919602428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366920249781-108</Id><Topic><Title>stick.man007, Anzor Tsarnaev &amp; Zubeidat Tsarnaev think the Boston bomber boys were innocent.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366919602428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha - you're a child playing on the Internet... !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366920249781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366920964243-109</Id><Topic><Title>Spanish Unemployment Rate Soars to Record 27.16%...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366919519883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:51:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does anyone remember how Barry held Spain up as the green jobs envy of the world and how Barry implored us to adopt Spain's green jobs economy including cap and trade? Is Barry still pushing Americans to adopt Spain's green jobs economy? I know that the Dems Babs Boxer teamed up with socialist Bernie Sanders to try to resurrect the cap and tax insanity, but is Barry on board?.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366920964243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366921032859-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I was a mediocre mowrawn I wouldnt advertise the fact</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366921032859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366921036718-111</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Wikipedia - In October 2005 Jones said he was "a rowdy nationalist"[15] before the King verdict was announced, but that by August of that year (1992) he was a communist.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366921036718</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366921099337-112</Id><Topic><Title>stick.man007, Anzor Tsarnaev &amp; Zubeidat Tsarnaev think the Boston bomber boys were innocent.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366919602428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you want the truth ask a child. I'm glad you enjoy my satire.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366921099337</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366921815615-113</Id><Topic><Title>Spanish Unemployment Rate Soars to Record 27.16%...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366919519883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:51:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NEW YORK – The real unemployment rate for December 2012 is closer to 23 percent, not the 7.8 percent reported by the Bureau of Labor Statistics, according to economist John Williams. Williams, author of the Shadow Government Statistics website, argues that the federal government manipulates the reporting of key economic data for political purposes, using methodologies that tend to mask bad news.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366921815615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366921899557-114</Id><Topic><Title>stick.man007, Anzor Tsarnaev &amp; Zubeidat Tsarnaev think the Boston bomber boys were innocent.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366919602428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not anymore far fetched than they BS that liberals come up with in this country.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366921899557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366922231552-115</Id><Topic><Title>Spanish Unemployment Rate Soars to Record 27.16%...</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366919519883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:51:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Are Feinstein and Boxer communists?" Yes, both of them admit to membership in the Democrat Party.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366922231552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366922513156-116</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a Democrat Trainwreck</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366915439971</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 14:43:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosima, a Kent Raven alias, squawking all day just like the Kent Raven does...........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366922513156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366922681704-117</Id><Title>737 order</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - Boeing Co (BA.N) said it received 50 new orders for its 737 jets from unidentified customers. The new orders bring Boeing's 2013 net orders through Tuesday to 259 aircraft.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366922681704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366923774127-118</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Published on Thursday, April 25, 2013 by Common Dreams Workers Decry Multinationals' Greed Following Disaster in Bangladesh Western brands reap "huge profits" as workers suffer - Lauren McCauley, staff writer As the body count following the collapse Wednesday of a large industrial building in Bangladesh reaches nearly 250 garment industry workers, hundreds of thousands have taken to the streets Thursday to protest against the gross "negligence" of multinational corporations who "continue to make huge profits" at the risk of workers' lives and health. A Bangladeshi woman shows a portrait of her missing daughter in-law, believed trapped in the rubble of the collapsed garment factory building in Savar, on the outskirts of Dhaka, on April 25, 2013. (Photo: AFP) "Grief turned to anger," reports the New Strait Times, "as the workers, some carrying sticks, blockaded key highways in at least three industrial areas just outside the capital Dhaka, forcing factory owners to declare a day’s holiday." After walking off the job, many of the demonstrators marched to the Dhaka headquarters of the main manufacturers association, demanding the owners of the collapsed factories be punished. Abdul Baten, police chief of Gazipur district where many of the large garment factories are based, estimated that the crowd swelled to "hundreds of thousands." Local media reports that rescue workers continue to search the rubble for additional casualties and survivors. Over 1000 people were injured and over 247 killed when the building—which housed five garment factories making clothes for a number of western brands including, previously, Wal-Mart Stores Inc, and Europe's C&amp;A—collapsed. Decrying the greed of multinational corporations who continue to abuse international workers in the name of profit, international workers' rights groups are demanding that the western brands and Bangladeshi garment bosses behind the disaster provide "proper medical treatment" and "urgent financial support for the workers and bereaved families," as well as an "independent probe that will bring to justice those responsible for the alleged negligence." "Multinational corporations, factory owners and the Bangladeshi government have once again failed to ensure that the health and safety of garment workers are at the forefront of the country's main export sector," declared War on Want senior programs officer, Laia Blanch. She added that it is unacceptable that these multinationals "continue to make huge profits from garments produced under appalling health and safety conditions." "This negligence must stop," seconded Amirul Haque Amin, president the National Garment Workers' Federation in Bangladesh. "The deaths of these workers could have been avoided if multinational corporations, governments and factory owners took workers’ protection seriously. Instead, the victims' families must with live with the terrible consequences of this tragedy.” Speaking on Democracy Now! Thursday morning, Charles Kernaghan, director of the Institute for Global Labour and Human Rights said: Bangladesh is sacrificing all these young women who have just been brutalized [with] starvation wages. There's no right to organize in Bangladesh, there's no unions with collective contracts. Every time the workers try to organize they are beaten. [...] Something has to change and the labels, you know Walmart, they'll pay nine cents for a garment and that's all they care about. This is completely out of control. Ahead of the disaster, workers expressed concern about the building's safety after cracks appeared in the walls Tuesday, survivors told CNN. However, factory owners told them the building was safe and ordered them to return to work though the bank. "The fact is we don't know yet how many people were killed actually ... but I can tell you the building was not built in compliance with the (safety) rules and regulations," Home Minister Mahiuddin Khan Alamgir told reporters Wednesday. He added that "the culprits would be punished". You can view Thursday's interview with Kernaghan and Bangladesh survivors of the Tazreen factory fire below. _____________________ This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 3.0 License.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366923774127</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366923886319-119</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Non-union factories in foreign countries - bah, humbug! Workers in these factories are the only ones capable of protecting their safety. When the workers try to organize, thugs hired by the factories disrupt their activities. It is immoral for WMT, GAP, and other First World companies to deal with non-union factories after so many massive disasters in non-union facilities.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1366923886319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:04:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366924005304-120</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appears you are clueless as to the free market. Was that your point?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366924005304</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366924070446-121</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a great opportunity for a good quality builder or even a construction association. But what ever they do, they shouldn't let the government be the regulator......we've tried that and and we still have buildings and bridges collapsing.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366924070446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366924146749-122</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have provided several sources including Mayor Bloomberg that he kid jihadist but you still believe he is innocent. Yes it is clear that I'm the idiot in this exchange. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366924146749</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366924393880-123</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking on Democracy Now! Thursday morning, Charles Kernaghan, director of the Institute for Global Labour and Human Rights said: Bangladesh is sacrificing all these young women who have just been brutalized [with] starvation wages. There's no right to organize in Bangladesh, there's no unions with collective contracts. Every time the workers try to organize they are beaten. [...] Something has to change and the labels, you know Walmart, they'll pay nine cents for a garment and that's all they care about. This is completely out of control.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366924393880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366924655503-124</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is EXACTLY like the free market as it existed in the US a century ago. See my Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire post. THIS is what you want US to go back to. Do you realize how utterly vile you and your ilk are?</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366924655503</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366924815348-125</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then who do you think should be responsible, and how would that be better?</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366924815348</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366925057221-126</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is where many Obama T-shirts come from.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366925057221</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366925273839-127</Id><Topic><Title>stick.man007, Anzor Tsarnaev &amp; Zubeidat Tsarnaev think the Boston bomber boys were innocent.</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366919602428</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 15:53:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm just poking fun at sticks as he is unaware that the jihadist has already confessed his guilt to several US agencies.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366925273839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:27:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366925379002-128</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so now Bloomberg is the court of law... ? -... ha ha ha You Are One Fk'd Up Individual !! I have not concluded either way on his innocence or guilt... i said; ". Innocent until proven guilty."... which is pretty much the way we do things in a US District Court !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366925379002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366925809621-129</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so now Bloomberg is the court of law... ? -... ha ha ha You Are One Fk'd Up Individual !! I have not concluded either way on his innocence or guilt... i said; ". Innocent until proven guilty."... which is pretty much the way we do things in a US District Court !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366925809621</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366925873396-130</Id><Topic><Title>Innocent until proven guilty !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366900828465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've said Nothing about jihadist</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1366925873396</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366926192990-131</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you say, "No regulations required", then post the article about the building that collasped in which the article states, "...but I can tell you that the building was not built in compliance with (safety) rules and regulations"?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1366926192990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366926878268-132</Id><Title>More Reefer Madness - Unfrackingbelievable</Title><Msg>Boise Police Seize Children of Marijuana Activists Reason Magzine online Mike Riggs|Apr. 25, 2013 Three marijuana advocates in Boise, Idaho, had their children taken by Child Protective Services this week after police found marijuana in one of the family's homes. According to an item posted today on the blog of Compassionate Idaho, Lindsey Rinehart and her husband Josh Rinehart went hiking with friend Sarah Caldwell earlier this week. When they came back, their kids had been taken. Officers with the Boise Police Department arrived at the house to conduct a "Well Child Check," allegedly at the behest of a school administrator. (I've requested information from the BPD, and will update this post when I hear back.) "The BPD intimidated our babysitter/friend and gained access to our home," Rinehart wrote. "Upon entering, and seeing that the house was Fine, the kids are Fine, they decided to go to my room." That's where police found the marijuana that Rinehart uses to treat her MS, and decided to call Child Protective Services. CPS took 10-year-old Laustin Rinehart and 5-year-old Elijah Rinehart, as well as Sarah Caldwell's children, 11-year-old Thomas Andrew and 6-year-old Kyle. Their parents are now desperate to get them back. All three are well-known marijuana activists: Lindsey works for Compassionate Idaho, Josh is the director of Idaho NORML, and Sarah Caldwell works for Moms for Marijuana International. "The crying doesn't stop," Rinehart wrote on her blog. "The heartache doesn't stop. You look around your house and their toys are there, and their/our dogs are here sad with us, their clothes are here. #$%$ CPS didn't even take their Tooth Brushes." Marijuana activists are rallying behind the families. According to a donation page set up to help cover their legal fees, "there is a dependency hearing for the children that is pending, and possible criminal charges relating to Marijuana might arise in the future." I've also reached out to Moms for Marijuana Interna</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1366926878268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366927063188-133</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regulations are irrelevant if they aren't enforced. Do you want to know WHY they are not enforced? Clue - Money and political influence, same as the US in 1900, and now. Putz.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366927063188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366927239388-134</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>( * )</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366927239388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366928074662-135</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell you what. I'll go along with you if the owners of any enterprise that injures or kills it's employees are held DIRECTLY responsible. If a death is due to negligence, they are guilty of manslaughter. If they are intentionally disregarding worker safety (as in this case) they are guilty of pre-meditated murder. They are to be punished as if they had killed someone with their car (which happens to many drivers now). How about it?</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366928074662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366928276226-136</Id><Title>Syria used chemicals to kill over 30,000 citizens and Obama does</Title><Msg>absolutley nothing, but howls for gun control when terrorist who are alowed to immigrate to the US (Obama friendly to terrorist policy) get on our welfare system and limit guns for citizen patriots.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366928276226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366928574247-137</Id><Topic><Title>Syria used chemicals to kill over 30,000 citizens and Obama does</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366928276226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:17:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't the fundamental transformation of America promised by Barry just the most wondrous thing you ever saw? Barry's too preoccupied with keeping tabs on Ron Paul supporters and US veterans to worry about Islamic jihadists on welfare.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366928574247</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366928887712-138</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA board public service announcement: Notice how the Kent Raven's strange obsession with (*) manifests itself through his other aliases.......His obsession with the (*) hole, it's just one of several ways to spot a Kent Raven alias..............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366928887712</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366929909702-139</Id><Topic><Title>The Movie Oblivian and Tom Cruise and Anti Illumanati symbology</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1366767804573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Allegories and Metaphors of life are lost on the likes of you aren't they ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366929909702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366929975137-140</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is obsessed with the word anal and all things or a rectal nature.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366929975137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366931072253-141</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and Floyd(s) are wrong about pretty much everything, including the assertion that I'm CG. The difference between you is that Floyds doesn't actually believe it; he just wants to be annoying in order to get the attention lacking in his "real" life. On the other hand, you actually DO believe this nonsense, which is par for your course. The one thing you both have in common is that you are putzes.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366931072253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366931512131-142</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The difference between you is that Floyds doesn't actually believe that Im CG" Actually he DOES believe it...and so do I..</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366931512131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366934711178-143</Id><Topic><Title>Police state show of force not working</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366932242054</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They probably meant this Govt...this Regime'. I don't trust them either. Obama's influence on decent info gathering and police work is pathetic, corrupt a matter of fact.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366934711178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366937148191-144</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it's just too obvious when his aliases have the same obsessions.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366937148191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 20:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366939996447-145</Id><Topic><Title>More Reefer Madness - Unfrackingbelievable</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1366926878268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or move to Washington State or Colorado. With our open border, I fervently hope that legal MJ here drives those fascists in Idaho utterly mad. Maybe they'll try to put up a wall. heh heh heh</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1366939996447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366940162558-146</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter what nick you post under, you always sound exactly the same.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366940162558</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:36:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366940209308-147</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make my point for me, putz.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366940209308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366940511368-148</Id><Topic><Title>The Free Market At Work</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366910813886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 13:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder what those conservative salt-of-the-earth denizens of West, Texas think about government mandated safety regulations now? At least, those who are still amongst the living.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1366940511368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 21:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366941715061-149</Id><Topic><Title>More Reefer Madness - Unfrackingbelievable</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1366926878268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, even if national MJ prohibition is repealed, the southern states will probably be last to legalize, if ever. I see that for the most part, Arkansas and neighboring states still haven’t even legalized alcohol!</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1366941715061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366943067484-150</Id><Title>Look Out Below!</Title><Msg>Too far too quick. Any bad news will force big spike down.</Msg><Username>gobabygo100</Username><Timestamp>1366943067484</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366943437406-151</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush Kept Us Safe For Eight Years</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366856372412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who can buy explosives has been regulated since the early 1970s thanks to radical Liberal Bill Ayers, and the Weather Men Underground bombings . Before that time dynamite could be bought in the local country hardware stores, and often was because it was used to blow stumps, I watched that activity with great interest as a child . At that time anyone who miss-used dynamite was dealt with personally and harshly by the authorities, the dynamite itself was not blamed . It was a very different, and much better world before a lot of Liberal freaks and their terrorist friends were allowed to run around loose in the good old USA . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1366943437406</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366944607181-152</Id><Topic><Title>More Reefer Madness - Unfrackingbelievable</Title><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1366926878268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 17:54:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah I knew some states still had dry counties, but I was very surprised by how many. check out http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Alcohol_control_in_the_United_States.svg</Msg><Username>general_melee</Username><Timestamp>1366944607181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 22:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366946396379-153</Id><Topic><Title>The Movie Oblivian and Tom Cruise and Anti Illumanati symbology</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1366767804573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get them just fine. You are so far from reality you could get close with a starship.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1366946396379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 23:19:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366946467184-154</Id><Topic><Title>The Movie Oblivian and Tom Cruise and Anti Illumanati symbology</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1366767804573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 21:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: You are so far from reality you COULDN'T get close with a starship.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1366946467184</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 23:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>