<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378959919961-1</Id><Topic><Title>This Administration is a 3 ring circus</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378932545516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 16:49:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be different if you were not lying when you delivered some of your most vile, fetid, rotten, hateful, ugly, filthy, racist posts.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1378959919961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 00:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378960497717-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why Couldn't This Have Happened BEFORE He Murdered Trayvon?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378942735404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 19:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of morons and Chemical_Ali_Infested, Batsh*t Bachmann and Louie Goonmert made fools of themselves in Egypt. Goons speaking goonese, just like Chemical_Ali_Infested does frequently right here without going to Egypt.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1378960497717</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 00:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378960925619-3</Id><Topic><Title>God, I Love President Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378934102005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 17:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody has lapsed out of character again. Using junior high school girl-speak abbreviations is a reliable sign.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1378960925619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 00:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378967459097-4</Id><Title>Obama's "Big Tent"</Title><Msg>Freeloaders, illegals, people on welfare, communists, pot smokers and low information voters. How clever.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378967459097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 02:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378975137657-5</Id><Topic><Title>Sad...rest of World turning to Russia as the good guys</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378955766125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:16:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought you didn't want a military strike on Syria. But when Russia steps in to help prevent it you seem to dislike the idea.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1378975137657</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 04:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378980708060-6</Id><Topic><Title>putin just stuck it to U.S</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1378951371074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 22:02:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was a funny speech.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378980708060</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378980751559-7</Id><Topic><Title>God, I Love President Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378934102005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 17:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz is a Kent Raven alias.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378980751559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378980825867-8</Id><Topic><Title>This Administration is a 3 ring circus</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378932545516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 16:49:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a funny little nutjob.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378980825867</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378980871921-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's "Big Tent"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378967459097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 02:30:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot AQ.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378980871921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378980908601-10</Id><Topic><Title>Sad...rest of World turning to Russia as the good guys</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378955766125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:16:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry us all a river...........and your aliases too.........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378980908601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378981000118-11</Id><Topic><Title>This Administration is a 3 ring circus</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378932545516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 16:49:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378981000118</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:16:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378981029401-12</Id><Topic><Title>God, I Love President Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1378934102005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 17:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a Kent Raven alias.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378981029401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378981470686-13</Id><Topic><Title>Sad...rest of World turning to Russia as the good guys</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378955766125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:16:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven thinks that this is a huge victory for Obama ....after Putin called Barry out on his lies.....kind of like the two of us calling the Raven out on his lies ...on a daily basis ...neither cartoon character has any credibility left</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378981470686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378981929668-14</Id><Topic><Title>majority of those polled either question the official 9/11 story or don’t believe it at</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378890227522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 05:03:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In case you didn’t get the memo, al-Qaeda – the group supposedly responsible for 9/11 – is now our ally in Syria</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378981929668</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 06:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378984210006-15</Id><Title>The Mark of the Beast...Passwords are dead...Embedded devices are next</Title><Msg>Google security exec: 'Passwords are dead' ...Embedded devices are next Speaking at TechCrunch Disrupt, Google's Heather Adkins says startups should look beyond passwords to secure users and their data. Daniel Terdiman by Daniel Terdiman | September 10, 2013 12:57 PM PDT New startups looking for ways to keep their users secure should know one thing, a top Google security executive said Tuesday: "Passwords are dead." Speaking on a TechCrunch Disrupt panel called "Spies Like Us," Heather Adkins, Google's manager of information security, told moderator Greg Ferenstein that in the future, the "game is over for" any startup that relies on passwords as its chief method to secure users and their data. Although Adkins didn't offer any real specifics on how Google will innovate beyond today's security, she did say the company is experimenting with hardware-based tokens as well as a Motorola-created system that authenticates users by having them touch a device to something embedded, or held, in their own clothing. "A hacker can't steal that from you," she said.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984210006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378984363747-16</Id><Topic><Title>Sad...rest of World turning to Russia as the good guys</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378955766125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:16:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the Raven can do is parrot talking points, no matter how fictional and absurd they are.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1378984363747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378984410753-17</Id><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Msg>I tell them they are RACIST if they don't give me a free meal.....they go white with fear ..never had better service</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378985357916-18</Id><Topic><Title>Sad...rest of World turning to Russia as the good guys</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378955766125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:16:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes..fictional, absurd and cartoonish...sums up the Raven .. Reminds me of that Robin Trower song.."Eagle and the Dove"...with all the Liberal Parrots brining our once great country down....we are living in the day of the "Raven and the #$%$"</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378985357916</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378988478983-19</Id><Title>S. Korea's ex-air force chiefs slam Boeing choice in fighter deal, BA capabilities criticism mounted, want stealth fighter</Title><Msg>South Korea's 15 former air force chiefs have signed a petition opposing the selection of Boeing Co's (BA) F-15 Silent Eagle for the country's 8.3 trillion won ($7.64 billion) fighter jet program, one former chief said on Thursday, saying the plane lacked the cutting-edge stealth capabilities of more modern fighters. The petition comes after Boeing's F-15SE became the only bid eligible to be chosen in South Korea's biggest-ever arms procurement program, ahead of Lockheed Martin's (LMT) costlier F-35 stealth fighter and the Eurofighter consortium's Typhoon. Experts said the defense ministry would take the veteran air force chiefs' petition seriously as criticism over Boeing's capabilities mounted.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1378988478983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 08:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378988832845-20</Id><Topic><Title>S. Korea's ex-air force chiefs slam Boeing choice in fighter deal, BA capabilities criticism mounted, want stealth fighter</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1378988478983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 08:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once more BA leaders don't get it, profit margin is not as important as updating the boeing product line, these current managers are a slap in the face of every past, present and future Boeing stockholder , robbing the company to line their own pockets and then retire. BA stock for 3 years up 70% Airbus stock up 144% on newer planes . "Like the United States and Japan, we need F-35s as fifth-generation aircraft. We can wait another one or two years, looking ahead 40 years, with the finally selected fighter jets," Kim told Reuters, referring to any delay if the current process is cancelled</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1378988832845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 08:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378989495430-21</Id><Topic><Title>Im telling women they are "RACIST" if they dont have sex with me</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378954943632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:02:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoozdik's boyfriend can have sex with him anytime he wants.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378989495430</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 08:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378989679223-22</Id><Title>Putin pulls Obama's strings</Title><Msg>Well, if you’re one of those out there who has thus far failed to see the dominance of Vladimir Putin in the Putin/0bama relationship … the light surely must be shining now. In the last 24 hours our Dear Ruler has managed to show not only America, but the rest of the world, just how weak he is on the world stage. A bit of a recap here to show you what kind of a bind 0bama was in: 0bama goes off-teleprompter (always a dangerous thing) and comes up with this “red line” gaff. He is then on the record as saying that Assad will be dealt with harshly if he dares to use chemical weapons. Assad uses (or at least 0bama and Kerry say he used) chemical weapons against his own people. 0bama realizes how badly he screwed up with his “red line” comment. His credibility, whatever is left of it, is on the line. 0bama seeks help from Great Britain. For the first time since 1792 the British Parliament refuses to go along with a request from the Prime Minister to use force. 0bama is in this on his own. 0bama needs someone to stand with him on this, so he tells the nation he will seek an approval vote for the Congress. It soon becomes clear the congress is not going along. The Senate .. maybe … but not the house. 0bama is feeling even more lonely and exposed. 0bama calls in the campaign team, Plouffe et al. It’s not policy he’s looking for, it’s words. They tell him to tell the world that the red line isn’t really his. Fail. Virtually all polls taken of the American people show strong opposition to 0bama’s planned attack on Syria. So … here’s how I see the developments of the last few days. Either it’s all very simple, or I’m just simple-minded. (Sorry, we’re not going to take a poll on that.) Putin (background – #$%$-kicking KGB operative) sees a way to take advantage of this situation to both embarr#$%$ and establish a stronger dominance over 0bama (background – pot-smoking community organizer). Putin heard John Kerry make a bit of a mistake at a presser. Kerry is asked what Assad can do to avoid an attack. The Poodle suggests that Assad could turn over his chemical weapons. The White House immediately refutes the idea, and Kerry’s handlers start trying to walk the comment back. But Putin was listening … and he makes his move. Putin, loyal to his primary goal here is to keep his pal Assad in power, immediately seizes on Kerry’s idea and makes it a firm proposal. Just that quickly Putin takes control. Now 0bama sees a way out. He knows that Putin is controlling the situation here, but at least now he can avoid an embarr#$%$ing congressional “no” vote, the first in American history. But hmmmmmm. Maybe 0bama can get some of his grove back here. So he tells us that he was actually talking about this plan for Assad to give up his chemical weapons when he was meeting with Putin last week! Yeah … sure. So …. Here we are. Harry Reid has already put off the Senate vote. After tonight’s speech by 0bama Reid will probably announce that the vote is postponed indefinitely. The House may go ahead with a vote, but in light of Putin’s little parlay that vote will be cast as nothing more than an attempt to embarr#$%$ 0bama. An agreement will be reached between the #$%$-kicker, the community organizer and the g#$%$er for Syria to turn over “all” of its chemical weapons. Of course “all” of the weapons will not be turned over. There will be inspections, but Putin will work with Assad to make sure the inspections are not too thorough. In the end Assad will keep a good portion of those chemical weapons, and Putin will supply him with even more arms. The violence in Syria will continue, though the rebels will be dispirited. In time Assad will once again use whatever chemical weapons he retained to keep the rebels at bay if that becomes necessary. But wait! How can Assad use these weapons and not as much as admit that he didn’t turn them all over to the United Nations? Well, that one is easy. He’ll use the weapons and tell the world “See! I told you I didn’t use those weapons in the first place! You didn’t believe me. Now I gave up my chemical weapons .. yet they’re still being used against the rebels! This just proves, as I said, that the rebel factions have these weapons and are using them and blaming it all on me!” High fives in Putin’s lair! Neal Boortz</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378989679223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 08:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378990352456-23</Id><Title>"This Has Been one of the Most Humiliating Episodes in Presidential History"</Title><Msg>Behold what 'smart power' hath wrought: Naive about the levers of power: Where to start? Obama reversed course on congressional authorization at the last minute, after a private chat with his chief of staff, and to the surprise of his national security team--all in violation of presidential best practices. He then left the country on a quixotic trip to Russia, allowing misgivings to grow in Congress and the public before he could build a case for striking Syria. Boxed in, Obama seized upon a Russian proposal to put Syria's weapons in the hands of the international community. It's an impractical solution, a fig leaf. Either Obama trusts Russian President Vladimir Putin (a mistake) or he is a partner in deceit (an outrage). A Democratic strategist who works closely with the White House, and who requested anonymity to avoid political retribution, told me, "This has been one of the most humiliating episodes in presidential history." ... As he faced an international and constitutional crisis, Obama and his team were in a familiar state: isolated, insular, and alone.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378990352456</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 08:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378991594310-24</Id><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Msg>NY Times a) He has stalled and possibly ended the threat that his client thug, President Bashar al-Assad, will be struck by American missiles for gassing his own people. As long as the international community is debating the endless complications of finding, verifying and locking down Assad’s chemical arsenal, Congress and the allies have ample excuse to do nothing. b) He has diminished the already small prospect that the United States will attempt to shift the balance in Syria’s war. That sound you hear is John McCain’s head exploding. c) He has further demoralized the Syrian resistance, and strengthened the jihadi radicals among them, by demonstrating that American red lines mean little. d) He has recast Russia – whose military helped the Assad dynasty create its chemical weapons program in the first place – as the global peacemaker. e) He has, incidentally, assured continued Syrian demand for Russian-made “conventional” ordnance, so that the extermination of Syrian civilians can proceed by marginally less inhumane means. f) While seeming to help President Obama out of a political fix, he has made the American president seem even more the captive of events. A president who once seemed sure-footed, combining prudent diplomacy with the occasional bold stroke (killing Osama bin Laden) now stands accused of being, as his Texan predecessor might have put it, all hat and no cattle. He vowed to bring the Benghazi killers to justice, to stand against the return of military rule in Egypt, to arm the rebels in Syria, to enforce a red line against weapons of mass destruction. So far, he has accomplished none of the above. The other day the neoconservative uber-hawk Norman Podhoretz offered a bizarre theory: that Obama, the “left-wing radical,” has actually embarked on a sly campaign to sabotage American influence in the world, “camouflaging his retreats” as incompetence. The screed sounded like the work of satirists at The Onion. But at least it credited the president with having a plan.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378992578177-25</Id><Title>How it was so Easy for Putin to Checkmate Obama and Kerry</Title><Msg>On the list of principles compiled by the chess strategist Bill Wall, number 21 is “Do not make careless pawn moves. They cannot move back.” This is especially true if you are sitting across the board from Vladimir Putin, who comes from the motherland of chess masters. Secretary of State John Kerry seemed to have played a careless pawn when he told a questioner at a news conference Monday that President Assad could avoid an American military strike if he agreed to have his poison gas placed under international control and ultimately destroyed. “Turn it over, all of it, without delay and allow the full and total accounting,” Kerry said Monday at a news conference. “But he isn’t about to do it, and it can’t be done.” By day’s end Kerry’s comment had become the Putin proposal, endorsed (sort of) by Syria and (wholeheartedly) by the U.N. secretary general. It was the Russian president’s most headline-stealing stunt since he dressed up as an alpha bird, boarded a motorized glider and led a migration of endangered Siberian cranes.</Msg><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378992578177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:29:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378992707497-26</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Putin should be ashamed of himself for abusing a defenseless liberal. Obama brings nothing with him accept a background of sheepishness. A phony, "I'm sorry for all the problems we've caused " liberal, that gets abused by Putin, and disrespected by the international community. Better off to send Dennis Rodman.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378992707497</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378993038227-27</Id><Topic><Title>How it was so Easy for Putin to Checkmate Obama and Kerry</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378992578177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:29:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With Putin, Obama, and Kerry you have 3 guys at the table that dislike the USA. Putin is a little more subtle in saying it. His is more by deed, but both Obama, and Kerry have said it. How is the USA supposed to come out on top? Man against boys.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378993038227</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378993980852-28</Id><Title>GOP Love their Putin</Title><Msg>mention Putin and the rednecks think its pudding time...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1378993980852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378995048750-29</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You bring up a good point doublehaul. Obama's only experience in the real world was being a community organizer. The kind of organizations our community organizer in chief organized never produced anything. They simply used their collective power to demonstrate, protest and demand the government give them some of what others produced. It's easy to convince ignorant, greedy and lazy people that they deserve what others work hard for. He never considers the long term consequences of his ill-conceived idea and policies - that's why we have Obamacare even though it's terribly destructive to the economy, healthcare and most Americans don't want it. When it comes to dealing with hard issues and getting people to be responsible and seriously think for themselves about serious issues, he's a total failure and the country is left leaderless. On the bright side, it finally looks like this is being recognized by both left and right so maybe he is bringing us together after all.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1378995048750</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378995225574-30</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBL thinks differently about your opinions.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378995225574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378995412302-31</Id><Topic><Title>A Putin Obama Comparison</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1378861002849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-10 20:56:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, he's been in a lot of water that's way over his head.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1378995412302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378995645556-32</Id><Topic><Title>COMMUNists Concede Negotiations and World Stage</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378994653169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A fly-by-nite Obama administration that prepares off the seat of their pants. But liberalism is always that way, all chalkboard ideology theory, and lousy performance where the rubber meets the road.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378995645556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378995820645-33</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBL fell victim to GW Bush's intense investigation practices on Al Qaeda terrorists..investigative procedures that you liberals fought to prevent.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1378995820645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378996416702-34</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you brought up OBL rocks4brains. Why is Obama letting the Doctor who helped get OBL languish and be tortured in prison while the U.S, keeps giving billions to the folks torturing him. Not exactly an inspiration for those who might be inclined to help the USA.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1378996416702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378996418457-35</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You folks need to get a little more pro American , your garbage nonstop trash talk is getting ridiculous , you sorry losers are following the ex head of the KGB for you talking points? YOU PATHETIC WEASELS NEVER CEASE TO AMAZE ME.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378996418457</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378996561371-36</Id><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Msg>Just keep it up !!!!</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378997031655-37</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You people are so screwed , Obama is not letting anybody languish and be tortured what kind of sick mind does it take to come up with that? or are these just pre programed talking points that the talking heads have programed you to repeat? THE FREAKING BAD GUYS ARE THE ONES DOING THE LANGUISHING AND PERFORMING TORTURE and all you can do is repeat negativity 24-7 about you President and Country why don`t you little pathetic weasels leave if you hate this place so much. go join Snowden hiding away in Russia !</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1378997031655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1378998087591-38</Id><Title>ARE WE ALL FEDERAL CRIMINALS</Title><Msg>Anyone who actually takes the time to read the U.S. Constitution will see that there are only three crimes specifically enumerated as federal offenses: treason, piracy and counterfeiting. So why has Congress undertaken an overzealous expansion of criminal laws? A report from the Heritage Foundation’s Center for Legal and Judicial Studies recently determined that there are some 4500 federal crimes listed in the US Code. It used to be that Congress would create one particular crime by passing a new law. But in recent years, multiple crimes are listed within the same statute. One new law enacted right after 9/11 contained 60 new crimes. Was that really necessary? Our representatives in Washington now want to delve into any number of local crimes, flaunting the intention of our country’s founders. Drugs, robbery, car theft, the list goes on and on. What happened to the 14th amendment and states rights? Many of the federal crimes on this expanded list are bewildering and seem to be punitive and arbitrary. Harvard law professor William Stuntz puts it this way: “We are coming even closer to living in a country where laws on the books makes everybody a felon, and prosecutors get to decide what the law is and who has violated it.” Did you know that it is a federal crime to deal in the interstate transport of unlicensed dentures? For this you get one year in jail. Another law says you can go to jail for six months if you pretend to be a member of the 4-H club? And you can get six months for degrading the character of Woodsy Owl, or his associated slogan: “Give a hoot — Don’t pollute.” I’m not making this up. You will love this one. It’s a federal crime to disrupt a rodeo. Now in Louisiana, we yield to no one in our desire for orderly rodeos. But getting taken into federal custody for excessive heckling? Give me a break! In 400 B.C., the Greek orator Isocrates stated: “Where there is a multitude of specific laws, it is a sign that the state is badly governed.” Tasedus wrote in the 1st century A.D. of Rome: “Formerly we suffered from crimes. Now we suffer from laws.” A little more common sense in Washington would go a long way in allowing Congress to deal better with problems of national concern. Leave the parochial to the states. And for goodness sake, let us get a little rowdy at our rodeos. J. Brown</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378998087591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378998418422-39</Id><Topic><Title>COMMUNists Concede Negotiations and World Stage</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378994653169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you #$%$ iddiot- don't you know that there arenht any communists on this planet-- how GD stooopid can you be------ its doubtful that there were ever any communists- only the propaganda of the Bolsheviks and Stalinists which are both long gone ---so what the F..... is the matter with you?????????</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378998418422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1378998548786-40</Id><Topic><Title>COMMUNists Concede Negotiations and World Stage</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378994653169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it weren't for liberalism you would at best be a serf on Charlie Kochs empire- and you would have to ride in the back of the bus and wouldn't be allowed to vote</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378998548786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:09:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379000128330-41</Id><Topic><Title>Im telling women they are "RACIST" if they dont have sex with me</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378954943632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:02:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No...if its one thing you taught me Hoozdik, its that the Monicker "Racist" is a magic word that causes Liberals to cower in fear everytime it is used...I never knw the possibilities</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379000128330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379000933577-42</Id><Title>Harry Reid's Bizarre Definition of an Anarchist</Title><Msg>Dem. Senate Leader says People who want Lower Taxes, Smaller Government, and for congress to obey the constitution are Anarchists. Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid on Thursday said “anarchists” have taken over Congress. “They’ve taken over the House and now they’ve taken over the Senate. “People who don’t believe in government — and that’s what the Tea Party is all about — are winning, and that’s a shame.” Poor Harry is confused as usual.....he thinks people who don’t believe in a huge overbearing, abusive, unaccountable and unconstitutional government, don’t believe in government at all and are therefore anarchists. He couldn't be more wrong or more delusional. Harry is a big government socialist but doesn’t have the gonads or honesty to call himself what he is – at least Bernie Sanders does that much. Bernie is the one that Democrats emulate most in deed, why not recognize him as their leader rather than some hypocritical lying buffoon like Harry Reid?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379000933577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379001143985-43</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err waterboarded as a child err spaz err bumper err fascist err we are doomed</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1379001143985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379001229220-44</Id><Topic><Title>COMMUNists Concede Negotiations and World Stage</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378994653169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Socialists are hardly communist mowrawn- the entire modern world uses hybrid economies with at least a small fraction of their economy socialist with the remainder of their economy capitalist------it takes a lot of stoooooopidity on your part to believe the way you do-must have been caused by your mother. When she dropped you on your head out of a 40 story building. BTW the military in all modern nations is an example of a socialist entity as are infrastructures such as highways bridges municipal sewer and water systems and many more items. What is it with you that you cant acknowledge such unchallanged facts?? Personally I think it is your paranoid schizophrenic psychosis which requires these bogeymen- so that you dont have to face your real problems- like your inborn hatred and your inferiorties-perhaps your sexual perversions especially #$%$--turn yourself in to the authorities- have them incarcerate you for life or sentance you to the gallows or something</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379001229220</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379001395569-45</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical response from the truly deluded Obama haters. 1. Obama give the go for mission. 2. Bin Laden dead. 3. Deluded right wing response: "Obama loses helicopter!"</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1379001395569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379001435571-46</Id><Title>Secret Hillary get-out-the-vote 2008 effort bankrolled by man at center of DC corruption scandal...</Title><Msg>The D.C. businessman at the center of an ongoing city corruption investigation secretly spent more than a half-million dollars on get-out-the-vote efforts for Hillary Rodham Clinton’s 2008 presidential campaign, according to interviews and court documents filed Wednesday. Jeffrey E. Thompson, a former city contractor who allegedly financed a secret campaign for then-mayoral candidate Vincent C. Gray (D) in 2010, financed an independent effort to reach urban voters on behalf of Clinton in Texas and at least three other states during the 2008 Democratic primaries, according to the interviews and documents. Thompson allegedly paid Troy White, a New York marketing executive, more than $608,000 to hire “street teams” to distribute posters, stickers and yard signs beginning in February 2008 to help raise Clinton’s profile during her primary battle with then-Sen. Barack Obama, according to the documents and interviews with several people familiar with the investigation. A search of federal campaign records found no evidence that Thompson or White disclosed the alleged expenditures or activities to the Federal Election Commission, as required by campaign finance laws. The new accusations came to light when White pleaded guilty Wednesday to a misdemeanor tax charge, becoming the latest Thompson associate implicated in a far-reaching investigation that has explored the businessman’s alleged secret role in funding political campaigns.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379001435571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379001568018-47</Id><Topic><Title>Secret Hillary get-out-the-vote 2008 effort bankrolled by man at center of DC corruption scandal...</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379001435571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir(de): Thanks for reminding us that we will be saying "President Clinton" again in a few years.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1379001568018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379001822195-48</Id><Topic><Title>Secret Hillary get-out-the-vote 2008 effort bankrolled by man at center of DC corruption scandal...</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379001435571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be careful--Mirde might again bless us with his vast knowledge of converting C to F and how his education is superior. HAR HAR HAR.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1379001822195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379002540472-49</Id><Topic><Title>Secret Hillary get-out-the-vote 2008 effort bankrolled by man at center of DC corruption scandal...</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379001435571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just checked.....temperature here in Georgetown is 84 degrees F which is 29 degrees C but I would still enjoy it no matter what it was......there’s no income tax here. BTW what do they keep the temperature at in your jail cell? Bawawawawawahahahah</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379002540472</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379002684223-50</Id><Title>God Floods Colorado</Title><Msg>thou shall not worship guns over God ***************************************** Torrential rain drenched parts of Colorado, washing away homes and causing at least three deaths as officials worked Thursday to evacuate towns and keep people out of the path of the rising water. The National Weather Service described a “life-threatening situation” in an emergency message issued just after midnight local time for several areas around Boulder, where about 6.5 inches of rain fell in a 24-hour period, according to the National Weather Service. The first death was reported near Jamestown, according to officials, and was thought to be because of a building collapse. Another person was found dead on Linden Drive in Boulder, officials said. The Colorado Springs Fire Department reported a third death on Thursday morning after a body was recovered near Interstate 25.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379002684223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379003003100-51</Id><Topic><Title>Thomas Sowell and Ben Carson are jealous hateful blacks who cant stand to see Obama out do them</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1378830542468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-10 12:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Black unemployment rate 22% while blacks scream approval</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1379003003100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379005042937-52</Id><Topic><Title>Im telling women they are "RACIST" if they dont have sex with me</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378954943632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:02:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh I agree buddy..this "calling people a 'Racist" gig is a swell way to manipulate people....I never had any idea how many doors this opens</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379005042937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379005313834-53</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its holding up pretty good today$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379005313834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379005397481-54</Id><Topic><Title>A List of the Ways Putin Ate Obama's Lunch</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378991594310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jumbo...You're slightly short on accurate info. Obama knew where OBL was located, and wouldn't give the OK for 10 months until Obama was assured he wouldn't be blamed for a failed mission, AND Obama found out OBL's location through intelli gathered by BUSH! And that is a fact.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1379005397481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379006402076-55</Id><Title>CNN Poll: Large Majority Opposes 'All' or 'Most' Obamacare Provisions</Title><Msg>Another day, another brutal poll for President Obama, this time on healthcare. CNN's big takeaway is that voters would blame Republicans more than Obama for a government shutdown or a credit default crisis. To which I respond, what else is new? Plus, we'll address the substance of those results in a moment. But tucked away in the nationwide survey of American adults are several important findings: (1) On all three issues tested, President Obama's job approval is significantly underwater (the economy 43/56 - deficits 36/61 - and healthcare 42/55). (2) Obamacare's weak public support continues to erode Asked whether they support all or most of the law's provisions, or oppose all or most of the provisions. Here's how respondents broke down: Support all: 6 percent (!) Support most: 33 percent Overall support: 39 percent Oppose all: 20 percent Oppose most: 37 perent Overall opposition: 57 percent That's an 18-point gap, with a solid majority opposed. Two years ago, the spread was only five points.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379006402076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379006501067-56</Id><Topic><Title>God Floods Colorado</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379002684223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a drowning man grasping at straws.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379006501067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379007522134-57</Id><Topic><Title>WayneMyDick, you wasted two months of bash for nothing..</Title><Username>osulin_4</Username><Timestamp>1379007278832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SHHHH osulin I want it to hit $120$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379007522134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:38:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379007565570-58</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cutt it fells great you called a good one$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379007565570</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379007821410-59</Id><Topic><Title>WayneMyDick, you wasted two months of bash for nothing..</Title><Username>osulin_4</Username><Timestamp>1379007278832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two months? More like four years. The only verifiable stock predictions Wayneker has ever made was saying Boeing was going to collapse every step up the way since it's rise from $30.00. And he claims to be a stock oracle.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379007821410</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379007890209-60</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid's Bizarre Definition of an Anarchist</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379000933577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:48:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry hasn't seen anything yet. Wait until the elections next year. Dems will get punished even with their voting fraud running as hard as it can.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1379007890209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379008548974-61</Id><Title>The American System</Title><Msg>As the Ludwig von Mises Institute points out, until recently there has never been much of a movement to bring full-fledged socialism to America. The ideological was not so much as capitalism versus socialism but capitalism and freedom versus interventionism and paternalistic regulation and taxation. The interventionists won out, todays’s system is best described as participatory fascism. It is crony capitalism financed by a central bank, government borrowing, and pervasive taxation: a system of plutocratic elites, for plutocratic elites and by plutocratic elite. The massive welfare state is merely used to buy votes to maintain the “legitimacy” of the system.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379008548974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379008583803-62</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is this board full of political nut jobs? I mean I know its a company with a military division but jeez its boring. So what's the consensus on Year End Price Targets on Boeing? I'm thinkin 120 by year end. The market cap should be 100b based on backlog and the new cycle. That would put it at 132. Split it at 120 2:1 and make a run for 75 by year end 2014 (150 pre split).</Msg><Username>ashok66</Username><Timestamp>1379008583803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379009074929-63</Id><Title>Obama and the Midle Class</Title><Msg>Saul Alinski’s principles advocate the destruction of the backbone of capitalism –the middle class, namely small business owners. Obama’s ‘you didn’t build that comment reflects his mentoring by Alinski and Frank Marshal Davis. The destruction of private medicine and the over burdening of small businesses by Obamacare will further the cause of destroying the middle class</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379009074929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379009295294-64</Id><Title>OH YEAH 110 and a bit....</Title><Msg>It should hold too ;-)</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1379009295294</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379009415079-65</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't know restaurants listed the owners' political affiliations for patrons. Do they put it on the front door? Or the menu? It's been quite a while since they have done that in the south -- you know, "Whites Only."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379009415079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379009515046-66</Id><Topic><Title>Sad...rest of World turning to Russia as the good guys</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378955766125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:16:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"... kind of like the two of us calling the Raven out ..." Enough said. A mouthful, really. I can't think of a thing to add. Har har har har</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379009515046</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:11:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379009764085-67</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ash you should visit GE one can't even post anything there! Nice new HIGH $110.22!</Msg><Username>chicarones787</Username><Timestamp>1379009764085</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379009832327-68</Id><Topic><Title>WayneMyDick, you wasted two months of bash for nothing..</Title><Username>osulin_4</Username><Timestamp>1379007278832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oracle??? LMFAO$$$</Msg><Username>chicarones787</Username><Timestamp>1379009832327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379009943363-69</Id><Topic><Title>WayneMyDick, you wasted two months of bash for nothing..</Title><Username>osulin_4</Username><Timestamp>1379007278832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just release Boeing to test flight 787-9 Friday$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379009943363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379010028461-70</Id><Topic><Title>WayneMyDick, you wasted two months of bash for nothing..</Title><Username>osulin_4</Username><Timestamp>1379007278832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next week My bad!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1379010028461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:20:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379010150858-71</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG, you're right. They are still talking about President Bush. My lord. $110!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ashok66</Username><Timestamp>1379010150858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379011353302-72</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Political nut jobs are on all Yahoo Boards. Any wonder why Congress struggles to get anything done? The # number # far right and left nut jobs on these boards should give a you a strong clue to why Congress struggles to get anything done. Always pointing to the other side as the problem and refusing to listen or engage in meaningful discussion to resolve issues.</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1379011353302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379011499042-73</Id><Topic><Title>Putin Gets it Right</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1379002826757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:20:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You commie lovin' bastid!</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1379011499042</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012028786-74</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know you are going into a liberal restaurant when you see an EBT card decal on the door instead of American Express. Seriously!</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379012028786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012086354-75</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty is not a political nut he's just rationally challenged.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1379012086354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012129669-76</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>120 at year end is reasonable.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1379012129669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012254096-77</Id><Topic><Title>110 today !!!! Nice and Easy does it</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1378996561371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And highly probable.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1379012254096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 14:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012544367-78</Id><Topic><Title>Putin Gets it Right</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1379002826757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:20:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Putin is your model leader........guess how many others feel the same way as you..............NADA....Zilch.....</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379012544367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012634623-79</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's "Big Tent"</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378967459097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 02:30:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is AQ?</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1379012634623</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012728092-80</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you knew ahead of time that the "Restraunt" was owned by liberals....what makes me think you would bother to take your pure #$%$ in there in the first place</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379012728092</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012957386-81</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Poll: Large Majority Opposes 'All' or 'Most' Obamacare Provisions</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379006402076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:20:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have not read the Obamacare law - can YOU summarize what most people oppose.......haven't read medicare either or most other medical plans that I've been fortunate to be covered by but sure was glad I was covered when I or my family needed some care........oh by the way my coverage was through my employer and I worked decades no freebies on this end</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379012957386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012971808-82</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Purely as a Social Experiment....I had a Hypothesis and the results were verified by empirical evidence.....</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379012971808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379012972988-83</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you frequent soup kitchens?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379012972988</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379013117824-84</Id><Topic><Title>Pigs Fly, Ted Cruz Praises Obama - I do Too</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378999054069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:17:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I appreciate the senator's (born in Canada) thoughts on the matter......good to see there are some areas when he can praise the president.</Msg><Username>brotech_az</Username><Timestamp>1379013117824</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379013789404-85</Id><Topic><Title>Putin Gets it Right</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1379002826757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:20:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now Putin is warning us, and the world about North Korea wanting to restart an aging nuclear facility. They should have him advertising Dos Equis; he's the most interesting man in the world.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1379013789404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379014741174-86</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wrong with having a "whites only" restaurant or a non-smoking restaurant. Have you grown to be so anti-freedom that you don't believe in freedom of association? Isn't the Miss Black America Pageant says it is the oldest and most prestigious pageant for women of color. Sound like Black only to me but more power to them.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379014741174</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379015823534-87</Id><Title>Democrats and The Obama Administration are Schizophrenic about Wages</Title><Msg>How can someone support labor monopolies that lead to above-market wages in every other industry but favor the government’s using its buying power to obtain below-market wages for everyone who works in health care? One of the arguments for single-payer national health insurance is that the government monopsonist (single buyer, for those of you who are victims of socialized government education) can pay below-market prices. Economist Paul Krugman thinks this is what Medicaid does, and he approves. Yet, he is pro-union in all other sectors. Wouldn’t it be more honest of the left to advocate legalizing slavery so we could force the slaves to provide lower cost medical care. Good luck when that slaves performs surgery on one of its government slave masters.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379015823534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379015968914-88</Id><Topic><Title>Pigs Fly, Ted Cruz Praises Obama - I do Too</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378999054069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:17:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many and I do mean many natural born American citizens that were born in other countries.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379015968914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379015970180-89</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A sign which states " sparticus13579 or ale lee ases not allowed " would be legal, since it is not gender,race, religion or men tally disabled specific . could be the basis for a great onlilne sign business, first printing of maybe 1 million would probably sell out !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1379015970180</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379016817254-90</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes they gave you a glass of ice water and you ate some bread sticks before you fled fearing liberalitisis would attack you</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379016817254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 16:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379016914596-91</Id><Topic><Title>Pigs Fly, Ted Cruz Praises Obama - I do Too</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1378999054069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 11:17:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even in the state of Hawaii</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379016914596</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 16:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379018335645-92</Id><Title>EPA to De Facto Ban All Construction of New Coal Power Plants</Title><Msg>According to the Wall Street Journal, the Environmental Protection Agency will propose new rules next week banning the construction of new coal power plants in the United States that do not meet expensive new and ridiculous efficiency standards. The new standards will force power plants underground, literally. The Obama administration plans to block the construction of new coal-fired power plants unless they are built with novel and expensive technology to capture greenhouse-gas emissions, according to people familiar with a draft proposal. The administration's rule on emissions from new power plants, a long-awaited measure that is one of the capstones of the administration's climate-change agenda, is set to be formally proposed by the end of next week. While the new rule isn't final yet and is likely to face a legal challenge, it would be another blow to a coal industry already buffeted by a bonanza of cheap natural gas and increasing regulation. The person and others briefed on the rule said such stringent limits would ban new coal plants, which generally release about twice as much carbon dioxide as the proposed limits. Even the newest, most advanced coal-fired power plants in the world would fall far short of that revised standard, they said. The only way coal plants could comply is to capture carbon-dioxide emissions and stick them underground—a costly process that hasn't been demonstrated at commercial scale before. "This shows the administration discounts and does not appreciate the value of coal and how it can serve the country. You're impairing the backbone of the power grid," said Hal Quinn, chief executive of the National Mining Association, an industry trade group. And of course, this hurts the middle class and poor people the most not only through an increase in utility costs but through job losses.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379018335645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 16:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379018740200-93</Id><Topic><Title>God Floods Colorado</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379002684223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick, As it turns out, Boulder is the center of liberalism in Colorado. From the WIKI: Politically, Boulder is one of the most liberal and Democratic cities in Colorado. As of April 2012, registered voters in Boulder County, which includes Boulder's more conservative suburbs, were 41% Democratic, 20% Republican, 1% in other parties, and 38% unaffiliated. To residents and detractors alike, the city of Boulder is often referred to as the "People's Republic of Boulder," and "25 square miles surrounded by reality." If, as you say, though I am not sure where you get your information, God is "punishing" Colorado relative to ownershp of guns, it would be logical to conclude that being against guns is the problem. And, by the way, if God were punishing Colorado, there would not be any ambiguity. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1379018740200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 16:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379019016239-94</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't know it was liberal owned until I saw a picture of Karl Marx over the bar, and Mickey Moore's picture next to it. All the napkins had Saul Alinsky's picture on them.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1379019016239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 16:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379019218872-95</Id><Topic><Title>Senator McCain played polka on his smart phone while.....</Title><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1378925369119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 14:49:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My iPad can't spell. I think Obama is in over his head in foreign relations, and it's showing badly.</Msg><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1379019218872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 16:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379019370942-96</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. Your experiment proved that they are the racists.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1379019370942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 16:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379019765931-97</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and there is only one thing on the menu so that everyone gets the same thing...............however, the price and proportions are set as follows: to each according to their ability and to each according to their need..........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1379019765931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379019833760-98</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does that include the Kent Raven and his aliases?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1379019833760</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:03:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379019978114-99</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would have thought such a restraunt would be established in the middle of Arkansas......hope you left before they tried to drug you with a shrimp cocktail and a glass on Pinot Grigio</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379019978114</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379020311418-100</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Poll: Large Majority Opposes 'All' or 'Most' Obamacare Provisions</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379006402076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:20:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't had medical insurance in about 30 Years. I figure if insurance companies can make profits off my premiums I can do the same, thank you. I'm way ahead of the game and my wife is a Doctor. She doesn't take 3rd party payments and her fees are less than half what most doctors have to charge insured covered patients. I have had over 1,600 employees over the past 45 years and have never paid them any benefits not mandated other than free medical care provided by the doctors who worked for my wife. I refused to hire employees who were too dumb to manage their own money. I paid them the money the benefits would have cost me and let them spend it as they saw fit - they earned it. Some times there were tax disadvantages but the employees must have thought getting the higher pay on their checks was preferable to benefits because my turnover was almost zilch. I did have the heart breaking experience of laying off several employees when I closed shop in the North West because of the spotted owl hoax. I took a few of the ones who had been with me from the beginning to build a bridge on a piece of property I had purchased in Texas.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379020311418</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379020581790-101</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Love their Putin</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1378993980852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Putin....Palin....Trump....Colter.....Cruz</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379020581790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:16:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379020819566-102</Id><Topic><Title>This Administration is a 3 ring circus</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378932545516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 16:49:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing is true Syria is a country another thing is...people are dying there another is ......not due to us shooting or bombing or gassing them another is......you don't REALLY care if we step in or not to do something about it another is......I guess I don't either (care whether we step in OR care if you care)</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379020819566</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379020873486-103</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like the "evidence" you have that Obama is not legally qualified to be president. You're not only a loon, you're a putz. I don't know if that makes you a loony putz or a putzy loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379020873486</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379020919599-104</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1379020919599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379021020491-105</Id><Topic><Title>CNN Poll: Large Majority Opposes 'All' or 'Most' Obamacare Provisions</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379006402076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 13:20:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a farmer and hire migrant workers....good for you, and when there's a bad year with crops your wife's business gets you through the day</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379021020491</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379021437835-106</Id><Title>Things Wayne Doesn't Want You to Know</Title><Msg>The 737 is the best selling commercial A/P in history. As of June 2013, more than 11,000 737s have been sold to 265 customers around the world. Boeing’s Renton, WA factory alone has produced a full 40% of the world’s commercial A/Ps. Boeing Co. stock closed today just shy of $110 per share.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1379021437835</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379021662811-107</Id><Title>BA/Airbus deliveries</Title><Msg>In August, Airbus delivered 47 commercial planes, BA delivered 56. For 2013 thru August, Airbus delivered 394 commercial planes, BA delivered 414. Looking forward to seeing the September shipment info..</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1379021662811</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379022104403-108</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Love their Putin</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1378993980852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the difference between Obama and Putin.......other than the fact that Putin is competent and loves his country.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379022104403</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379022305464-109</Id><Title>Why Republicans Love Putin</Title><Msg>... homophobes stick together !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379022305464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379022386900-110</Id><Topic><Title>BA/Airbus deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1379021662811</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:34:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to numbnuts airbust delivered over 100 planes,,,,,,109.80 excellent</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1379022386900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:46:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379022402660-111</Id><Topic><Title>When I go to a Restraunt owned by Liberals</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378984410753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 07:13:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you go to a Restaurant owned by a liberal, you can bet, "he didn't build that."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379022402660</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379022462813-112</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Love their Putin</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1378993980852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so... you love competent communism ?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379022462813</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379022553972-113</Id><Topic><Title>God Floods Colorado</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379002684223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just yanking your chain bobby - but beware of those that Love their guns more than God !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379022553972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379023015504-114</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats and The Obama Administration are Schizophrenic about Wages</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1379015823534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 15:57:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9 million fewer people have jobs than when Obama fist took office and now he wants to shut down in entire industry and eliminate the cheapest source of electrical energy. The president is waging an all out war against the middle class.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379023015504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 17:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379023313808-115</Id><Title>Why is it when someone shouts OBAMA</Title><Msg>Liberals form a line in hopes of getting free stuff? Is that the hope part of hope &amp; change?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379023313808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379023391788-116</Id><Topic><Title>Why is it when someone shouts OBAMA</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379023313808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it does.</Msg><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1379023391788</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379023716519-117</Id><Topic><Title>God Floods Colorado</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379002684223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 12:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yanking is good. I suppose, though, there are those out there that love their guns more than the Lord. I haven't come across anyone that I would put into that category. We are almost all guilty, I include myself, of placing some things or others before the Lord.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1379023716519</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379024319345-118</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Love their Putin</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1378993980852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think that would be better than Obama's incompetent communism?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379024319345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:18:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379024605583-119</Id><Topic><Title>A Putin Obama Comparison</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1378861002849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-10 20:56:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't make a silk purse out of a sows ear and you can't make a competent president out of a Marxist minded community organizer either.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379024605583</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379025654553-120</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking: Boehner Campaign Under Investigation By Federal Election Commission For Violations</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379024769662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Total lie. All investigators are pressing hard to force Obama to release the evidence of his involvement in the Benghazi murders of 4 Americans. They have no time for trivial matters regarding John Boehner.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1379025654553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379025901588-121</Id><Topic><Title>Why is it when someone shouts OBAMA</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379023313808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What they are really getting is a free ticket to abject poverty with no safety net provided by good conservative economic policy. They do, however, keep the back alley dumpsters cleaned out. And not many rats in the back alleys anymore.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1379025901588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379026124364-122</Id><Topic><Title>Why is it when someone shouts OBAMA</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1379023313808</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:01:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone remember the black lady that said, "I won't have to make anymore house payments now that Obama is President?" I'm surprised that many of Obama's supporters can even read or write!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1379026124364</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379026275779-123</Id><Topic><Title>COMMUNists Concede Negotiations and World Stage</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1378994653169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 10:04:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Socialism in a small way has been existant thruout the world for centuries- perhaps millenia certainly in Europe with out those nations falling into " totalitarian Communism" . Once again I ask you how you can be so F..ckd..d up-and so f....n stooooopid- can you answer that for once?? Cmon give it a try- it wont kill you. If you try real hard for a minute or two you can make your delusions go away and the voices subside and think rationally</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379026275779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379028825547-124</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking: Boehner Campaign Under Investigation By Federal Election Commission For Violations</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379024769662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 18:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean the investigators arent going to continue with the investigation of GHW Bush's iddiot child's criminal war in Iraq that cost the US more than 4000 KIA????????????????????</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1379028825547</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379029215441-125</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Love their Putin</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1378993980852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plus Batsh*t Bachmann and Louie Gomert making fools of themselves (and the USA) on their trip to Egypt.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1379029215441</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379029729073-126</Id><Topic><Title>Im telling women they are "RACIST" if they dont have sex with me</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378954943632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:02:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes yes ...Im a racist....Nanny Nanny boo boo (spoken in my calmest NPR voice)</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379029729073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379030122692-127</Id><Title>The Global Elite..figured (arrogantly) that if the people swallowed the lies of 9-11</Title><Msg>you know...like AlQaeda guys in caves planned 9-11 ...then Americans swallowed the lies about WMDs in Iraq....Obama and crew figured Americans would swallow ANYTHING....guess what?.....they over reached in Syria..thinking you would swallow THAT nonsense too ...and Americans are NOT swallowing the lies any more</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379030122692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379030245243-128</Id><Title>Dont feel bad that the American Empire is dying</Title><Msg>...its REALLY the Goldman Sachs and JP Morgan Central Banker Empire...and YOU sure as heck are not in the club</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379030245243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379030636629-129</Id><Topic><Title>A Putin Obama Comparison</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1378861002849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-09-10 20:56:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times have you been to Russia.........when did you ever objectively evaluate Obama........ "None" you answer to both questions...?? Then shut the "F..." up</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379030636629</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 20:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379030776888-130</Id><Topic><Title>Im telling women they are "RACIST" if they dont have sex with me</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1378954943632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:02:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another day......another lie</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1379030776888</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 20:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379031775177-131</Id><Topic><Title>Dont feel bad that the American Empire is dying</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379030245243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:57:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are halucinating. We are just temporarily under leftist management, and will recover here shortly.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1379031775177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 20:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379032292119-132</Id><Topic><Title>Dont feel bad that the American Empire is dying</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379030245243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:57:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ill bet you even think the Federal Reserve is actually FEDERAL ?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379032292119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 20:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379034779397-133</Id><Title>Putin Gets it Right II</Title><Msg>Earlier today when i posted Putin gets it right I got called a Commie. Putin offered away to avoid the US getting into another war. What do you guys prefer more American body bags. Putin was also right that this notion of exceptionalism requiring America to stick its nose in every countries business, has gotten America into more trouble than it was worth. But what irks me more than being called a commie is that some jerk who can't live with free speech got Yahoo to remove my post. I am not the Commie the jerk is.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1379034779397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379037062412-134</Id><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Msg>…to consider a proposal that was a mistake…In order to back off a Redline I never drew….I hope that clears things up ?"</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379038180541-135</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals spend large amounts of time patching up the holes in their anti-reality bubble . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379038180541</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379038555991-136</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What type of Djumbosca bubble was this classic? Re: The Kimberly Clark Paper Mill in Everett Will Be Closing 9-Dec-11 08:06 pm Infants don't live under water, and humans don't drink salt water, so try again dimbulb . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1379038555991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379038751390-137</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or this one: Liberal, G, dim, no surprise there . Re: Anderson Cooper--Is there anyone who DIDN'T already know? Anyone else notice that cooper rhymes with pooper ? Life is full of clues . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1379038751390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379039111115-138</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A reply to your foolish assertion that closing down a paper mill, losing 800 well paid manufacturing union jobs, was somehow a good thing 'cause it would be beneficial to "babies" . 'guess by your clueless Q. it never made it through the bubble . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379039111115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379039196030-139</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So ... get one . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379039196030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379039742702-140</Id><Topic><Title>How it was so Easy for Putin to Checkmate Obama and Kerry</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1378992578177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 09:29:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like taking candy from an over-rated, arogant baby chimpanzee . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379039742702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1379039907647-141</Id><Title>Kerry Has Reminded Me</Title><Msg>... in the last few days why he was so easily defeated by Bush . Kerry makes Biden look smart . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379039907647</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379040188552-142</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Charts Don't acknowledge jumbo. Anybody who derives something from words that rhyme with somebody's last name is lost. Just be thankful for having some brains. Jumbo simply cannot help it--this is the best he can do in life.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1379040188552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379040732311-143</Id><Topic><Title>Obama:... "I decided to Postpone a vote I never wanted"...................................</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1379037062412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charts missed this one: jumbojetski • March 29, 2013 Liberals can pitch, but they can't catch . Unless it's AIDS . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1379040732311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379040920377-144</Id><Topic><Title>Putin Gets it Right II</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1379034779397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 21:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HUH? English, please.</Msg><Username>jumboyjetski</Username><Timestamp>1379040920377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379042910427-145</Id><Topic><Title>Kerry Has Reminded Me</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379039907647</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 22:38:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ya gotta be dumber than a post to pull that off</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1379042910427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 23:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379043316974-146</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Can't Be The Worlds Policeman</Title><Username>obamastamps</Username><Timestamp>1378956563046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 23:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Team Obomunist, World Police . Hilarious . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379043316974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 23:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379044283745-147</Id><Topic><Title>The 41st Time's the Charm</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379030650432</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 20:04:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh shut up</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1379044283745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 23:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379044345613-148</Id><Topic><Title>Giving Credit Where It's Due</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_the_third</Username><Timestamp>1379028163589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 19:22:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh shut up</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1379044345613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 23:52:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1379044425922-149</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Leading From Behind?</Title><Username>jerrybrownbucks</Username><Timestamp>1378916239624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-11 12:17:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B.O. thought he would jump in behind the French, again . A nice safe place for a Liberal, but the wily Frogs outsmarted him and did the reverse leap-hop, ending up safely behind Fearless Leader . Haven't heard a peep from 'em since . Whine &amp; cheese, anyone ? Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1379044425922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-12 23:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>