<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358831783869-1</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because "she" was really a he, as I and many others believe. Nothing about her was feminine. Did "she" look like a woman to you?</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1358831783869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:16:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358832241980-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Debacle: Seven Lessons Every CEO Must Learn</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1358461826122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:30:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I found Mikes comment very disappointing. I've worked with him in the past and one of the teams I was on got an award from him so it pains me to see him make a bone headed statement like that. He is a passionate guy and has been a big booster of engineering but sometimes lets emotion get in the way of logic particularly when he is challenged by someone like Goforth. He is a good troubleshooter/butt kicker and has a sharp engineering mind but is not a deep strategic thinker and is somewhat out of his depth in his present position in my opinion.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1358832241980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:24:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358832285464-3</Id><Topic><Title>For All you Smart A.ss_Li.ck.s - There is A Real Amcrican Foe Right Off Shore</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1358830765024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 23:59:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this info from the CIA ????</Msg><Username>redwoodtoo</Username><Timestamp>1358832285464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358833635580-4</Id><Topic><Title>Official Texas Sheriff's Exam</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358820744418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 21:12:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can take the trailer out of Texas, but you can't take the Texan out of the trailer.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1358833635580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:47:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358833713179-5</Id><Topic><Title>Why 787 Dreamliner Battery Woes Are the Tip of Boeing's Iceberg</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358798223906</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 14:57:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Don, , On November 12, 2001, American Airlines flight 587 crashed into a residential neigborhood shortly after takeoff from Kennedy International Airport in New York. Within a day or two of the crash, the vertical tail of the Airbus A-300 was found nearly intact in nearby Jamaica Bay. The investigation began to focus on this composite structure, and what role if any the materials may have played in the crash. So Don, is the composite 787 really safe, forgetting the fire and fuel issues. How easy is it to determine if a composite bolt or tail is damaged, what are the cow pucky numbers Don ? The study of composites is a highly specialized discipline. Although aircraft manufacturers have been using these materials for many years, the National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) does not have any composite experts on staff. The resources on this page provide both the novice and the expert with background information on composites as they relate to aircraft design and this crash in particula Would you say that aluminum has more data than carbon composites, and would a military composite plane have the extent of carbon composites like the 787 to do a like on like comparison? Don after the testing, then to the actual use, would you say that a new 787 passenger composite airplane gets more use than any past or current military plane in any situation but all out war over a 30-50 year life ? Has there been an actual study of damage to composite parts and how they find the damage and what any missed inspection of carbon damage with fatigue will cause over time? I know a passenger plane with a carbon tail lost the tail right ! What was the cause of the lost tail/ Was it noticed before the accident ? .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358833713179</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:48:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358833766805-6</Id><Topic><Title>787 Dreamliner, Oops, Big oops</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358796105906</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 14:21:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know it says Wayne, but is that you Dell.George? Did your old username get dumped because your were naughty?</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1358833766805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:49:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358833848735-7</Id><Title>The Americans With No Abilities Act</Title><Msg>From Free Republic, this is humor today, but could be reality tomorrow: Posted on 1/20/2013 5:49:33 AM by NCjim President Barack Obama and the Senate are considering sweeping legislation that will provide new benefits for many Americans. The Americans With No Abilities Act is being hailed as a major legislative goal by advocates of the millions of Americans who lack any real skills or ambition. "Roughly 50 percent of Americans do not possess the competence and drive necessary to carve out a meaningful role for themselves in society," said California Sen. Barbara Boxer. "We can no longer stand by and allow People of Inability (POI) to be ridiculed and passed over. With this legislation, employers will no longer be able to grant special favors to a small group of workers, simply because they have some idea of what they are doing." In a Capitol Hill press conference, former House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid pointed to the success of the U.S. Postal Service, which has a long-standing policy of providing opportunity without regard to performance. Approximately 74 percent of postal employees lack any job skills, making this agency the single largest U.S. employer of Persons With No Ability. The Transportation Security Agency was a close runner up. Under the act, it will be perfectly acceptable to be in second place. Private-sector industries with good records of non-discrimination against the inept include retail sales (72 percent), the airline industry (68 percent), and home-improvement warehouse stores (65 percent). At the state government level, the Department of Motor Vehicles also has an excellent record of hiring Persons with No Ability (63 percent). Under the Americans With No Abilities Act, more than 25 million mid-level positions will be created, with important-sounding titles but little real responsibility, thus providing an illusory sense of purpose and performance. Mandatory non-performance-based raises and promotions will be given to guarantee upward mobility for even the most unremarkable employees. The legislation provides substantial tax breaks to corporations that promote a significant number of Persons of Inability (POI) into middle-management positions, and give a tax credit to small and medium-sized businesses that agree to hire one clueless worker for every two talented hires. Finally, the Americans With No Abilities Act contains tough new measures to make it more difficult to discriminate against the nonabled, banning, for example, discriminatory interview questions such as, "Do you have any skills or experience that relate to this job?" "As a nonabled person, I can't be expected to keep up with people who have something going for them," said Mary Lou Gertz, who lost her position as a lug-nut twister at the GM plant in Flint, Mich., due to her inability to remember righty tighty, lefty loosey. "This new law should be real good for people like me. I'll finally have job security." With the passage of this bill, Gertz and millions of other untalented citizens will finally see a light at the end of the tunnel. Said Vice President Joe Biden: "As an ex-senator with no abilities, I believe the same privileges that elected officials enjoy ought to be extended to every American with no abilities. It is our duty as lawmakers to provide each and every American citizen, regardless of his or her inadequacy, with some sort of space to take up in this great nation and a good salary for doing so."</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1358833848735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:50:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358834057285-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why 787 Dreamliner Battery Woes Are the Tip of Boeing's Iceberg</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358798223906</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 14:57:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you always talk about yourself in third person?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1358834057285</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:54:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358834102809-9</Id><Topic><Title>787 Dreamliner, Oops, Big oops</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358796105906</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 14:21:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>custerius read up on TOS violations, the part about harassment applies to you this is all personal to you that is not allowed the above now has the person who said it, the LOT report not Dell or any other person so custerius you are having a personal problem</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358834102809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 00:55:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358835041097-10</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Management is in denial about the 787 grounding very scary , safety is unimportant</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358757992057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 03:46:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Boeing company paid 15 million dollars to a law firm for not minding the boeing Store under Condit, but the real reason for the lawsuit and settlement was to bar any larger lawsuits from the same type of complaint !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358835041097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:10:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358835377638-11</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>condit spin story was move to Chicago to be closer to the well nothing, but somehow he was of the opinion that being in the middle of Chicago was a good thing for building products right !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358835377638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358835719349-12</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner jets will not fly again -U.S. Transportation Secretary</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358540329808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 15:18:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep and the Boeing data on carbon fiber passenger planes is zero. with a foot note to Don S. , who has an opinion that there is secret data or a partial carbon military or a non-passenger military airplane is comparable and is good data</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358835719349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:21:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358836077919-13</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price , 2 billion stock buyback for 2013 not shorting do not listen to Boeing enablers</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358459878214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:57:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>man_in_stock , you are eaxty right, that is how it is done a little bad news or medicine at a time or a little less respect or a little less benefits or seperate the class , new hires first then seniors. Notice the boeing Executives are getting more not less. . first them then the workers they are the leaders right !Boeing Co. CEO James McNerney Jr. received $18.4 million in pay last year, which was more than Boeing paid in federal taxes, according to calculations by the Institute for Policy Studies.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358836077919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:27:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358836327812-14</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner jets will not fly again -U.S. Transportation Secretary</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358540329808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 15:18:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yo dummy u said (I) claim ... that there is secret data .. Yep the "secret" data found on the public Boeing site !!! Your tinfoil hat has sprung another leak of Bozo(n) rays B2 is not exactly partial carbon composite. wings, body, spars, ribs, and most ' feathers" ( spoilers, split flaps, etc are carbon composite capable of taking lightning strikes, high g loads, and high altitude. spend some of your time on the Boeing site, and you can find a lot of data as to compisite parts of almost any Boeing plane.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358836327812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:32:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358836713444-15</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Debacle: Seven Lessons Every CEO Must Learn</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1358461826122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:30:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lazertech_3d, You did a good job; this is what is wrong with Boeing and outsourcing in the USA. Boeing is no longer a manufacturing company, it is run by stock brokers and a CEO who refused to use his MBA, and he is supposed to listen to his engineers. look at who is on the Boeing Board of Directors bankers, financial planners where are the skilled engineers and manufacturing experts ?David Calhoun, Chief Executive Officer and Executive Director, Nielsen Holdings Arthur Collins, Oak Hill Capital Partners; Former Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Linda Cook, Former Executive Director, Royal Dutch Shell. Kenneth Duberstein, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, The Duberstein Group Edward Liddy, Partner, Clayton, Dubilier &amp; Rice; Former Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, Allstate. Susan Schwab, Professor, University of Maryland School of Public Policy Ronald Williams, Former Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, Aetna Mike Zafirovski, Senior Advisor, The Blackstone Group; Former President and Chief Executive Officer, Nortel. James McNerney, Chairman, President and Chief Executive Officer, Boeing who had to leave GE when he was passed over, who was a weak 3M CEO, and got his job at Boeing from a man named Lewis Platt who was temporary Director after Phil Condit quit, instead of being terminated. Sadly Mr. Platt has no aerospace experience and was unqualified to make a selection. Platt was ME but was in non aerospace engineering for HP.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358836713444</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:38:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358837990003-16</Id><Topic><Title>Have they reached their $2 billion in share buybacks yet?</Title><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614513537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:55:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>eucheme, your right on, I can tell , so far, you have 9 thumbs down and not a single reader statement about why you got any thumbs down. Eucheme, . That means the Boeing Mismanagement enablement police message board team has nothing to say, the 2 billion buy back is on. It is easy to see. The average Boeing daily share volume is 5 million , to see it, just go to the yahoo Boeing page read the average then click on daily historical volume , the volume has doubled to 10 million shares. That means there is a double of the share volume and half are selling that is 5 million per day average, so in order to cover for the institutional selling, the Boeing shareholders are spending their money to prop up the share price on the approved share buyback plan. Eucheme , If the 787 does fly for a long time the stock price will take a hit more than the yearly loss to date. Boeing stock price is down by minus .69% for one year, while the Dow Average for one year is up 8.5% so Boeing was a dog of the Dow prior to the fires the fuel, and the grounding of the 787. Eucheme it gets worse for Boeing shareholders, up next the potential strike that is a lot of cover stock to buyback for the Boeing shareholders But even worse is the, plus the 550 million lost revenue payment for the grounded 787s so far. Next the union strike will cost Boeing shareholders 400 million per day, all good reasons to get out of Boeing. I pointed that out in my 1-9 2013 user comment that without any of the 787 problems that came up after my stock chart reading, Boeing was a kill zone stock and the institutions were selling I noticed that before the grounding that the large institutions were selling out. It is easy if you leave your opinion and look at a stock chart. If you trade your opinion then you lose your money ! !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358837990003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 01:59:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358839214441-17</Id><Topic><Title>Sabre 6 this is Bongo 52 on secure Havequick...</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358820289793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 21:04:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boys and their toys ... They never grow up.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358839214441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 02:20:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358839921653-18</Id><Topic><Title>Batteries</Title><Username>gordon939</Username><Timestamp>1358782576499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 10:36:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps because too many of pumpers and dumpers are talking through their hats?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358839921653</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 02:32:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358848941429-19</Id><Topic><Title>GALLUP: Obama's 1st-Term Approval Rating Among Lowest of Post-WWII Presidents...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358784296615</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 11:04:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"by then, Medicare for all and guns off the streets" Indeed! And by then, GOP is dead meat, only the loser maggots will be left squirming in its corpse!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1358848941429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 05:02:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358852112558-20</Id><Topic><Title>Sabre 6 this is Bongo 52 on secure Havequick...</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358820289793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 21:04:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sabre 6.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358852112558</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 05:55:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358854303203-21</Id><Topic><Title>Colin Powell slams GOP for 'idiot presentations,' 'demonizing' the president'</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1358849078652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 05:04:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you make judgements based solely on race, don't you call that racism? Powell is a racist.</Msg><Username>hot_hipps</Username><Timestamp>1358854303203</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:31:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358854709543-22</Id><Topic><Title>Plato’s Tree Cut Down For Firewood</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358828457047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 23:20:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you suggesting we will end up like Greece ...or should we simply chain ourselves to a cave and stare at the shadows on a wall that tell us our economy is doing great ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358854709543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:38:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358855071209-23</Id><Title>New 787 Dreamliner report doesn't suggest a quick fix</Title><Msg>New 787 Dreamliner report doesn't suggest a quick fix Sunday's NTSB announcement "doesn't bode as well for a quick fix as Boeing would have liked," said John Goglia, a former member of the NTSB, the nation's top aviation investigation agency. The fact that the NTSB is basically looking at every component around the battery, including the computer hardware and the (memory) software, means that they have no idea yet about a culprit and (they) suspect everything," Ordonez said. The examination of the Boston plane's flight recorder data indicated the APU battery did not exceed its designed voltage of 32 volts, according to Sunday's NTSB statement. The cost to Boeing shareholders for lost revenue demands from grounded 787 airlines will be 50 million dollars per day,( revenue loss payments) Next, the arrogant Boeing executives refuse to negotiate with SPEEA , the union strike cost for the Boeing shareholder is another 400 million per day. This FAA 787 grounding and lack of any apology to the shareholders, customers and flying public by the arrogant Boeing Executives demonstrates that they are living in denial.. The executive employee’s are excessively paid and have great retirement plans. . However when it comes to negotiating a labor contract with Boeing engineers, needed to work the grounded 787, the Executives have rejected the SPEEA offer to accept current contract and get to work to fix the outsourced airplane . Instead Boeing executives have put the shareholders at a stock value loss, the customers at a revenue loss, and the public at a safety risk by indicating they would try to fix the problems of outsourcing with yet another outsourcing fix by using engineers unfamiliar with the 787 from California This is doubling down on a bad bet , like the 787 a experimental airplane built with experimental engineering with experimental new carbon material on a much larger scale . . This will slow down and jeopardize any engineering fix and the safety of the plane.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358855071209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:44:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358855207699-24</Id><Topic><Title>Rapper thrown off stage at Inaugural event</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358826459656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 22:47:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The black rapper...wasnt so much bashing the US but Obama specifically “You have someone who is a great speaker, but kills little children – our President,” he said during “I’m talking about ordering a drone attack. Ordering drone attacks that go and kill mothers, innocent bystanders, children. Militants too, but the collateral damage. You’re responsible for that, too.”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358855207699</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:46:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358856796276-25</Id><Title>Kindergartner Suspended For “Bubble-Gun Terrorism”</Title><Msg>Awash in a sea of insane Liberalism...take a good look at our Brave New World Kindergartner Suspended For “Bubble-Gun Terrorism” Brandon Smith Alt Market Jan 21, 2013 Now obviously, anyone with any common sense would react to this story with immediate shock and disbelief. The 5 year old child merely discussed “shooting bubbles” with a bubble gun she didn’t even have with her, and she is immediately suspended? How does this compute? Have school districts gone completely insane? Actually, I believe they are quite aware and cognizant of what they are doing… “A 5-year-old girl was suspended from school earlier this week after she made what the school called a “terrorist threat.” Her weapon of choice? A small, Hello Kitty automatic bubble blower. The kindergartner, who attends Mount Carmel Area Elementary School in Pennsylvania, caught administrators’ attention after suggesting she and a classmate should shoot each other with bubbles…” Teachers and school administrators attend educational seminars (propaganda seminars) just like law enforcement, social workers, and most other state employees. They are given “action plans” and memo’s on “suspicious behavior”. They are trained to create very specific environmental conditions within their classrooms. Do they understand the full implications of their behavior towards their students? Probably not. But they are aware that they are implementing an educational regime designed to condition out certain behaviors and ideas in the children they teach. I remember well the DARE program from my early years, which taught us that drug possession was paramount to murder and that it was okay to turn in one’s own parents for usage because it would “save their lives”. I also remember the constant drone of environmentalism (some of which was legitimate, but most of it nonsense), which taught us the evils of humanity and “overpopulation”, as well as the horrors that awaited us in the year 2000 (including the complete disappearance of fresh drinking water. I guess they missed the mark on that one…).</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358856796276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:13:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358858497256-26</Id><Title>Typical American unions can't build sh::it.</Title><Msg>And you wonder why all the big companies go to 3rd world countries to find workers that don't whine all the time and want 15 breaks a day.</Msg><Username>bsimpson888</Username><Timestamp>1358858497256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:41:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358860660229-27</Id><Topic><Title>New 787 Dreamliner report doesn't suggest a quick fix</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358855071209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is going to get messy and just the start. Just emagin when the lawyers jump in. Lawyer costs and lost revinue for all involved.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1358860660229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:17:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358860885077-28</Id><Topic><Title>New 787 Dreamliner report doesn't suggest a quick fix</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358855071209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quality can't be added on, it needs to be built in, and controlled.</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1358860885077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:21:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358861048532-29</Id><Topic><Title>New 787 Dreamliner report doesn't suggest a quick fix</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358855071209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It won't be long before it's below $70. A lot of profit is flying out the windows as contracts are re-negotiated</Msg><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1358861048532</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:24:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358861129423-30</Id><Topic><Title>BA might be the next SEFE!</Title><Username>villnavebarrett</Username><Timestamp>1358856973426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:16:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good</Msg><Username>andrewhancock39</Username><Timestamp>1358861129423</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:25:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358861477798-31</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: Watch Video Now!</Title><Username>jeniffer6382</Username><Timestamp>1345642806000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-22 09:40:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its a Must See Chart Pattern</Msg><Username>rexlinjkbruce</Username><Timestamp>1358861477798</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:31:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358861650802-32</Id><Topic><Title>BA might be the next SEFE!</Title><Username>villnavebarrett</Username><Timestamp>1358856973426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:16:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope so!!! What a spectacular chart! Nice fall.</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358861650802</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 08:34:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358863644209-33</Id><Topic><Title>Typical American unions can't build sh::it.</Title><Username>bsimpson888</Username><Timestamp>1358858497256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:41:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The batteries are made in Japan idiot</Msg><Username>tapps62</Username><Timestamp>1358863644209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:07:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358863847888-34</Id><Topic><Title>Plato’s Tree Cut Down For Firewood</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358828457047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 23:20:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is the unusually cold weather a result of global warming. I hear record cold weather is all over Russia.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358863847888</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358864099699-35</Id><Title>It's Full Speed Ahead to a Socialist State</Title><Msg>That's the essence of Obama's second term agenda. Guess he doesn't think he did enough damage in the first one.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864099699</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:14:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358864570323-36</Id><Title>KISS OF DEATH - Buy recommendation reiterated by Cramer...</Title><Msg>Remember his Bear Stearns recommendation?</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358864570323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:22:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358864623435-37</Id><Title>Are Liberals in Denial about the Consequences of Massive Deficits and Debt?</Title><Msg>Who do they think is going to pay for this insanity......some rich guys?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864623435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:23:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358864752188-38</Id><Topic><Title>It's Full Speed Ahead to a Socialist State</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864099699</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:14:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's turned his entire election team aparatus into a lobby group towards a socialist agenda. Team Obama while attempt to chip away at decent congressional Republicans.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358864752188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:25:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358864977509-39</Id><Title>Once a Critic of Deficits, Obama Now Goes for Broke</Title><Msg>"You don't have to be a deficit hawk to be disturbed by the growing gap between revenues and expenses," said Sen. Barack Obama during a Nov. 3, 2005, debate on the Senate floor. At the time, Obama had been a senator for less than a year and the federal budget deficit was in fact shrinking, from $248 billion in fiscal 2006 to $160 billion in fiscal 2007. Still, Obama seemed deeply concerned about the deficit, and he appeared to believe it when he said the only way to close the shortfalls was to force Congress to pay for what it spends. A few months later, on March 16, 2006, Obama returned to the same theme -- "You don't have to be a deficit hawk ..." -- in a sobering floor speech as the Senate considered whether to raise the nation's debt ceiling from $8.184 trillion to $8.965 trillion. "The fact that we are here today to debate raising America's debt limit is a sign of leadership failure," Obama said. "It is a sign that the U.S. government can't pay its own bills. It is a sign that we now depend on ongoing financial assistance from foreign countries to finance our government's reckless fiscal policies." The deficit, Obama argued, handcuffed government in many ways. The money paid in interest on the debt was money that could not be spent on education, transportation, disaster relief or many other worthy causes. And borrowing so much from foreign countries meant America's economy would be "tied to the whims of foreign leaders" who might not wish the best for the United States. "Increasing America's debt weakens us domestically and internationally," Obama concluded. "I therefore intend to oppose the effort to increase America's debt limit." Obama made good on his promise. Joined by then-Sen. Joe Biden, Senate Democratic leaders Harry Reid, Richard Durbin, Charles Schumer and indeed every other Democrat, Obama voted against raising the debt ceiling. Republicans, who controlled the Senate with a Republican in the White House, voted for the increase, which became law. Later, as president, Obama admitted his '06 debt ceiling vote was a political maneuver. "That was just an example of a new senator making what is a political vote as opposed to doing what was important for the country," Obama told ABC in April 2011. "As president, you start realizing, 'You know what? We can't play around with this stuff.'" These days, Obama's partisans defend that '06 vote by pointing out that Democrats weren't in control back then and couldn't have actually blocked a debt limit increase even if they had wanted to. So Obama could "play around" with the vote. But did Obama's words sound like a man who was playing around? In that '06 Senate speech, he made a cogent and convincing case against deficits. If he didn't believe a word of it, he didn't show it. And now, under his own administration, the problem is so much worse. The budget deficit that headed from $248 billion to $160 billion in 2006 and 2007 shot up to $458 billion in 2008 and $1.4 trillion in 2009 as the economic crisis took hold and Obama became president. In 2010, the deficit was $1.3 trillion, then another $1.3 trillion in 2011, then $1.1 trillion in 2012. It's projected to be above $1 trillion again in 2013, extending Obama's record of presiding over unprecedented trillion-plus deficits. And now President Obama, who in 2006 balked at raising the debt ceiling to $8.965 trillion, is demanding that Congress, without question, negotiation, or condition, raise the debt ceiling somewhere far above its current $16.4 trillion. "There is ... no ready, credible solution, other than Congress either give me the authority to raise the debt ceiling, or exercise the responsibility that they have kept for themselves and raise the debt ceiling," Obama said at his recent news conference. "We are not a deadbeat nation." But the interest on the debt, now vastly higher than when Obama addressed the issue in 2006, is still money that can't be used for education, transportation and other priorities. And the money borrowed from other countries, also vastly more than in '06, leaves the U.S. even more at the whims of foreign leaders. Did the president believe what he said back then, or does he believe what he is saying now? Who knows? But perhaps the Barack Obama of 2013 should listen to the Barack Obama of 2006. He was an emerging Democratic superstar back then. And no wonder -- he made a lot of sense. B York</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864977509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:29:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358865196954-40</Id><Topic><Title>Typical American unions can't build sh::it.</Title><Username>bsimpson888</Username><Timestamp>1358858497256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:41:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why didn't they have the batteries made in China? Japan makes over priced goods by lazy workers now like the USA. We'd do as well having planes made by Hasbro, or Matel then made by Boeing in Seattle.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358865196954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:33:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358865280953-41</Id><Topic><Title>Kindergartner Suspended For “Bubble-Gun Terrorism”</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358856796276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:13:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It all made very good sense to liberals. Called rational decision making if you are a libdem.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358865280953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:34:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358866289489-42</Id><Title>Does Obama Really want to Protect the most vulnerable among us......</Title><Msg>.....wouldn't that be children still in the womb?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358866289489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:51:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358866315607-43</Id><Topic><Title>It's Full Speed Ahead to a Socialist State</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864099699</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:14:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"decent congressional Republicans." LOL, that will be the OXYMORON of the year, and the year is young!</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1358866315607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:51:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358866349248-44</Id><Topic><Title>Kindergartner Suspended For “Bubble-Gun Terrorism”</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358856796276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:13:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just like always eh hawfaeces- a shard of truth is found and you go ahead with your lies anyway even tho the total facts are not known and when found out explain your hate and lies away</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358866349248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:52:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358866647548-45</Id><Topic><Title>Does Obama Really want to Protect the most vulnerable among us......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358866289489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Progressives need to create more victims not reduce them. Create victims, and then blame the other side for creating them as if you are the savior of the downtrodden. The facts always indicate it is just the opposite that happens.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358866647548</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:57:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358867397410-46</Id><Topic><Title>Does Obama Really want to Protect the most vulnerable among us......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358866289489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about people start taking care of themselves instead of becoming a government leech and wanting to become a ward of the taxpayers. People that refuse to take care of their own basic needs should just be left to perish by their own hand.</Msg><Username>jctuttle13</Username><Timestamp>1358867397410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:09:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358867564165-47</Id><Title>Nobody wants to take responsibility for the battery failures.</Title><Msg>The #$%$ say its the charger and boeing says its the battery.How about they cut the problem off at the knees and just replace the suppliers of both.</Msg><Username>jctuttle13</Username><Timestamp>1358867564165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:12:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358867653804-48</Id><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Msg>As usual, I have been light years ahead of the brilliant government elitists that have gotten us into this mess. And as usual, fools will dismiss warnings even when the elitists they put their trust and their family's well being in finally are forced to admit I have been right all along. I have been telling you way in advance so you could prepare. The time for that is short. (GATHER) – A newly released GAO report finds that “…absent policy changes…the federal government continues to face an unsustainable fiscal path.” The Government Accountability Office completed its annual audit of the government and the news is just sad. It is no surprise, and it won’t be reported by the mainstream media [properly], but it is sad nonetheless. The report gives a jab at those in the government who do not seem capable of providing accurate financial information. The report said that the federal government “must have ready access to reliable and complete financial and performance information.” This information is needed when audits are done. The “weaknesses” cited in the report are astonishing, and abundant. It is no surprise that for the non-accountable federal government, tracking tax-payer money would just be an annoyance. Nobody will report on the fact that the American economy is imploding, so why should the government bother to maintain financial records? The main problems cited were “serious financial management problems at DOD,” the federal government’s “inability to adequately account for and reconcile intragovernmental activity and balances between federal agencies,” and the federal government’s “ineffective process for preparing the consolidated financial statements.” Pathetic. To add insult to injury, President Obama has repeatedly made it clear that he is not interested in negotiating with Congress over raising the debt ceiling. The GOP has repeatedly asked to negotiate spending cuts and entitlement reform, but despite Obama’s position in 2006 that raising the debt ceiling was a sign of “leadership failure,” he has clearly changed his mind while he holds the purse strings. The GAO report should be a wake-up call. Subject: Financial Audit: U.S. Government’s Fiscal Years 2012 and 2011 Consolidated Financial Statements</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358867790951-49</Id><Title>jWhen will the massive everyone sue everyone ?</Title><Msg>It is going to get nasty. When are they going to bring this to the courts. It could make the biggest law suit in history. So many companies , airlines , parsts mfgs , Boeing, FAA...... the list goes on.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1358867790951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:16:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358867900071-50</Id><Title>Counting on you savings, 401-Ks, Pensions and Social Security for retirement?</Title><Msg>.....better think again, they could all become worthless at the same time.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867900071</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:18:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358867912223-51</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants to take responsibility for the battery failures.</Title><Username>jctuttle13</Username><Timestamp>1358867564165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:12:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did anyone check with the union workers responsible for hooking it up, and see that the red cable went to the positive terminal, and the Black one to the negative?....or does an independent council have to be brought in?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358867912223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358867945360-52</Id><Title>how low can this go? just a blip now</Title><Msg>its a small blip compared to massive failure with 787. There a slew of lawsuits waiting</Msg><Username>yourkk</Username><Timestamp>1358867945360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:19:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358868714372-53</Id><Topic><Title>BA might be the next SEFE!</Title><Username>villnavebarrett</Username><Timestamp>1358856973426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:16:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already registered since last week.</Msg><Username>bryant.vernon</Username><Timestamp>1358868714372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:31:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358868990924-54</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mir(de) showed up again, blathering as usual? by mir_roguns.Dec 20, 2012 3:53 "Thermometers in Siberia touched -50 degrees Celsius . . . For you victims of socialized government education -50 degrees Celsius is equal to - 50 degrees Fahrenheit." This is the screed courtesy of Mir(de) in which he claimed the number quoted 3 times was a typo.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1358868990924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:36:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358869100405-55</Id><Topic><Title>how low can this go? just a blip now</Title><Username>yourkk</Username><Timestamp>1358867945360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:19:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its not obviously junk at the sametime it will be huge loss for BA if 787 not good enough to fly. Definitely, there is someone in the board who received huge kickbacks for skipping quality checks when going for the batteries. There must be a shareholder lawsuit to bring the culprit out.</Msg><Username>yourkk</Username><Timestamp>1358869100405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:38:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358869356770-56</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants to take responsibility for the battery failures.</Title><Username>jctuttle13</Username><Timestamp>1358867564165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:12:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its not the workers its their bread and butter. its the white collar executives who got sub standard products with huge kickbacks.</Msg><Username>yourkk</Username><Timestamp>1358869356770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:42:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358869973047-57</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have comments on the non-partisan GAO assessment warning that President Obama and congress better do something to resolve the "...unsustainable fiscal path" or do you feel the GAO is incorrect?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358869973047</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:52:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870019420-58</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing falls down</Title><Username>melvin.dugas</Username><Timestamp>1358854920854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:42:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you</Msg><Username>robertbailey781</Username><Timestamp>1358870019420</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:53:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358870124230-59</Id><Title>pay4ityoursef got an F in economics 101 and wants us all to sink to his level</Title><Msg>Thruout the modern industrial world national governments have been using deficit financing during recessions versus surpluses and debt reduction during boom times. Only in the USA is this idea under attack. Bush blocked Clinton's debt repayment during the boom of the late 90s by cutting taxes- thus setting the stage for the massive 10 trillion dollar national debt under the republicans and the economic collapse of 2007-2008. Now Obama and Bernanke have been forced to run up an additional 5 trillion just to get us out of recession. As soon as the economy shows some real strength it will be appropriate to return to the Clinton budget of 1993, raise taxes to the late 1990s level and commence to repay all the debt. Unfortunately the republicans with their 16th century ideas on economics will sabotage any such efforts once again and ignorant racist redneck Americans will probably return these moe rooons to office every time there is an election</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870124230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:55:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870253007-60</Id><Topic><Title>The real truth behind the 787 grounding...UNREAL !</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1358869593328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:46:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you Sparty's kid? You sound just as insane as he does.</Msg><Username>rividiot</Username><Timestamp>1358870253007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:57:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870317550-61</Id><Topic><Title>Kindergartner Suspended For “Bubble-Gun Terrorism”</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358856796276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:13:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While real terrorists are killing Americans abroad we can all rest easier knowing that we are safe from homeland terrorists with pink soap bubble dispensers that look like hair dryers.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358870317550</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:58:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870344407-62</Id><Topic><Title>The real truth behind the 787 grounding...UNREAL !</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1358869593328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:46:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frank - get help fast- before you start a nuclear war</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870344407</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:59:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870639525-63</Id><Topic><Title>pay4ityoursef got an F in economics 101 and wants us all to sink to his level</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870124230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:55:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Only in the USA is this idea under attack." zosima.....What cave do you live it? Have you ever heard of a continent called Europe. Ever hear of the Lost Decade (now plural) of Japan? Did you study economics in Argentina?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358870639525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:03:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870817584-64</Id><Topic><Title>Once a Critic of Deficits, Obama Now Goes for Broke</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864977509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:29:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Post! Perhaps zosima thinks Obama is either a fool or a self contradicting politician.......nawwww.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358870817584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:06:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358870935920-65</Id><Topic><Title>Kindergartner Suspended For “Bubble-Gun Terrorism”</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358856796276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 07:13:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Noticed no one is mentioning the 15 year old killing 5 family members a couple days ago outside Albuquerque. And yes, one of the weapons involved was AR 15.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1358870935920</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:08:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358871597170-66</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insanity rules throughout the liberal world. Here's their logic. Some people use a credit card and pay off the balance every month - Excellent!. Others charge charge more than they can immediately pay off and pay 22% interest but eventually pay it off because they didn't charge more than they could pay off. The liberal mind says....don't worry about paying off what you charge.....just raise the limit and get more cards. Since the second guy above ran a deficit and had a debt.....that's proof deficits and debt don't matter so just charge away. And if the first and second had debt and deficits too so don't complain about the ones we're running up.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358871597170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:19:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358871757090-67</Id><Topic><Title>Plato’s Tree Cut Down For Firewood</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358828457047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 23:20:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty- We all know that no rich developed Western nation that has established the "Great Society" and social justice could ever end up with people dying by the thousands from unaffordable energy because we know that our "Great Society" Western governments are focused on taking care of all the needs of the little folks. Why would they allow people to have axes that can cut down trees? The government will keep them warm as it is providing for all their needs so they don't need axes and they should be banned and confiscated. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358871757090</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:22:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358871815793-68</Id><Title>Polish OUTRAGED! Suing Boeing!</Title><Msg>Polish airline LOT is in a big financial bind because their Dreamliners won't be delivered on time. In addition, their VIP's are outraged that they won't be able to fly to Chicago on its previously announced Inaugural VIP flight for the big parties there. There is nothing more madder than a pole that misses a party and their vodka!</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358871815793</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:23:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358871935647-69</Id><Topic><Title>how low can this go? just a blip now</Title><Username>yourkk</Username><Timestamp>1358867945360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:19:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is holding the stock from a catastrophic slide?</Msg><Username>ymsz</Username><Timestamp>1358871935647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:25:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358872004146-70</Id><Topic><Title>Once a Critic of Deficits, Obama Now Goes for Broke</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864977509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:29:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's only one of many flops Obama has taken causing decent folks to not even listen to the guy. He gets no trust from honest, decent folks. "Trust me" is something folks with decent values do not do for B. Husein Obama.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358872004146</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:26:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358872010382-71</Id><Title>World battery expert blasts Boeing!</Title><Msg>The world reknowned scientist and battery expert Ji-Guang Zhang, of the Northwest National Laboratory, has blasted Boeing for using vastly outdated battery technology. GS Yuasa used lithium cobalt oxide cathode material which is the original problem material used by Sony!</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358872010382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:26:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358872165699-72</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody wants to take responsibility for the battery failures.</Title><Username>jctuttle13</Username><Timestamp>1358867564165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:12:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joedokes: You sound like a very technical person,</Msg><Username>devoo1</Username><Timestamp>1358872165699</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:29:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358872553561-73</Id><Title>The Progressive View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Msg>While Hooz has his head in the sand shaking his willie, there is a paper in the UK, "The Telegraph" that has an article by one of the far rights heroes, Sir David Attenborough, that explains what progressive leaders really think about humans. Here is the headline: 'David Attenborough - Humans are plague on Earth' Humans are a plague on the Earth that need to be controlled by limiting population growth, according to Sir David Attenborough. Now a quiz: Is there anybody in the Obama administration that was also supportive of population control?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358872553561</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:35:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358872571385-74</Id><Topic><Title>Entire fleet of 787 grounded?</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1358865998321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:46:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Yes, don't know, and yes.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1358872571385</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:36:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358872776921-75</Id><Topic><Title>The Progressive View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358872553561</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:35:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>S/B far left's heroes not far right.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358872776921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:39:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358872886388-76</Id><Title>closing 75+</Title><Msg>hurry hurry</Msg><Username>billionare_tk</Username><Timestamp>1358872886388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:41:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358872973621-77</Id><Topic><Title>closing 75+</Title><Username>billionare_tk</Username><Timestamp>1358872886388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:41:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>money is flowing out look at MFI</Msg><Username>yourkk</Username><Timestamp>1358872973621</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:42:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358873119816-78</Id><Topic><Title>pay4ityoursef got an F in economics 101 and wants us all to sink to his level</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870124230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:55:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only in the USA---------- why don't you cite just one exception to my statement about economic policy to provide a stable economy- I take it you flunked the same session of econ 101 with pay4ity</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873119816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:45:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358873754089-79</Id><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Msg>Deny them health insurance Deny them voting rights Deny them Civil Rights Deny them a living wage Deny them Social Security Deny them etc etc etc etc</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358873881256-80</Id><Topic><Title>pay4ityoursef got an F in economics 101 and wants us all to sink to his level</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870124230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:55:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Feb 1, 2012 – HONG KONG BUDGET 2012-2013 ... this the 8th consecutive year that the government have announced a budget surplus, ... However the FS anticipates that for the next few years Hong Kong will experience balanced budgets including a small consolidated deficit, in the amount of HK$3.43bn, for 2012-13.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358873881256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:58:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358874067631-81</Id><Topic><Title>pay4ityoursef got an F in economics 101 and wants us all to sink to his level</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870124230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:55:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Hong Kong Budget being balanced and the economy stable and in fact booming- there would appear to be no need for fiscal or fiduciary manipulation of its economy would there be eh?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358874067631</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:01:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358874363810-82</Id><Topic><Title>pay4ityoursef got an F in economics 101 and wants us all to sink to his level</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870124230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:55:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another stupid, ignorant lib post. And he understands Econ 101? lol! Some deficit spending fine, but it is all about the percentage of GDP that you spend. In Obama's case it is catastrophic. Obama has debt exceeding our entire GDP. As he spends money we do not have, he punishes the source of revenue, the private sector, by high fascist govt regulation, and control that is extemely expensive for the private sector as well has raising their taxes. 40 cents out of every dollar of spending just goes to servicing the debt Obama is creating! Obama is basically following, and exceeding FDR's govt spending experiment that resulted in a DECADE of Recession.....10 yrs of economic pain when a normal recession lasts but for 6 to 9 mo.'s ! In the USA it comes under attack because the majority our citizens are NOT SOCIALISTS like in Europe!</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358874363810</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:06:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358874558178-83</Id><Topic><Title>Once a Critic of Deficits, Obama Now Goes for Broke</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864977509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:29:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz progressives feel that humans are a plague as we were reminded by Sir David Attenborough yesterday in an article in "The Telegraph" (I know you only read progressive blogs so you weren't aware). Years of reinforcement that humans are bad and destroying the planet and such, has manifested in progressives developing a sense of self-loathing and hate for other humans. Obama tapped into that self-loathing and hate by reinforcing that progs and all humans are indeed unworthy #$%$ and that our life is hopeless with no direction but it isn't our fault. He then manipulated progs as to where to focus their hate and sold them twice, via hope, change and forward, to lead us all to a happy place because we can't get to a happy place without him. Romney couldn't compete with that. Romney came across with the dynamism of a kitchen appliance at Best Buy and never tapped and manipulated anyone's feelings.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358874558178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:09:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358874700395-84</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only the parasites.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1358874700395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:11:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358874776643-85</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which of the above list have you been denied?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358874776643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:12:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358874922727-86</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Generation after generation...too STUPID and LAZY to make their way through life. If you want send them a big check, BUT don't ask the rest of us to support the Cretins.</Msg><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1358874922727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:15:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358874974749-87</Id><Title>Public Deficit by Country 2006-2013</Title><Msg>"Government deficit or surplus is the difference between government receipts and government spending in a single year. A deficit occurs when the expenditures of a government exceed the revenues collected by the government; a surplus is when revenues exceed spending. It is usually presented as a percent of gross domestic product (GDP). Total deficit for OECD countries went from -1.2% of total OECD GDP in 2006 to -6.6% in 2011. Individual countries within the OECD ranged in 2011 from a surplus of 12.5% for Norway and 0.8% in Korea and Switzerland, to a close-to-balanced budget in Estonia and Sweden (at 0.1%). At the other end of the spectrum, some countries had severe deficits in 2011, including a -10.3% deficit in Ireland, -10% in United States, -9.4% in the UK, -9% in Greece and -8.9% in Japan." There is a difference between between slight, small, modest, medium, large, humongous and completely unsustainable and insane levels.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358874974749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:16:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875134940-88</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>History has well confirmed the millions of folks that liberals have cast off as not worth saving...let them die. From the millions that Saddam was slaughtering to the thousands of Blacks left in their apartment houses hanging out the upstairs windows as the flood waters rose in New Orleans..left to die when they were promised by the Dem. liberals in power they would be bused to safety. The libs fled saving their own lives leaving the poor to die in their apt. buidings. Obama didn't even care to save his own foreign embassaduer in Benghazi when he had months to save the 4 Americans killed there.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358875134940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:18:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875187284-89</Id><Topic><Title>pay4ityoursef got an F in economics 101 and wants us all to sink to his level</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870124230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:55:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hawfaeces I doubt if you flunked the same econ 101 course that the previous posters did since you must have been home schooled down there in that tin shack in the swamps. FDR's deficit spending of course includes the peace as well as war budgets of 1933-1946 and ran the national debt up to 130% of the GNP in 1945 and produced a boom which ran during the years 1946, 1948 thru 1968 under Truman, Eisenhower and LBJ. The fact that the national debt was at 130% of the GNP in 1945 tells those of us who are rational that a debt of 100% of the GNP altho a pain is quite manageable and as Paul Krugman the economist explains exactly what is needed till the economy recovers fully. Keep one thing in mind swamp dweller- the reason we are here is because you trogdalytes and your ilk voted the moe rooon Junior into office. Also his predecessors raygun, and GHW Bush to move the debt from 400 billion to more than 10 trillion and then through away all the things we learned in the great depression to create the great recession of the 21st century</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358875187284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:19:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875209710-90</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you liberals want all those things and you want everyone else to have all those things, you're free to reach into your own pockets and provide them.....so what's the problem?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358875209710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:20:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875323623-91</Id><Topic><Title>World battery expert blasts Boeing!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358872010382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:26:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Following fires involving lithium-polymer batteries made by Avestor used in AT&amp;T U-verse network cabinets, the company replaced 17,000 similar batteries. The Li-battery construction is so complicate that it caused fires in several incidents and ATT had to replace them. What would happen if the GS Yuasa batteries cause fire above the Pacific Ocean again. I think NTSA should look into GS Yuasas's test records.</Msg><Username>hondaz369</Username><Timestamp>1358875323623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:22:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875457400-92</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you don't need it for personal protection... then you don't need it !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358875457400</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:24:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875464058-93</Id><Topic><Title>World battery expert blasts Boeing!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358872010382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:26:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10-4 there good buddy, over and out.</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358875464058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:24:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358875484682-94</Id><Title>Battery fix is near</Title><Msg>Boeing telling airlines it expects 787 fix soon.</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358875484682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:24:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875486775-95</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly the the theory of Nietsche and his book Beyond Good and Evil and Heinrich Himmler and his Schutzstaffel- a monstrous interpretation of evolutionary theory-</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358875486775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:24:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358875722957-96</Id><Title>"Increasing America's debt weakens us domestically and internationally,"</Title><Msg>I would have to agree with that.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358875722957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:28:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875734576-97</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slaughtered!</Msg><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1358875734576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:28:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875747656-98</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is "them"? Your not being specific enough to make any sense. My family were never given health insurance, voting rights, civil rights or social security so I guess we are the them you refer to. Which of the things on your list do you not have?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358875747656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:29:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875918717-99</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals of course were the only salvation for the victims of the quasi Nazzie RWNJ policies of Junior and his acolytes. These liberals have been denounced and lied about for the past 10 years by the forces of evil the RWNJs of which hawfaeces must surely be one of the leading voices. This Hitlarian, Himmlerish survival of the fittest is nothing less than the conservative and RWNJ evil philosophy and explains their compulsive behavior when it comes to social welfare programs</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358875918717</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:31:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358875928084-100</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pssssst.....Nietsche is dead ;-)</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358875928084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:32:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358876163524-101</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Roguns if you don't like liberal ideology and policys then you are free to reach into your own pocket and take out enough money to buy yourself a ticket out of the country and never to return - likely to some place which would provide the kind of social safety net you would like to see like Somalia and Mogadishu</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358876163524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:36:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358876306451-102</Id><Title>Pro-Gun vs Pro-life !</Title><Msg>... seems conservatives are confused on which saves lives..</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358876306451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:38:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358876500057-103</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ali you guys living down there in Africa and other third world areas of the globe are gaining economically and surely will gain some of the social safety nets that the civilized world is enjoying in due time</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358876500057</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358876618175-104</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ever try to get health insurance if you had diabetes or some other similar debilitating illness. ever notice that your medical expense absorbs all you are able to earn you seem to be room temperature IQ I guess</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358876618175</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:43:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358876633295-105</Id><Topic><Title>Assault Weapons Ban is Not the Answer</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358806074904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 17:07:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... if the intent is to drive the GOP kooky'er ... its working !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358876633295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:43:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358876703729-106</Id><Topic><Title>Pro-Gun vs Pro-life !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358876306451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:38:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you libs need to take Chicago on as an expiriment. So far the libs running Chicago have been a dismal failure for saving lives with tough gun laws. It's a war zone in Chicago, a testimonial to liberal policy. Why should you think you can save lives given the gun deaths in Liberal Central Headquarters?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358876703729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:45:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358876891893-107</Id><Topic><Title>Pro-Gun vs Pro-life !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358876306451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:38:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>think for a second... how long has Chicago (plus NY &amp; LA) been a war zone...?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358876891893</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:48:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358877047898-108</Id><Title>The Economic Ignorance of Liberals on this Board is Hilarious</Title><Msg>Not even the archaic and disproved theory of Keynesian economics advocate overwhelming debt.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1358877047898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:50:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358877048305-109</Id><Topic><Title>"Increasing America's debt weakens us domestically and internationally,"</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358875722957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:28:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Caused us to have to cut our military budget in 1/2 as Obama indicated he wanted, putting US citizens in harms way. Remember, and Identify those that fight the good fight to hold back fed. spending...the Tea Party folks, the conservatives in congress, AND foreigners that buy up our debt depending on the dollar to remain stable...like the Chinese that are a major force in cutting back Obama's desire to increase the debt. They hold our dollars, lots of them, and will see, demand he doesn't destroy the value of the dollars that they hold.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358877048305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:50:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358877550700-110</Id><Title>Is anyone buying BA?</Title><Msg>The market was down and ba was 74. The market is up and ba is 74.</Msg><Username>mexpan18</Username><Timestamp>1358877550700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:59:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358877653154-111</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Clear Sailing Now</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358876427641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:40:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't tell anyone but the House is controlled by the Republicans and they all won thier elections too.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1358877653154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:00:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358877714345-112</Id><Topic><Title>The Economic Ignorance of Liberals on this Board is Hilarious</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1358877047898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:50:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not even at a 3rd grade level which is a big reason Romney lost the election. When Obama told the big lie over and over again. "He (Romney) wants to return us to the policies that got us in trouble in the first place." That was a big lie, and Romney needed to take Obama to task on that false statement, and many false statements that Obama made. It is big govt spending that is getting us into trouble taking more, and more disposable income out of the private sector that creates investments, new businesses, money spent supporting private businesses that pay taxes, creates jobs. All capitalist thinking that made the USA the greatest country in the world, and capitalism our anti-capitalist President portrays as the problem.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358877714345</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:01:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358878175193-113</Id><Topic><Title>The Economic Ignorance of Liberals on this Board is Hilarious</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1358877047898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:50:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So many conservatives are anti-government while spending long careers drawing paychecks from the taxpayers?. Why also do conservatives "bash government largesse while seeking as much of it as they can get for their constituents and friendly interest groups?" Why do conservatives criticize entitlements and big government yet promise their older, conservative base they will "never, ever to cut their Medicare or Social Security?" And what about defense? Why do Republicans support the free market yet refuse to consider any cuts at all in the bloated Military Industrial Complex that takes taxpayer dollars and transforms them into private profits.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1358878175193</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:09:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358878216170-114</Id><Title>Liberals - Keep up the good Fight - You're Winning</Title><Msg>I know it's a struggle trying to justify economic insanity but you're fighting hard and you're winning over a lot of economic illiterate liberals. They may curse you when they learn the truth but for now enjoy your dissemination of total nonsense.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1358878216170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:10:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358878495913-115</Id><Topic><Title>Battery fix is near</Title><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358875484682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:24:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's it??</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1358878495913</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:14:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358878601958-116</Id><Title>The Bible Says "the borrower is slave to the lender."</Title><Msg>Guess the Democrats just can't let go of wanting people to be slaves.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358878601958</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:16:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358878715115-117</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FatherZ We now live in the USA. We paid for our health care our whole lives including in the USA. We joined the USA military in order to enter the USA legally and we only became citizens because we earned a place here. Until we earned them we had no voting or civil rights. We paid for our own social security. In my case I will actually lose money having participated in SS, but again no one gave it to us. My first several jobs did not pay a living wage and I worked all but 6 hours per day doing several jobs. So AAGAIN I ask you to be specific about what you feel you have been denied?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358878715115</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:18:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358878960612-118</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals - Keep up the good Fight - You're Winning</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1358878216170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:10:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When there is a hole in the bottom of the boat the solution is to make another bigger hole in the bottom of the boat to let more water out. A progressive taught me that but I'm sure it would also work with spending.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358878960612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:22:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358879245593-119</Id><Title>Say what! Beyonce lip synced the national anthem?</Title><Msg>Its okay they did it at Lincoln's inaugural also. And the band didn't actually play? Its hard to tell whats real and what isn't.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358879245593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:27:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358879387336-120</Id><Title>Republican Oath of Office Ceremony</Title><Msg>" i do solemnly swear that i will faithfully execute my plan to bring down the Federal Government "</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358879387336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:29:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358879504680-121</Id><Title>Anyone seeing the trend around Lithium Ion batteries?</Title><Msg>Lithium Ion Battery Cars that have had reported fires: Tesla, Fisker, Smith Electric Vehicles, Chevy Volt, etc Lithium Ion Battery Laptops that have reported fires: Apple, Dell, Lenovo. (note too, cell phones have been reported to catch on fire too!) Remember, don't use around gas stations as we were once told. Lithium Battery Makers that went out of biz, sold, or haven't produced a damn thing LG Chen lithium ion, A123 systems, Ener 1, etc. What do all these companies have in common other than Lithium batteries that have reportedly failed? They were all companies that received money from the Federal Gov't (exlcuding apple and dell). The problem here is that Lithium Batteries was part of the radical green energy plan that was pushed as being the Obama admin plan however all the experts said Lithium Ion is highly volatile, don't do it, etc. Now it is playing out at Boeing. Keep in mind that the power the Dreamliner is processing through these batteries is equivalent to hundreds of homes. That is serious load and demand on something that experts have been saying for 4 years is a bad idea and simply dangerous. Mainstream news doesn't talk about Lithium Ion because it makes Obama look really bad. If the experts are right, and I heard MIT experts are saying this, then this isn't going to end well for the Dreamliner. You can't pull out the Lithium Ion and replace with something else. The whole plane seems to be built around Lithium Ion.</Msg><Username>nsn456</Username><Timestamp>1358879504680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:31:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358879539975-122</Id><Topic><Title>Is anyone buying BA?</Title><Username>mexpan18</Username><Timestamp>1358877550700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:59:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good question maybe funds buying for long term hold ? everybody waiting for more news</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1358879539975</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:32:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358879617244-123</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Al Capone used a baseball bat for a teaching moment and killed a man did we take Stan Musial's bat away from him? Is my pursuit of happiness dictated by you now? If what I do doesn't harm anyone why do you want to be the boss of my life and tell me what I need or don't need? Please explain.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358879617244</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:33:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358879649394-124</Id><Topic><Title>World battery expert blasts Boeing!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358872010382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:26:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AT&amp;T may have done HALT-HASS testing to establish/understand failure mechanisms. These problems must be prevented by robust design and process margins establsihed by rigorous evaluation and testing. No other way to ensure ongoing safety.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1358879649394</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:34:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358879652638-125</Id><Topic><Title>Battery fix is near</Title><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358875484682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:24:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Fisker, Chevy, Tesla, LG Chen lithium ion, A123 Systems, and everyone else be fixing the fires on the lithium ion batteries as well? It is a bad technology, go read what MIT experts have said for 4 years.</Msg><Username>j5678</Username><Timestamp>1358879652638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:34:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358879849652-126</Id><Title>8 million Fewer People Have Jobs Than in 2009......</Title><Msg>......when Obama came into office. That's in spite of nearly 12 million additional job seekers entering the job market. And the Democrats are jumping up and down over the 5 million new jobs they supposedly created.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358879849652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:37:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358880173372-127</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@ "the government that leads governs the best." Is this a quote from the Third Reich or the communist manifesto? I prefer this one better. "That government is best which governs least" - Henry David Thoreau</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358880173372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:42:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358880646845-128</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Real life isn't a Kevin Costner movie. After the St Valentine's Day Massacre, we DID take away automatic weapons.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358880646845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:50:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358880982059-129</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya......wouldn't be great if only the government and criminals are allowed to have guns! What's sad is the leftest idiots that are being so badly used and they don't even have a clue. If they would read a bit of history they'd know that when they have lost heir usefulness they will be killed!</Msg><Username>tomfranklin96753</Username><Timestamp>1358880982059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:56:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881131151-130</Id><Topic><Title>The Economic Ignorance of Liberals on this Board is Hilarious</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1358877047898</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:50:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So many conservatives are anti-government" Could you explain what you mean by "anti-government?" I have never met any conservatives who are "anti-government." This should be good.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881131151</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 13:58:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881451516-131</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree and it's time men in the USA take back control of women's bodies the way China has. China aborts mostly females and this would be good for Obama as there would be far more men than women for him to have sex with. While we're adopting China policy we should also adopt China's post birth abortion policy too. Only men over 60 get a say and when young college students disagree, they get aborted. Yes that China abortion thingy is a great idea. ;-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358881451516</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:04:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881567946-132</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's really interesting is the lamestreet did not cover this at all. What do you think they would have done with such a report during the Bush administration?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881567946</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:06:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881643856-133</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet we didn't ban Valentine's day. You still have more work to do to keep me safe Chris.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358881643856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:07:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881715682-134</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>please don't listen to Ali, his pursuit of happiness includes an Assault Rifle... meaning, he's not happy til he destroys... kinda like Adam Lanza !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358881715682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:08:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881759091-135</Id><Topic><Title>Public Deficit by Country 2006-2013</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358874974749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:16:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Debt to GDP - we are worse off than Greece.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881759091</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:09:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358881789679-136</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do the Republicans want to send financial aid to countries that provide aborting on demand paid for by the government? That's your money financing abortion.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1358881789679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:09:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358881995031-137</Id><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Msg>....to overthrow an abusive government.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358882054771-138</Id><Topic><Title>Official Texas Sheriff's Exam</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358820744418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 21:12:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Q: What do you call a virgin in Texas ? A: A girl who can out run her Brothers...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358882054771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:14:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358882263540-139</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Chris you did not take away all the machine guns that criminals have in Chicago as you incorrectly stated in your post about the Valentines Day Massacre. It is only you and other progressives living in the fictional world of movies. So I invite you to come to Chicago as I have other progressives, and go to some of our lovely Southside areas and confiscate the machine guns that the criminals on the street still have but that law abiding citizens can't have. Let me know when you'll be in Chicago....soon I hope.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358882263540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:17:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358882501635-140</Id><Title>Message from the market?</Title><Msg>The market is on track to have it's best January since 1997. If you recall January 1997 Bill Clinton was sworn in for his second term.</Msg><Username>benson_bridges_baydreams</Username><Timestamp>1358882501635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:21:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358882860459-141</Id><Title>Genna Thinks Criminals In Chicago Have No Automatic Weapons</Title><Msg>He says they were all taken away after the St. Valentine's Day Massacre. It must be nice living in the progressive movie-like fantasy world of Chris Genna that he imagines I'm living in.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358882860459</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:27:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358882963108-142</Id><Topic><Title>Will Somebody Inform x6xxx234...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358882780435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:26:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't you just send him a picture of your's?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358882963108</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:29:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358883062431-143</Id><Title>They may not have taken all the machine guns, ali ...</Title><Msg>But they got enough of them to cut down the number of St. Valentine's Day Massacres. That's what gun control is all about -- to improve the odds. After they did that, REAL Americans who wanted to fire on full auto did what PATRIOTS do -- they joined the military, That's where those guns belong. The TV series "The A-Team" was always good for laughs in two places in the script: When Hannibal/Peppard said "I love it when a plan comes together." and when the A-Team members ran in the open into automatic weapons fire. Great fun, but only the right-fringe thought it was real.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358883062431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:31:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358883231556-144</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you send him a picture of your clown costume yet? If you haven't then don't get on his case about improper clown uniforms. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358883231556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:33:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358883549546-145</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It worked out really well for the Branch Davidians.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1358883549546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:39:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358883657687-146</Id><Title>Obama is focused on Social Justice?</Title><Msg>.....isn't not being able to get a job and take care of your family the worst form of social justice?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358883657687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:40:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358883791241-147</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see several places in the report that says that "while significant progress has been made in improving federal financial management since the federal government began preparing consolidated financial statements 16 years ago"....... So it wasn't all bad.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1358883791241</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:43:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358883875847-148</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is focused on Social Justice?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358883657687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:40:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have a job? Must explain why you are here all day, every day, whining about the President. Go look for a job and use your computer to search for work instead of whine here all day.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1358883875847</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:44:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358883934560-149</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gerbilfool is obviously a victim of socialized government education and flunked history. Branch Davidians weren't trying to overthrow the government but the continental army was. It worked out pretty well for them.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358883934560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:45:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358884069248-150</Id><Topic><Title>Are Liberals in Denial about the Consequences of Massive Deficits and Debt?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864623435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:23:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservatives are responsible for a good portion of the deficit as well as liberals. We all know it has to be paid down and that spending has to be cut, but is it your wish to adopt harsh austerity measures? Do you think that will affect everyone but you?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1358884069248</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:47:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358884237082-151</Id><Title>The Sky is Falling....The Sky is Falling....</Title><Msg>Looked up at the Moon, thought I saw a Dreamliner, Schat in my pants.....</Msg><Username>rogerjames55346</Username><Timestamp>1358884237082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:50:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358884416441-152</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent... the name fits like a snug condom... mir(de)'s inability to comprehend conversion of temperatures is the stuff of BA-board legends...</Msg><Username>analgonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1358884416441</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:53:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358884505013-153</Id><Topic><Title>pay4ityoursef got an F in economics 101 and wants us all to sink to his level</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358870124230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:55:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, thank you.</Msg><Username>analgonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1358884505013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:55:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358884697670-154</Id><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Msg>(CNN) -- Students at a community college in Houston are taking shelter after reports of a gunman on campus. Multiple people have been shot at the North Harris Campus of Lone Star College, CNN affiliate KPRC reported, citing law enforcement. There were more than 10,000 students at the campus, a school spokesman said. Police and emergency responders swarmed an entrance to the campus, aerial video from KPRC showed. Medical personnel were seen treating at least two people and moving them to ambulances. Students were jogging away from some buildings, with their hands up in the air, presumably in response to police instruction. One student, speaking to CNN affiliate KTRK, reported hearing five gunshots outside a breezeway between a cafe and a library. Another witness told KTRK he saw blood on the ground and someone shot in the leg. "Beside him, there was one guy in handcuffs," he said. "I just heard somebody screaming and then after that I heard the shots," another student told KPRC. It was not immediately clear whether any arrests had been made or a gunman remained on the loose. A Harris County Sheriff's deputy told KTRK one suspect was in custody. Lone Star College spokesman Jed Young could only confirm that there were reports of a shooter on campus. The Lone Star College system is the largest institution of higher education in the Houston area, and the fastest-growing community college system in Texas, according to its website.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358884738093-155</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh thanks. Now I totally understand it.</Msg><Username>burger_barn</Username><Timestamp>1358884738093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358884802276-156</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many carried a weapon for OUR Country, All of them gave Some and some gave parts of their self and there were some that gave All. You and your usual suspects were GIVEN those Rights yet youall want some more for your nothing contributions and have the Gall to insult MY America...ESaD</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1358884802276</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:00:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358884829001-157</Id><Topic><Title>They may not have taken all the machine guns, ali ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358883062431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:31:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@"But they got enough of them to cut down the number of St. Valentine's Day Massacres. That's what gun control is all about -- to improve the odds." This was probably very deep thinking for you Chris, but you only reinforce the fact that you live in a movie like fictional world. To believe that 7 mobsters getting mowed down in a Chicago warehouse led to excellent gun control that "improved the odds" is fiction as the reality is that 500+ Chicagoans died of gum homicides in Chicago in 2012 under a strict gun ban. That's your idea of improving the odds? You must have been on a lot of drugs in your youth to develop a brain like yours.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358884829001</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:00:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358885010631-158</Id><Title>Boeing exec THROWN OFF THE Uof I Board!!!</Title><Msg>IL Governor DUMPS and humiliates Lawrence Oliver II because it is too embarassing to have a Boeing exec on a prominent board. Oh, how th mighty have fallen!</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358885010631</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:03:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885152019-159</Id><Topic><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were at least ten shootings on college campuses in the four years following the Virginia Tech shooting. In 2012, there were at least five shootings on or steps away from a college campus. Fewer than three weeks into 2013, at least three such shootings occurred... ... reported 01/17/2013... then Baam, another !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358885152019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:05:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358885195783-160</Id><Title>Dreamliner batteries consume FIVE times the juice to ..</Title><Msg>... operate than the larger 777. In addition, the cells are not spaced enough to disipate heat. And evrything is powered virtually by electricity unlike previous planes. SOURCE: Barron's 01/21/13 Page 16</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358885195783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:06:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885279030-161</Id><Topic><Title>Polish OUTRAGED! Suing Boeing!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358871815793</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the Polish will be just the tip of the iceberg. There are many more and bigger Asian airplines that stand more to lose!</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1358885279030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:07:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885330653-162</Id><Topic><Title>They may not have taken all the machine guns, ali ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358883062431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:31:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The odds of you having a clue are not very good. Any #$%$, any felon that wants to commit a crime with a gun has to laugh at fools like you.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358885330653</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:08:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885446355-163</Id><Topic><Title>Will Somebody Inform x6xxx234...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358882780435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:26:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$.........Is your blow up love doll wearing a clown costume now or do you still dress it up with that Sgt. Pepper uniform....Oh, what's the difference.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358885446355</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:10:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885476302-164</Id><Topic><Title>They may not have taken all the machine guns, ali ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358883062431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:31:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You imagine, and assume, I said things I didn't. You seem to want to invent points for me that are easy for you to refute -- Like how we should do away with Valentines Day to eliminate massacres. There's a classic of the genre -- the more you argue, the more pathetic and indefensible and off-the-wall your arguments become.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358885476302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:11:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885814152-165</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing falls down</Title><Username>melvin.dugas</Username><Timestamp>1358854920854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 06:42:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>personally I do not like it, but it's all true. Good work</Msg><Username>andrewperez170</Username><Timestamp>1358885814152</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:16:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358885870257-166</Id><Title>Confirmed: Beyoncé Lip-Synced “The Star-Spangled Banner”</Title><Msg>I will admit it was pretty fitting for an admistration that has been faking it for the past 4 years. "Beyoncé sang the national anthem at yesterday’s inauguration ceremony for President Obama and received overwhelming praise for her performance, ranging from Business Insider (“It was just amazing”) to TMZ (“f*cking awesome”). But to close observers, it appeared the performer was not singing live. To press seated just below the podium, in front of the “President’s Own” Marine Corps Band, it was evident that the band wasn’t actually playing during the song—even though band director Colonel Michael J. Colburn was conducting energetically and the band members mimicked blowing into their instruments. Separately, at one point during her performance, Beyoncé removed her earpiece. A hint as to the actual origins of the version Beyoncé sang came from her own hand: On January 20, the day before the ceremony, Beyoncé posted pictures to her Instagram account that appeared to show her in a recording studio. In one, she holds a copy of the sheet music to “The Star Spangled Banner” in front of a microphone attached to a recording device, and in another she sits in front of recording equipment while members of the Marine Corps Band stand clutching sheet music behind her."</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358885870257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:17:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358885923042-167</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just to be clear, our rights were granted to us by God with a big assist to the guys who fought the British. You had nothing to do with it. You may have fought to preserve those rights but so are all who fight the tyranny of those who would undermine the constitution by executive fiat. If you swore an oath to uphold the COTUS you are obligated to prevent an executive branch that is undermining the COTUS. Why do you think so many law enforcement people will not honor a federal gun ban mandate declared only by the executive office and which would bypass congress should one be declared by the president?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358885923042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:18:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358886410284-168</Id><Topic><Title>Confirmed: Beyoncé Lip-Synced “The Star-Spangled Banner”</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358885870257</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:17:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appropriate since the individual being sworn in is a phony too.</Msg><Username>rividiott</Username><Timestamp>1358886410284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:26:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358886454922-169</Id><Topic><Title>Battery fix is near</Title><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358875484682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:24:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You did not read today's Wall St Journal. Two different sources looking into the problem. Say complex wiring on the airplane. US and Japan looking into the problem. It won't be fixed in a week as we were told last week. Suzanne</Msg><Username>ewblanchard</Username><Timestamp>1358886454922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:27:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358886613262-170</Id><Title>Do Gun Control Laws Control Guns?</Title><Msg>The gun control controversy is only the latest of many issues to be debated almost solely in terms of fixed preconceptions, with little or no examination of hard facts. Media discussions of gun control are dominated by two factors: the National Rifle Association and the Second Amendment. But the over-riding factual question is whether gun control laws actually reduce gun crimes in general or murder rates in particular. If, as gun control advocates claim, gun control laws really do control guns and save lives, there is nothing to prevent repealing the Second Amendment, any more than there was anything to prevent repealing the Eighteenth Amendment that created Prohibition. But, if the hard facts show that gun control laws do not actually control guns, but instead lead to more armed robberies and higher murder rates after law-abiding citizens are disarmed, then gun control laws would be a bad idea, even if there were no Second Amendment and no National Rifle Association. The central issue boils down to the question: What are the facts? Yet there are many zealots who seem utterly unconcerned about facts or about their own lack of knowledge of facts. There are people who have never fired a shot in their life who do not hesitate to declare how many bullets should be the limit to put into a firearm's clip or magazine. Some say ten bullets but New York state's recent gun control law specifies seven. Virtually all gun control advocates say that 30 bullets in a magazine is far too many for self-defense or hunting -- even if they have never gone hunting and never had to defend themselves with a gun. This uninformed and self-righteous dogmatism is what makes the gun control debate so futile and so polarizing. Anyone who faces three home invaders, jeopardizing himself or his family, might find 30 bullets barely adequate. After all, not every bullet hits, even at close range, and not every hit incapacitates. You can get killed by a wounded man. These plain life-and-death realities have been ignored for years by people who go ballistic when they hear about how many shots were fired by the police in some encounter with a criminal. As someone who once taught pistol shooting in the Marine Corps, I am not the least bit surprised by the number of shots fired. I have seen people miss a stationary target at close range, even in the safety and calm of a pistol range. We cannot expect everybody to know that. But we can expect them to know that they don't know -- and to stop spouting off about life-and-death issues when they don't have the facts. The central question as to whether gun control laws save lives or cost lives has generated many factual studies over the years. But these studies have been like the proverbial tree that falls in an empty forest, and has been heard by no one -- certainly not by zealots who have made up their minds and don't want to be confused by the facts. Most factual studies show no reduction in gun crimes, including murder, under gun control laws. A significant number of studies show higher rates of murder and other gun crimes under gun control laws. How can this be? It seems obvious to some gun control zealots that, if no one had guns, there would be fewer armed robberies and fewer people shot to death. But nothing is easier than to disarm peaceful, law-abiding people. And nothing is harder than to disarm people who are neither -- especially in a country with hundreds of millions of guns already out there, that are not going to rust away for centuries. When it was legal to buy a shotgun in London in the middle of the 20th century, there were very few armed robberies there. But, after British gun control zealots managed over the years to disarm virtually the entire law-abiding population, armed robberies became literally a hundred times more common. And murder rates rose. One can cherry-pick the factual studies, or cite some studies that have subsequently been discredited, but the great bulk of the studies show that gun control laws do not in fact control guns. On net balance, they do not save lives but cost lives. Gun control laws allow some people to vent their emotions, politicians to grandstand and self-righteous people to "make a statement" -- but all at the cost of other people's lives. T. Sowell</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358886613262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:30:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358886768911-171</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing exec THROWN OFF THE Uof I Board!!!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358885010631</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:03:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Darn, Boeing exec's being the liars and thieves they are. It would seem they could fit into most any Illinois institution.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358886768911</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:32:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358886850163-172</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm betting on the government"........so was King George.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358886850163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:34:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358886920672-173</Id><Title>HELP ! ! !</Title><Msg>Can someone come up with the physical size of the problematic battery and the weight? The wife and I got into quite an argument over this. I maintained it appeared to be the size of a small fork lift battery and maybe 400-500 pounds She says no, not that big. Help even if I''m wrong.. Al</Msg><Username>bankie3</Username><Timestamp>1358886920672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:35:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358887049695-174</Id><Title>Sarkozy 'to Move to London' to Avoid France's High Taxes...</Title><Msg>Nicolas Sarkozy is preparing to move to London to set up a billion pounds plus investment fund, it was claimed today. If the move goes ahead, the controversial Frenchman will become the latest to escape a potential top tax rate of 75 per cent in his home country. He and his former supermodel third wife Carla Bruni-Sarkozy would be likely to settle in an affluent district like South Kensington – so becoming the most high profile Gallic celebrity couple in the city.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358887049695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:37:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358887455524-175</Id><Topic><Title>Are Liberals in Denial about the Consequences of Massive Deficits and Debt?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864623435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:23:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We all know it has to be paid down and that spending has to be cut, but is it your wish to adopt harsh austerity measures?" The more debt we amass the more harsh the austerity measures will have to be.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358887455524</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:44:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358887649343-176</Id><Topic><Title>Do Gun Control Laws Control Guns?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358886613262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:30:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's much easier for the politicians to control law abiding citizens with more laws. Our cities have been taken over by violent gangs with zero respect for others.. Yet there is no demand that the politicians, mayors, governors, courts, take action. Instead we see the politically correct hand wringing and excuse making. Yet enforcement resources are directed at red light cameras, speed cameras, the "war on drugs", what a joke... Women and children being molested at the airports for what ? Screw the PC bullcrap and insist that the police put the radar guns aside and deal with serious crime. Insist the courts hand out severe sentences. There's already too many gun control laws that only pertain to non criminals.</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1358887649343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:47:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358887654634-177</Id><Topic><Title>They may not have taken all the machine guns, ali ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358883062431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:31:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your argument is not supported by facts and figures. If you want to reminisce about the A-team Hooz the idiot seems interested in your mindless A-team emotional and factless nonsense. Let me recap the key points for you: 1) There are still automatic weapons in Chicago in the hands of criminals as well as the mob which is alive and well. 2) Gun regulations DID NOT "improve the odds" of reducing gun related homicides in Chicago. MOB related deaths after 2/14/29 did not stop. 3) You don't have to join the military to obtain an automatic weapon and not everyone that joins the military is a patriot. I CAN gain obtain an automatic weapon by breaking the law which is easy. However if I am a patriotic law abiding citizen, I CAN NOT own an automatic weapon. 4) Denying patriotic law abiding citizens access to automatic weapons has done nothing to stop criminal use of automatic weapons or lower gun homicides in Chicago. This is all based on REAL Chicago and FBI data I have accessed not movies or A-team TV shows.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358887654634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:47:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358887943758-178</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing exec's are oinkers and several other things.</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358469181976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:33:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>{{{"Too much current flowing too fast into a battery can overwhelm it, causing it to short-circuit and overheat even if the voltage remains within its design limit, he said."}}} where has this been presented before, Oh right here. Boeing didn't take that bit for friendly advice and use it. Its not in their nature. Like crows and magpies they would rather steal it. In any case what has been shown this last week is that Boeing and others don't have a good grasp of how lithium batteries work. They also don't have a good grasp of how their own charging system works. It may or may not even be in accord to the design and drawing spec's.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358887943758</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:52:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358887987381-179</Id><Topic><Title>Do Gun Control Laws Control Guns?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358886613262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:30:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm discussing this with Genna on another post after looking at Chicago and FBI homicide and my research is indicating gun control has been ineffective in Chicago were criminals have large caches of automatic weapons but law abiding citizens can't even carry a pistol.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358887987381</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:53:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358888076390-180</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God set the basic rights of Man in writing and their responsibilities (ten Commandments and Golden rule in Christianity). Many have sacrificed to protect those rights for Americans and for many around the world. YOU casually misuse / abuse those rights and the TRUST that those that protected your God given Rights, with your Hateful / violent comments. What have YOU done for US all? As the first Democracy we/America has a majority rule, while most newer democracies have a more representative style. So sorry for you that you cant have everything you want and also that your life appears to be wrapped around posting your hateful opinions on a Stock message board. ..JMHFO...</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1358888076390</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:54:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358888581589-181</Id><Topic><Title>how low can this go? just a blip now</Title><Username>yourkk</Username><Timestamp>1358867945360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:19:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the 787 becomes a piece of junk then BA ================ Whaddya mean? It already IS a piece of junk! GO AIRBUS :)))))))</Msg><Username>cindyjanel0</Username><Timestamp>1358888581589</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:03:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358889050086-182</Id><Title>Hoozdik Arrested - Now out on bail.</Title><Msg>SHERMAN OAKS, Calif. (KTLA) — A male nurse at the Sherman Oaks Hospital has been arrested for allegedly having sex with a corpse. Alejandro Razo, AKA hoozdik_hertz_333, was arrested on Sunday on a state Health and Safety Code violation after being caught by security guards, police said. He is free on $20,000 bail and is due in court on Feb. 11, according to online records. The L.A. County coroner will perform an autopsy on the body, police said. The findings could determine if more charges will be filed. The coroner’s office declined further comment on the case, citing a security hold. No other details were immediately available. Anyone with information is asked to call the LAPD.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358889050086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:10:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358889102713-183</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So is your god Bastiat. And that weird old man mAyn Rand.</Msg><Username>analgonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1358889102713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:11:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358889247302-184</Id><Topic><Title>They may not have taken all the machine guns, ali ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358883062431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:31:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha! So you think that eliminating Valentine's Day will reduce shootings? Whats the matter, didn't you ever get a card? BTW. Are you on SSRI's?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358889247302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:14:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358889424076-185</Id><Topic><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think that most are done by Liberals?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358889424076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:17:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358889647288-186</Id><Topic><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are all conservatives as pathetically stupid as you?</Msg><Username>rividiot</Username><Timestamp>1358889647288</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:20:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890283755-187</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik Arrested - Now out on bail.</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358889050086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:10:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>beware the #$%$</Msg><Username>rividiott</Username><Timestamp>1358890283755</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:31:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890418170-188</Id><Topic><Title>The Conservative View: Humans Are A Plague</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1358873754089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 11:55:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissy. Your obsession with Ayn Rand and your spelling give you away.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358890418170</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:33:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890466097-189</Id><Topic><Title>Battery fix is near</Title><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358875484682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 12:24:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Thales battery controller has a lot of semiconductor memory as well as logic chips to run it. Soft errors in memory chips that could lead to hard errors in the controller, could lead to logic errors or a short circuit that could start a fire with that much power being controlled. Neutrons and protons in the atmosphere at 30,000 or 40,000 feet are very prevalent up there, and they can cause soft errors in high tech chips. If they find problems with the controller, I hope they look at this potential problem. It is Very hard to simulate such soft errors in memory or logic at normal earth altitudes.</Msg><Username>dontdropyourlunch</Username><Timestamp>1358890466097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:34:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358890487159-190</Id><Title>Dreamliner's Bad News Is Getting worse</Title><Msg>Dreamliner's Bad News Is Getting worse Now investigators at the NTSA, the FAA and their international counterparts are widening their focus to examine the entire auxiliary power unit –and that’s where Boeing starts to have a problem. In addition to its novel electrical design, the Dreamliner pioneered new depths of subcontracted manufacturing: While each 787 was assembled at Boeing’s plant in Everett, Washington, more than 70% of the jets’ individual components were outsourced to more than 900 subcontractors all over the world. By outsourcing construction of the Dreamliner’s systems, Boeing reduced the complexity and cost of manufacturing the new jets. But they also increased the complexity of tracking down problems; the auxiliary power unit alone contains parts from Japan’s GS Yuasa Corporation, France’s Thales Group and North Carolina-based UTC Aerospace Systems, a subsidiary of Connecticut’s United Technologies. Investigators will have to deal with a complicated network of global interests, experts and technologies just to figure out how the Dreamliners’ power system was supposed to work in the first place, much less how it ended up broken. It’s not the sort of problem you can unravel in just a couple of weeks. Further complicating the problem: The different international aviation authorities involved in the investigation already seem to be taking different approaches. Japanese officials seem focused on GS Yuasa’s batteries, while the FAA and NTSB seem to be more interested in UTC’s the electrical controllers. It could be a long time before anyone knows what went wrong, how to fix it so the longer the Dreamliner is grounded, the bigger this problem gets.. Costs to Boeing shareholders 50 million per day to downed airline customer in revenue loss payments, and shareholder pay 400 million per day due to the arrogant Boeing management for the strike due to excessively paid and huge retirement benefits allowed to executives but the same leaders refuse to allow the workers to keep their existing contract the same for another contractual period. The arrogant Boeing executives want to take away from new employee’s their retirement first then go after retiree’s and then the most experienced Boeing workers in a step by step take away. And yet the executives keep getting excessive pay and bonus and benefits while failing on the cheap outsourcing of the 787!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358890487159</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:34:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890504445-191</Id><Topic><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because they were picked on in school and now are taking psychotropic drugs in order to cope.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358890504445</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:35:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890508285-192</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when they have lost heir usefulness they will be killed! ==================== By whom? You and your fascist ilk?</Msg><Username>rightholeleaking</Username><Timestamp>1358890508285</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:35:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890776556-193</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing falls behind Northrop Grumman and Lockheed Martin, lags the Dow Jones , strike !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1356997454028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-31 18:44:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now the 787 is costing shareholders even more money to sit , first late by 3.5 years now payments to the airlines for lack of use , only the Boeing executies are making money , not the shareholders, customers and the flying public are scared of the 787</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358890776556</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:39:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890892616-194</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so how is that cheap outsourcing working for you now Boeing Executies</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358890892616</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:41:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358890908018-195</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who decides that a a govt is "abusive"? You and spartakook and a couple hundred other whackjobs? All I can say is I'm glad the govt has more firepower than you and your misguided squad, if it ever comes down to that.</Msg><Username>rightholeleaking</Username><Timestamp>1358890908018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:41:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358891076172-196</Id><Topic><Title>Message from the market?</Title><Username>benson_bridges_baydreams</Username><Timestamp>1358882501635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:21:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sure had a fine day in the market today, all the more so for having sold all my BA a couple days ago...</Msg><Username>analgonquin11</Username><Timestamp>1358891076172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:44:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358891214307-197</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Debacle: Seven Lessons Every CEO Must Learn</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1358461826122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:30:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump.</Msg><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1358891214307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:46:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358891426369-198</Id><Title>The Liberal's War On Poor Blacks</Title><Msg>"Severe restrictions on building housing in San Francisco have driven rents and home prices so high that blacks and other people with low or moderate incomes have been driven out of the city. ... Liberals try to show their concern for the poor by raising the level of minimum wage laws. Yet they show no interest in hard evidence that minimum wage laws create disastrous levels of unemployment among young blacks in this country, as such laws created high unemployment rates among young people in general in European countries. The black family survived centuries of slavery and generations of Jim Crow, but it has disintegrated in the wake of the liberals' expansion of the welfare state. Most black children grew up in homes with two parents during all that time but most grow up with only one parent today. Liberals have pushed affirmative action, supposedly for the benefit of blacks and other minorities. ... But who cares about facts, when you are on a liberal crusade that makes you feel morally superior?" --economist Thomas Sowell "Severe restrictions on building housing in San Francisco have driven rents and home prices so high that blacks and other people with low or moderate incomes have been driven out of the city. ... Liberals try to show their concern for the poor by raising the level of minimum wage laws. Yet they show no interest in hard evidence that minimum wage laws create disastrous levels of unemployment among young blacks in this country, as such laws created high unemployment rates among young people in general in European countries. The black family survived centuries of slavery and generations of Jim Crow, but it has disintegrated in the wake of the liberals' expansion of the welfare state. Most black children grew up in homes with two parents during all that time but most grow up with only one parent today. Liberals have pushed affirmative action, supposedly for the benefit of blacks and other minorities. ... But who cares about facts, when you are on a liberal crusade that makes you feel morally superior?" --economist Thomas Sowell "Severe restrictions on building housing in San Francisco have driven rents and home prices so high that blacks and other people with low or moderate incomes have been driven out of the city. ... Liberals try to show their concern for the poor by raising the level of minimum wage laws. Yet they show no interest in hard evidence that minimum wage laws create disastrous levels of unemployment among young blacks in this country, as such laws created high unemployment rates among young people in general in European countries. The black family survived centuries of slavery and generations of Jim Crow, but it has disintegrated in the wake of the liberals' expansion of the welfare state. Most black children grew up in homes with two parents during all that time but most grow up with only one parent today. Liberals have pushed affirmative action, supposedly for the benefit of blacks and other minorities. ... But who cares about facts, when you are on a liberal crusade that makes you feel morally superior?" --economist Thomas Sowell</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1358891426369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:50:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358891857283-199</Id><Topic><Title>I see light in the tunnel !</Title><Username>mandi.mcclanahan</Username><Timestamp>1358885259585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:07:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this article.</Msg><Username>ryanyoung879</Username><Timestamp>1358891857283</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:57:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358892060852-200</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal's War On Poor Blacks</Title><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1358891426369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:50:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just take the minimum wage laws liberals pass. That was the first thing I came to. It screws the poor person that needs a job, and an opportunity to get training, and skills needed to move up the ladder. There are always the "unintended consequences" of liberal policy. Good results never happen.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358892060852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:01:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358892504075-201</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick man says, "you don't need it!" Stick man thinks he is the Chosen One just like Obama thinks he is. He's there to tell the consumer what they need, and don't need, as if the consumer was too stupid to decide what they want to spend their money on. Obama has his wide bottomed wife telling American children what they need to eat, and what she will work hard to see that they don't get to eat in school, and their parants are stupid if they allow their kids to eat what she says they are not allowed to eat in school. From light bulbs to cars that burn gas. The left is there to regulate you.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358892504075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:08:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358893338919-202</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't mean to embarrass you but America is not democracy and wasn't the first nation to incorporate democracy into its system of government. My ancestors were the first to do so and their blood sweat and sacrifices to remain free from the Persians is arguably the only reason that much of the world enjoys freedom and that you had a chance to be born in a free land. I would ask you to read Plato's Republic to understand how a democracy can be immoral and unjust as you appear to know little about democracy. My family military service is none of you business but since you asked and I respect your service, we began our military service in 1926. We contributed to the development of the Norden Bombsight used in WW2, the first electron microscope (used to create many military innovations), night vision technology in Viet Nam and LASER technology now used in a variety of ways too expansive to cover here. We were at Pearl Harbor, Guadalcanal, Korea and now both Iraq and Afghanistan. Lastly my opinions are not hateful and it is you that takes it that way most likely because I am different than you and you see me as too unworthy toexpress my views here.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358893338919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:22:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358893500761-203</Id><Title>Mississippi's Last Abortion Clinic</Title><Msg>It's been 40 years since Roe vs. Wade made abortion a constitutional right across the land. But if states can't make the practice illegal, they can pass stringent new laws. In Virginia, for instance, the state legislature recently regulated the location of bathrooms and the sizes of the hallways within clinics, requirements that have been deemed impossible to follow. In April 2012, the Mississippi legislature passed House Bill 1390, which requires abortion providers to gain hospital admitting privileges. Since then, Parker and the other physicians at the clinic have been rejected by the area's seven local hospitals. Five rejected them outright because they were opposed to being associated with an abortion provider, according to the Center for Reproductive Rights. One wrote that giving doctors admitting priveleges "would lead to both an internal and external disruption of the Hospital's function and business within this community." If the Jackson clinic is closed, the 2,000 women who go there for abortions each year will need to travel out-of-state. That will mean paying for bus fare or gas, as well as covering childcare and the loss of wages. There will also be hotel fees: many nearby states require a 72-hour waiting period between a state-mandated counseling session and an abortion. And the procedure itself can cost $450 or even more. (Several of the women in the waiting room of the Jackson clinic said they had received financial assistance from the National Abortion Federation.) All of this may make abortions prohibitively expensive for many Mississippi women, who are among the poorest in the union. According to the latest census, Mississippi had a poverty rate of 22.6 in 2011. The clinic's clientele fall disproportionately into this poorest sector. The bill's supporters insist they aren't trying to make things difficult for low-income women; they're simply trying to protect them. Outside the clinic, protestors, seated on foldable lawn chairs, are eager to tell visitors about the medical risks of abortion, handing out leaflets and models of fetuses. One woman, 64-year-old Ester Mann, calls has been picketing the clinic for many years and has been arrested twice. She says the clients who come there are "disdaining God" and the "precious gift" of pregnancies. She is eagerly awaiting the court decision later this month as she sits outside the clinic, day after day, praying for it to close.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358893500761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:25:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358893540139-204</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Debacle: Seven Lessons Every CEO Must Learn</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1358461826122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:30:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing made a huge mistake in outsoursing critical componeints for the 787. That being said, I feel we have board members that continue to award their top management with large somes of money. I have made this point year after year. Recently HPQ had a bad year and what did they do?? They awarded the CEO with millions. The same goes with any company that does not meet guidance on revenues, should not give a dollar to upper management. Pay for performance is the name of the game! As a stockholder you should vote out all these board members for allowing this to happen. P.S. I believe Boeing will get to the battery problem sooner than later. Holding my shares and not concerned. There is more to BA than the 787.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358893540139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:25:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358894069617-205</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're losing it stick.man Lanza did not use an assault rifle at Sandy Hook. I am a peaceful warrior and you are living in an alternate fictional reality making things up.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358894069617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:34:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358894135637-206</Id><Topic><Title>Mississippi's Last Abortion Clinic</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358893500761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:25:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would anyone want to kill innocent babies.......oh wait a minute stick.man007 I do understand.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358894135637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:35:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358894270779-207</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not saying that our government could be taking over by another country but anything could happen,.</Msg><Username>gpcdist</Username><Timestamp>1358894270779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:37:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358894923116-208</Id><Topic><Title>You dont need a assualt rifle to protect your family or yourself.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358815264793</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-21 19:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And as you said before hooz...that is why you are a communist.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358894923116</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:48:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358896308533-209</Id><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Msg>It uses the energy released in the snap to redraw the bow in a fraction of a second. Problem to over come is seating the arrow on the string. Vibrations can cause a slight turn of the arrow and keep it from lining up on the bow string. Should be able to fix this problem with a little machining. Mathews, Bowtech and Hoyt all very interested in my patent.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358896941268-210</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Mir(de). Imagine "living" a made-up life like this on a stock message board and publicly unwittingly dropping your own pants like Mir(de). This self-illumination makes him a mainstream Republican in many respects and goes a long way in explaining why the black guy got re-elected.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1358896941268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:22:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358897440593-211</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik Arrested - Now out on bail.</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358889050086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 16:10:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the corpse had only had a handgun, it could have defended itself.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358897440593</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:30:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358897610692-212</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you considered designing your own arrows using a slotless overlapping magnetic based system? For the cost of a semi-auto bow costlier arrows would be fine. Without seeing what you already have that's all I have.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358897610692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:33:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358897659860-213</Id><Topic><Title>Do Gun Control Laws Control Guns?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358886613262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:30:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one I read here has recommended prohibiting pistols. And once the manufacture and importation of automatic and automatic-convertible weapons is prohibited NATIONWIDE, the ability to bring them into Chicago from, say, Indiana will probably stop too.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358897659860</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:34:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358897816188-214</Id><Topic><Title>They may not have taken all the machine guns, ali ...</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358883062431</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:31:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"if I am a patriotic law abiding citizen, I CAN NOT own an automatic weapon." Good. Now all we have to do is round up the illegal automatic weapons. Just think how easy that would be if we didn't make more. After every major crime committed with one, it gets thrown in the river. :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358897816188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:36:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358898021422-215</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those committed to revolution will always get the weapons they need. I remember how in Vietnam about 1964, almost every VC weapons cash found consisted of U.S. or French weapons. It was later that they started getting Kalashnikovs. And not a one of those, I bet, was in the hands of Vietnamese civilians before WE got there.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358898021422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:40:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358898134262-216</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And YOU get to decide what "undermining" is, and who is doing it? Sounds like dictatorial power to me.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358898134262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:42:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358898161568-217</Id><Topic><Title>GAO Report Warns Of Economic Collapse</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1358867653804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:14:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is only one number that is a typo. orly, you may be too stupid to type in convert Celsius to Fahrenheit but I don't think Mir is.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358898161568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:42:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358900817028-218</Id><Topic><Title>will this boondoggle affect my boeing pension check and healthcare? These mgrs and shi* and fall in it but please not me.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358900574630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:22:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, it will. you don't expect Boeing insiders to take the hit do you?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358900817028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:26:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358900901270-219</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where would the American people get those guns from? Mexican Drug Lords via the Obama administration ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358900901270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:28:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358901607340-220</Id><Topic><Title>will this boondoggle affect my boeing pension check and healthcare? These mgrs and shi* and fall in it but please not me.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358900574630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:22:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will have a worse effect on your pension plan and healthcare than any Boeing mgr. ever could have. Union pension funds are going unfunded bigtime everywhere.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358901607340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:40:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358901668121-221</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ill bet your were dizzy with laughter while innocent women and children were burned to death at WACO..what a POS you r.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358901668121</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:41:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358902372169-222</Id><Title>Under $70 coming, get the H-e-I-I out now!</Title><Msg>it could be more $60s is possible.</Msg><Username>styuiksv</Username><Timestamp>1358902372169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:52:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358902717607-223</Id><Topic><Title>I Just Finished A Completely Automatic Compound Bow that shoots 7,000 Arrows</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358898009131</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:40:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You more likely have 7000 cockroaches fighting each other for the last bit of gray matter inside your skull.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358902717607</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:58:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358903162103-224</Id><Topic><Title>will this boondoggle affect my boeing pension check and healthcare? These mgrs and shi* and fall in it but please not me.</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358900574630</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:22:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really, Jpe? Tell us how - be specific.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1358903162103</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:06:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358903256413-225</Id><Topic><Title>Under $70 coming, get the H-e-I-I out now!</Title><Username>styuiksv</Username><Timestamp>1358902372169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:52:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. My guess is that the shorts are waiting for BA to exhaust it's $3.5 billion authorized share buy-back program before the jump in and short the hell out of the stock. It should only be a matter of 1 to 2 days before that happens. I can't imagine that anyone in the right mind is actually buying BA stock in light of these developments. Why would anyone take a huge risk and hold on to or buy BA when there is so much money to be made elsewhere in the market. My guess is that Boeing is the only buyer right now in a desparate effort to prevent a precipitous drop in the price of the stock. This can't go on forever as they will soon deplete their authorized buyback funds and then watch out. With an enourmous debt and reduced cash on hand due to the buybacks, BA may be handed for BK if the problem does not get fixed soon.</Msg><Username>fternoss</Username><Timestamp>1358903256413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:07:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358903308547-226</Id><Topic><Title>Under $70 coming, get the H-e-I-I out now!</Title><Username>styuiksv</Username><Timestamp>1358902372169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:52:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing put so much trust on Lithium Batteries. We all know it's not a safe technology from the very beginning, starting with cell phones and laptop fires. I heard there is a much newer technology out there, the so called Nano batteries. So now, how long will they keep the Boeing 787 Dreamliner grounded ?</Msg><Username>lucky_me2010</Username><Timestamp>1358903308547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:08:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358903740828-227</Id><Title>WARNING: BOEING HAS ENTERED THIS SITE TRYING TO SPEAK POLITICS INSTEAD OF THEIR FAILED PLASTIC NIGHMARELINER</Title><Msg>Warning: boeing has entered this site trying to speak politics instead of their failed plastic nighmareliner</Msg><Username>copyright_member</Username><Timestamp>1358903740828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:15:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358904019929-228</Id><Topic><Title>Under $70 coming, get the H-e-I-I out now!</Title><Username>styuiksv</Username><Timestamp>1358902372169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:52:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The FAA will be very hesitant to expeditethe lifting of the grounding due to the huge liability and critcism that will follow in the event another incident happens. They will not take the chance unless 1000% sure at this time. They have already being criticized as being cozy with the BA management just prior to the grounding. FAA officials better be worried. Public safety will not be sacrificed for to protect Boing's bottom line. FAA will be charged wit criminal acts and fraud if it is determined that they have been acting in the best interest of BA's bottom line instead in the best interest of public safety.</Msg><Username>fternoss</Username><Timestamp>1358904019929</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:20:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358904192604-229</Id><Title>YOU PLEASE BOEING WHEN TALKING POLITICS AND AVOIDIND TALKS ABOUT THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Msg>You please boeing when talking politics and avoidind talks about the 787 disaster</Msg><Username>copyright_member</Username><Timestamp>1358904192604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:23:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358904509220-230</Id><Title>Boeing Dreamliner fires spark new doubts about a green energy technology</Title><Msg>When Federal Aviation Administration officials grounded Boeing's fleet of 787 Dreamliner commercial jets last week due to unexplained battery fires, one of President Obama's favorite green energy technologies got another black eye. Technologists and safety experts had long warned of problems with the lithium ion battery when in 2009 the president began betting billions of tax dollars that it should be the green power of choice for cars, trucks, and even aircraft. Just three years before that, a UPS cargo plane made an emergency landing when a shipment of lithium ion batteries it was carrying caught fire. The plane landed safely but was destroyed by the ensuing conflagration. Small lithium ion batteries are widely used in consumer electronics, but powering vehicles like a car or an aircraft is a much greater challenge. The 787, for example, has to generate 1.5 megawatts of electrical power, enough to light up several hundred homes. Boeing and the FAA said the 787 will not fly again until the battery fires are explained and fixed. There have been a total of four reported fires, including one during 2010 pre-delivery flight, according to Scientific American. The problem, according to the MIT Technology Review, is that "because the electrolyte materials used are flammable, no lithium-ion batteries are completely safe." And last April, the National Fire Protection Association warned that "as lithium-ion battery use increases, so do the concerns related to the fire-safety hazards of these devices." Some experts believe the batteries have been oversold to the public. "Lithium ion batteries just won't do the trick in the kind of mass vehicle applications that the environmental community is pushing for," said Jon Entine, founder of ESG Media Metrics, a Cincinnati-based environmental consulting firm.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358904509220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:28:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358904615027-231</Id><Title>THE FAILED BOEING CEO IS DOING SOME BYBACK BUT VERY SOON HE WILL BE SELLING SHARES</Title><Msg>EOM...</Msg><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1358904615027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:30:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358904932359-232</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hadn't thought of that, I'll have to kick it around with the engineer working on the project. There are some videos online that have several different systems but no of them are as fast as ours. We've played with compressed gas and looked at electric models but they're still too slow. Hydraulics triggered by snap energy is pretty fast. Thanks for the idea.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358904932359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:35:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358905159089-233</Id><Title>BOEIN IS PAYING SOME PEOPLE TO SPEAK HERE ABOUT OTHER THINGS THAN THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Msg>EOM...</Msg><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1358905159089</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:39:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358905251007-234</Id><Title>BOEING IS PAYING SOME PEOPLE TO SPEAK HERE ABOUT OTHER THINGS THAN THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Msg>EOM...</Msg><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1358905251007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:40:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358905254927-235</Id><Title>BOEING IS PAYING SOME PEOPLE TO SPEAK HERE ABOUT OTHER THINGS THAN THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Msg>EOM...</Msg><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1358905254927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:40:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358905305731-236</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will there be a flaming option........like the 787-Torch</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1358905305731</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:41:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358905323373-237</Id><Title>FAA OFFICIALS SHOULD BE CHARGED WITH CRIMINAL ACTS</Title><Msg>If the 787 grounding is lifted prematurely and a catastrophic event happens, the faa officials should be arrested. when faa officials were standing next to ba upper managementand insisted that the 787 planes were safe, just to change their mind a day later, tells us that these guys are in bed with the boeing managment team and they were only trying to protect the company's bottom line and cared less about public safety. congress should fire them now. the faa's number one priority should be the welbeing and safety of the traveling public. unfortunaely, these so called faa oficials have failed miserably to do their job. it's crying shame!!!</Msg><Username>fternoss</Username><Timestamp>1358905323373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:42:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358905742116-238</Id><Topic><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both suspects in custody. Both injured, as well as a couple others who were not involved in disagreement.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1358905742116</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:49:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358906011886-239</Id><Topic><Title>Under $70 coming, get the H-e-I-I out now!</Title><Username>styuiksv</Username><Timestamp>1358902372169</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 19:52:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the buyback hasn't even started yet. It's not happening after the earnings release.</Msg><Username>tan.tomas55</Username><Timestamp>1358906011886</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:53:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358906044372-240</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>creative good luck ... hail the American creative spirit</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358906044372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:54:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358906614960-241</Id><Topic><Title>Do Gun Control Laws Control Guns?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358886613262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:30:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you have such trouble coming up with a rational thought?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358906614960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:03:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358906646982-242</Id><Topic><Title>12 Ways Obama Smacked Down the Right in His Inauguration Speech</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358895159537</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 17:52:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well .... Peter Piper Picked a Peck...that sure was a Pretty speech #$%$. The country needs more then words....we are on the verge of bankruptcy and endless war perpetuates itself and virtually EVERY amendment of the consitution is under attack despite the Orwellian denials by Barrys speechwriter...but golly gee those words were wonderful....you MAY Remember the biblical injunction: "By his DEEDS, ye shall know him"</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358906646982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:04:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358906924099-243</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you seen all 3 Batman movies?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358906924099</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:08:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358907964959-244</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING IS PAYING SOME PEOPLE TO SPEAK HERE ABOUT OTHER THINGS THAN THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1358905254927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:40:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bingo</Msg><Username>pierre_from_geneva</Username><Timestamp>1358907964959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:26:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358908222216-245</Id><Title>SHAME ON BOEING FOR PUTTING PASSENGERS AT RISK ON A 787 DISASTER</Title><Msg>EOM...</Msg><Username>speaker_737</Username><Timestamp>1358908222216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:30:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358908594378-246</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING IS PAYING SOME PEOPLE TO SPEAK HERE ABOUT OTHER THINGS THAN THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1358905254927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:40:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must not have been following this board for long. This is actually below the average political and off topic postings.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1358908594378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:36:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358908624998-247</Id><Title>A new gun threat gets 5 yr old child suspended</Title><Msg>A mental evaluation needs to be given to the principal A 5-year-old girl was suspended from school earlier this week after she made what the school called a “terrorist threat.” Her weapon of choice? A small, Hello Kitty automatic bubble blower. The kindergartner, who attends Mount Carmel Area Elementary School in Pennsylvania, caught administrators’ attention after suggesting she and a classmate should shoot each other with bubbles. “I think people know how harmless a bubble is. It doesn’t hurt,” said Robin Ficker, an attorney for the girl’s family. According to Ficker, the girl, whose identity has not been released, didn’t even have the bubble gun toy with her at school. The kindergartner was ordered to undergo a psychological evaluation during her 10-day suspension, which was later reduced to two days. The evaluation deemed the girl normal and not a threat to others, Ficker said. The girl’s family is considering a lawsuit against the school to get the blemish – all because of bubbles – off their daughter’s record. “The mother has tried to get the girl in another school since this time, and they won’t take the little girl because of this mark on her record,” Ficker said.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358908624998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:37:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358908672462-248</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ali, you distorted my words and certainly their meanings. My opinion was clear and many of my posts carry the same message.. Thanks to your family members for their long time sacrifices for American Democracy. I have read some and slightly understand the differences between Persian and Arabian and accept some of your version of History. The heading of this thread brought my original reply to 'x234' and your reply to my post on God and Rights was answered in tone. I would hope that people/Americans that enjoy the Blessing of Liberty and protections of God's and America's Rights would understand my replies. .. And as an American I respect your Rights. I still do not support the concept of Armed insurrection or Law enforcement / military not obeying the Law. .</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1358908672462</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:37:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358908808510-249</Id><Topic><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the hell are two young black students in a Texas college doing on campus with guns? Must be that Super Macho Black BS Thing!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1358908808510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:40:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358909164766-250</Id><Topic><Title>WARNING: BOEING HAS ENTERED THIS SITE TRYING TO SPEAK POLITICS INSTEAD OF THEIR FAILED PLASTIC NIGHMARELINER</Title><Username>copyright_member</Username><Timestamp>1358903740828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:15:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like it's been real hard to find anything on line or in the MSM about the 787. Looks like Boeing has been very successful in suppressing articles. I like to get my info from YAHOO finance boards where people can throw out their theories and opinions on how airplanes work. LOL</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1358909164766</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:46:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358909659281-251</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Lautenberg introduces ban on high-capacity magazines</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358898843883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:54:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now only criminals will have access to high-capacity magazines. How fair is that? This is the beginning of the Disarming of the American People by Government. I heard that under Obamacare your doctor will be required to ask you if you own a weapon when you go in to see him for treatment. I'm afraid that if you refuse to answer that question your doctor can refuse your treatment. I see this eventually going all the way to the Supreme Court.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1358909659281</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:54:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358909816008-252</Id><Topic><Title>Are Liberals in Denial about the Consequences of Massive Deficits and Debt?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864623435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:23:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Deficits don't matter" Richard Cheney</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1358909816008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:56:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358909952497-253</Id><Topic><Title>A new gun threat gets 5 yr old child suspended</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358908624998</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:37:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Left wing ding bats are totally void of commonsense. The worst form of child abuse is placing them in a public school.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358909952497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 21:59:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910171471-254</Id><Topic><Title>WARNING: BOEING HAS ENTERED THIS SITE TRYING TO SPEAK POLITICS INSTEAD OF THEIR FAILED PLASTIC NIGHMARELINER</Title><Username>copyright_member</Username><Timestamp>1358903740828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:15:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>source ??? credible source ?? Just cuz youre paranoid doesnt mean they afrent out to get you ! Check under the bed before mommy tucks you in !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358910171471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:02:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910183066-255</Id><Topic><Title>Are Liberals in Denial about the Consequences of Massive Deficits and Debt?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864623435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:23:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ronald Reagan exploded the federal debt, eventually to over a trillion dollars, by cutting taxes while demanding that the nation fund a huge expansion of the military. Even the Wall Street Journal at the time was aware of the unsound nature of this Republican deficit-spending scheme. They and other newspapers warned of the "baleful effects of big [government] deficits." Reagan was hopeful that the deficits would frighten the American people into supporting a wide-ranging series of cuts in social spending, not military spending, and while some cuts were made in welfare programs, which increased the suffering of the poor, the debt as a percentage of GDP ballooned under Reagan and George H. W. Bush (Bush I) back to a point it had been at under another Republican, Dwight Eisenhower.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1358910183066</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:03:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910308458-256</Id><Topic><Title>BOEING IS PAYING SOME PEOPLE TO SPEAK HERE ABOUT OTHER THINGS THAN THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1358905251007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 20:40:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xawa, your right , just flag it and report it, Yahoo will ban them , it has been going on for a long time, but then boeing has been ahving so many problems they employ these spam and hate posters to keep boeing financial interested people away , it does work but then they just go to the professional and the news on Boeing is worse now anyway. Tht thumbs down with no comment can be traced by Yahoo and most likely that user is a Boeing managment enabler, they come out hard to police the Boeing message board and Yahoo is getting wise and going to continue to impove the monitoring and eventually the spam , and Boeing managment enablers who use harassing coments as users will be gone</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358910308458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:05:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910335572-257</Id><Topic><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the altercation did not meet criteria for the valid use of firearms, then the shooters should go to jail and lose firearm privileges. If Hoozdik is an idiot and shoots 7,000 arrows at an apple on Beyoncé's head I'm fine with you taking away his weapon because he has shown that he is irresponsible and abusive in using a bow, but no one else should suffer for his stupidity and have ther weapons confiscated even if it can shoot 7,000 arrows.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358910335572</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:05:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910496602-258</Id><Topic><Title>Are Liberals in Denial about the Consequences of Massive Deficits and Debt?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864623435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:23:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What office does Richard Cheney hold?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358910496602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:08:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910735190-259</Id><Topic><Title>You Need Assualt Rifles if you are going to fulfill your duty......</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358881995031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:13:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Military my be on our side...then what you #$%$ gonna do?</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358910735190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:12:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358910786066-260</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I developed this super sling shot that shoots armor piercing pellets.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1358910786066</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:13:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358910927863-261</Id><Title>SOON AIRLINES WILL ASK THEIR MONEY BACK AND START CANCELLING THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Msg>EOM...</Msg><Username>communicator_777</Username><Timestamp>1358910927863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:15:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358911370970-262</Id><Topic><Title>Do Gun Control Laws Control Guns?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358886613262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:30:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent #$%$ cant hold the thread of an argument....even IF this is just about automatic weapons gun control statistics show over-whelmingly where there are handguns OR automatic weapons, violent crime is lower when law abiding citizens are armed. Even Piers Morgan (the guy that got kicked out of Great Britain on a charge of fraud) is wrong about stats in England...violent crime is actually HIGHER since English citizens were disarmed.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358911370970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:22:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358911581906-263</Id><Title>The Importance of Gun Ownership</Title><Msg>“The Constitution shall never be construed to authorize Congress to prevent the people of the United States, who are peaceable citizens, from keeping their own arms.”  – Samuel Adams “Who are the militia? Are they not ourselves? Is it feared, then, that we shall turn our arms each man gainst his own bosom. Congress have no power to disarm the militia. Their swords, and every other terrible implement of the soldier, are the birthright of an American…” – Tench Coxe 1788 “The Constitution preserves “the advantage of being armed which Americans possess over the people of almost every other nation…(where) the governments are afraid to trust the people with arms.” - James Madison, The Federalist, No. 46 “Ideas are more powerful than guns. We would not let our enemies have guns, why should we let them have ideas.” - Joseph Stalin “In earlier times, it was easier to control one million people than to physically kill one million people; today, it is infinitely easier to kill one million people than to control one million people.” - Zbigniew Brzezinski “Death solves all problems – no man, no problem.” - Joseph Stalin “Education is a weapon whose effects depend on who holds it in his hands and at whom it is aimed.” - Joseph Stalin “The only real power comes out of a long rifle.” - Joseph Stalin “The best we can hope for concerning the people at large is that they be properly armed.”  – Alexander Hamilton, The Federalist Papers “Those now possessing weapons and ammunition are at once to turn them over to the local police authority. Firearms and ammunition found in a Jew’s possession will be forfeited to the government without compensation. Whoever willfully or negligently violates the provisions will be punished with imprisonment and a fine.” - Nazi Law (Regulations Against Jews’ Possession of Weapons), 1938 “Arms discourage and keep the invader and plunderer in awe, and preserve order in the world as well as property… Horrid mischief would ensue were the law-abiding deprived of the use of them. ” –Thomas Paine “It is the duty of the patriot to protect his country from its government.” - Thomas Paine “When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny. The strongest reason for the people to retain the right to keep and bear arms is, as a last resort, to protect themselves against tyranny in government.” - Thomas Jefferson “Those who beat their swords into plowshares usually end up plowing for those who didn’t. ” – Ben Franklin “If the opposition disarms, well and good. If it refuses to disarm, we shall disarm it ourselves.” - Joseph Stalin “What country can preserve its liberties if their rulers are not warned from time to time that their people preserve the spirit of resistance. Let them take arms.” – Thomas Jefferson “A free people ought not only to be armed and disciplined, but they should have sufficient arms and ammunition to maintain a status of independence from any who might attempt to abuse them, which would include their own government.” – George Washington “Guard with jealous attention the public liberty. Suspect everyone who approaches that jewel. Unfortunately, nothing will preserve it but downright force. Whenever you give up that force, you are ruined…The great object is that every man be armed. Everyone who is able might have a gun.”  – Patrick Henry “Are we at last brought to such an humiliating and debasing degradation that we cannot be trusted with arms for our own defense?” – Patrick Henry “The right of the people to keep and bear…arms shall not be infringed. A well regulated militia, composed of the people, trained to arms, is the best and most natural defense of a free country…”  –James Madison, I Annals of Congress 434 (June 8, 1789) “(The Constitution preserves) the advantage of being armed which Americans possess over the people of almost every other nation…(where) the governments are afraid to trust the people with arms.” –James Madison “If the representatives of the people betray their constituents, there is then no recourse left but in the exertion of that original right of self defense which is paramount to all positive forms of government…” – Alexander Hamilton, The Federalist (#28) “To disarm the people is the best and most effective way to enslave them.” – George Mason “The supreme power in America cannot enforce unjust laws by the sword; because the whole body of the people are armed, and constitute a force superior to any bands of regular troops that can be, on any pretense, raised in the United States.”  – Noah Webster, “An Examination into the Leading Principles of the Federal Constitution (1787) “A free people [claim] their rights as derived from the laws of nature, and not as the gift of their chief magistrate.” –Thomas Jefferson, Rights of British America, 1774 “The balance of power is the scale of peace. The same balance would be preserved were all the world destitute of arms, for all would be alike; but since some will not, others dare not lay them aside. And while a single nation refuses to lay them down, it is proper that all should keep them up. Horrid mischief would ensue were one half the world deprived of the use of them; for while avarice and ambition have a place in the heart of man, the weak will become a prey to the strong.” - Thomas Paine, “Thoughts on Defensive War”, July, 1775 “Political power grows out of the barrel of a gun.” - Mao Zedong, “Problems of War and Strategy”, 1938 “To preserve liberty, it is essential that the whole body of the people always possess arms, and be taught alike, especially when young, how to use them.” - Richard Henry Lee, 1778 “The right of citizens to bear arms is just one more guarantee against arbitrary government, one more safeguard against the tyranny which now appears remote in America, but which historically has proved to be always possible.” - Hubert Humphrey, “Know Your Lawmakers”, Guns magazine, February 1960 “The most foolish mistake we could possibly make would be to allow the subject races to possess arms. History shows that all conquerors who have allowed their subject races to carry arms have prepared their own downfall by so doing.” - Adolf Hitler, April 1942</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358911581906</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:26:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358911719478-264</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck and have fun.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358911719478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:28:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358911762659-265</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I have</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358911762659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:29:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358912158749-266</Id><Topic><Title>SOON AIRLINES WILL ASK THEIR MONEY BACK AND START CANCELLING THE 787 DISASTER</Title><Username>communicator_777</Username><Timestamp>1358910927863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:15:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my fear is if they start flying again with their plasticliner and kill some people</Msg><Username>copyright_member</Username><Timestamp>1358912158749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:35:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358912333283-267</Id><Topic><Title>Another College Shooting... Texas !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358884697670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:58:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What they're doing.? Looking for white girls to bang!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1358912333283</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:38:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358912610863-268</Id><Topic><Title>Have they reached their $2 billion in share buybacks yet?</Title><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614513537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:55:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>up to the top of the board you go....</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358912610863</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358913494757-269</Id><Title>AT THE END BOEING WILL HAVE TO STOP THE PRODUCTION OF THE 787 DISASTERLINER</Title><Msg>EOM...</Msg><Username>communicator_777</Username><Timestamp>1358913494757</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:58:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358913934096-270</Id><Topic><Title>Are Liberals in Denial about the Consequences of Massive Deficits and Debt?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358864623435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 09:23:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Closet LibDem</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1358913934096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 23:05:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358913936668-271</Id><Topic><Title>Do Gun Control Laws Control Guns?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1358886613262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 15:30:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There there--it'll all be okay. In 4 years less one day, when Obama finishes his 2nd term.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1358913936668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 23:05:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358914085693-272</Id><Topic><Title>AT THE END BOEING WILL HAVE TO STOP THE PRODUCTION OF THE 787 DISASTERLINER</Title><Username>communicator_777</Username><Timestamp>1358913494757</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 22:58:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very probable</Msg><Username>xawa</Username><Timestamp>1358914085693</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 23:08:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358914107496-273</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Working on a Semi-Automatic Compound Bow that shoots up to 50 Arrows</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1358896308533</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 18:11:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Floyd's slip: Take it easy. These are not documentaries you are dreaming about.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1358914107496</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 23:08:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358914591245-274</Id><Title>SOON BOEING WILL BE SELLING THEIR STOCK TO PAY FOR THE PLASTIC 787 DISASTERLINER</Title><Msg>EOM...</Msg><Username>speaker_737</Username><Timestamp>1358914591245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 23:16:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>