<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364620792524-1</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik now Chrissie's Official Crotch Snifer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364585861520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:37:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know me so well ... Loon. What does "stands for nothing" mean? That I don't buy into YOUR lunacy?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364620792524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 01:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364631674166-2</Id><Title>Wayne, when do you think the big bird will be cleared for takeoff. Your friends at Art Vandaley Industries</Title><Msg>My pal, Joe Sacamano thinks July, 4th.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1364631674166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 04:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364635025462-3</Id><Topic><Title>GS YUASA CRISIS DEEPENS w/ CAR BATTERY FIRE</Title><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364521091071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:38:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think GS YUASA is putting people's lives at risk and the entire lithium battery setup should be junked AND THE WEIGHT ISSUES SHOULD BE SACRIFICED. IF THERE IS NO ROOM, MAKE ROOM! I WILL NEVER FLY ON A 787 AS LONG AS THEY USE LITHIUM BATTERIES. SO THEY BUILT A BOX TO "CONTAIN ANY FIRE". SO WHAT ??!!! WHAT ARE THEY THINKING !!!!! !!!?? THAT IS IS IN EFFECT SAYING, "WE KNOW IT MIGHT BURN, MONEY IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN PEOPLE", and "MY STOCK OPTIONS ARE WORTH A LOT OF MONEY TO VESTED EMPLOYEES AND SR MANAGEMENT". IF IT DOES THE PLANE WON'T BURN BEFORE IT CRASHES BEFORE IT LOSES POWER, HOPEFULLY THE BACK BOX WILL BUN UP ALSO, I SPECULATE. i HOPE RAY LAHOOD DOES HIS JOB AND THE GOVERNMENT IS NOT INTIMIDATED AND THE WINKY BLINKY CORRUPTED FAA IS INCORRUPTIBLE, which is a serious question that over time will be answered; or NOT ANSWERED. .</Msg><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364635025462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 05:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364635845659-4</Id><Title>LITHIUM BATTERIES CREATE INTENSE FLASH FIRES !</Title><Msg>It has happened to computers, cell phones and now a hundred million dollar plus "white elephant airplane", that to me lookss like the titanic of the big sky. i guess that the faa will wait for the first one to crash, perhaps into the city of denver (???) and five hundred very dead people and or a big patch of scorched real estate(??) to deal with. fact: the faa is corruptible as many faa senior managers once worked for or with boeing sr management. They are most likely and are winky blinky with management at boeing. president obama, speak out on this issue to the american people, now !!!!!!!!!!!! Reassure us that battery will be thrown into the garbage can, until it is 1000% right, years from now please...</Msg><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1364635845659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 05:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364637772946-5</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik now Chrissie's Official Crotch Snifer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364585861520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:37:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has so many that he has to have a census.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1364637772946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 06:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364638050139-6</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik now Chrissie's Official Crotch Snifer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364585861520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:37:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you stand for? When you're not projecting, that is......</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1364638050139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 06:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364649060024-7</Id><Title>You can alwas tell when a liberal Can't Defend their Communist Dogma</Title><Msg>They will turn to calling anyone who questions them names.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364649060024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 09:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364654185189-8</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan Republican, Uses Facebook To Condemn The 'Filthy' Lifestyle Of 'Homosexuals'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364596267537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoozdik is very sensitive about criticism of homosexuals. He takes it very personal.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364654185189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:36:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364654226267-9</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan Republican, Uses Facebook To Condemn The 'Filthy' Lifestyle Of 'Homosexuals'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364596267537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does this story add to the discussion about gay marriage? I've seen comments here with progressives casting similar dispersions on Southern Whites for example. Is there a difference between Dem prejudice and Repub prejudice? Of course there isn't except in the minds of those blind to motivated reasoning.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364654226267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364655394073-10</Id><Title>What's the Difference between a Communist and Democrat?</Title><Msg>I couldn't think of anything either.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364655394073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364656943715-11</Id><Title>The “Cyprus deal” collapse of fractional-reserve banking</Title><Msg>The “Cyprus deal” as it has been widely referred to in the media may mark the next to last act in the the slow motion collapse of fractional-reserve banking that began with the implosion of the savings-and-loan industry in the U.S. in the late 1980s. This trend continued with the currency crises in Russia, Mexico, East Asia and Argentina in the 1990s in which fractional-reserve banking played a decisive role. The unraveling of fractional-reserve banking became visible even to the average depositor during the financial meltdown of 2008 that ignited bank runs on some of the largest and most venerable financial institutions in the world. The final collapse was only averted by the multi-trillion dollar bailoutof U.S. and foreign banks by the Federal Reserve. Even more than the unprecedented financial crisis of 2008, however, recent events in Cyprus may have struck the mortal blow to fractional-reserve banking. For fractional reserve banking can only exist for as long as the depositors have complete confidence that regardless of the financial woes that befall the bank entrusted with their “deposits,” they will always be able to withdraw them on demand at par in currency, the ultimate cash of any banking system. Ever since World War Two governmental deposit insurance, backed up by the money-creating powers of the central bank, was seen as the unshakable guarantee that warranted such confidence. In effect, fractional-reserve banking was perceived as 100-percent banking by depositors, who acted as if their money was always “in the bank” thanks to the ability of central banks to conjure up money out of thin air (or in cyberspace). Perversely the various crises involving fractional-reserve banking that struck time and again since the late 1980s only reinforced this belief among depositors, because troubled banks and thrift institutions were always bailed out with alacrity – especially the largest and least stable. Thus arose the “too-big-to-fail doctrine.” Under this doctrine, uninsured bank depositors and bondholders were generally made whole when large banks failed, because it was widely understood that the confidence in the entire banking system was a frail and evanescent thing that would break and completely dissipate as a result of the failure of even a single large institution.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364656943715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364659364172-12</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie, hoozdik and other Communists Enjoy seeing Americans Suffer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364653872944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, there is a very creepy world view that goes with being a liberal. They are the ultimate hypocrites. They have no trouble pointing out all of Bush's many faults, but they let Obama do any discusting thing he wants without anything but mindless praise for all his immoral actions and con games. There is really no need to take seriously anything a liberal says, because they are either misinformed or lying. Probably both! That's just the way they roll.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1364659364172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364659909112-13</Id><Topic><Title>march deliveries increasing</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1364338532173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-26 18:55:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as of 9am PT deliveries are up to 50 for March. 33 737's, 5 747's, 1 767, 11 777's.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1364659909112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364660017991-14</Id><Title>Littoral Combat Ships Are Fast</Title><Msg>According to naval analysts they will sink fast after one salvo. Sailors, remember wear clean underwear and don't take off your life jackets.</Msg><Username>palinbigbazzoo</Username><Timestamp>1364660017991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364663532834-15</Id><Topic><Title>Jim Carrey Calls Fox News ‘a Media Colostomy Bag’</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364606382739</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 21:19:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now I get it! Carrey no longer has a movie career. He's become irrelevant to most of us. Try to stimulate his waning career by getting involved in politics. Poor SOB. Facial expressions can no longer carry his career.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364663532834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364664518160-16</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between a Communist and Democrat?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364655394073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both of them prefer the Communist Manifesto over the U.S. Constitution.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1364664518160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364664917181-17</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan Republican, Uses Facebook To Condemn The 'Filthy' Lifestyle Of 'Homosexuals'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364596267537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dispersions? Really?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364664917181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364664964607-18</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik now Chrissie's Official Crotch Snifer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364585861520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:37:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Chrissie doesn't quit making those quick turns to the left hoozdik's nose will be bent permanently in a 90 degree angle to the left.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1364664964607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364665211652-19</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik now Chrissie's Official Crotch Snifer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364585861520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:37:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can always tell when the right-fringer haters have nothing. They just hate.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364665211652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:40:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364665346737-20</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan Republican, Uses Facebook To Condemn The 'Filthy' Lifestyle Of 'Homosexuals'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364596267537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And this would matter to anyone here why. precisely? This isn't another lame right-fringe attempt to be clever, is it? Get over yourself.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364665346737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364665431218-21</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik now Chrissie's Official Crotch Snifer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364585861520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:37:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is so full of hate as a left-wing liberal. That's why they Always turn to insullting and name calling. Chrissie is one of the worst.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1364665431218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364666355859-22</Id><Topic><Title>787 bad news</Title><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364360407092</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 01:00:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good news for shorts</Msg><Username>nicehereinca</Username><Timestamp>1364666355859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364666598781-23</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik now Chrissie's Official Crotch Snifer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364585861520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:37:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You call people communists. At least I only call you what you really are. a $ $ wipe</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364666598781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 14:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364667306598-24</Id><Topic><Title>Wayne, when do you think the big bird will be cleared for takeoff. Your friends at Art Vandaley Industries</Title><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1364631674166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 04:21:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne9534 contact tower on 3454.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1364667306598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 14:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364668014068-25</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie, hoozdik and other Communists Enjoy seeing Americans Suffer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364653872944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They must, they keep praising the source of the suffering.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1364668014068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 14:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364668122016-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik now Chrissie's Official Crotch Snifer</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364585861520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:37:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for proving my poInt.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1364668122016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 14:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364671922801-27</Id><Title>What ift Feels like to have your Life savings stolen by N.W.O. Global Elite Banksters</Title><Msg>How would you feel if something like this happened to you? For example, just consider the case of one 65-year-old retiree that has had his life savings totally wiped out by the “wealth tax” in Cyprus. His very sad story was recently featured by the Sydney Morning Herald… ”Very bad, very, very bad,” says 65-year-old John Demetriou, rubbing tears from his lined face with thick fingers. ”I lost all my money.” John now lives in the picturesque fishing village of Liopetri on Cyprus’ south coast. But for 35 years he lived at Bondi Junction and worked days, nights and weekends in Sydney markets selling jewellery and imitation jewellery. He had left Cyprus in the early 1970s at the height of its war with Turkey, taking his wife and young children to safety in Australia. He built a life from nothing and, gradually, a substantial nest egg. He retired to Cyprus in 2007 with about $1 million, his life savings. He planned to spend it on his grandchildren – some of whom live in Cyprus – putting them through university and setting them up. There would be medical bills; he has a heart condition. The interest was paying for a comfortable retirement, and trips back to Australia. He also toyed with the idea of buying a boat. He wanted to leave any big purchases a few years, to be sure this was where he would spend his retirement. There was no hurry. But now it is all gone. ”If I made the decision to stay, I was going to build a house,” John says. ”Unfortunately I didn’t make the decision yet. ”I went to sleep Friday as a rich man. I woke up a poor man.” How would you feel if you suddenly lost almost everything that you have been working for your entire life? And many small and mid-size businesses have been ruined by the bank account confiscation that has taken place in Cyprus.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364671922801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364672230879-28</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan Republican, Uses Facebook To Condemn The 'Filthy' Lifestyle Of 'Homosexuals'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364596267537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about the gay people who are against gay marriage? Gay Marriage IS a Threat — To Gay Sexual Freedom 05Jul11 As this Salon column (which links to us!) points out, gay marriage is in fact a threat, but not to families or straight marriage. It’s another nail in the coffin of outwardly acceptable gay sexual freedom. I say outwardly, because we all know boys are gonna have their fun anyhow — they’ll just feel worse about it. Society has been moving toward greater freedom in many social areas: girls are now more empowered to be sluts if they so choose, homosexuality in general is more accepted than ever, fetishes of all kinds are quite legally represented in pornography and more openly spoken of in public and media than ever before. Many people see this as a threat to Out Christian Culture, and I agree and cheer as all us deviants should. But now some gays, because they grew up with the ideal of the white wedding (despite the fact only girls wear the dresses) and religion-based monogamy, want to stomp on the brakes of all this progress. Let’s drop all this wonderful freedom and mimic the ceremonies that celebrate the ancient, oppressive domination of the Church over men, and of men over women. I say all this because of the big deal made over the difference between civil unions and “marriage.” Gay activists are rejecting civil unions that are literally identical to state-enforced marriage contracts except in name, on principle. This is because they want to mimic the religious heterosexuals that hate them. It’s also to send the message that gays can be just as boring and domestic as religious weirdos; a desperate desire to be seen as a “traditional family.” Sorry, honey, as long as your junk don’t interlock, you’re not. This has transcended mere legal equality and the convenience of standard-form contracts and crossed into ceremonial jealously. more</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364672230879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364672481710-29</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan Republican, Uses Facebook To Condemn The 'Filthy' Lifestyle Of 'Homosexuals'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364596267537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you're an equal opportunity Homosexual Hooz...the last thing you want to be caleld is a racist .... hey...are you friends with Larry Sinclair too ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672481710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364673149997-30</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the ones who were actually on that mission are telling tales.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1364673149997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364673602424-31</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between a Communist and Democrat?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364655394073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The label of communism may describe a growing segment of the Democratic Party but the Secular Progressives and transnational progressives are the bigger threat to the USA for the moment. Communism still carries with it the concept of strong ties to sovereignty like the former USSR or China. The bigger threat right now is the open society/open borders transnational progressives that want to end US sovereignty, cede power to an international governing/taxing body and the elimination of borders. These are the people who don't want border enforcement or immigration laws. When you simply throw out communism you create barriers for those that fear McCarthyism but when you expose those who trample the Bill of Rights with the intent of ending US sovereignty, more people are willing to listen to your ideas.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364673602424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364673807833-32</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan Republican, Uses Facebook To Condemn The 'Filthy' Lifestyle Of 'Homosexuals'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364596267537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I seem to have that effect on mindless fanatics.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364673807833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364675087701-33</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between a Communist and Democrat?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364655394073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As the USA continues to be threatened by the likes of North Korea now and China later Americans will relearn the fact that these other nations that transnational progressives want to cede US sovereignty to, couldn't care less if the USA was wiped off the face of the Earth. In fact most transnational progressives would welcome it. Once the Democratic Party is seen as the party that wants to do away with sovereignty and individualism, it will be the beginning of the end for the Hoozdiks of the world that propagandize the fanatical idealism of a one world society run by progressive overlords.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364675087701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364675266684-34</Id><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing HACK VALUE SHARP SHOOTERS</Title><Msg>For the 6 boeing hacks in all their various names . boeing stock for the year to date has gained as much today as boeing has gained going back three years 18 percent. airbus has gained 26 percent year to date airbus has gained 152 percent in three years . In two message board comments a suggestion was made about a stock acad while all my critics who slammed me for 15 years on aapl while it went up from 8 to 700 dollars kept making excuses. Now once more for a short term trade all my critics the boeing message board hacks have ignored acad you could have made 25 percent last week, you could have made 70 percent year to date you could have made 264 percent in one year and you could have made 418 percent in three years . Now why did i suggest acad a month ago and you could have made 50 percent because i knew as boeing hacks your unable to look past your pump for boeing a bad stock value and remeber i told you about wnr up 120 percent when i moved on and it is now in a range like boeing has been forever. So nope don't want to imopress you with what i make until i am done your losers . So rona anderson 727, or custerious or whstleffanms or all the versions of sparti and he is the worst he attempted to pick what he thought was a stock to show me up , it was a tracking stock to test the trade platform this spartacus99991 is the worst critic in the boeing hack squad</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364675266684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364675608617-35</Id><Topic><Title>Michigan Republican, Uses Facebook To Condemn The 'Filthy' Lifestyle Of 'Homosexuals'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1364596267537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz Google: Gay Marriage IS a Threat — To Gay Sexual Freedom I couldn't paste part 2 as but there is some excellent advice for you on accepting reality and what to do to take your mind off concerns about gay marriage. For some reason you don't seem interested in discussing the other side of the coin that opposes your view. Is it because you think that the only gay view that is correct is the one that you agree with?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1364675608617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364675865959-36</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between a Communist and Democrat?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364655394073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only Commies left on this planet are Republicans, Tbaggers and ignorant racist red-necks. These jackoffs also exhibit an unusually strong Fascistic bent as well. The worst commies are the ones who attack others for being communists never mind that they aren't communists. The worst offenders are ali infested, pay4ity, regains, etc etc</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364675865959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364675930232-37</Id><Topic><Title>“The Five” Absolutely Destroy Jim Carrey’s Absurd Press Release</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364663728250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:15:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd be wise of Carrey if he found a rock to hide under.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364675930232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364676012176-38</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between a Communist and Democrat?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364655394073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Korean situation escalates we are going to have to round up these commies and incarcerate them to keep them from harming themselves and others. Perhaps as things calm down we will be able to deport them to some of their commie friends like North Korea</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364676012176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364677054537-39</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"dead men tell no tales" Unless and until channeled by Orly Taitz.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1364677054537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364677499735-40</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing HACK VALUE SHARP SHOOTERS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364675266684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, please, please stop bringing up my big mistake of mentioning IGZ last week. I am truly sorry for any misleading statement I might have made about it. Almost as embarrased as you should be about saying the markets would be closing early last Thursday. Could that have been the first misinformation you've posted to this board? LOL P.S. Tops was up 34 percent on March 22nd.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1364677499735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:04:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364678385667-41</Id><Title>War Likely</Title><Msg>with North Korea under this weak U.S. president. Lame Stream Media sure are quiet today over the brew-ha-ha! If this had happened during Bush's watch, the media would have stuck a fork in the president and thrown him on the barbecue. But, all is silent.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364678385667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364679120320-42</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you suppose that is?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1364679120320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364679211214-43</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between a Communist and Democrat?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364655394073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you sound like an anti American communist insurgent?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1364679211214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364679690281-44</Id><Title>Can any of you Democrats Explain what's Wrong with Communism.....</Title><Msg>....and how it differs from what Democrats Want?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1364679690281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364679959439-45</Id><Title>The sorriest thing this country every produced were MBAs</Title><Msg>MBAs are making technical decisions and the everyone wonders why every large program is all f'd up (behind schedule, over cost, not meeting specs). Does anyone remember when aerospace companies staffing were 70% technical?</Msg><Username>armageddon_ycqm</Username><Timestamp>1364679959439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364680046841-46</Id><Topic><Title>“The Five” Absolutely Destroy Jim Carrey’s Absurd Press Release</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364663728250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:15:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah know, since hollywood has become so gay and morally depraved, I know longer need to waste my hard earned money on movie tickets. If we work together we can put hollywood out of business. There are better alternatives besides watching continuous propaganda from the left.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364680046841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364680116074-47</Id><Topic><Title>“The Five” Absolutely Destroy Jim Carrey’s Absurd Press Release</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364663728250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:15:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know, I no!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364680116074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364680265683-48</Id><Title>Hey Boeing, if problem solved why FAA limiting range?</Title><Msg>Boeing, in collaboration with the FAA, is using humans as an experiment</Msg><Username>america_wants_change</Username><Timestamp>1364680265683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364680401509-49</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Boeing, if problem solved why FAA limiting range?</Title><Username>america_wants_change</Username><Timestamp>1364680265683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:51:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The FAA has not announced any range restriction. That has not stopped shorts or some members of the press from speculating a range reduction might be part of an FAA decision.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1364680401509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:53:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364680670624-50</Id><Topic><Title>War Likely</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364678385667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364680670624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364681161776-51</Id><Topic><Title>The sorriest thing this country every produced were MBAs</Title><Username>armageddon_ycqm</Username><Timestamp>1364679959439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:45:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne claims he has an MBA from Gonzaga. 'Nuf said?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1364681161776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:06:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364681472250-52</Id><Topic><Title>War Likely</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364678385667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary and the Pres directly responsible for the murders of 4 patriotic Americans in Benghazi. But, all is silent from the Media.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364681472250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364681634672-53</Id><Topic><Title>War Likely</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364678385667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Pres and Holder directly responsible for the murder of Brian Terry because of Fast and Furious. But, all is silent from the Media.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364681634672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364681906389-54</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes and they cant seem to keep their story straight can they ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364681906389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364682543020-55</Id><Topic><Title>War Likely</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364678385667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing weak is whats inside your head.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1364682543020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364682642628-56</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The entire Prince Osama Bin Laden story is a hoax. Glad some of you finally figured it out. Yet, many of you still buy into the holocaust hoax, and think 6,000,000 people were gassed when a massive two year search, by the US Army, for just one GASSED body came up empty handed. The 9-11 hoax, took 8500 FBI agents off drug interdiction and drug smuggling activity in 2001, to look for non existent OBL cells. They never found a single one. However, the Mexican Cartels increased drug traffic into america by 400% and saw their yearly profits climb from $10 billion to $40 billion. The 9-11 hoax contributed to a massive increase in illegal drugs on America streets.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1364682642628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 18:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364684504628-57</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between a Communist and Democrat?</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1364655394073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Floyd you are one of the commies Im talking about and that is in addition to being light in the loafers</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364684504628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 19:01:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364684526104-58</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jawhol, Herr Oberst.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364684526104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 19:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364684573267-59</Id><Topic><Title>War Likely</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364678385667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You refrain from making sense, too, Loon.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364684573267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 19:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364685189479-60</Id><Title>can pay4ityourself explain whats wrong with communism</Title><Msg>he cannot- because he is a Marxist and a commie himself as well as a welfare bum and consequently he is blind to the faults of communism. His taunts to the board about communism are simply to cover up his own weakness for this evil and make every body believe is an anti commie</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364685189479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 19:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364685395490-61</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pretty hard to find any of those bodies- they all went out the smokestack at the crematoriums except for all the ash that was dumped in the nearby river</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364685395490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 19:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364690388775-62</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9-11 was aHoax and Bin Ladin was working for the CIA at various times .....hell..Obama is even SUPPLYING ALQaeda...do you need any more proof of the backscratching and dirty dealing then that....and of COURSE 9-11 was an inside job...all free thinking men who have looked at the evidence know that. BUT....You are TOTALLY wrong about the Holocoust though....6 million people were killed by totalitarianism....Its NOT the #$%$ who run the world...although some zionist New World Order bankers are involved.....in fact history shows the zionists sold out many of the #$%$ gassed in Germany...just as the bankers put Mo in power ..Cyprus were the latest victims.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364690388775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 20:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364690670109-63</Id><Topic><Title>can pay4ityourself explain whats wrong with communism</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364685189479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 19:13:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, he hasn't come out of the closet, yet.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1364690670109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 20:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364691185156-64</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what Jesus said about "peace": "Do not think that I have come to bring peace to the earth. I did not come to bring peace, but a sword." (Matthew 10:34) "Peace I leave with you; my peace I give you. I do not give to you as the world gives. Do not let your hearts be troubled and do not be afraid." (John 14:27) So, it depends upon what you mean by peace. Peace to "do your thing"? Not a chance. And, Jesus did not speak in parables about "peace". He was pretty straight about it. Consider why Jesus came and what was His message and, in particular, what did the Resurrection signify (the meaning behind Easter Sunday). Jesus said, “I am the resurrection and the life. The one who believes in me will live, even though they die; and whoever lives by believing in me will never die. Do you believe this?” (John 11:25) If you don't, you are lost. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1364691185156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 20:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364692919689-65</Id><Topic><Title>War Likely</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364678385667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama responsibled for more deaths then Bush.....the English was very straight forward Raven</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364692919689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364693178630-66</Id><Topic><Title>War Likely</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1364678385667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:19:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have posted some weeks ago that the crazy kid in NK will go to war to try to prove to himself he is a man. He thinks to himself what do I have to lose if thousands of NK are killed. No big deal. For this sick mental midget with no moral compass its all a game about playing with real guns, jet fighters, real (toy) soldiers and maybe a chance to try out his nuclear weapons. Our show of strength does not phase a sick mind.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1364693178630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364693311822-67</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, Hooz, what is your "take away" from that verse you just quoted?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1364693311822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364693529040-68</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Matthew 10 goes on to say (verses 35 and 36): "For I have come to turn a man against his father, a daughter against her mother, a daughter-in-law against her mother-in-law - a man’s enemies will be the members of his own household." Do you understand what this means?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1364693529040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364694000581-69</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi survivors not being allowed to speak ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364692829427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:20:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it curious (though obviously tragic) that three women were raped in Bengahzi and culprits are captured and confess within one week? And the Libyans are "all over it" calling for death to the perps. Yet, what happened to Ambassador Chris Stevens, someone who helped the people of Libya obtain their freedom from a brutal dictator, has faded from memory, certainly by the Libyans, and apparently here in the United States.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1364694000581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364694269811-70</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds made to order for you rabid Bible thumpers. And as for what it means, I don't have to say, or express and interest, or even a disinterest. Because I have FAITH you're going to tell us.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364694269811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364694351176-71</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi survivors not being allowed to speak ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364692829427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:20:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of those theories expressed by anyone with the fisrt frickin clue. Only an agenda.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364694351176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364694410940-72</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi survivors not being allowed to speak ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364692829427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:20:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mysteries of this President. Lots of leads end up in a dark hole.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1364694410940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364694777894-73</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, Contradictions are in the eye of the beholder. If you were a lawyer, then God would be incapable of speaking one admissible sentence. (Note the sardonic tone.) Of these verses that we have quoted, you and I, there are no contradictions, for those that understand what is being said. Here I expect Chris to pounce on me for opining "context"; however, context is always required to understand anything. Jesus brings "peace" through salvation, but He is basically telling His followers, "do not expect 'peace' at home." So, why is He saying this? Consider this message board. How often have I shared with many that Jesus is the path of eternal salvation and forgiveness for sins. And have I ever said anything disparaging to anyone? (I don't recall.) Yet. Yet, I have been barraged with nasty comments and simply down right hate. I am OK with that, BECAUSE, Jesus said that would happen. And it is as Jesus said, "they know not what they do." The message is simple, please relax for a moment, and consider what Jesus did when He died on the cross for our sins and rose again on the third day - to provide victory over the punishment of sin. But only by believing in Him.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1364694777894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364694891188-74</Id><Title>on taxes</Title><Msg>Washington, D.C .. HELLO!!! ... Are all your calculators broken?? Tax his land, Tax his wage, Tax his bed in which he lays. Tax his tractor, Tax his mule, Teach him taxes is the rule. Tax his cow, Tax his goat, Tax his pants, Tax his coat. Tax his ties, ; Tax his shirts, Tax his work, Tax his dirt. Tax his tobacco, Tax his drink, Tax him if he tries to think. Tax his booze, Tax his beers, If he cries, Tax his tears. Tax his bills, Tax his gas, Tax his notes, Tax his cash. Tax him good and let him know That after taxes, he has no dough. If he hollers, Tax him more, Tax him until he's good and sore. Tax his coffin, Tax his grave, Tax the sod in which he lays. Put these words upon his tomb, 'Taxes drove me to my doom!' And when he's gone, We won't relax, We'll still be after the inheritance TAX!! Accounts Receivable Tax Building Permit Tax CDL License Tax Cigarette Tax Corporate Income Tax Dog License Tax ; Federal Income Tax Federal Unemployment Tax (FUTA) Fishing License Tax Food License Tax Fuel Perm it Tax Gasoline Tax Hunting License Tax Inheritance Tax Inventory Tax IRS Interest Charges (tax on top of tax), IRS Penalties (tax on top of tax), Liquor Tax, Luxury Tax, Marriage License Tax, Medicare Tax, Property Tax, Real Estate Tax, Service charge taxes, Social Security Tax, Road Usage Tax (Truckers), Sales Taxes, Recreational Vehicle Tax, School Tax, State Income Tax, State Unemployment Tax (SUTA), Telephone Federal Excise Tax, Telephone Federal Universal Service Fe e Tax, Telephone Federal, State and Local Surcharge Tax, Telephone Minimum Usage Surcharge Tax, Telephone Recurring and Non-recurring Charges Tax, Telephone State and Local Tax, Telephone Usage Charge Tax, Utility Tax, Vehicle License Registration Tax, Vehicle Sales Tax, Watercraft Registration Tax, Well Permit Tax, Wo</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1364694891188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364694933237-75</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi survivors not being allowed to speak ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364692829427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:20:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey ...you're the Out of Work reporter...maybe you can enlighten us to what happenned in Banghazzi</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364694933237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364694972267-76</Id><Topic><Title>on taxes</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1364694891188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:54:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Social Security Tax, Road Usage Tax (Truckers), Sales Taxes, Recreational Vehicle Tax, School Tax, State Income Tax, State Unemployment Tax (SUTA), Telephone Federal Excise Tax, Telephone Federal Universal Service Fe e Tax, Telephone Federal, State and Local Surcharge Tax, Telephone Minimum Usage Surcharge Tax, Telephone Recurring and Non-recurring Charges Tax, Telephone State and Local Tax, Telephone Usage Charge Tax, Utility Tax, Vehicle License Registration Tax, Vehicle Sales Tax, Watercraft Registration Tax, Well Permit Tax, Workers Compensation Tax. STILL THINK THIS IS FUNNY? Not one of these taxes existed 100 years ago, and our nation was the most prosperous in the world. We had absolutely no national debt, had the largest middle class in the world, and Mom stayed home to raise the kids. What happened? Can you spell 'politicians!' And I still have to 'press 1' for English.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1364694972267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364696406264-77</Id><Title>New World Order Banksters doing a number in Cyprus</Title><Msg>...they will be doing a number on you soon......if you have money in the bank..you're an idiot</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364696406264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 22:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364698330091-78</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi survivors not being allowed to speak ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364692829427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:20:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ h i t Happens.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1364698330091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 22:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364698863288-79</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. if 6,000,000 were gassed and cremated as you suggest, then explain why Auschwitz had coal deliveries for at most 80,000 cremations. LMAO. There is no forensic evidence to support even 1 gassed human. The hoax is more transparent than the bigfoot hoax.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1364698863288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364699232945-80</Id><Topic><Title>on taxes</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1364694891188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 21:54:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. What a bit o' genius there from Uncle Donny. I propose this one instead: "Don't tax you. Don't tax me. Tax THAT fellow (behind the tree)."</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1364699232945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:07:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364699533264-81</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does this have to do with the winner of today's Dubai Cup? Animal Kingdom won convincingly but what happened to Royal Delta? Report back in time for the Kentucky Derby, please. (Always first Saturday in May).</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1364699533264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364700653452-82</Id><Topic><Title>He , Jesus used to speak of Peace</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1364522298390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 21:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wondered for a while whether it was just the animosity between us that made you sound so bitter and disrespectful....but I read your posts to Bulky Bob who rarely if ever has an unkind or disrespctful word about anyone and all you have is ridicule for a man who quotes a very good book. ...the fault Dear Brutus is in yourself.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364700653452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364700922467-83</Id><Topic><Title>Since The Bin LAdin Death Fable 25 members of Seal Team 6 have been killed</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1364672329662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the SS lives on!</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1364700922467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364701406842-84</Id><Topic><Title>can pay4ityourself explain whats wrong with communism</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1364685189479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 19:13:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The number one thing wrong with communism is it's too much like what the Democrats are trying to fundamentally transform America into.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1364701406842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:43:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>