<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361337208409-1</Id><Title>set free itch and scratchydupur and all thr spartussi</Title><Msg>Type message</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361337208409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:13:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361337226615-2</Id><Topic><Title>Drone Attacks .... Innocent until Proven Guilty</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361329125264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:58:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you plan to stop whining in this lifetime?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1361337226615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:13:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361337292278-3</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the company goes BK, what do you really have? Who cares about executive play, as it is an American Industry issue and unacceptable. In the real world, nobody will care that members are on strike that are earning $100K plus on average as you are in the top 10% of wage earners in the US. BA could follow GM into BK due to legacy costs and be governement aircraft company, which it is kind of already.</Msg><Username>douglas_delivers</Username><Timestamp>1361337292278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:14:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361339318254-4</Id><Topic><Title>set free itch and scratchydupur and all thr spartussi</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361337208409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:13:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let 3 people free</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361339318254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361339650855-5</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>douglas, You said it very well.</Msg><Username>ksmh228</Username><Timestamp>1361339650855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 00:54:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361340060425-6</Id><Title>profs pass- techs reject contract</Title><Msg>Here are the results: 18,043 votes cast. Professional Group Accept: 5,691 Reject: 4,810 Do Authorize Strike: 3,316 Do Not Authorize Strike, 2,586 Technical Group Accept: 2,801 Reject: 3,014 Do Authorize Strike: 3,796 Do Not Authorize Strike: 2,098 The Tech group will return to the bargaining table in hopes of reaching a new agreement.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361340060425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:01:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361341620150-7</Id><Title>should win again]</Title><Msg>Type message</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361341620150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:27:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361341864211-8</Id><Topic><Title>should win again]</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361341620150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by more thjanm 13 points 2nd in the natiom... it is noit beczauder i do not lijke ewe beep</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361341864211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:31:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361343823532-9</Id><Topic><Title>should win again]</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361341620150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ballme threethings: 1. not tell truth 2, say jesus is az dwa man 3. so why did,i come here for</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361343823532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:03:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361344224808-10</Id><Topic><Title>should win again]</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361341620150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bet\ on ALL excpt AZ</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361344224808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:10:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361344307195-11</Id><Title>SPEEA will discuss plans on the 22 of February</Title><Msg>Technical Unit rejected the company’s offer to them by 2,868 to Accept and 3,203 to Reject. Technical workers granted strike authorization by a vote of 3,903 Do grant strike authorization to 2,165 Do Not. On Friday (Feb. 22), SPEEA is holding a press conference at the National Press Club in Washington, D.C., to outline the impact a strike by technical workers will have on airlines, defense programs, trade and the tourist industry. SPEEA last struck Boeing in 2000 when more than 19,000 engineers and technical workers walked off the job for 40 days. That strike slowed airplane production to a crawl and prevented Boeing from delivering aircraft. While engineers and technical workers bargain at the same time, the contracts are separate and independent agreements. With engineers accepting Boeing’s offer, the 15,550 employees in SPEEA Professional Unit are in position to provide inside support to technical workers if Boeing forces a strike. With this second rejection by technical workers of Boeing takeaways, it’s time for the company to stop wasting resources and improve its offer to reflect the value and contributions technical workers bring to Boeing. That way, we can avoid a strike and focus on fixing the problems of the 787 and restoring customer confidence in Boeing.”</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361344307195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:11:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361345329071-12</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA will discuss plans on the 22 of February</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361344307195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:11:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When shareholders read that Jim McNerney was voted a highly deserved 34 percent bonus last year, they must just roll their eyes. Imagine this: you pose in a few photo sessions, oversee the 787 outsourcing development debacle that in the end will cost Boeing at least 10 fold what Boeing engineering priced it at ($5 billion in 2001-2002 vs $33 billion--and counting--)... life is good. When you’re the CEO and give himself f a 22 million dollar pension, not a 401K. The idea that a company can afford a stockholder dividend increase, pensions for the executives, great earnings huge backorder of airplanes, , and then get some kind of dementia at contract time and cannot afford pensions is ridiculous. It would be nice if the techs can get back to the IAM union, I doubt Boeing would allow that, divide and conquer.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361345329071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361345753322-13</Id><Topic><Title>profs pass- techs reject contract</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361340060425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TE BATTERIES ON THE MOON NEED REPLACING BEE-P</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361345753322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:35:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361345945244-14</Id><Topic><Title>profs pass- techs reject contract</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361340060425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:01:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A manned mission jusong the chimpzanzes, I suggest, by the end of the e-cade</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361345945244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:39:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361346725377-15</Id><Title>reuters on the SPEEA strike vote or maybe volt how is that 787 battery issue now</Title><Msg>SEATTLE (Reuters) - The largest group of engineers working at Boeing Co approved the planemaker's latest contract offer in a vote on Tuesday, likely paving the way for a full agreement as Boeing attempts to focus its resources on fixing battery problems on its 787 Dreamliner. However, members of the union representing about 23,000 engineers also authorized it to call a strike, giving the union some leverage as parties head back toward negotiations. According to the Seattle-based Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace (SPEEA), its "professional" members - who perform the main engineering duties on Boeing planes - voted narrowly in favor of accepting the contract, while a smaller group of "technical" members - who support the engineers - voted to reject it. Both groups voted in favor of authorizing the union to call a strike. The groups negotiate together, but their contracts are separate. The partial resolution of the drawn-out labor talks is a #$%$ of light for Boeing, which is struggling to get to the bottom of battery malfunctions on its 787 and needs engineers in its factories to carry out its planned production ramp-up. "There are pathways to a negotiated agreement available," said Ray Goforth, executive director of SPEEA, in a statement. "With this second rejection by technical workers of Boeing takeaways, it's time for the company to stop wasting resources and improve its offer to reflect the value and contributions technical workers bring to Boeing. That way, we can avoid a strike and focus on fixing the problems of the 787 and restoring customer confidence in Boeing."</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361346725377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 02:52:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361350412890-16</Id><Topic><Title>should win again]</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361341620150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 01:27:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ball me</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361350412890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 03:53:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361351313769-17</Id><Title>wall street view of Boeing and the 787 problem, BA stock down 3% Airbus up 11% airplane deliveries don't count , if the cost to deliver is too high</Title><Msg>Boeing is finding it increasingly difficult to convince Wall Street that its balance sheet is not going to be strained by the crisis. Until the Dreamliner is cleared to fly again, which could be several months, Boeing will be starved of delivery payments but still has to keep producing and maintaining the 787s it is making. The world's largest plane maker is being hit on a number of financial fronts, as well as suffering potential damage to its brand image. It is unable to deliver the five Dreamliners being produced per month, missing out an about $200 million in final cash payments from customers every month the 787 is grounded, while it has to pay out millions of dollars to clean, maintain and insure the parked planes. The delay may also force Boeing to postpone plans to double production by the end of this year. Meanwhile, it is spending as much as $1 billion a month to keep the production line running, according to Russell Solomon, an analyst at Moody's Investors Service, as the 787 program is still in the early, cost-heavy stage. On top of that, it will have to pay the extra costs of putting engineers to work on the battery problem and the expense of reworking the 100 or so Dreamliners that have so far rolled off the production lines once it resolves the problem. Wall Street initially pegged those costs at $350 million to $625 million, but as investigations drag on with no clear indication of a fix, analysts have held back on updating those figures. The longer the delay, the more complex and expensive the fix is likely to be. "They've got all that carbon fiber sitting on the ramp, when they'd like to have the cash," said Carter Leake, an analyst at BB&amp;T Capital Markets. "This is going to be a slow slog for a long time." CASH DRAIN So far, analysts and one source familiar with Boeing's thinking do not expect the cash squeeze will prompt Boeing to borrow more, even at current low interest rates. The company itself said only that it has not adjusted its cash management strategy. Boeing's cash flow could be cut by as much as $1.5 billion over six months if the 787s are still unable to fly, analysts said. "The longer the plane is grounded, the greater the risk of the company's 2013 cash flow meaningfully declining," said Solomon at Moody's. . Airlines are being notified of late deliveries, but none has canceled any orders. The shares have fallen 3 percent since the 787 grounding in mid-January, compared to an 11 percent gain for Airbus parent EADS Bob Crandall, former head of American Airlines and an industry figurehead, said "It's a shame, and will inconvenience airlines and passengers, and hurt Boeing financially. But progress and safety are the two games in play," he said. Favorable market conditions are helping Boeing and its rival Airbus sell and produce record numbers of jets, worth about $88 billion last year, said Richard Aboulafia, a senior aerospace analyst at the Teal Group in Fairfax, Virginia. High oil prices are prompting airlines to order new fuel-efficient planes, and low interest rates make the purchases easier to finance them and make the loans attractive to investors looking for yield. "You could not ask for those three variables to get any better for airplane output," he said. But, he added, it's unclear how long it will last. DELAY LOOMS The U.S. and Japanese investigations into burning lithium batteries are moving slowly, and there is no sign of a resolution. The longer that goes on, the longer deliveries are pushed back. More importantly, it suggests that the work Boeing will have to do to rectify battery problems on the more than 100 Dreamliners it has already produced could be significant and will hamper its efforts to ramp up production. Two weeks ago, Chief Executive Jim McNerney said Boeing was sticking with the ambitious plan - hatched long before the current battery problems came to light - to increase 787 production to seven a month by mid-year and 10 a month by the end of 2013. Boeing spokesman Charles Bickers said that is still the plan, and it is too early to know what the financial impact of the 787 grounding will be. It still flies in the board room ! The steep ramp-up is crucial to the profitability of the 787, as the lion's share of outlays happen early in a plane program. The quicker Boeing can refine the process and ramp up production, the quicker it will reach the target of 1,100 planes, the point where it calculates it will break even on the program. At planned production rates that are already a decade away. "A slowdown would be crushing," said Leake at BB&amp;T. "As long as the program accounting assumptions don't change, Boeing can keep booking the same margin in the current production block. But once production rates change or slow, their assumptions on both revenue and cost will have to change." Revenue will likely go down as Boeing will have to offer aggrieved customers more concessions on future purchases to keep them happy, while it loses hundreds of millions of dollars in "progress" payments, which airlines pay as planes near completion. At the same time, costs will stay higher for longer than Boeing has been counting on. Boeing's credit rating is not immediately under threat, but the trend is concerning analysts. "If the grounding persists for many more months, planned increases in the monthly production rate look increasingly suspect - and expensive, possibly further eroding Boeing's otherwise strong credit profile," said Solomon at Moody's.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361351313769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 04:08:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361351910823-18</Id><Title>she said she said</Title><Msg>Feel to b dead honest to the pointof recklosness mxxing with jews</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361351910823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 04:18:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361352381260-19</Id><Topic><Title>she said she said</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361351910823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 04:18:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thiis space is gettng hot apparently they have rules about laser light pens and throwing snowballs</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361352381260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 04:26:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361357398320-20</Id><Topic><Title>she said she said</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361351910823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 04:18:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>107 zrer'o peresonally</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1361357398320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 05:49:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361357448918-21</Id><Topic><Title>What Would Happen if Liberals Suddenly Decided to.......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361220023888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 15:40:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Not likely. Racism, bigotry, intolerance and hate are your primary values!" And number 1 in that list is UNFETTERED GREED.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1361357448918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 05:50:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361358358897-22</Id><Topic><Title>wall street view of Boeing and the 787 problem, BA stock down 3% Airbus up 11% airplane deliveries don't count , if the cost to deliver is too high</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361351313769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 04:08:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're awesome, dude. All this good information, for free?!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1361358358897</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 06:05:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361358566965-23</Id><Topic><Title>Secret Service thoughts about Obama and Michelle</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361252156531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 00:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anal, you sound like an uneducated #$%$.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1361358566965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 06:09:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361360350664-24</Id><Topic><Title>More jobs leaving for SC</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361295781366</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 12:43:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry,retired at 55.How is the bath house job?</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361360350664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 06:39:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361362089480-25</Id><Title>Daniel Ellsberg thinks Obama should be Impeached</Title><Msg>Daniel Ellsberg says Obama should be impeached over NDAA J. D. Heyes Natural News February 18, 2013 These days, political historians are about the only ones who know who Daniel Ellsberg is. That’s because his heyday, so to speak, took place more than 40 years ago. For those who are not familiar with Ellsberg, he became famous during the nation’s most tumultuous time in recent memory: The waning days of the Vietnam war, in the early 1970s, when the nation was tearing itself apart socially, culturally and politically. Ellsberg, you see, was once the country’s most famous whistleblower. The information he leaked did more to sour a generation on the federal government than even Bob Woodward and Carl Bernstein, the two Washington Post reporters who brought down President Richard Nixon by exposing the Watergate scandal beginning in 1972. What did Ellsberg do? He leaked the Pentagon Papers, a collection of documents that revealed secret information regarding U.S. involvement in Vietnam decades before American troops were sent to die there. Officially known as “United States-Vietnam Relations: 1945-1967: A Study Prepared by the Department of Defense,” the papers served as the first in a series of revelations that disillusioned tens of millions of voters for decades. At the time, Vietnam was being blamed – or scapegoated – for most of what many Americans thought ailed the country, so to find out their government had been involved in the Southeast Asian nation for decades before the war began was devastating. Now, Ellsberg is once again seeking to hold the government to account for what he believes (and we believe) is a grave miscarriage of justice. In an interview with Democracy Now, an extreme left-wing advocacy group, he says he has become a plaintiff in a federal lawsuit aimed at having a provision of the 2012 National Defense Authorization Act (NDAA) allowing permanent detention of American citizens without ever being charged with a crime struck down. History of tyrannical legislation As Natural News founder and Editor-in-chief Mike Adams reported more than a year ago, that provision of the NDAA allows the military to indefinitely detain anyone even remotely suspected of being a terrorist “with no jury, no trial, no legal representation and not even any requirement that the government produce evidence against the accused.” A d v e r t i s e m e n t A federal judge, Katherine Forrest of the Southern District of New York, has already struck down the indefinite detention provision, ruling that it most likely violates the First and Fifth Amendments. But President Obama ordered his Justice Department to quickly appeal that ruling, saying the 2012 NDAA merely reinstates an existing statute giving the U.S. military the power of infinite detention. Ellsberg begs to differ. In the interview, he says that, as an American citizen, he’s “whipsawed” by what he is doing but understands it must be done. “On the one hand, I’m here to attend the court hearing at the circuit court…at the federal court building where I expect to see the Obama administration cover itself with shame in arguing that an American citizen can be detained indefinitely in military custody without charges, indefinitely, violating really, the core principles of law that go back to the [13th century English] Magna Carta,” he said. “On the other hand, I was up late last night reading the 112-page document of Katherine B. Forrest, and I have to say at the end of that…the judgment granting an injunction saying that these provisions of the law that will be argued and defended by – shamefully, by the Obama administration and by three U.S. senators, who will be claiming that the detention is constitutional and legal – her argument was that it was facially unconstitutional.” An impeachable offense Ellsberg said after he read her detailed ruling and the government’s tortured argument attempting to justify said indefinite detention as constitutional, “I felt pride as an American.” “I thought, this is the American citizen that I fought for as a Marine. This is a constitutional order, a rule of law, a judge, appointed by Obama, who’s willing to say that her boss was mistaken in claiming that this rule is compatible with our rule of law,” he told his interviewers. The veteran whistleblower said Obama, like Prof. John Yoo of Berkeley, who authored memos during the Bush administration authorizing torture of some terrorist suspects, “has to be seen as either a rotten constitutional lawyer or a man who, like Yoo, believes that the Constitution simply does not bound an American prisoner in any way in an indefinite law of torture.” “And either way, I believe we have here impeachable offenses by all of the people arguing this case, including the three senators – McCain, others – who will be arguing today on this,” Ellsberg said. “We should be looking at [John] Brennan [Obama's nominee to head the CIA] and the other people connected with the torture program not in terms of confirmation hearings, but in terms of impeachment hearings and convictions.” Ellsberg said the NDAA provision is merely an extension of unconstitutional government behavior stemming from the 9/11 attacks and the U.S. global war on terror. As a law, the provision is “unprecedented, but as a practice – what we’ve seen for the last 10 years is a systematic assault on the Constitution of the United States in every aspect – in the aspects of the illegal surveillance, the warrantless surveillance, which was conducted against me 40 years ago by President Nixon and then led to his impeachment proceedings, but is now regarded as legal. That’s the way the law has changed.”</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361362089480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 07:08:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361362590106-26</Id><Title>Obama thinks Daniel Ellsberg should be Impeached</Title><Msg>Impeached?? Not only Elsberg but even Obama has to use sensationalism to get people to read his blather sometimes</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1361362590106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 07:16:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361362976311-27</Id><Title>Battery problem fixed!</Title><Msg>Air India to start flying 787s april 1.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361362976311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 07:22:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361365082367-28</Id><Title>Where are all the doom and gloomers today ??? Goof balls...</Title><Msg>strike is off and the 787 is fixed...</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1361365082367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 07:58:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361365644113-29</Id><Title>We have a 787 fix and a strike averted ....... $80.00 per share next stop !!</Title><Msg>up we go !!!</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1361365644113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:07:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361365759309-30</Id><Topic><Title>Drone Attacks .... Innocent until Proven Guilty</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1361329125264</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 21:58:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If habeus corpus isn't something that goes into a Twinkie, then the Kent Raven doesn't care if it's gone........now take away his rights to unlimited Twinkies, then you'll have one angry bird.............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361365759309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:09:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361365792562-31</Id><Topic><Title>Secret Service thoughts about Obama and Michelle</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361252156531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 00:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you talking with yourself again?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361365792562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:09:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361365837885-32</Id><Title>Strike is on.....</Title><Msg>Engineers at Boeing ratified a new contract but technical workers rejected theirs and authorized a strike that could shut assembly lines. NEW YORK (CNNMoney) The last thing Boeing needs right now is a strike but that may just happen after 11,000 technical workers voted to reject a new contract in a dispute that could shut its assembly lines. As it races to bring the Dreamliner plane back into service, Boeing faces the prospect of wider disruption after 15,500 engineers said they too could strike even as they accepted a similar contract offer.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361365837885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:10:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361366111474-33</Id><Title>New wiring problems found!</Title><Msg>Japan Widening Boeing 787 Search to Include Wiring By Dow Jones Business News, February 20, 2013, 07:45:00 AM EDT Vote up TOKYO--The head of a Japanese air safety organization looking into battery problems on a Boeing 787 said Wednesday that the investigators will expand the scope of their search to include the jet's circuit wiring after finding part of its installation to be "unusual." The investigating team discovered that the circuit wiring of the burned battery and another one were connected, even though this is unusual in airplanes, Norihiro Goto, chairman of the Japan Transport Safety Board said at a press conference. He added that the JTSB has already notified Boeing and All Nippon Airways Co. (9202.TO) of the finding and is seeking feedback from the aircraft maker.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361366111474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:15:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361366351500-34</Id><Title>75.85 up 1.20</Title><Msg>In pre markets....Shorts get hit again,,,too bad.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361366351500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:19:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361367524262-35</Id><Topic><Title>Secret Service thoughts about Obama and Michelle</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361252156531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 00:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mir, doesn't believe that the rich should pay no taxes. That's just another lie spread by the Kent Raven and other Marxist.. Mir is in favor of the "FAIR TAX" .....well because it's fair and gives people more freedom.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361367524262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:38:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361367686999-36</Id><Title>787 stuffed with stuffed with faulty and irrregularly installed circuity</Title><Msg>"We have been investigating what happened, but as we haven't got to a point where we can say why it happened yet, we can't say we've made progress," Mr. Goto said. He also stressed that the new finding has little to do with the overheating, since the battery system has a diode module to block any reverse current. As the JTSB has found nothing wrong with the module, it is believed to have functioned normally, he said. and this could cost billions in lost time and man power to correct. Clock is ticking and all we hear and read is the 787 won't get another test flight until April. And remember faulty circuity could be as big as a problem and battery. Still, the chairman said he is concerned there may be other irregularly installed circuitry.</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1361367686999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:41:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361367725692-37</Id><Title>Both groups voted in favor of the union authorizing a strike!</Title><Msg>According to the Seattle-based Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace (SPEEA), its "professional" members - who perform the main engineering duties on Boeing planes - voted narrowly in favor of accepting the contract, while a smaller group of "technical" members - who support the engineers - voted to reject it. Both groups voted in favor of authorizing the union to call a strike. The groups negotiate together, but their contracts are separate.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361367725692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:42:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361367876423-38</Id><Topic><Title>787 stuffed with stuffed with faulty and irrregularly installed circuity</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1361367686999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:41:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All hype this morning. Problems are FAR from being resolved.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361367876423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:44:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361368114032-39</Id><Topic><Title>Secret Service thoughts about Obama and Michelle</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361252156531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 00:35:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone reading clorox's post now gets it as to how totally ignornant liberals are..."do you feel that the rich should pay no taxes?" blah, blah, blah. About as dumb a statement as any braindead ever born could make. The IRS has the stats, and they've been published many times as to the percentage of taxes the upper 1% pay, and then the upper 10% pay. Anyone like clorox that can decipher simple percentage stats needs to be institutionalized. And 70% of all economic growth is created by small business folks. The percentage earner folks produce/create virtually all the jobs! The reason jobs aren't being created now is Obama is punishing those folks with more regulations, and higher taxes. Does clorox think they are as dumb as he is, and will just give more of their money to Obama by investing in more jobs? WalMart memos were just intercepted by the news media, and they indicated since this FEB. consumer spending is in big time trouble due to Obama's economic policies, and increased govt taxes. When you talk to the clorox's so a 3rd grader can understand it, and they don't get it what's the next step?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361368114032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:48:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361368234023-40</Id><Title>BA no where close to fixing battery problems - but they want u to think they are</Title><Msg>In a February 19 email, Sadoway, John F. Elliott Professor of Materials Chemistry in MIT’s Department of Materials Science and Engineering, wrote, “This can’t be all there is to it. What is described is how to contain a fire, not how to prevent a fire. Weird. This story must be incomplete. Otherwise, Boeing is evading the real issue which is how to prevent a fire from starting in the first place.” So Boeing would rather let electrical or battery fires start on operating planes and then tell the flying public they can contain such fires at the point of emission so you can continue to enjoy your flight and peanuts. HA</Msg><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1361368234023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:50:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361368249660-41</Id><Topic><Title>75.85 up 1.20</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361366351500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:19:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not really shorts get a chance to reload again</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1361368249660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:50:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361368356421-42</Id><Topic><Title>Both groups voted in favor of the union authorizing a strike!</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361367725692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:42:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This spells the end of the union in WA ST. Boeing will now move more rapidly to move more jobs out of the state to right to work states. Doesn't take a genius to understand why.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361368356421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:52:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361368449853-43</Id><Topic><Title>75.85 up 1.20</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361366351500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:19:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Point one: The strike has been approved by both parties..engineers and workers. Point two: Electrical wiring problems now surfaced</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361368449853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:54:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361368674235-44</Id><Title>Sequester Is Product Of Obama's 'Failed Leadership'</Title><Msg>"Most Americans are just hearing about this Washington creation for the first time: the sequester," Boehner writes. "What they might not realize from Mr. Obama's statements is that it is a product of the president's own failed leadership." http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/02/20/john-boehner-sequester_n_2721608.html</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1361368674235</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:57:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361368802262-45</Id><Title>Nothing resolved....strike looms</Title><Msg>Boeing Engineers Approve Deal as Technical Workers Grant Strike The divided results show labor peace remains elusive even as Chicago-based Boeing counts on its workforce to help get the Dreamliner flying again. Boeing is working to find the source of two battery malfunctions and make repairs to put the fleet of 49 787s back in the air and resume deliveries of new planes. “In an engineering company, what’s vital is good relations with the engineers,” Harley Shaiken, a labor professor at the University of California at Berkeley, said in an interview before the voting. “You want people inspired by what they’re doing, not at odds with the company management.” Boeing’s contract offer was ratified by engineers with 54 percent of the vote, the union said, while the accord was turned down by 53 percent of the technical workers. Those employees authorized a strike with 64 percent of the vote.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361368802262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:00:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361368854497-46</Id><Title>When will the Economic Collapse Come?</Title><Msg>That's a good question, I'm glad I asked it. The collapse has already arrived for 12 million Americans. After 6 years of Democrat control of the Senate and 4 years of Obama, there are fewer Americans with jobs than when Obama first took office. The collapse can take many forms and it could be drug out for several years or could come in a few months.....but it will happen. Thanks to Obama, Democrats and RINOs we has passed the point of no return. It's like having so many bills and so much debt, you and everyone else in you household could work 3 jobs 24/7/365 and still not put a dent in it. Most rich guys like myself will not only survive but we will thrive and accumulate great wealth by buying up the pieces of assets from folks forced to liquidate for pennies on the dollar. There is time to position yourself to survive and thrive but you need to get to work on it. Find out what's going on in Greece today. Technically we are worse off than Greece.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361368854497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:00:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361368897505-47</Id><Title>unidentified person says battery fix in the works</Title><Msg>Unidentified?????? This is all rumor mill stuff to boost the stock. ‘Deeply Disappointed’ The shares rose 1.4 percent to $75.70 at 8:36 a.m. in New York before regular trading. Reuters, citing a person it didn’t identify, reported that Boeing had found a way to fix faults in the 787’s lithium-ion batteries by increasing the space between the cells. Engineers approved a four-year contract while technical workers, who act as their liaison with machinists, rejected the deal and authorized a strike any time, according to the Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace. The union said it will first resume negotiations with the planemaker.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361368897505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:01:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361369047863-48</Id><Topic><Title>BA no where close to fixing battery problems - but they want u to think they are</Title><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1361368234023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:50:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But what about the unidentied person stating the fix is in the works?? ‘Deeply Disappointed’ The shares rose 1.4 percent to $75.70 at 8:36 a.m. in New York before regular trading. Reuters, citing a person it didn’t identify, reported that Boeing had found a way to fix faults in the 787’s lithium-ion batteries by increasing the space between the cells.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361369047863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:04:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361369516900-49</Id><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Msg>A Milwaukee County Sheriff has warned that a second American Revolution may be sparked if unconstitutional gun laws are enforced by police and sheriff’s department officials. Sheriff David Clarke recently urged the citizens he serves to consider learning firearm safety because of “a duty to protect yourself and your family.” In a message posted on the Sheriff’s website, Clarke wrote “I need you in the game, but are you ready? With officers laid-off and furloughed, simply calling 9-1-1 and waiting is no longer your best option. You can beg for mercy from a violent criminal, hide under the bed, or you can fight back; but are you prepared?” “Consider taking a certified safety course in handling a firearm so you can defend yourself until we get there. You have a duty to protect yourself and your family. We’re partners now. Can I count on you?” the message urged. Speaking on the Morning Show yesterday, the Sheriff hit home his opinions on the gun control proposals that are being pushed via presidential executive orders. “First of all, to me that would be an act of tyranny. So the people in Milwaukee County do not have to worry about me enforcing some sort of order that goes out and collects everybody’s handgun, or rifles, or any kind of firearm and makes them turn them in.” Clarke said. “The reason is I don’t want to get shot, because I believe that if somebody tried to enforce something of that magnitude, you would see the second coming of an American Revolution, the likes of which would make the first revolution pale by comparison.” the Sheriff urged.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361369650980-50</Id><Title>Bloomberg speaks with forked tongue!</Title><Msg>BA: Boeing Engineers Approve Deal as Strike by Others Planned - at Bloomberg BA: Boeing Avoids Strikes in Split Contract Votes - at Bloomberg</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361369650980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361370562948-51</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing resolved....strike looms</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361368802262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:00:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical misguided comments foxgang. Someday you will wake up and sense reality. Well probably not!</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1361370562948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:29:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361370619703-52</Id><Title>Colorado Democrat: Use a Ballpoint Pen to Fight a Gunman</Title><Msg>Colorado Democrat Jessie Uliberri argued people should defend themselves against a madman shooter with.... ballpoint pens. Two things wrong with this. The first being that Uliberri argues people should waiting until a crazy person reloads before taking action, or in other words, wait until they are done shooting people. The use of a firearm for defense in this case wouldn't require a waiting period but rather would stop a madman from continuing his rampage. The second, ballpoint pens? Really? I was always told not to take a ballpoint pen to a gunfight. KP</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361370619703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:30:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361370624807-53</Id><Title>Boing Strike Threat - ITS ON</Title><Msg>The last thing Boeing needs right now is a strike but that may just happen after 11,000 technical workers voted to reject a new contract in a dispute that could shut its assembly lines. As it races to bring the Dreamliner plane back into service, Boeing faces the prospect of wider disruption after 15,500 engineers said they too could strike even as they accepted a similar contract offer.</Msg><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1361370624807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:30:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361371040829-54</Id><Title>Go Boeing$$</Title><Msg>When the Engineers approved the latest contract those tech are going to falling in line or their Out!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1361371040829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:37:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371054769-55</Id><Topic><Title>REC Jesse Jackson's son Congressman Jackson in Federal Court today $750,000 stolen in campaign funds. The Fed Judge probably getn calls from the President</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1361370693745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:31:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the Jackson's were more adept at stealing than that...only $750 K ? That is chump change for his father. His dad was a professional extorsionist extorting millions of dollars from Corporations accusing them of racism, and filing suits, then settling out of court. Young Jackson is ruiining the family name with that amateur like thievery.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361371054769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:37:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371137988-56</Id><Topic><Title>Colorado Democrat: Use a Ballpoint Pen to Fight a Gunman</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361370619703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:30:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it the "assault" ball point pen with flash suppressor in a semi auto or full auto? Will they issue a permit for one of those scary pens?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361371137988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:38:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371159034-57</Id><Topic><Title>Boing Strike Threat - ITS ON</Title><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1361370624807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:30:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is in that pipe you are smoking just keep?</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1361371159034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:39:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361371180558-58</Id><Title>Report: Yeah, Democrat run Detroit Might Be Forced To Declare Bankruptcy</Title><Msg>What happens when a city government tries to tax, spend, and borrow its way to prosperity? Hint: it goes broke: A state-appointed review team has determined Detroit is in a financial emergency, paving the way for Republican Gov. Rick Snyder to appoint an emergency manager who would need to come up with a new plan to get the city out of its fiscal crisis. The team released its findings Tuesday, saying in a report to Snyder that "no satisfactory plan exists to resolve a serious financial problem." The review team pointed to the city's ongoing cash crisis, which have threatened to leave the city without money to pay its workers or other bills. It noted that the city's deficit could have reached more than $900 million in fiscal year 2012 if the city had not borrowed enormous amounts of money; that Detroit has long-term liabilities, including underfunded pensions, of more than $14 billion; and that the city's bureaucratic structure makes it difficult to solve the financial problems. "The cash condition has been a strain on the city," said state Treasurer Andy Dillon, a member of the review team. "The city has been running deficits since 2005 ... (and) masking over those with long-term borrowing." Under Michigan law, Snyder has 30 days to decide for himself whether there's a financial emergency. Mayor Dave Bing would have 10 days to request a hearing. Snyder could then revoke his decision or appoint an emergency manager. Sure, Governor Snyder has exactly one month to appoint an emergency manager to handle the city’s finances. But declaring bankruptcy might be Detroit’s only option at this point: However, others said that even with an emergency manager, municipal bankruptcy may be the city's only way out of the financial mess. "Is it imminent? Well not tomorrow," said Doug Bernstein, managing partner of the Banking, Bankruptcy and Creditors' Rights Practice Group for Michigan-based Plunkett Cooney law firm "You need to give a financial manager the opportunity to formulate a plan and let the plan have a chance to succeed or fail. It may not avoid a bankruptcy, but you don't need to do a bankruptcy today." Snyder spokeswoman Sara Wurfel said he will review the team's report carefully. "He won't make a determination immediately, but sooner rather than later," she said. "The governor believes that a strong and successful Detroit is key to Michigan's continued comeback." Detroit’s systemic budgetary and spending problems should be a wake up call to members of both political parties. But at least Republicans seem to understand that a government that spends more money than it takes in every single year is destined to go bankrupt. Remember: Congressional Republicans actually pass budgets and want to cut federal spending; the same can’t be said about Congressional Democrats. Syndicated columnist Mark Steyn calls America the Brokest Nation in History and perhaps he’s correct. But I can assure you that if Detroit’s political leaders continue down the reckless fiscal path they’re on, the once thriving metropolis will one day be known for something else: being the Brokest City in America. DD</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361371180558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371244286-59</Id><Topic><Title>Colorado Democrat: Use a Ballpoint Pen to Fight a Gunman</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361370619703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:30:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About as sensible as our Homeland Security Chief that says you should hide under a desk, then open a drawer, and take out a pair of scissors, and attack the mentally deranged shooter.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361371244286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:40:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361371573842-60</Id><Topic><Title>Boing Strike Threat - ITS ON</Title><Username>justkeepushin</Username><Timestamp>1361370624807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:30:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you feel so confident then short the stock......... lol</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1361371573842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:46:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361372411980-61</Id><Topic><Title>Colorado Democrat: Use a Ballpoint Pen to Fight a Gunman</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361370619703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:30:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals aren't very smart.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361372411980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361372898945-62</Id><Title>This time, it blasts through 80 bucks.</Title><Msg>never looks back.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361372898945</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:08:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361372955122-63</Id><Title>Anti-austerity strike to bring Greece to a standstill</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - Greek workers walk off the job on Wednesday in a nationwide anti-austerity strike that will disrupt transport, shut public schools and tax offices and leave hospitals working with emergency staff. Greece's two biggest labor unions plan to bring much of the near-bankrupt country to a standstill during a 24-hour strike over the cuts, which they say only deepen the plight of a people struggling to get through the country's worst peacetime downturn. Representing about 2.5 million workers, the unions have gone on strike repeatedly since Europe's debt crisis erupted in late 2009, testing the government's will to implement necessary reforms in the face of growing public anger. "The (strike) is our answer to the dead-end policies that have squeezed the life out of workers, impoverished society and plunged the economy into recession and crisis," said the private sector union GSEE, which is organizing the walkout with its public sector sister union ADEDY. "Our struggle will continue for as long as these policies are implemented," it said. Prime Minister Antonis Samaras's eight-month-old coalition government has been eager to show it will implement reforms it promised the European Union and International Monetary Fund, which have bailed Athens out twice with over 200 billion euros. It has taken a tough line on striking workers, invoking emergency law twice this year to order seamen and subway workers back to the job after week-long walkouts that paralyzed public transport in Athens and led to food shortages on islands. But in a sign it is buckling under pressure, it announced on Monday it would not fire almost 1,900 civil servants earmarked for possible dismissal, despite promising foreign lenders it would seek to cut the public payroll. STRIKES PICKING UP Strikes have picked up in recent weeks, underscoring Greeks' anger at record high unemployment and poverty levels. A one-day visit by French President Francois Hollande in Athens on Tuesday went largely uncovered as Greek journalists were on strike. In northern and central Greece, farmers have been protesting at high production costs and fuel prices for nearly a month, occasionally blocking the country's main north-south highway. Most business and public sector activity is expected to come to a halt during Wednesday's strike, with school teachers, train and bus employees and bankers among various groups joining the walkout. Hospitals will have only emergency staff and ships will stay in port as seaworkers plan to defy government orders to return to work. Several marches are expected to culminate in demonstrations outside parliament on central Syntagma square, where they have often ended in violent clashes between police and protesters in the past. Analysts said Greece securing bailout funds in December, which averted bankruptcy and ended months of uncertainty over the country's future in the euro, created expectations among Greeks that things would improve on a personal level as well. "If these expectations are not satisfied by the summer, then whatever is left of the working class will respond with more protest," said Costas Panagopoulos, head of Alco pollsters.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361372955122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:09:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361373249466-64</Id><Topic><Title>BA no where close to fixing battery problems - but they want u to think they are</Title><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1361368234023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:50:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 787 will fly until 2014 at best. Nobody will want to fly on it.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361373249466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:14:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361373297427-65</Id><Title>ANA says 787 was miss-wired</Title><Msg>http://news.yahoo.com/japan-probe-finds-miswiring-boeing-105141412.html ....Yep! I thought so.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1361373297427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:14:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361373401685-66</Id><Title>The 787 is an engineering falure. Nobody will fly it.</Title><Msg>If it does fly it will be only months before one ends up at the bottom of the Pacific.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361373401685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:16:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361373429317-67</Id><Topic><Title>Battery problem fixed!</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361362976311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 07:22:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soon to be a non issue.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361373429317</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:17:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361373479303-68</Id><Topic><Title>This time, it blasts through 80 bucks.</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361372898945</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:08:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA has just taken off..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361373479303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:17:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361373555135-69</Id><Title>Monoply business...</Title><Msg>is worth PE of 20...</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361373555135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:19:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361373563098-70</Id><Topic><Title>Anti-austerity strike to bring Greece to a standstill</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361372955122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:09:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Greek union workers are as slow above the shoulders as the liberal posters on this thread. They think along the lines of Obama. Austerity?! They want MORE govt spending for their benefits, and pay raises, and early retirement, not AUSTERITY!! And it ain't in the cards. We are broke just like they are, and we can't print up anymore money just like they can't. They Chinese won't let us continue to run the printing presses. And with Obama shrinking the private sector that provides the funding it is getting worse not better, just like in Greece.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361373563098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:19:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361373829203-71</Id><Topic><Title>REC Jesse Jackson's son Congressman Jackson in Federal Court today $750,000 stolen in campaign funds. The Fed Judge probably getn calls from the President</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1361370693745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:31:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's just typical Democrat ideology . Democrat think "government" should have the right to take what someone has earned and spend it on or give it to someone who didn't earn it. In this case the Democrat cut out the middle man and spent it on himself.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361373829203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:23:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361374501903-72</Id><Title>Caterpillar January Orders went Negative Worldwide !!!!!!!!!!! CAT RED !</Title><Msg>thoughts ? comments ?</Msg><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1361374501903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:35:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361374794402-73</Id><Title>Why Does the Mediocre Class Get so Angry?</Title><Msg>....when they find out that class warfare is just a smokescreen for fleecing the mediocre class. Who suffers most when they tax the rich and the rich say to heck with it and close down marginal businesses? Who will suffer the most when they will have to pay $20,000 a year of for minimum coverage under Obamacare? Who will suffer the most when no one will hire a new college graduate because the cost of mandated benefits is too high? There's no reason to get angry......you were warned but because you let them convince you that mediocrity was a lofty goal to achieve and that somehow mediocrity was was a sacred class you became very malleable in their hands. Why is it that devious politicians that tell you the mediocre class is special and those evil rich guys are the enemy are all rich themselves?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361374794402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:39:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361375081199-74</Id><Topic><Title>REC Jesse Jackson's son Congressman Jackson in Federal Court today $750,000 stolen in campaign funds. The Fed Judge probably getn calls from the President</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1361370693745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:31:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhymin" Jessee has his baby mamma and his offspring has his mistress and perhaps a baby mamma in the woodpile somewhere. These are typical "community leaders" in the Chicago tradition. The 750K is only what the feds are alleging. There's probably much more involved.. Moochie Obama is / was tight with Rhymin'Jesse's daughter and spent alot of time at the Jackson home in her younger days. President Obumble is a typical Chicago community organizer, just look how organized Chicago is !!!! Shootings everywhere even though the city is a gun free zone ... What a farkin joke.</Msg><Username>king_kwanza</Username><Timestamp>1361375081199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:44:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361375102980-75</Id><Topic><Title>BA price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>kondocarroll</Username><Timestamp>1361373775442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:22:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes going high</Msg><Username>emerywarren149</Username><Timestamp>1361375102980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:45:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361375736481-76</Id><Title>ILNS could have cure for ALZHEIMERS DISEASE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>THAT WOULD BE A MONSTER!!!!!</Msg><Username>fivefoldto</Username><Timestamp>1361375736481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:55:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361375750435-77</Id><Title>Another Anonymous source</Title><Msg>Where do they get these guys? Rumors and heresay treated as news today. Watch out! Will Boeing Dreamliners Take Off In April? By Mark Knapp February 20, 2013Page 1 of 2It hasn’t been the best of news for Boeing (NYSE:BA) lately, with delivery delays and groundings of its 787 Dreamliners, but that may soon change. An anonymous source has it that the company may get the jets fixed and in the air as soon as April.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361375750435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:55:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361375760048-78</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure a gun control law would work out really well! Look at the other things that the government tries to control. Alcohol now that didn't work out to well, but the gangsters seemed to like it. Oh yes, drugs now that's working out well isn't it. With a successful record like this I think it's just like Obama to tr y and control guns. LMAO, what a fool he is!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361375760048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:56:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361376097250-79</Id><Title>Poland's LOT suspends taking delivery of new Dreamliners</Title><Msg>Feb 20 (Reuters) - Polish flag carrier LOT has put on hold taking delivery of the three 787 Dreamliner jets it is slated to receive from Boeing, Polish Treasury Minister Mikolaj Budzanowski said on Wednesday. State-controlled LOT has taken delivery of two Dreamliners and was to receive three others by the end of next month. But last month the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration grounded all 50 Boeing Dreamliners in commercial service after a series of battery-related incidents. The Polish airline has so far lost 7.7 million zlotys ($2.5 million) in relation to the Dreamliner problems, Budzanowski said in a statement to parliament</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376097250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:01:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361376563426-80</Id><Title>a month to discover the electric lady is miswired ?hummmm</Title><Msg>It's taken them more than a month to discover this? The Electric Lady not only has friends in high places but in the less lofty heights of spin doctoring</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376563426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:09:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361376765171-81</Id><Topic><Title>Monoply business...</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361373555135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:19:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something AAPL does not have. LMAO..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1361376765171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:12:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361377088052-82</Id><Title>Subject</Title><Msg>Breaking News! Boeing Shorts, are getting short circuited!</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1361377088052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:18:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361377686679-83</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the while the right wing gun nuts scream about wanting to ban abortion, gay marriage interracial marriage,taxes, pot. baggy pants and anything else they can`t accept lol</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1361377686679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:28:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361377954411-84</Id><Topic><Title>Another Anonymous source</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361375750435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:55:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In support of your position, look no further than the Republacan politicians! "Is the Obama Administration preparing to give prisoners at Guantanamo Bay GI Bill benefits as part of a plan to “completely crush their souls with bureaucracy?” Wired Magazine reports that Republican Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell’s office asked the Pentagon that very question after a constituent sounded the alarm. The problem? That far-fetched notion came from a story on the satirical site “The Duffel Blog,” a military-focused answer to The Onion. (Wired posted the constituent’s letter and the query from McConnell’s office on its top-notch “Danger Room” blog on national security). “I am writing on behalf of a constituent who has contacted me regarding Guantanamo Bay prisoners receiving Post 9/11 GI Bill benefits,” McConnell wrote. “I would appreciate your review and response to my constituent’s concerns.” What triggered the unnamed Kentuckian’s worries? This post. “By allowing the detainees to use the Department of Veterans Affairs, we hope to completely crush their souls with bureaucracy,” a (fake) Pentagon spokesman says in the piece. Veterans Affairs Secretary Eric Shinseki is then quoted as saying: “Because most ‘guests’ at Guantanamo Bay have been there nearly a decade and there is no end in site for their ‘visit,’ the Department of Veterans Affairs is ready to have their claims processed in 12-15 years as per standard operating procedure.” This is, as Danger Room reporter Spencer Ackerman points out, an attempt “to send up the inadequate, mollasses-slow [sic] benefits the government provides to the nation’s veterans.” No word on whether any lawmakers have expressed outrage about this Duffel Blog post: “Study: Infantry Battalions Commanded By Females More Likely To Stop For Directions, Arrive Late.” But it only went up Wednesday morning. McConnell’s office is hardly the first to have a little trouble distinguishing humor sites from actual news sources (though, in their defense…nahh, better not). It wasn’t that long ago that a Chinese paper congratulated Kim Jong Un on being named "Sexiest Man Alive" by The Onion.</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1361377954411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:32:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361378125964-85</Id><Title>The Mediocre Class Doesn't need to Get so Angry at Its Self for being Duped.</Title><Msg>The mediocre class of a whole country was duped in 1917. The Mediocre class in Cuba was duped. You can name a dozen other countries. What you should get angry about is being bamboozled because you didn't learn from history or worse yet, because you weren't taught REAL history in those socialized government schools.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361378125964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:35:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361378566932-86</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you Communists hate Americans so much?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1361378566932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:42:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361378811445-87</Id><Topic><Title>The Mediocre Class Doesn't need to Get so Angry at Its Self for being Duped.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361378125964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:35:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs work hard at rewriting history. They don' like the facts as told by hisorians. They don't fit very well into their liberal agenda theme, so they rewrite it. The kinda stuff Walt Disney would be proud sell. Look how many of these libtads still follow the lib historical account of how GW Bush ruined the economy for Obama, and Obama is still working on straightening it out.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361378811445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:46:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361378954504-88</Id><Topic><Title>Really need to price in looming defense cuts</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361377448012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:24:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think all this has to do with Obama care that is kicking in. Obama care is going to cut jobs and have a huge slow down on growth. The cuts that are coming up will not hurt the economy, what is coming that will kill jobs and growth is going to be Obama care.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1361378954504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:49:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361379020298-89</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WA St. passed a gun law that you can own some of the new guns, BUT, the fine print says the govt. can come knockin on your door, and go through your personal belongings. Then libs said "Really? We didn't know that. We wouldn't have voted for it knowing that was in the fine print." Just like ObamaCare, and we are still reading the fine print, and businesses are laying off workers, and not hiring because of it.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361379020298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:50:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361379261227-90</Id><Topic><Title>Really need to price in looming defense cuts</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1361377448012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:24:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are a mountain of factors regarding Obama policy that is bringing down the economy. The direction is self evident, forget about a good news line once in awhile. ObamaCare, layers of expensive, burdensome regulations, new taxes like the payroll tax that is suddenly hitting those that get a paycheck. Rising gas prices because of Obama's willingness to let the far left environmentalists get a death grip on the economy, and many other factors.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361379261227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:54:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361380329080-91</Id><Topic><Title>BA price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>kondocarroll</Username><Timestamp>1361373775442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:22:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks legit</Msg><Username>guzmanandrew658</Username><Timestamp>1361380329080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:12:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361380428806-92</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don`t know why they do? Maybe they don`t and you have just been programmed to react that they do? idk lets ban some more stuff like porn and video games heck we can blame everything in the world on gun violence except guns that would not fit our agenda would it?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1361380428806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:13:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361381471053-93</Id><Topic><Title>BA price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>kondocarroll</Username><Timestamp>1361373775442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:22:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apple products rock man</Msg><Username>mitchelljuan314</Username><Timestamp>1361381471053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:31:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361382694161-94</Id><Title>The Sequester Cuts are Way too Small</Title><Msg>Here's what we know: The Congress and the President are incapable of cutting anything from any program, ever. If the only way to reduce spending is by instituting automatic cuts, then I am for allowing the sequester to take effect and see what happens.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361382694161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:51:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361382799483-95</Id><Title>What does the strike mean to you, when you walk out the door??</Title><Msg>It means your chekcbook balance is going to go down faster than a speeding bullet and your wife will be on your case constantly. Your dog won't even lick your face and when you go out to the garage, the fridge won't have you favorite beer. Your wife did buy you a six pack of light beer, so drink it down and forget about the fact that you can't afford to buy Kentucky Fried Chicken. . But then again, don't worry. That check you got from the union strike fund will buy you a few rolls of toilet paper.....</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1361382799483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:53:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361383004527-96</Id><Topic><Title>The Sequester Cuts are Way too Small</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361382694161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:51:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1361383004527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:56:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361383193241-97</Id><Title>Greece Signs Pipeline Deal As Unemployment Hits 27% - Will U.S. Wait That Long?</Title><Msg>Greece has signed a Trans Adriatic Pipeline Agreement, which it hopes will help ease its 27% unemployment rate. Meanwhile, Pres. Obama ponders the Keystone XL pipeline's fate.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361383193241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:59:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361383731269-98</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of nuts, Batsh*t Bachmann is on the Intelligence Committee. Says it all.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1361383731269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:08:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361384635747-99</Id><Topic><Title>a month to discover the electric lady is miswired ?hummmm</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376563426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:09:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Question that needs to be answered will be whether Boeings production certificate is in trouble to let something like this slip thru, or was it a maintance facility that caused it. Either way, there needs to be a production test that catches these things before flying</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361384635747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:23:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361385222083-100</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs like rummaging through other people's personal belongings. It's very liberal.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361385222083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:33:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361385279251-101</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Warns Of “Second American Revolution” If Gun Grabbers Get Their Way</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361369516900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are defending the Communist position rather well.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1361385279251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:34:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361385342664-102</Id><Topic><Title>BA price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>kondocarroll</Username><Timestamp>1361373775442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:22:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wgats their next big pick</Msg><Username>rollingdarren</Username><Timestamp>1361385342664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:35:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386109996-103</Id><Topic><Title>a month to discover the electric lady is miswired ?hummmm</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376563426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:09:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the Electric Lady?</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361386109996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386306455-104</Id><Topic><Title>Another Anonymous source</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361375750435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:55:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foxgang. Another stupid Fox viewer. What an idiot. Do you know your fat honey bun is "doing" the black garbage man? Again.</Msg><Username>kgnicetoo</Username><Timestamp>1361386306455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:51:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386359574-105</Id><Topic><Title>a month to discover the electric lady is miswired ?hummmm</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376563426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:09:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was given as the root cause weeks ago by the old professor at MIT. And as usual he was dead right.</Msg><Username>kgnicetoo</Username><Timestamp>1361386359574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:52:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386721949-106</Id><Topic><Title>Greece Signs Pipeline Deal As Unemployment Hits 27% - Will U.S. Wait That Long?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361383193241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:59:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't take a genius to see the benefits to the economy given Obama would have signed the Pipeline contract. But that is just one of the impediment roadblocks Obama has put in front of economic recovery.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1361386721949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:58:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361386811066-107</Id><Title>Criminal Reporting and laughable solution</Title><Msg>Person not authorized to speak says all is well. Ray Hood, Trans Secy, won't let plane fly. Also, solution to battery, vent the fires!!! Boeing Said to Propose 787 Battery Fixes to U.S. FAA By Alan Levin &amp; Susanna Ray - Feb 20, 2013 1:40 PM ET Boeing Co. officials are scheduled to meet with U.S. regulators Feb. 22 to propose fixes to the 787 Dreamliner in a bid to end the plane’s grounding, a person with knowledge of the talks said. The proposal, which includes protections to ensure that another lithium-ion battery fire wouldn’t damage the plane or release smoke into the cabin, is subject to approval by the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration, according to the person, who wasn’t authorized to speak about the meeting and asked not to be identified. It would also have to be approved by U.S. Transportation Secretary Ray LaHood, who has said the Dreamliner won’t fly again until U.S. officials are “1,000 percent sure” it’s safe. Boeing’s proposal will include a more fire-resistant box housing the eight cells in each of the two batteries aboard the 787, the person said. The planemaker’s engineers also want to create a tubing system to vent smoke or fumes emitted by the battery in case of an incident, according to the person.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361386811066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361387522619-108</Id><Topic><Title>75.85 up 1.20</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361366351500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 08:19:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>point 3 BA still up 1.07.........hahaha</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1361387522619</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:12:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361388255278-109</Id><Title>Boeing trying to resolve the battery probelm with band aids</Title><Msg>"Vent the smoke from any fires" The battery has a long history of being explosive and a fire hazard. It can't even be transported by planes! Go back to the old battery and focus on the malfunctioning electrical system.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361388255278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:24:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361388486245-110</Id><Title>Any Truth to the Rumor Hozdik and his Blow Up Doll have Broken Up?</Title><Msg>It seem his blow up doll sprung a leak during one of Hoozdik's love making sessions. It angered hoozdik so much when he had to stop and blow the doll back up that he threatened to leave him flat and buy a female doll. There's still a chance though that he could patch things up and save the relationship.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361388486245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:28:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361389446367-111</Id><Title>Obama Pal Headed To Jail With His Wife</Title><Msg>Jackson's only sin in the eyes of Dems and Obama, is that he got caught. WASHINGTON -- Former Rep. Jesse Jackson Jr. (D-Ill.) pleaded guilty in a federal courtroom Wednesday morning to using campaign funds to purchase an array of personal items including Bruce Lee memorabilia, a $43,000 Rolex watch and a mink cashmere cape. He pleaded guilty to conspiracy before U.S. District Judge Robert L. Wilkins. His wife, Sandra Jackson, who resigned from her position on Chicago’s city council, is expected to plead guilty to filing false tax returns before the same judge on Wednesday afternoon. Jackson, dressed in a blue tie, blue shirt and a blue suit, looked back in the direction of his father and wife several times during the hearing. At one point he appeared to mouth, "I'm sorry." The former representative, who co-wrote a 1999 book with his father, Rev. Jesse Jackson, titled It's About the Money!: How You Can Get Out of Debt, Build Wealth, and Achieve Your Financial Dreams, was accused of spending $750,000 in campaign funds on personal items for himself and for his wife.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361389446367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:44:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361390234796-112</Id><Title>TIMMMMMMMBER!</Title><Msg>Market going to he ll after Fed minutes</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361390234796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361390256675-113</Id><Title>Maybe Hoozedik Should get a Mooslum Blow up Doll</Title><Msg>....I hear they blow themselfs up.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361390256675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361391771905-114</Id><Title>Going to Bed Red</Title><Msg>Got that "unposter 76"?</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361391771905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:22:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361391993895-115</Id><Title>Battery Fix Weight Impact</Title><Msg>Added weight, will it be less than using conventional batteries? Creamic Plates Titanium Enclosures Overboard Venting System</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361391993895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:26:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361392293642-116</Id><Topic><Title>Caterpillar January Orders went Negative Worldwide !!!!!!!!!!! CAT RED !</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1361374501903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tried to warn you and you bashed me with 5 thumbs down ! this shows the extent tof bullishness here ! I don't think that Battery replacment is going to be the end of this either ! And massive defense cuts are not out of the question either !</Msg><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1361392293642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:31:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361392702555-117</Id><Topic><Title>Having Added Record $5.9T to Debt, Obama Claims He’s Cut Deficit $2.5T</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361381802979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:36:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is an incorrigible criminal. He defiles the very church halls that he walks through. His thinking is corrupt. It's a paradox that he should even be the leader of the Free World.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361392702555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:38:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361393189631-118</Id><Topic><Title>Having Added Record $5.9T to Debt, Obama Claims He’s Cut Deficit $2.5T</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361381802979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:36:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem with the US debt is much worse than the Fed's think. WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. Federal Reserve may have to slow or stop buying bonds before seeing the pickup in hiring the bold program is designed to deliver, a number of Fed officials felt last month, according to minutes of the central bank's January policy meeting. "A number of participants stated that an ongoing evaluation of the efficacy, costs, and risks of asset purchases might well lead the (policy-setting) committee to taper or end its purchases before it judged that a substantial improvement in the outlook for the labor market had occurred," the minutes released on Wednesday said.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1361393189631</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:46:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361393675039-119</Id><Topic><Title>TIMMMMMMMBER!</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361390234796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like they are thinking about stopping the endless flow of free money into financial institutions. How's that going to work out now?</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361393675039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:54:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361393974122-120</Id><Title>Wher is the Kent Raven - We could use a Good Laugh at Some of His.......</Title><Msg>.....sissy left wing lunatic dogma.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361393974122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:59:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361393997641-121</Id><Topic><Title>What does the strike mean to you, when you walk out the door??</Title><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1361382799483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:53:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think the SPEEA union has a strike fund!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1361393997641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:59:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361394117931-122</Id><Topic><Title>The 787 is an engineering falure. Nobody will fly it.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361373401685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:16:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be thrilled to fly in a 787. It does not get more exciting than this.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361394117931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:01:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361394263114-123</Id><Topic><Title>TIMMMMMMMBER!</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361390234796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:57:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The question becomes......where will the money go? Stocks will tumble on less QE (no FED support of equities) Bonds will tumble on less QE (no bond buying leads to higher supply) Commodities will tumble on less QE (Recession) All this will be worldwide. What comes ot mind in protecting your wealth. GOLD</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361394263114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:04:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361394508032-124</Id><Topic><Title>What does the strike mean to you, when you walk out the door??</Title><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1361382799483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:53:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Boeing has the upper hand now, Engineers accepted the contract, tech's didn't. I don't see how a strike by the tech's is going to do much good. If new engineers do not get a pension, I doubt the Tech's will be able to bargain for one.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361394508032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:08:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361395047679-125</Id><Title>Is This a Veiled SPEEA Threat?</Title><Msg>The SPEEA web site states "SPEEA Professional Unit are in position to provide inside support to technical workers..." in the event of a strike. Boeing may have a unfair labor practice complaint against a union that writes about a sympathy strike.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361395047679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:17:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361395599672-126</Id><Topic><Title>Is This a Veiled SPEEA Threat?</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361395047679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:17:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I owned a company would I open it in USA. Not with all these rules, regulations. So SPEEA is at a disadvantage healthcare is too high. You can expect co mpanies to survive on such expensive health care. I think SPEEA is not living in a reality world or should I say spoiled. Boeing has to move out of USA. China, and Vietnam best choices. Even India can be good. Goodbye SPEEA..</Msg><Username>cmps309</Username><Timestamp>1361395599672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:26:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361396235812-127</Id><Title>I'm asking a favor of the longs.....</Title><Msg>I know you won't sell your stock now, or even a few points lower. However, please sell it to me at the 56 support level, reached in 2011, and 2010. Thanks in advance</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361396235812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:37:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361396373283-128</Id><Title>Picka fix........any fix (truly lauaghable) And they want me to fly in this coffin?!?!?</Title><Msg>[$$] Boeing to Propose Package of 787 Battery Fixes to FAAat The Wall Street Journal(Wed 4:07PM EST)</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361396373283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361396424540-129</Id><Topic><Title>a month to discover the electric lady is miswired ?hummmm</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361376563426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:09:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice stock move and bust today al the spin still soes not work a month and still no fly. electrick lady for foxgang7878 refers to the 787 it needs more electric power to run the systems and it has a electric problem so that is a nickname like negative and positive is a positive if you know the math equation here</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361396424540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:40:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361397530960-130</Id><Topic><Title>The 787 is an engineering falure. Nobody will fly it.</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1361373401685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:16:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go ahead and kiss your A.S.S goodbye NOW. While you still can.</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1361397530960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:58:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361397793741-131</Id><Topic><Title>Caterpillar January Orders went Negative Worldwide !!!!!!!!!!! CAT RED !</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1361374501903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:35:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think that Battery replacment is going to be the end of this either ! You're def right about that! And let's not forget that composite junk that will shatter and crumble in the softest of all crash landings!!! Mark my wurds! It's got DISASTER written all over it!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1361397793741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:03:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361399306826-132</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Fix Weight Impact</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361391993895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:26:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Proposed temporary fix. If a permanent fix can be found that still incorporates the lithium ion batteries, it will be vastly superior to reverting back to any of the older style batteries.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1361399306826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:28:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361401000949-133</Id><Title>PR all hands on deck. We have a problem</Title><Msg>Feb 21 (Reuters) - Australia's flagship carrier Qantas Airways Ltd said it has received compensation from Boeing Co for delays in deliveries of the grounded 787 Dreamliner jet, as it reported a 10.4 percent increase in first-half profit. Qantas said on Thursday the result included A$125 million ($128.6 million) of compensation income from Boeing because of delays by the U.S. planemaker in delivering the Dreamliner.</Msg><Username>apollo5</Username><Timestamp>1361401000949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:56:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361402017736-134</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Fix Weight Impact</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361391993895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:26:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>term s/b HALF-VAST</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361402017736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:13:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361402111366-135</Id><Title>What's that Sound?</Title><Msg>Most liberals who think we don't have a spending problem are like people leisurely paddling downstream in a canoe and people on the bank are screaming, stop, stop, get out....there's 600 foot waterfall down stream. The people in the canoe laugh at the people on the bank and ignore the warnings and the paddling seems to be getting easier.....then one of them says......what's that sound? The collapse is coming better get prepared. The great depression ran from 1929 to 1942 and WWII but actually continued to 1946. "FDR's policies prolonged Depression by 7 years, UCLA economists calculate By Meg Sullivan August 10, 2004 Two UCLA economists say they have figured out why the Great Depression dragged on for almost 15 years, and they blame a suspect previously thought to be beyond reproach: President Franklin D. Roosevelt. After scrutinizing Roosevelt's record for four years, Harold L. Cole and Lee E. Ohanian conclude in a new study that New Deal policies signed into law 71 years ago thwarted economic recovery for seven long years. "Why the Great Depression lasted so long has always been a great mystery, and because we never really knew the reason, we have always worried whether we would have another 10- to 15-year economic slump," said Ohanian, vice chair of UCLA's Department of Economics. "We found that a relapse isn't likely unless lawmakers gum up a recovery with ill-conceived stimulus policies." In an article in the August issue of the Journal of Political Economy, Ohanian and Cole blame specific anti-competition and pro-labor measures that Roosevelt promoted and signed into law June 16, 1933. "President Roosevelt believed that excessive competition was responsible for the Depression by reducing prices and wages, and by extension reducing employment and demand for goods and services," said Cole, also a UCLA professor of economics. "So he came up with a recovery package that would be unimaginable today, allowing businesses in every industry to collude without the threat of antitrust prosecution and workers to demand salaries about 25 percent above where they ought to have been, given market forces. The economy was poised for a beautiful recovery, but that recovery was stalled by these misguided policies." Hmmmmmm........sound familiar? UCLA? Isn't that one of the country's most liberal universities?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361402111366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:15:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361402333834-136</Id><Topic><Title>PR all hands on deck. We have a problem</Title><Username>apollo5</Username><Timestamp>1361401000949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:56:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now multiply that by ????? We're not talking peanuts.</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361402333834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:18:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361405378019-137</Id><Title>I support Obama's sequestration plan</Title><Msg>Obviously he knew he had a spending addiction with no real solutions to help Americans and he put sequestration into place to prevent further reckless government spending. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361405378019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:09:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361406171000-138</Id><Title>NASA Priority Was Helping Muslims Feel Better About Themselves Rather Than Asteroid Collisions</Title><Msg>Obama's leadership has been mostly based on stupidity but occasionaly ventures into insanity. Let's let Muslims deal with their own self esteem and pay more attention to large rocks headed for Earth. What do you say Obama?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361406171000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:22:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361407749135-139</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Fix Weight Impact</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361391993895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:26:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's good about the lithium-ion batteries is that they are rechargeable. They can be recharged a thousand times. A real cost saver.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361407749135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:49:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361408163111-140</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Fix Weight Impact</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361391993895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:26:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If that is true, why has there been about 150 battery replacements on the 50 delivered planes</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361408163111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:56:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361408182319-141</Id><Topic><Title>Battery Fix Weight Impact</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1361391993895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:26:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have heard several times a replacement batter using proven technology would weigh about twice the LI battery and be considerably larger. So they can up the strength of the case considerably and still hold a big weight and size advantage. Also ceramic insulating plates inserted between cells to protect adjacent cells from the heat of a cell undergoing thermal meltdown wouldn't add much weight. As they would be similar to the lightweight thermal tiles on the Space Shuttle, but the case will need to be bigger to make space for them. Also one thing a lot of people are missing is the safer battery that would replace the LI batter has a lot of compromises compared to the LI battery besides weight and size. LI batteries can be charged, and discharged faster without damage. Can survive more discharge recharge cycles, and don't have the memory issues the replacement for LI has. The LI is not just lighter and smaller, it performs at a higher level as well. Which is the reason BA took the risk of going with them despite the known pitfalls. By the way I don't think the new case will need to be that much heavier to do the job. The old case despite having no venting and major buckling from the pressure inside, likely would have had minor to no buckling if it had been vented. The big difference will come in the way of gas tight flanges for the cover, to insure all the nasty elements from a battery undergoing a catastrophic failure will not be vented into the interior of the aircraft, and that should not add that much weight.</Msg><Username>stocksentinel</Username><Timestamp>1361408182319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:56:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361410056243-142</Id><Title>A Miswired battery caused a billion fiasco</Title><Msg>All Nippon Airways concluded from its investigation that a fire in its 787 came about due to miswiring in that the battery of the aircraft's auxiliary power unit was incorrectly connected to the main battery that overheated.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361410056243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:27:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361410195694-143</Id><Topic><Title>A Miswired battery caused a billion fiasco</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361410056243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:27:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Subject should read: A miswired battery caused a billion dollar fiasco</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1361410195694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:29:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361410878079-144</Id><Title>Quantas Gets $128 million for late 787 deliveries</Title><Msg>Does anyone besides me this it very off that Quantas was paid $128 USD for late deliveries of the 787 when Quantas is not due to get a single 787 unitl the second half of this year and reportedly has Quantas recently said they have not been told of any delays. If we were to extrapolate ANA should be good for about a billion USD since it now has 17 planes grounded. Something sounds very fishy about this Quantas payment.</Msg><Username>instantkarma22</Username><Timestamp>1361410878079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:41:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361411995726-145</Id><Topic><Title>I support Obama's sequestration plan</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361405378019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:09:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First he was for it now he's against it! I think the President is just f--king with our minds!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1361411995726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:59:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361413867856-146</Id><Topic><Title>I support Obama's sequestration plan</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361405378019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:09:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he is still on crack. His brain is fried.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361413867856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:31:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361414747651-147</Id><Title>TECHNOLOGY BREAKTHROUGH - Energy from coal with no pollution or CO2</Title><Msg>Ohio State develops clean coal technology When a team of Ohio State students worked around the clock for nine days straight recently, they weren't pulling the typical college "all-nighters." Instead, they were reaching a milestone in clean coal technology. For 203 continuous hours, they operated a scaled-down version of a power plant combustion system with a unique experimental design--one that chemically converts coal to heat while capturing 99 percent of the carbon dioxide produced in the reaction. This new technology, called coal-direct chemical looping, was pioneered by Liang-Shih Fan, professor of chemical and biomolecular engineering and director of Ohio State's Clean Coal Research Laboratory. (Fan is a Distinguished University Professor and a 2012 Innovator of the Year.) Typical coal-fired power plants burn coal to heat water to make steam, which turns the turbines that produce electricity. In chemical looping, the coal isn't burned with fire, but instead chemically combusted in a sealed chamber so that it doesn't pollute the air. A second combustion unit in the lab does the same thing with coal-derived syngas, and both produce 25 thermal kilowatts of energy. "In the simplest sense, combustion is a chemical reaction that consumes oxygen and produces heat," Fan says. "Unfortunately, it also produces carbon dioxide, which is difficult to capture and bad for the environment. So we found a way to release the heat without burning." Dawei Wang, a research associate and one of the group's team leaders, says the technology's potential benefits go beyond the environment: "The plant could really promote our energy independence. Not only can we use America's natural resources such as Ohio coal, but we can keep our air clean and spur the economy with jobs." The researchers are about to take the technology to the next level: a pilot plant is under construction at the U.S. Department of Energy's National Carbon Capture Center. Set to begin operations in late 2013, that plant will produce 250 thermal kilowatts using syngas. Tests there will set the stage for future commercial development. "At Ohio State, with a team of creative minds, we can take a technological concept closer to real commercial use," Wang says. The technology looks promising: as doctoral student Elena Chung explained, the 203-hour experiment could have continued even longer. "We voluntarily chose to stop the unit. Honestly, it was a mutual decision by Dr. Fan and the students. It was a long and tiring week where we all shared shifts," she says. Fan's students were thrilled to be involved in this breakthrough, even if they did lose some sleep. "Ohio State has been very supportive of our research efforts," Fan says. The result of the university's backing? A place, he says, where "brilliant invention and cutting-edge research can be successful and progressive."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361414747651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:45:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361417222468-148</Id><Topic><Title>Hoozdik must be terrified of losing his welfare</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1361324773132</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:46:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is hoose still being paid for doing nothing if he spends all day trying to troll up a stock message board with dim propaganda ? It almost seems that in a way he's earning his pay from his dim bulb masters . . . . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1361417222468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:27:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361418252103-149</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine the sheer panic from the righties. A black first lady, a black President, and the next President will terrify them: "President Hillary Clinton."</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1361418252103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:44:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361418594261-150</Id><Topic><Title>TECHNOLOGY BREAKTHROUGH - Energy from coal with no pollution or CO2</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361414747651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 21:45:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It makes me happy that you had fun because I always have fun. This enormous breakthrough was made at a cost that was 1/4 the cost of Obama's weekend golf trip. Captured CO2 can be sold for commercial use and it can be used in fracking. You are full of #$%$ as far as saying this is nothing new as the developer has 37 new patents on his process. You do know what a patent is right? From the new scientist: 'Fracking could be combined with carbon capture plans' "Talk about a win-win situation. Compressed carbon dioxide may be more suitable than water for fracturing methane-rich rock – a finding that could help the growing hydraulic fracturing industry extract more natural gas from spent fields. And because the carbon dioxide is then trapped below ground, the discovery could also spur the development of large-scale carbon sequestration. Natural gas production has soared worldwide in recent years as a result of hydraulic fracturing, or fracking – a process of injecting pressurised water into shale formations to fracture the rock and release massive amounts of natural gas trapped inside."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361418594261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:49:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361418683134-151</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>King Kong was pretty too.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1361418683134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:51:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361419453265-152</Id><Topic><Title>Having Added Record $5.9T to Debt, Obama Claims He’s Cut Deficit $2.5T</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1361381802979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:36:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALL the fact checkers say you're full of it.</Msg><Username>windyhorn</Username><Timestamp>1361419453265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:04:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361420443978-153</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Obama's Portrait For 2013</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1361407736277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Given that she terrified Bill Clinton, why not the rest of the country?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1361420443978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:20:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361421048290-154</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, ironic that I am using the name Douglas, which was forced to merge in 1967 with McDonnell, then 1997 with BA. The Long Beach Plant is abandoned except the C-17 line, the commercial buildings have been vacant for 7 years and it was the number one aircraft company in the world in the 1950s. Now out of business and becoming a distant memory.</Msg><Username>boeingman_1</Username><Timestamp>1361421048290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:30:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361422419311-155</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the name Douglas was the number aircraft company in the world in 1950s due to prop aircraft, then was a slow adopter to jet engine aircraft and played caught up for years, but could not overcome the late start and development costs to catch up with the 707. Convair tried to compete with the CV880/990 with Douglas and Boeing. Douglas yielded the number one position to Boeing by the late 50s and tried to win back the market with the DC-9, but the 737 came in around 1965 to become the standard for narrow body aircraft for airlines. The 5 across aisle, was an Achilles hill for the DC-9/MD-80/MD-90/MD-95.</Msg><Username>boeingman_1</Username><Timestamp>1361422419311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:53:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361422624171-156</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the real point of this history lession is that one must stay innovative to complete in the future. Let Douglas live in the mines of many as it is now part of the Legacy Boeing company and a victim of not being innovative at a crucial time in its history and becoming a follower, in lieu of a leader. This is leason for all people who value Boeing as a national treasure.</Msg><Username>boeingman_1</Username><Timestamp>1361422624171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:57:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361422651638-157</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lession that is.</Msg><Username>boeingman_1</Username><Timestamp>1361422651638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:57:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361422689196-158</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Strike Threat Looms After Tumult on 787 Grounding</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1361323461941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-19 20:24:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cannot spell or structure sentences correctly tonight, foregive me.</Msg><Username>boeingman_1</Username><Timestamp>1361422689196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:58:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>