<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377662454613-1</Id><Topic><Title>The Red Line Gets a Little Fuzzy</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1377646425710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 19:33:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let us be perfectly clear; “It is our firm conviction that Syria's future cannot include Assad in power, but this deliberation and the actions that we are contemplating are not about regime change,” the spokesman insisted. Obama has not made a final decision on the course of action and might still stop short of using force, Carney said. At the same time, Carney escalated the rhetoric about the Assad regime’s alleged Aug. 21 chemical weapons attack, saying that failing to punish Syria would pose a “significant” threat to the United States. “Absolutely, allowing the use of chemical weapons on a significant scale to take place without a response would present a significant challenge to or threat to the United States' national security interests,” Carney said. Including the United States itself? “Correct,” he said. “To allow it to happen without a response would be to invite further use of chemical weapons.” Kieth_Unterman ( dem hedge-miesters )</Msg><Username>kieth_unterman</Username><Timestamp>1377662454613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 00:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377671340458-2</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the war protestors?</Title><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1377652509513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya the Dixie Chicks, Hollywood and even Cindy Shehan all got lock jaw. I haven't even seen any ribbons that libs love to pin on their chest to show how much they care.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1377671340458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 02:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377671885687-3</Id><Topic><Title>In what branch of the Military did Obama Serve?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377651687894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:01:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too young.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377671885687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 02:38:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377674994242-4</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the war protestors?</Title><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1377652509513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a sounding board for political concerns</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377674994242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377675132227-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Red Line Gets a Little Fuzzy</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1377646425710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 19:33:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will bring a regime change of course as their power degrades by the day. This will not be all that difficult. They have a sound 3 step process that is posted if there is a action</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377675132227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377675190834-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama push's Nations into World War III</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377645751198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 19:22:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is not controlling that madman. Are you ok?</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377675190834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377675538989-7</Id><Topic><Title>How to spot a barker ,rs2ms2ts2ks72 on the Tesla message board his claim IS bs LIKE HERE BA message board</Title><Username>gsylvia16</Username><Timestamp>1377658941260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 23:02:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You ok? Never a lie on Yahoo. Boeing info from their website and trade journals and Telsa is a very debateable subject. Try and stay professional in your dealings.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377675538989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377675752701-8</Id><Topic><Title>Automotive Industry on cars ratings and how tesla rates it better boeing on stock price gain too</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461840438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:17:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Telsa and Boeing can not be compared by any rationale thought. 2 different animals</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377675752701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377675785747-9</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA price increase is 20.1 times faster than the S&amp;P 500! boeing is lower than the S&amp;P for 3 weeks</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377452299860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 13:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>setting a new high speaks nothing of risk???</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377675785747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377675890105-10</Id><Topic><Title>FAA Inspector opinion on the 787 Richard Wyeroski</Title><Username>gsylvia16</Username><Timestamp>1377495728704</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-08-26 01:42:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't put down people on the board. You have problems trying to become professional. Bad attitude toward people</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377675890105</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377675941405-11</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla Is Outselling Porsche, Volvo, and Land Rover in California</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377473855005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't call out specific posters. This is a message boards to share thoughts and not attack like you</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377675941405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:45:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377675999998-12</Id><Topic><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is with you and Boeing pension. This is a message board. Cause trouble else where</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377675999998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377676180899-13</Id><Topic><Title>apache sale</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377632902602</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 15:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to see you back. Board has become a source of no information except for youself and a few others. Too bad</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1377676180899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 03:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377681540797-14</Id><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Msg>Punitive war. That's something I'm betting the Norwegian Nobel Committee never would have predicted a recipient of their peace prize engaging in. This is not defensive war, since the Assad regime doesn't present even the remotest threat to America. It isn't a humanitarian war either, since U.S. airstrikes won't cripple the Assad regime's military capacity and may even get more civilians killed. Obama is waging a war, as Miller explained, "to make a point." Given the fact that a mere 9 percent of Americans actually support a U.S. military intervention in Syria, I wonder what it would do to public opinion if Obama was honest with the American people about his petty disciplinary war. If the president sat in the Oval Office and told the American public that he was bombing another country, not to protect Americans or even Syrians, but "to make a point" or "punish" the Assad regime, with no greater utility, I seriously doubt the mission would gain any legitimacy in the eyes of voters. With a backbone like an earthworm, President Obama is bowing to pressure - not from the American public or from Congress, but from "foreign-policy experts and politicians," as Leslie Gelb, president emeritus of the Council on Foreign Relations, described it -- to go to war for his own "credibility." Obama told the world that Assad's use of chemical weapons would be a "red line" that would prompt U.S. military action. So, to protect Obama's reputation as a reliable war-maker who keeps his promise to bomb people, we have to go to war in Syria? It's difficult to imagine a weaker case for using international force. Which brings us to a final point: for this apparently imminent U.S. bombing raid to be legal, it has to get the approval of both the U.S. Congress and the United Nations Security Council. Congress is likely to push back on Obama's call to war and Russia and China are sure to veto any proposal at the UN.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377682973652-15</Id><Topic><Title>In what branch of the Military did Obama Serve?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377651687894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:01:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good question. Could he have got in?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377682973652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377688622890-16</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the war protestors?</Title><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1377652509513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will be dropping Non Racist, Loving, Liberal, Peace Prize bombs on Brown people in Syria...it will be without congressional approval but it will be trendy</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377688622890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377688830266-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ouch: Doctor Shortage Could Spell (More) Disaster for Obamacare</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377653712825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe it.....its from multiple sources...Drs getting out of the profession cause they have had it with the petty government Beaureacracy and they know this does not help patients....</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377688830266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377689220363-18</Id><Title>22 Reasons why starting war with Syria is a Real bad idea</Title><Msg>#1 The American people are overwhelmingly against going to war with Syria… Americans strongly oppose U.S. intervention in Syria’s civil war and believe Washington should stay out of the conflict even if reports that Syria’s government used deadly chemicals to attack civilians are confirmed, a Reuters/Ipsos poll says. About 60 percent of Americans surveyed said the United States should not intervene in Syria’s civil war, while just 9 percent thought President Barack Obama should act. #2 At this point, a war in Syria is even more unpopular with the American people than Congress is. #3 The Obama administration has not gotten approval to go to war with Syria from Congress as the U.S. Constitution requires. #4 The United States does not have the approval of the United Nations to attack Syria and it is not going to be getting it. #5 Syria has said that it will use ”all means available” to defend itself if the United States attacks. Would that include terror attacks in the United States itself? #6 Syrian Foreign Minister Walid Muallem made the following statement on Tuesday… “We have two options: either to surrender, or to defend ourselves with the means at our disposal. The second choice is the best: we will defend ourselves” #7 Russia has just sent their most advanced anti-ship missiles to Syria. What do you think would happen if images of sinking U.S. naval vessels were to come flashing across our television screens? #8 When the United States attacks Syria, there is a very good chance that Syria will attack Israel. Just check out what one Syrian official said recently… A member of the Syrian Ba’ath national council Halef al-Muftah, until recently the Syrian propaganda minister’s aide, said on Monday that Damascus views Israel as “behind the aggression and therefore it will come under fire” should Syria be attacked by the United States.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689220363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377689255930-19</Id><Topic><Title>22 Reasons why starting war with Syria is a Real bad idea</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689220363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:27:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#9 If Syria attacks Israel, the consequences could be absolutely catastrophic. Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is promising that any attack will be responded to “forcefully“… “We are not a party to this civil war in Syria but if we identify any attempt to attack us we will respond and we will respond forcefully” #10 Hezbollah will likely do whatever it can to fight for the survival of the Assad regime. That could include striking targets inside both the United States and Israel. #11 Iran’s closest ally is Syria. Will Iran sit idly by as their closest ally is removed from the chessboard? #12 Starting a war with Syria will cause significant damage to our relationship with Russia. On Tuesday, Deputy Prime Minister Dmitry Rogozin said that the West is acting like a “monkey with a hand grenade“. #13 Starting a war with Syria will cause significant damage to our relationship with China. And what will happen if the Chinese decide to start dumping the massive amount of U.S. debt that it is holding? Interest rates would absolutely skyrocket and we would rapidly be facing a nightmare scenario. #14 Dr. Jerome Corsi and Walid Shoebat have compiled some startling evidence that it was actually the Syrian rebels that the U.S. is supporting that were responsible for the chemical weapons attack that is being used as justification to go to war with Syria… With the assistance of former PLO member and native Arabic-speaker Walid Shoebat, WND has assembled evidence from various Middle Eastern sources that cast doubt on Obama administration claims the Assad government is responsible for last week’s attack. You can examine the evidence for yourself right here. #15 As Pat Buchanan recently noted, it would have made absolutely no sense for the Assad regime to use chemical weapons on defenseless women and children. The only people who would benefit from such an attack would be the rebels… The basic question that needs to be asked about this horrific attack on civilians, which appears to be gas related, is: Cui bono? To whose benefit would the use of nerve gas on Syrian women and children redound? Certainly not Assad’s, as we can see from the furor and threats against him that the use of gas has produced. The sole beneficiary of this apparent use of poison gas against civilians in rebel-held territory appears to be the rebels, who have long sought to have us come in and fight their war. #16 If the Saudis really want to topple the Assad regime, they should do it themselves. They should not expect the United States to do their dirty work for them. #17 A former commander of U.S. Central Command has said that a U.S. attack on Syria would result in “a full-throated, very, very serious war“. #18 A war in the Middle East will be bad for the financial markets. The Dow was down about 170 points today and concern about war with Syria was the primary reason. #19 A war in the Middle East will cause the price of oil to go up. On Tuesday, the price of U.S. oil rose to about $109 a barrel. #20 There is no way in the world that the U.S. government should be backing the Syrian rebels. As I discussed a few days ago, the rebels have pledged loyalty to al-Qaeda, they have beheaded numerous Christians and they have massacred entire Christian villages. If the U.S. government helps these lunatics take power in Syria it will be a complete and utter disaster.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689255930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377689294366-20</Id><Topic><Title>22 Reasons why starting war with Syria is a Real bad idea</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689220363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:27:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#21 A lot of innocent civilians inside Syria will end up getting killed. Already, a lot of Syrians are expressing concern about what “foreign intervention” will mean for them and their families… “I’ve always been a supporter of foreign intervention, but now that it seems like a reality, I’ve been worrying that my family could be hurt or killed,” said one woman, Zaina, who opposes Assad. “I’m afraid of a military strike now.” “The big fear is that they’ll make the same mistakes they made in Libya and Iraq,” said Ziyad, a man in his 50s. “They’ll hit civilian targets, and then they’ll cry that it was by mistake, but we’ll get killed in the thousands.” #22 If the U.S. government insists on going to war with Syria without the approval of the American people, the U.S. Congress or the United Nations, we are going to lose a lot of friends and a lot of credibility around the globe. It truly is a sad day when Russia looks like “the good guys” and we look like “the bad guys”.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689294366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377689631555-21</Id><Topic><Title>22 Reasons why starting war with Syria is a Real bad idea</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689220363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:27:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is all this talk about war. The Obama administration will not do anything in Syria. They will all sit around and talk about Syria, but they are not going to do anything. Kerry said that in his speech yesterday, so forget about it..</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1377689631555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377689917587-22</Id><Title>Kucinich: "striking Syria would turn the United States military into al-Qaeda's Air Force"</Title><Msg>Former congressman Dennis Kucinich (D., Ohio) said today that striking Syria would turn the United States military into “al-Qaeda’s air force.” Kucinich, who voted against the Iraq War and campaigned for the Democratic nomination for president in 2004 and 2008, lambasted the idea that Obama could act without congressional authorization, which he said would be a violation of the Constitution. He also warned that intervening in Syria would entangle the United States in another war in the Middle East and encourage Islamists who are fighting the forces of Syrian president Bashar Assad. “So what, we’re about to become al-Qaeda’s air force now?” Kucinich sarcastically asked The Hill. He went on to warn against attempting to “minimize” an intervention by terming it a “targeted strike.” Such a strike, he said, would still constitute an act of war. Kucinich also blasted the Obama administration for “rushing” into what he said could become a third world war, and he cast doubt on reports by rebels of governmental forces using chemical weapons. He declared that the use of chemical weapons in Syria was a “pretext.” “The verdict is in before the facts have been gathered,” Kucinich said. “What does that tell you?”</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689917587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377690501100-23</Id><Topic><Title>In what branch of the Military did Obama Serve?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377651687894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:01:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to show valid I.D. to get in the military</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377690501100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377691912048-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ouch: Doctor Shortage Could Spell (More) Disaster for Obamacare</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377653712825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:35:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the future most doctors will have green cards. Can't wait to meet Raji my new GP and Hajib my next protologist....the secret is, do not get sick.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1377691912048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 08:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377691917441-25</Id><Topic><Title>Putin in Pink</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377652557959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Russia does ban "insulting representatives of authority." The United States bans them at Rodeos as well.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377691917441</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 08:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377695657607-26</Id><Topic><Title>How to spot a barker ,rs2ms2ts2ks72 on the Tesla message board his claim IS bs LIKE HERE BA message board</Title><Username>gsylvia16</Username><Timestamp>1377658941260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 23:02:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rs2ms2ts2ks72 you ok, try to not be telling message board users that the tesla battery is only good for a short time , the tesla warrantee specifies 8 years you get it now rs2ms2ts2ks272 try research not what come out of your hot air hole for a change when you become professional then we can talk</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377695657607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377695690479-27</Id><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Msg>An American military attack on Syria could begin as early as Thursday and will involve three days of missile strikes, according to "senior U.S. officials" talking to NBC News. The Washington Post has the bombing at "no more than two days," though long-range bombers could "possibly" join the missiles. "Factors weighing into the timing of any action include a desire to get it done before the president leaves for Russia next week," reports CNN, citing a "senior administration official." The New York Times, quoting a Pentagon official, adds that "the initial target list has fewer than 50 sites, including air bases where Syria's Russian-made attack helicopters are deployed." The Times adds that "like several other military officials contacted for this report, the official agreed to discuss planning options only on condition of anonymity." Thus do the legal and moral requirements of secret military operations lose out in this Administration to the imperatives of in-the-know spin and political gestures. It's always possible that all of this leaking about when, how and for how long the U.S. will attack Syria is an elaborate head-fake, like Patton's ghost army on the eve of D-Day, poised for the assault on Calais. But based on this Administration's past behavior, such as the leaked bin Laden raid details, chances are most of this really is the war plan. Which makes us wonder why the Administration even bothers to pursue the likes of Edward Snowden when it is giving away its plan of attack to anyone in Damascus with an Internet connection. The answer, it seems, is that the attack in Syria isn't really about damaging the Bashar Assad regime's capacity to murder its own people, much less about ending the Assad regime for good.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377696068555-28</Id><Title>Labor Unions Mad at Obama Adminstration Again</Title><Msg>Leaders from major labor unions like the Teamsters, UCFW and UNITE-HERE are already livid with the Obama administration over Obamacare and now, unions representing pilots and flight attendants are ripping the Department of Justice for blocking the merger between U.S. Airways and American Airlines. At least four labor unions have joined in opposition to the Justice Department's Aug. 13 anti-trust suit that essentially argues the proposed, $11 billion merger could reduce the number of flight choices for customers, allow the two airlines to control pricing, and increase fares and fees. The Allied Pilots Association, which represents 10,000 American Airlines pilots, argues the merger would make the two airlines competitive with industry leaders Delta and United, help bankrupt American Airlines and “significantly expand the choices of travel destinations.” Further, they question why the federal government is attempting to block this merger after approving similar ones. "It makes no sense for the Justice Department to conclude now that the airline industry consolidation is somehow undesirable,” argues the pilot’s union, which has the backing from unions representing flight attendants from both airlines. The Association of Flight Attendants, which represents US Airway attendants, called the suit a “war on workers.” Scribner thinks Obama’s course of action on the recent issues is “definitely a risk,” considering Big Labor has long supported Democratic candidates. Just last week, AFL-CIO Nevada passed a resolution to openly criticize the Obama administration over its failure to fix problems with Obamacare which they say will kill the 40 hour work week and eliminate healthcare coverage for workers. It's time for Republicans to start making some friends in labor on the topics of Obamacare and DOJ overreach.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377696068555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377696678224-29</Id><Topic><Title>Labor Unions Mad at Obama Adminstration Again</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377696068555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How long does it take folks to realize Obama, and his progressive approach to governing was going to fail miserably where the rubber meets the road? Liberalism always does. You can not take in workin folks' tax dollars, and pass them down through a huge Federal bureaucracy that you increased in size dramatically give a lot of the money to your crony rich contributor friends, and have anything left for the folks' that expected to get any of it. Then you promise those folks you will get more money from rich folks....stick a fork in progressivism it's done.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377696678224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377696811823-30</Id><Title>Syrian strategy</Title><Msg>Who wants to bet what Obama will come up with to punish Syria? Concern for our national defense, or he wants to save face concerned about Obama?</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377696811823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377697694453-31</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries still increasing</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377633107373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 15:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now 46 planes. Air India finally got financing for 787 (L/N 90).</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377697694453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377698086025-32</Id><Title>satellite launch today</Title><Msg>VANDENBERG AIR FORCE BASE, Calif. (AP) -- A powerful rocket carrying a National Reconnaissance Office satellite is expected to be launched into orbit Wednesday from the California coast. The 235-foot Delta IV Heavy rocket is scheduled to lift off from Vandenberg Air Force Base at 10:52 a.m., according to United Launch Alliance (LMT/BA joint venture). The rocket is set to send a classified spacecraft into orbit for the NRO, which is in charge of U.S. intelligence-gathering satellites.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377698086025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377698599918-33</Id><Topic><Title>satellite launch today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377698086025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can watch the launch at United launch alliance website (google it).</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377698599918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377699196987-34</Id><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Msg>this stock should be at least 110. #$%$ ?</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377699864805-35</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be interesting to know what your mind set is/was in using "pool hall buddies" as people who don't give Obama respect. Never have I heard the use of "pool hall buddies" in such a manner on this message board or the words pool hall except for when I mentioned pool hall in the post "WWII vet, 88, beaten to death by black teens". Could it be your mind is trying to reconcile the dissonance in your feeble little brain over Shorty's death after he was murdered by Obama' sons.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377699864805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377699945732-36</Id><Topic><Title>Labor Unions Mad at Obama Adminstration Again</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377696068555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Post Double!</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377699945732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377700021808-37</Id><Topic><Title>Wife of George Zimmerman pleads guilty to perjury</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377698186691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The person who paid the ultimate price for being guilty was Trevan. A few more of these murderous thugs need to pay the ultimate price via attacking folks that are packin. And Colin Powell still trying to pursue the Zimmerman case while Blacks murder Blacks, and Whites by the droves....sad.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377700021808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377702630824-38</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Iv used that quote a dozen times on this board...favorite quote from our greatest President and the guy who understood individual liberty better then any man before or since.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377702630824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377702648005-39</Id><Topic><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get a grip man and don't worry about short term price fluctuations.</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1377702648005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377702650226-40</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377701477849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:51:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dance to a runcible tune. - Heather</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377702650226</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377703036637-41</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the war protestors?</Title><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1377652509513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you control the media, then you can control the libs. They are easily influenced by propaganda and have trouble thinking for themselves. Notice how MSNBC libs now support the war effort. What total hypocrates! Many will die from the bombing and many more will die by rebel hands, and Syria will sink into chaos like the other muslim countries we have attacked directly or by stealth. That should be good for Isreal. That's the plan and it's working it's way through the middle east and north africa, at least for now.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377703036637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377703391385-42</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the war protestors?</Title><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1377652509513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes a big difference when the WMDs are real.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1377703391385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:23:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377703657039-43</Id><Title>President al-Assad: “Syria will Never become a Western Puppet State”</Title><Msg>“Syria will Never become a Western Puppet State” that’s the real reason for the Western attack on Syria</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377703657039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377703961293-44</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377701477849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:51:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was thinking the Macarena!!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377703961293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377703974565-45</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the war protestors?</Title><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1377652509513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As 10s of thousands of Kurds and Iranians will attest to.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377703974565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377704014751-46</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you must be joking... you think Obama will attack Syria to make a point ?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377704014751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377704118519-47</Id><Topic><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cutt seems that yesterdays trades were tied in to the HFT. Todays action is there no volume sit back and buy the dips.</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377704118519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377705044958-48</Id><Topic><Title>Iranian Court Rejects Appeal from Jailed American Pastor, Obama Remains Silent on Case</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377627015760</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 14:10:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK then, drinking buddies. Pinochle buddies. Circle-jerk buddies. You know, like your side would say bath-house buddies. And you are no one to talk about feeble brains. I have said how I felt about this crime. Only right-fringers and racists like you feel the need to wallow in it.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377705044958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377705129048-49</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian strategy</Title><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377696811823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:33:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We know you'll have an anti-Obama explanation no matter what happens.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377705129048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377705171512-50</Id><Topic><Title>Labor Unions Mad at Obama Adminstration Again</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377696068555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you hate unions, so where does that leave you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377705171512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377705388587-51</Id><Topic><Title>Putin in Pink</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377652557959</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. That's awful old news to be mad about. Surely there's something from today? (The clown should have been suspended for a week or two, not banned. But don't try to tell me that in a free market with all that individual liberty floating around, the customers who protested aren't always right. That would be un-American and un-capitalist of you.)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377705388587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 11:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377706343678-52</Id><Title>Warren Buffet - getting into JCP</Title><Msg>There is a high probability that Warren B. may be buying shares of JCP. I would not sell now. Short % is high Hedge funds are buying big time. We'll see 18 dollars by December 2013.</Msg><Username>private.nguyen</Username><Timestamp>1377706343678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377706357352-53</Id><Title>super hornet</Title><Msg>ST. LOUIS, Aug. 28, 2013 – During three weeks of flight testing the Advanced Super Hornet, Boeing [NYSE: BA] and partner Northrop Grumman demonstrated that the fighter can outperform threats for decades to come with improvements that make the jet much harder for radar to detect and give it significantly more combat range. Through 21 flights in St. Louis and Patuxent River, Md., that began Aug. 5, the team tested conformal fuel tanks (CFT), an enclosed weapons pod (EWP), and signature enhancements, each of which can be affordably retrofitted on an existing Block II Super Hornet aircraft or included on a new jet.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377706357352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377707466300-54</Id><Topic><Title>Warren Buffet - getting into JCP</Title><Username>private.nguyen</Username><Timestamp>1377706343678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we'll see. Buy on the dip. In at 12.45</Msg><Username>private.nguyen</Username><Timestamp>1377707466300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377707486043-55</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the war protestors?</Title><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1377652509513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong war. Thought you put me on ignore?</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1377707486043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377707725124-56</Id><Topic><Title>Where are the war protestors?</Title><Username>fredjones801</Username><Timestamp>1377652509513</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right, the situation in the Middle East is irrelevant to Boeing, even though Saudi Arabia has 70 F-15s and Israel has 43.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377707725124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377707866054-57</Id><Topic><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA has been underperforming the market lately, put in a triple top, the trendline has shifted from positive to negative, and the volume technicals (OBV and TSV) have diverged. That plus a deterioration in the overall market indicates it's time to move up the stops on this trade. I usually get out early and let others take the increased risk of getting the next increment of profit.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1377707866054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377708120018-58</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian strategy</Title><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377696811823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:33:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their strategy is start a war get bombed then surrender then ask US for Billons to rebuild!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377708120018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377709908427-59</Id><Topic><Title>Does Genna Want Obama to Attack Syria?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377706107689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I don't. OK, putz?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377709908427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377709935729-60</Id><Topic><Title>Is Genna Experiencing PMS?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377705915516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would know all the symptoms.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377709935729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377709981205-61</Id><Topic><Title>Labor Unions Mad at Obama Adminstration Again</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377696068555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make your hatreds all too obvious/ Otherwise, why would you post this tripe?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377709981205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377710533397-62</Id><Topic><Title>Does Genna Want Obama to Attack Syria?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377706107689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>totally out of Character that the raven does not support every single white House talking point..... dont worry tho...next week he will say he was for the war before he was against it</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377710533397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377711126824-63</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes....to punish Assad for using Chemical weapons that Assanever even used ... but the real point is that I s r a e l will be appeased and profits for central bankers will increase...In other news Larry Summers is the leading candidate to replace Bernacke for the Federal Reserve....Just in case there are folks out there that doubt who Obama is working for</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377711126824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377711380903-64</Id><Topic><Title>Does Genna Want Obama to Attack Syria?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377706107689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What answer would calm your fevered thought process, Loon?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377711380903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:36:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377711663939-65</Id><Topic><Title>Is Genna Experiencing PMS?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377705915516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Genna is on the rag cause he is not getting the love and "respect he imagines he deserves"...he would be getting less public scorn but he hasnt figured out that usually respect is earned.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377711663939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377711777407-66</Id><Topic><Title>Kucinich: "striking Syria would turn the United States military into al-Qaeda's Air Force"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689917587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377711777407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377711881093-67</Id><Topic><Title>Is Genna Experiencing PMS?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377705915516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you tell me what response would make you happy, Loon? I'd be only too happy to do anything I could to help settle you down. You can tell ME. I crave your respect. Surely it cannot be that NOTHING would make you happy?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377711881093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377711939972-68</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I fought in my war, Floyd. You don't need to be so jealous.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377711939972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377712208904-69</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at Wesley Clark's talk with Amy Goodman 2 March 2007. Clark said he heard about the neocon agenda back in 2001: "Take out seven countries in five years, starting with Iraq, and then Syria, Lebanon, Libya, Somalia, Sudan and, finishing off, Iran." It's on Youtube. " General Wesley Clark: Wars Were Planned"</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377712208904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377712231626-70</Id><Topic><Title>satellite launch today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377698086025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Launch time is in about 13 minutes.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377712231626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377712558359-71</Id><Topic><Title>satellite launch today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377698086025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interestingly, the NRO facility near Dulles airport was evacuated during the attacks on 9/11.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377712558359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377712568762-72</Id><Topic><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, forgot to mention that insider selling is picking up including a whopper from Ray Conner and a mega whopper by J McNerney.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1377712568762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377712768383-73</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's changed since Jefferson's time is that now we have a huge corporate propaganda machine trying to convince us that liberty means freeing our beloved corporations from government regulation.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377712768383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 13:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377712833289-74</Id><Topic><Title>satellite launch today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377698086025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is one big #$%$ rocket. So is the payload capsule.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377712833289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377712853857-75</Id><Topic><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't blame people for converting their options from near lows and selling at near highs. It's part of how they get paid. You can blame the board for issuing those options if you want.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377712853857</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377712987381-76</Id><Title>Decisive Penetration of 50-day average</Title><Msg>The uptrend is definitely broken. MACD is turning negative for the first time since this rally started almost 6 months ago. And yet MFI is in nowhere near oversold territory.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377712987381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377713613249-77</Id><Topic><Title>satellite launch today</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377698086025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worked on some of those rocket parts. Even just a part can be quite large, and had to be covered up when not actually working on it.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377713613249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377713695980-78</Id><Topic><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right. But worry about changes in trend, and that's what we're looking at now.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377713695980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377713848415-79</Id><Topic><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I'm not assigning blame, my shares all came restricted stock units issued by Boeing. What I am saying is that if the senior managers start selling the stock could be reaching a top since they have access to information the rest of us don't. Like you said they are "selling at near highs". It's just one more fundamental indicator that investors need to pay attention to.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1377713848415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377713926730-80</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a childish question! We tried that. We get botulism in cans, we tainted meat, we get E Coli in our produce, we get poisonous pharmaceuticals, we get salmonella in our mayonnaise, we get killer automobiles, buildings that fall down, stock markets that are just circuses of swindle.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377713926730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377714033321-81</Id><Topic><Title>Kucinich: "striking Syria would turn the United States military into al-Qaeda's Air Force"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689917587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would have voted for Kucinich in 2008. I wouldn't vote for IBombYa.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377714033321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377714099452-82</Id><Title>ual launch completed</Title><Msg>great launch. More to come...</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377714099452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377714322015-83</Id><Topic><Title>Decisive Penetration of 50-day average</Title><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377712987381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:03:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA gave you 30% from March to June. Why get greedy? In the last two months it's given nothing.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377714322015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377714347996-84</Id><Topic><Title>Is Genna Experiencing PMS?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377705915516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kent Raven "Cry me a River" Spartacus ; "Build a Bridge and get over it"</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377714347996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377714506216-85</Id><Topic><Title>Kucinich: "striking Syria would turn the United States military into al-Qaeda's Air Force"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689917587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also shows the stupidity of the Phony Left right paradigm when Kucinich actually ACTS like a real old time anti war liberal....vrs the PRO War NeoCon Obama who acts without congressional authorization over the flimsiest of pretex's......</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377714506216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377714611899-86</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're funny tard.....we still get E Coli and meat tainted with Kangaroo meat after spending all that money on a false security provide by our FDA. There are plenty of private industry associations that can regulate their own industries far better than the government. They have a real incentive to because if they don't they'll go out of business and a competing association will take over. A government agency has no such incentive.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377714611899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377714848455-87</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries still increasing</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377633107373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 15:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now 48 planes, 2 more 737's delivered so far today, 5 test flights under way. British Air 787 is a B2 flight.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377714848455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:34:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377714923375-88</Id><Title>CARSON: MLK would be alarmed by black-on-black violence, lack of family values...</Title><Msg>It is hard to believe that 50 years have elapsed since the famous “I have a dream speech” of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. on the Mall in Washington. I was an 11-year-old child in Detroit languishing in the midst of poverty, but very interested in the strides that were being made in the civil rights movement. I was the only black kid in my seventh-grade class and over the previous two years had risen from the bottom of the class to the top. My mother had forced us to read, which had a profound positive effect on both my brother Curtis and myself. I was quite optimistic that things were getting better for black people in America. If King could be resurrected and see what was going on in America today, I suspect he would be extraordinarily pleased by many of the things he observed and disappointed by others. He, like almost everyone else, would be thrilled to know that there was a two-term black president of the United States of America and a black attorney general, as well as many other high government officials, business executives and university presidents. Perhaps just as thrilling would be the sight of black doctors, lawyers, airline pilots, construction foremen, news anchors, school superintendents and almost any other position imaginable in America. The fact that seeing blacks in such positions no longer raises eyebrows is a testimony to the tremendous progress that has been made in America over the last 50 years. There are some areas, however, where I suspect he might be less than thrilled. The epidemic of black-on-black violent crime indicates that there has been a significant deterioration of values in the black community. Not only are the lives of their fellow blacks and others being devalued by street thugs, but the lives of unborn babies are being destroyed in disproportionate numbers in the black community. There was a time when blacks were justifiably angry that the larger community discounted their value, but now, ironically, many members of the black community themselves place little or no value on these precious lives that are snuffed out without thought. I think King would be waging a crusade against the marginalization of black lives in America. Another area of great concern would be the fact that 73 percent of black babies are born out of wedlock. When this occurs, in most cases the educational pursuits of the mothers are terminated and the babies are condemned to a life of poverty and deprivation, which makes them more likely to end up in the penal system or the welfare system. This is a burden not only for the black community but for the nation at large. Although I believe King would be very concerned for all parties in these tragedies, his energies would be primarily channeled into an attempt to give these young women the kind of self-esteem that would preclude their yielding to the charms of individuals who really don’t care about them and are only interested in their selfish pleasures. King was a huge advocate of education and would be horrified by the high dropout rates in many inner-city high schools. He, like many others, was vilified, beaten and jailed for trying to open the doors of education to everyone, regardless of their race. If he were alive today, he would have to witness people turning their backs on those open doors and choosing to pursue lives of crime or dependency. I do not believe he would simply complain about these things, however. Rather, he would be raising funds to create programs that would show these young people that they do have real choices that can greatly enhance the quality of their lives. Perhaps the biggest disappointment for King would be the wholesale adoption of a victim mentality that makes people feel that they are entitled to being cared for by others rather than working tirelessly to create wealth and opportunities for their progeny. The amount of wealth that resides within the black community today is staggering. If the black community, like Jewish, Korean and other cultures in America, learned how to turn over dollars within their own community at least a couple of times before sending them out into the larger society, they would create wealth. I believe King would advocate such economic policies and would encourage those who benefit from the wealth to reach back and pull others up by providing jobs and opportunities. I think he would stress the fact that this kind of philosophy will foster freedom and independence for the black community, regardless of whether anybody else helps or not. Finally, we should all remember the aspect of his dream in which he desired that people should be judged by their character and not by the color of their skin. In part, this means no one should assume that a black person would adhere to certain political orthodoxy any more so than a white person would.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377714923375</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377715213141-89</Id><Title>MLK III BEMOANS 'STAGGERING' JOBLESSNESS AMONG BLACKS UNDER OBAMA</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) -- The eldest son of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. says blacks can rightfully celebrate his father's life and work with pride, but much more must be accomplished. Martin Luther King III, preparing to join ceremonies Wednesday commemorating the 50th anniversary of his father's "I Have a Dream" speech, says the country should confront "staggering unemployment" among black males 18 to 30 years old. He called Barack Obama's election as the first African-American president a major breakthrough for America. But King also told NBC's "Today" show in an interview that he believes young blacks today still "are first judged by their color and then the content of their character." King said his father deftly used the lofty words of the Founding Fathers "to inspire, lift up and bring hope."</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377715213141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377716596615-90</Id><Title>A Minority View on Equal Opportunity</Title><Msg>This week begins my 34th year serving on George Mason University's distinguished economics faculty. You might imagine my surprise when I received a letter from its Office of Equity and Diversity Services notifying me that I was required to "complete the in-person Equal Opportunity and Prevention of Sexual Harassment Policies and Procedures training." This is a leftist agenda for indoctrination, thought control and free speech suppression to which I shall refuse to submit. Let's look at it. Ideas such as equity and equal opportunity, while having high emotional value, are vacuous analytical concepts. For example, I've asked students whether they plan to give every employer an equal opportunity to hire them when they graduate. To a person, they always answer no. If they aren't going to give every employer an equal opportunity to hire them, what's fair about forcing employers to give them an equal opportunity to be hired? I'm guilty of gross violation of equality of opportunity, racism and possibly sexism. Back in 1960, when interviewing people to establish a marital contract, every woman wasn't given an equal opportunity. I discriminated against not only white, Indian, Asian, Mexican and handicapped women but men of any race. My choices were confined to good-looking black women. You say, "Williams, that kind of discrimination doesn't harm anyone!" Nonsense! When I married Mrs. Williams, other women were harmed by having a reduced opportunity set. George Mason's Office of Equity and Diversity Services has far more challenging equity and diversity work than worrying about the re-education of Professor Williams. They must know that courts have long held that gross racial disparities are probative of a pattern and practice of discrimination. The most notable gross racial disparity on campus, and hence probative of discrimination, can be found on GMU's fabulous men's basketball team. Blacks are less than 9 percent of student enrollment but are 85 percent of our varsity basketball team and dominate its starting five. It's not just GMU. Watch any Saturday afternoon college basketball game and ask yourself the question fixated in the minds of equity, diversity and inclusion hunters: Does this look like America? Among the 10 players on the court, at best there might be two white players. In 2010, 61 percent of Division I basketball players were black, and only 31 percent were white. Allied with the purveyors of equity, diversity and inclusion are the multiculturalists, who call for the celebration of cultures. For them, all cultures are morally equivalent and to deem otherwise is Eurocentrism. That's unbridled nonsense. Ask your multiculturalist: Is forcible female genital mutilation, as practiced in nearly 30 sub-Saharan Africa and Middle Eastern countries, a morally equivalent cultural value? Slavery is practiced in Sudan and Niger; is that a cultural equivalent? In most of the Middle East, there are numerous limits on women -- such as prohibitions on driving, employment, voting and education. Under Islamic law, in some countries, female adulterers face death by stoning, and thieves face the punishment of having their hand severed. Are these cultural values morally equivalent, superior or inferior to those of the West? Western values are superior to all others. Why? The greatest achievement of the West was the concept of individual rights. The Western transition from barbarism to civility didn't happen overnight. It emerged feebly -- mainly in England, starting with the Magna Carta of 1215 -- and took centuries to get where it is today. One need not be a Westerner to hold Western values. A person can be Chinese, Japanese, Jewish, African or Arab and hold Western values. It's no accident that Western values of reason and individual rights have produced unprecedented health, life expectancy, wealth and comfort for the ordinary person. Western values are under ruthless attack by the academic elite on college campuses across America. They want to replace personal liberty with government control and replace equality before the law with entitlement. The multiculturalism and diversity agenda is a cancer on our society, and our tax dollars and charitable donations are supporting it.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377716596615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377717042922-91</Id><Title>Black tea party members dispute racist claims</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON — Black members of the tea party movement on Wednesday rejected charges that the group's activists are racist, saying they oppose President Barack Obama because of his policies not his skin color. The members gathered at a Washington news conference in the wake of allegations about its rank and file, heightened by the recent split with a Tea Party Express leader who had posted a letter on his blog written from "Colored People" to Abraham Lincoln. The post suggested that black people would choose slavery over having to do real work. The black members said the racism that has been attributed to the tea party movement came from outsiders who infiltrated the groups to discredit their work and it should be rejected. "These people do not oppose Barack Obama because of his skin color. They oppose him because of his policies," said Lloyd Marcus, a spokesman for the group. The NAACP last month approved a resolution condemning racism within the tea party movement and called on activists to "repudiate the racist element and activities" within the political movement. At the news conference, several members assailed Obama and the Democrats, often in harsh terms. "Democrats have re-enslaved America," said Kevin Jackson, president of the Black Conservative Coalition. He said tea party activists, if successful, would reduce the size of government and set in motion another Emancipation Proclamation, the document that President Abraham Lincoln signed that effectively ended slavery. "This time, even the white folks get freed," said Jackson, who accused Obama of viewing fellow blacks as "mongrels." Democratic National Committee spokesman Hari Sevugan declined to respond to the tea party leaders' criticism. The White House also declined to comment. Other tea party speakers called Democrats white supremacists and elitists. Conservative Moms for America leader Mary Baker said Democrats were pushing "anti-God politics." "Destroy America. That's what the D in Democrat Party means," she said. Alan Keyes, who unsuccessfully ran for the U.S. Senate against Obama in 2004, said the president "got elected on a virulent form of racism" by exploiting his race during the 2008 campaign. The Tea Party Express, one of dozens of libertarian-leaning and anti-tax groups, organized the meeting with reporters to denounce racism and then accused its opponents of using allegations of racism to censor dissent.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377717042922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377717323909-92</Id><Topic><Title>Kucinich: "striking Syria would turn the United States military into al-Qaeda's Air Force"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689917587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's wars are fulfilling the neocon agenda expressed in 2001. To see the 2-minute youtube where Wesley Clark talk about this in 2007 with Amy Goodman, google clark wars planned</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377717323909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:15:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377717367705-93</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BB; "When are we going to recover from this disease of being the world's policeman?" Answer; when you recover from the disease of being a right wing Republican !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377717367705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377717541773-94</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the neo-toads are slightly behind schedule</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377717541773</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:19:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377717593461-95</Id><Topic><Title>MLK III BEMOANS 'STAGGERING' JOBLESSNESS AMONG BLACKS UNDER OBAMA</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377715213141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 14:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MLK's family had a civil suit in 1999 in which they alleged that James Earl Ray did not kill MLK, but instead he was killed by a conspiracy that involved the government. The jury found for the family after just 1 hour's deliberation.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377717593461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377717803684-96</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the case of Kuwait, they were attacked because Ambassador Glaspie told Saddam that we had no interest in his border disputes. She basically gave him the green light to invade.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377717803684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377717859726-97</Id><Topic><Title>BA going the wrong way</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1377699196987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:13:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See cutt one can't keep a good Company down!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377717859726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:24:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377717940916-98</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BB, what makes you think Palin was McCain's choice? Yes, undeniably she sabotaged his campaign, but I don't think the choice was his to make.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377717940916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377718027474-99</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama in Libya, and soon Obama in Syria. And already Obama in Somalia, Sudan, Iraq, Afghanistan, Pakistan, Yemen.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377718027474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377718120142-100</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with you Poor.....What some folks call Capitilism is often confused with CRONY capitilism...where all the insiders with all the information rule...I mentioned in an earlier post that Larry Summers, founder of the derivitives crises in 2008 is the next FED CHAIRMAN ...The Elite do not want freedom for us nor do they want a level playing field in the arena of Capitilism...they want raw power and they want to win and that means winning at any cost ..legal or illegal</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377718120142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377718239940-101</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"when you recover from the disease of being a right wing Republican !!" That would be too much to hope for on your part.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1377718239940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377718448693-102</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither Afghanistan nor Iraq turned out to be as easy to conquer as our racist military planners believed.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377718448693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:34:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377718531870-103</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then you should know better than to tolerate wars today that are every bit as dumb and pointless as that one was.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377718531870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377719394130-104</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How true Poor How true The Raven still thinks thinks North Vietnam fired actual torpedoes at American Warships in the gulf of Tonkin..</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377719394130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377719750808-105</Id><Title>The "teleprompter" and chief doing a great job....</Title><Msg>Reading off the monitor from his Berkley and NYU speech writers. Nothing said on the innercity disaster of single parent households, mass killings, welfare dependancy and culture, DEM controlled cities with flat out corruption of their city officials , ....etc and sitting in the front rows are the multi millionares from hollywood, music industry artists and politicians saying WOE is me, we need change for the little person with funding by the tax payer. No doubt MSNBC and their very few viewers will slurp up the coolaide and blame it all on Bush! OK I'm ready for the avalanche of thumbs down.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377719750808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377719769500-106</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the point of the war is to distract us from a coming economic meltdown?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377719769500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377719857180-107</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem is not the free market.....it's people who hate the idea of a free market and won't let it work.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377719857180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377720357809-108</Id><Title>Was Joe McCathy Right? Did Communists Infiltrate our Government?</Title><Msg>The witches were real! There were indeed Communists who had infiltrated the federal government. And there was every reason to believe that the officials responsible for the lapses of security that had permitted this infiltration were engaged in a cover-up intended to prevent anyone from learning whether these lapses were mere incompetence or rather, as many suspected, something far more sinister. Don’t lecture me about the “civil rights” of dishonest villains who were willing stooges of the murderous totalitarian Josef Stalin, and don’t tell me that the faults or errors of Joseph McCarthy made him worse than the Communists he sought to expose.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377720357809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377720373471-109</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your only motive for getting after the Federal government is to empower states rights so that you can take part in the crimes of the antibellum south such as vote suppression, ending all womens rights even suffrage, suppression of the coloreds in the south by imposing slavery or starvation wages but most of all a dicatatorial power for your favorite oligarchs ie the Kochs--- boy are you a POS</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377720373471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377720617820-110</Id><Topic><Title>Was Joe McCathy Right? Did Communists Infiltrate our Government?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377720357809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:05:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe McCarthy was an evil alcoholic with a rapidly deteriorating mental condition- even psychosis. He couldnt have spotted a real communist in a hundred years. To McCarthy socialism equaled communism which in reality it doesnt. McCarthy roused the ignorant and the hate filled populists do but he was totally unsuccessful</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377720617820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377720737889-111</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian strategy</Title><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377696811823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:33:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Martin Luther King would be disgusted with Obama. Read King's Riverside speech, the one that got him killed.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377720737889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377721050030-112</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think so too..or new evidence that is coming out about Obama giving bribes to the Muslim brotherhood.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377721050030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377721178448-113</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"That would be too much to hope for" thats what i said when moderates insist your guys are Human</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377721178448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377722186738-114</Id><Topic><Title>Was Joe McCathy Right? Did Communists Infiltrate our Government?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377720357809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:05:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being a victim of socialized government education, it's as obvious as it is understandable zosima has never heard of Alger Hiss.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1377722186738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377723523008-115</Id><Topic><Title>Black tea party members dispute racist claims</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377717042922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 15:10:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's strange to have so many black people in a racist organization.......maybe the real racist are those who scream the TEA Party is racist.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1377723523008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377724357621-116</Id><Topic><Title>Labor Unions Mad at Obama Adminstration Again</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377696068555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! Is the Government supposed to wait until airline passengers are served by only 2 or 3 different companies?</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1377724357621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377724825764-117</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven (DFC), likes the "Brotherhood".............</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377724825764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377724973097-118</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven's Facebook pic kind of looks like Foghorn Leghorn.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377724973097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377725039616-119</Id><Title>Surprise: Tim Scott Not Invited to Speak at Let Freedom Ring Ceremony</Title><Msg>Somehow, the only black Republican in the United States Senate wasn’t invited to speak at the ceremony commemorating the 50th anniversary of the March on Washington this afternoon. Perhaps there was some sort of oversight or something? The Wall Street Journal has the scoop: Wednesday’s event on the National Mall is not overtly political, but the early undertones were hard to ignore. A number of Democrats are set to address the crowd, including Mr. Obama and former presidents Bill Clinton and Jimmy Carter. Labor leaders also talked about the importance of mobilizing large groups of American workers – a key theme 50 years ago. And some speakers stressed the importance of preserving voting rights for all Americans. Mr. Bush was invited to attend the event, but he declined because he recently underwent surgery to place a stent in a blocked heart artery. Mr. Scott was not invited to speak, but a spokesman said, “The senator believes today is a day to remember the extraordinary accomplishments and sacrifices of Dr. King, Congressman John Lewis and an entire generation of black leaders.” I’ll leave you with this: How do say you admire MLK and then be so partisan as to not invite America's only black Senator?</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1377725039616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377725080770-120</Id><Topic><Title>Kucinich: "striking Syria would turn the United States military into al-Qaeda's Air Force"</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689917587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are the New NeoCons. The Kent Raven likes that.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377725080770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377725141904-121</Id><Topic><Title>Is Genna Experiencing PMS?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377705915516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He does appear to have a very bad case of PMS along with his acute Jetjockenvy................</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377725141904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377725197285-122</Id><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Msg>Capitalist and their fake Christian crusades are stealing from the working man, imprisoning the poor and Attacking Sovereign Nations</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377726024943-123</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is capitalism occurring......other than the capitol?</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1377726024943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377726305977-124</Id><Title>The Opposite of Capitalism is Socialism and the Legalization of Theft</Title><Msg>Socialism is just a stepping stone on the way to communism.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1377726305977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377726309264-125</Id><Title>Syrians scramble to hide from Obama's Humantiraian Love Bombs</Title><Msg>“Every neighborhood has some government target. Where do we hide?” Paul Joseph Watson August 28, 2013 Despite the US and Britain justifying an imminent attack on Syria in the name of “protecting civilians,” Syrians themselves are scrambling to hide from Obama’s humanitarian love bombs, with one Damascus resident telling Reuters, “We live in the capital. Every turn, every street, every neighborhood has some government target. Where do we hide?” Although a torrent of criticism has forced both Washington and London to move towards some kind of symbolic gesture involving the United Nations, a senior US official told NBC News today “we’re past the point of return” and that US air strikes against Syrian targets would inevitably occur “within days.” That leaves thousands of Syrians living in major cities already ravaged by nearly two years of civil war and western-backed Al-Qaeda terrorist attacks looking up to the skies in anticipation of a fresh delivery of cruise missiles – all in the name of “protecting civilians” of course. As Reuters reports, “dozens of military sites are mixed in among the civilian population,” meaning that western attacks will almost inevitably mean more loss of life, not to mention the wider threat of a new war in the Middle East. Syrians have now begun hoarding supplies, including water, batteries, and food, with “the fear in people’s eyes” all too visible, while banks have been inundated with customers attempting to withdraw all their money. People are fleeing in an effort to rent houses away from military sites, but many cannot afford skyrocketing prices in safer areas. “What about my friend?” asked a woman whose family was lucky enough to be lent a house in a safe area. “Her whole family lives in this neighborhood. There</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377726309264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377726804960-126</Id><Title>LBJ May have been more right than he Knew</Title><Msg>When Eisenhower offered his dedication to civil rights legislation in 1957, LBJ found himself conflicted, caught between his devotion to segregation and his ambition to become president. In the end, he remained loyal to both in that year, outwardly supporting the '57 civil rights bill while colluding with other Democrats like Richard Russell of Georgia in amending the bill "so as to minimize its impact," which ultimately watered it down enough that the bill evaporated in a heated legislative process. But by the time LBJ had become president, he recognized that efforts to desegregate the South were gaining popularity with unstoppable steam, so he seized the opportunity to outwardly champion civil rights. After the passage of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, which journalist Ronald Kessler recalls LBJ saying would ensure the "(censored N word)s voting Democrat for the next 200 years,"</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1377726804960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377726810974-127</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian strategy</Title><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377696811823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:33:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“A nation that continues year after year to spend more money on military defense than on programs of social uplift is approaching spiritual death.” “War is not the answer. Communism will never be defeated by the use of atomic bombs or nuclear weapons. Let us not join those who shout war and, through their misguided passions, urge the United States to relinquish its participation in the United Nations.” Martin Luther King..... (Compare Kings words to the War Criminal in the White House)</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377726810974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727016585-128</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>usually don't explain things to a toad - but i shall try We are witnessing transitions from social-welfare states to social-control states around the world. We are facing a global crisis that is unprecedented, given its magnitude, its global reach, the extent of ecological degradation and social deterioration, and the sheer scale of the means of violence. We truly face a crisis of humanity; we have entered a period of great upheavals, of momentous changes and uncertainties. This systemwide crisis is distinct from earlier such episodes of world crisis in the 1930s or the 1970s precisely because world capitalism is fundamentally different in the early 21st century. Among the qualitative shifts that have taken place in the capitalist system in the face of globalization in recent decades, there are four I want to underscore. First is the rise of truly transnational capital and the integration of every country into a new globalized production and financial system. Second is the appearance of a new transnational capitalist class (TCC). This is a class group grounded in new global circuits of accumulation rather than the older national circuits. Third is the rise of what I term transnational state apparatuses. And fourth is the appearance of novel relations of inequality and domination in global society, including an increasing importance of transnational social and class inequalities relative to North-South</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377727016585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727094680-129</Id><Topic><Title>The Opposite of Capitalism is Socialism and the Legalization of Theft</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1377726305977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:45:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If government controls everything in a socialist society like consumer pricing, Manufacturing and retail will dry up in America because companies will decrease making consumer staples for fear of lost profits, or worse yet, taking greater losses. Companies usually reinvest profits back into the company, but if profits are lost, reinvesting will slow or come to a stop. To compete, reinvesting is necessary.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1377727094680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727101489-130</Id><Topic><Title>Was Joe McCathy Right? Did Communists Infiltrate our Government?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople3</Username><Timestamp>1377720357809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:05:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worse. K lan did.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1377727101489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377727288581-131</Id><Title>Bombshell: Evidence Syrian Rebels Carried Out Gas Attack</Title><Msg>“It’s one of the most serious moments in world history US has ever faced” Julie Wilson August 28, 2013 In an interview with Alex Jones, American author and political commentator Dr. Jerome R. Corsi confirmed that Syrian rebels were behind the sarin gas attack in Syria last week. Video evidence and reliable Middle Eastern sources on the ground, Corsi says, prove Syrian rebels launched the attack in an attempt to take over the Syrian government. He believes if the United States moves towards war with Syria it will surely result in World War 3. After news broke of the alleged chemical weapons attack, Secretary of State John Kerry took to the stage giving a speech in which he called the attack a “cowardly crime” and a moral “obscenity.” Kerry claims to have “undeniable” proof of the Syrian government’s guilt, however unsurprisingly he failed to offer it to the public. In an interview with a Russian newspaper, Syrian President Bashar Assad called the allegations “preposterous” and “completely politicized,” reported the LA Times. “How is it possible that any country would use chemical weapons, or any weapons of mass destruction, in an area where its own forces are located?” Corsi argues several reasons for the US not to go to war with Syria. First off, the US cannot financially or economically sustain another war. “Russia and China are not borrowing $1 trillion a year to make their budget, and the world knows it,” said Corsi. Secondly, public opinion is not there, and it’s most likely not going to get there. “The ramifications of getting into a shooting match with Russia and China is unpredictable,” said Dr. Corsi. “Risking a confrontation with Russia and possibly China is quite frightening and would become one of the most serious moments in US history.” When Alex asked Dr. Corsi</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377727288581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727332948-132</Id><Topic><Title>Bombshell: Evidence Syrian Rebels Carried Out Gas Attack</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377727288581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how Obama plans to get away with starting a war like this, he said Obama probably intends to continue “lying with impunity.” A report by WND reveals evidence assembled from various Middle Eastern sources that “cast doubt on Obama administration claims the Assad government is responsible for last week’s attack.” WND’s report says two YouTube videos show what looks like “Syrian rebel forces loading a canister of nerve gas on a rocket to fire presumably at civilians and possibly government forces.” (google it...its true) A screen capture from a Syrian TV report shows a chemical agent that appears to have been made in a “Saudi factory.” Another report from RT illustrates “captured rebel arsenals apparently with chemical agents manufactured in Saudi Arabia and gas masks,” support Russian claims that rebels are the culprits. The report further states that an intercepted phone call between a terrorist affiliated with the rebel civilian militia and his Saudi Arabian boss indicates Syrian terrorists, not the Assad government, were behind the chemical weapons attack. “The Syrian terrorist told him that one of the achievements of his “battalion” was the use of chemical weapons in Deir Ballba. “The recorded phone call disclosed the cooperation between two terrorist groups in Syria to bring two bottles of Sarin Gas from the Barzeh neighborhood in Damascus,” reported WND.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377727332948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377727395352-133</Id><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Msg>Where are the Atheist Hospitals, Libraries, orphanages and Schools......oops they do have public education.</Msg><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727662273-134</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love capitalism and it is making me wealthy. All my close friends from childhood are doing amazing under capitalism. If it isn't working for you maybe there is something wrong with you. Maybe you aren't a hard worker or motivated? Maybe you should take a hard look in the mirror for the real problem if capitalism hasn't rewarded you.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377727662273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727743040-135</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Speech: He hit the ball out of the park</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377721982834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:33:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now you can get your knee pads out again.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377727743040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727784174-136</Id><Topic><Title>Bombshell: Evidence Syrian Rebels Carried Out Gas Attack</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377727288581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven likes that.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377727784174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727803922-137</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why stop at 20 years Bob? From Infoplease World War II was the last war fought in which the President asked Congress for a declaration of war. Since then, United States armed forces have been in combat several times, including the following: Truman (D) 1950-1953 Korean War Communist North Korea, supported by China, invades non-communist South Korea. UN forces, principally made up of U.S. troops, fight to protect South Korea. The Korean War is the first armed conflict in the global struggle between democracy and communism, called the Cold War. Kennedy (D) 1961 Cuba The U.S. orchestrates the ill-fated Bay of Pigs invasion, an unsuccessful attempt by Cuban exiles to overthrow Fidel Castro's communist regime in Cuba. Kennedy (D) Johnson (D) Nixon (R) 1961-1973 Vietnam War In 1955, communist North Vietnam invades non-communist South Vietnam in an attempt to unify the country and impose communist rule. The United States joins the war on the side of South Vietnam in 1961, but withdraws combat troops in 1973. In 1975 North Vietnam succeeds in taking control of South Vietnam. The Vietnam War is the longest conflict the U.S. ever fought and the first war it lost. Johnson (D) 1965 Dominican Republic U.S. president Lyndon Johnson sends marines and troops to quash a leftist uprising; he fears the Dominican Republic might follow in the footsteps of Cuba and turn communist. Reagan (R) 1982 Lebanon U.S. troops form part of a multinational peacekeeping force to help the fragile Lebanese government maintain power in the politically volatile country. In 1983 241 U.S. Marines and 60 French soldiers are killed by a truck bomb. The multinational force withdraws in 1984. Reagan (R) 1983 Grenada U.S. President Ronald Reagan invades the Caribbean island nation of Grenada to overthrow its socialist government, which has close ties with Cuba. A U.S. peace-keeping force remains until 1985.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1377727803922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727824817-138</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush 1 (R) 1989 Panama U.S. President George H. W. Bush invades Panama and overthrows Panamanian dictator and drug-smuggler Manuel Noriega. Noriega is later tried and convicted on a number of charges, and is imprisoned in the United States. Bush 1 (R) 1991 Gulf War (Kuwait and Iraq) Iraq invades the country of Kuwait. The Gulf War begins and ends swiftly when a U.S.-led multinational force comes to Kuwait's aid and expels dictator Saddam Hussein's forces. Clinton (D) 1993 Somalia A U.S.-led multinational force attempts to restore order to war-torn Somalia so that food can be delivered and distributed within the famine-stricken country. Clinton (D) 1994 Haiti After Haiti's democratically elected president Jean-Bertrand Aristide is ousted in a coup in 1991, a U.S. invasion three years later restores him to power. Clinton (D) 1994-1995 Bosnia During the Bosnian civil war, which begins shortly after the country declares independence in 1992, the U.S. launches air strikes on Bosnia to prevent ethnic cleansing. It becomes a part of NATO's peacekeeping force in the region. Clinton (D) 1999 Kosovo Yugoslavia's province of Kosovo erupts in war in the spring of 1999. A U.S.-led NATO force intervenes with air strikes after Slobodan Milosevic's Serbian forces uproot the population and embark on a plan of ethnic cleansing of Kosovo's ethnic Albanian population. Bush 2 (R) 2001— Afghanistan The Taliban government harbored Osama bin Laden and the al-Qaeda terrorist group, responsible for the Sept. 11, 2001, attacks on the United States. After Afghanistan refused to turn over Bin Laden, the U.S. and UN coalition forces invaded. The Taliban government was ousted and many terrorist camps in Afghanistan were destroyed. Thereafter, the Taliban begin regrouping. By 2005, the Taliban and coalition troops are it was engaged in ongoing clashes with coaltition troops. The year 2006 was the deadliest year for U.S. soldiers in Afghanistan since 2001. Bush 2 (R) 2003— Iraq War The U.S. and Great Britain invade Iraq and topple the government of dictator Saddam Hussein. The U.S. engagement in Iraq continues for the next several years amid that country's escalating violence and fragile political stability.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1377727824817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377727956514-139</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your job cleaning toilets at walmart doesn't count as being wealthy !!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377727956514</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377728544320-140</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Policy on Syria</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377639720966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 17:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently you don't believe we've had a genuine Republican as President since Herbert Hoover. My own opinion is that we haven't had a real Republican president since Theodore Roosevelt. BTW if you want to learn about machine politics and political corruption in both parties, read Edmond Morris stunning 3 part biography of the utterly incorruptible TR and you will realize that absolutely nothing has changed.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1377728544320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377728863760-141</Id><Topic><Title>Bombshell: Evidence Syrian Rebels Carried Out Gas Attack</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377727288581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this starts World War III, and China and Russia get involved (some would say the Global Elite WANT to do this), then assuming we avod thermonuclear war, then at the lease the Good Old boys will bend over and lick the Governments boots and say "protect me..kill the Russians...take my rights..take my guns"...after all ...ALL the laws are in place for a Police State anyway....that is best case...worst case is all life on earth is destroyed.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377728863760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377728914350-142</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did clean toilet bowls when I started working at age 16. There is no shame in cleaning toilets because its honest work and it's better than taking hand outs. You sound elitist yet you're a failure in a system that rewards performance and whining like a child going through the terrible twos. Why is that? Why are you whining? Why are you doing so poorly in such a great system?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377728914350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377729067122-143</Id><Topic><Title>Barack Obama's Speech: He hit the ball out of the park</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377721982834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 16:33:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No honorable mention for the 3 teleprompters with battery back up. speech writers and the staff on emergency standby with ear piece to coach him thru ? this has been a longstanding joke from the Late night shows for years now. He is also just as good as Jesse Jackson when reading the "cat in the hat" rimes from the grinch who stole christmas.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377729067122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:31:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377729126183-144</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It certainly would make a lot more room for Spotted Owls and Kangaroo rats.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377729126183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377729131004-145</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalism sucking the life out of America !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1377725197285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 17:26:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever owned your own business? If not why not?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377729131004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377729325579-146</Id><Topic><Title>Bombshell: Evidence Syrian Rebels Carried Out Gas Attack</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377727288581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:01:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven likes that........as long as he doesn't have to go.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377729325579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377729790220-147</Id><Topic><Title>Does Genna Want Obama to Attack Syria?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377706107689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this gets as bad as it just might with China and Russia....we could have far bigger problems</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377729790220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377729820923-148</Id><Topic><Title>22 Reasons why starting war with Syria is a Real bad idea</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377689220363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 07:27:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377729820923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377731214929-149</Id><Topic><Title>Syrian strategy</Title><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377696811823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:33:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“A nation that continues year after year to spend more money on military defense than on programs of social uplift is approaching spiritual death.” “War is not the answer. Communism will never be defeated by the use of atomic bombs or nuclear weapons. Let us not join those who shout war and, through their misguided passions, urge the United States to relinquish its participation in the United Nations.” Martin Luther King..... (Compare Kings words to the War Criminal in the White House) Needs to be emphasized</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377731214929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377731378975-150</Id><Topic><Title>Kucinich: USA Will Become 'al-Qaeda's air force'...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377652608490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a Proxy war with Russia right now....and NO we do NOT have the moral high ground</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377731378975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377731593833-151</Id><Title>At least during the Cuban Missle Crises JFK showed the evidence of Missles in Cuba</Title><Msg>...and America kept the Moral High Ground....this time around with a Nuclear Confrontation with Russia and China over the False Flag chemical weapons attack carried out by AlQaeda (that Obama is supporting) ....we no longer have the moral hi ground....and both Kerry and Obama REFUSE to show the evidence to the world......The US has really fallen in the eyes of the world since those early days in 62.....and we may not be so lucky this time</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377731593833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733038244-152</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just think how bad it would be if there were no regulation. Weasel meat? Tastes just like chicken. Slug meat? Moist and nutritious.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377733038244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733302465-153</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did the Supreme Court rule that corporations can push their agenda anonymously (through super packs)?? So that consumers could NOT no which corporations to blame for their contributions to DS candidates and platforms. -- In other words, the Supreme Court prevented the free market from responding to their politics</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377733302465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:41:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733543146-154</Id><Topic><Title>Does Genna Want Obama to Attack Syria?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377706107689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't answer that question until the Loon tells me what he'd like me to say.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377733543146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733707430-155</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cannot answer that question until you tell me what you would like me to say.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377733707430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733726196-156</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do know that many community organizations are also corporations that do the same thing. Look how Obama got to the White House.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377733726196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733781076-157</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think I do tolerate such wars? Is this a case of you rejecting what I have posted and making up something you wish I had posted?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377733781076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733809121-158</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you refuse to answer the question, how about a Syrian war cry???</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377733809121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:50:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733850344-159</Id><Topic><Title>Kucinich: USA Will Become 'al-Qaeda's air force'...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377652608490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 21:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven would beg to differ.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377733850344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377733853669-160</Id><Title>I like it when hoozdik has to talk to himself</Title><Msg>He's the only one stupid enough to listen to himself.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377733853669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733893755-161</Id><Topic><Title>Does Genna Want Obama to Attack Syria?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377706107689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven likes that.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377733893755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377733915636-162</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure that was a rhetorical question, but even if not, I can't answer until Spartaloon tells me what answer I should make that would NOT bring him to a 3-foot hover.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377733915636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377734046797-163</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Floyd. I can't answer until Sparty tells me what answer will not rile him up.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377734046797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377734107343-164</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't speak Syrian. If you do, I think the FBI should take a look at you.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377734107343</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377734155691-165</Id><Topic><Title>"When governments fear the people, there is liberty. When the people fear the government, there is tyranny.</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377700850744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what happens when activist Supreme Court justices start legislating from the bench.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377734155691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:55:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377734224679-166</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC will be broadcasting the MLK I have a dream speech at the top of the hour</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377733982492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox is still outraged about Miley Cyrus.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377734224679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377734676712-167</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds about right. Atilla the Hun, Genghis Khan, Hitler, Stalin, Mao, Pol Pot, Castro, Che Guerra......not to mention the American Democrat party enabling the killing of 40 million innocent babies.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377734676712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377734953059-168</Id><Topic><Title>Why pursue Snowden when Obama 'is giving away plan of attack to anyone?'</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1377695690479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 09:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a hypocrite? A flip flopper? Or just an idiot?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377734953059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377735391251-169</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC will be broadcasting the MLK I have a dream speech at the top of the hour</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377733982492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think that Miley Cyrus is more important than the MLK speech?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377735391251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377735495043-170</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC will be broadcasting the MLK I have a dream speech at the top of the hour</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377733982492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had a dream about Miley Cyrus tongue around my *****!</Msg><Username>don_cornwell</Username><Timestamp>1377735495043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377735523547-171</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I feel I can leave that to arrogant hot-shots like you, Floyd. Now buzz off.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377735523547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377735567627-172</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377735567627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377736304086-173</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries still increasing</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377633107373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 15:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now 49 planes. 787 L/N 21 delivered</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377736304086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377736485096-174</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go kill Syrians, then, jet jock. Let us know if you come back with a DFC.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377736485096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377736531147-175</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC will be broadcasting the MLK I have a dream speech at the top of the hour</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377733982492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did it make THAT blue, too?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377736531147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377737184016-176</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not yet, floyd. But keep hoping; perhaps soon you and mouseturd will get a chance to punch your ticket, win promotion and medals, and generally just justify your miserable retrograde existence.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377737184016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377737987977-177</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC will be broadcasting the MLK I have a dream speech at the top of the hour</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377733982492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean MS DNC- home of racist Al Sharpton et al .. ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377737987977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377738802612-178</Id><Topic><Title>WHATS THE POINT OF THE COMING WAR ?</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377681540797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 05:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm- since we have now released the target list, weapon types, timetable we must be waiting for assad to send his notice back that he has 1) Bunched up his helicopters in groups of 10 at one end of the runway xx, and likewise bunched up his other jet aircraft at the other end- using no more than three runways for that grouping. And please put large red flags on all missile launch sites, and use only one runway for groupingm his tanks and armored vechiles. Would he then make no more than three weapons cache of everything larger than ak -47 and pistols Since we are opertating under the OBAMA sequester rules, I'm shure Assad realizes we must get the gbiggest bang for the buck with our cruise missles and drone use. The saudies have agreed to give us free JP-4 fuel, and the turks have lent us use of their airfields to help meet budget guidelines. Italy has agreed to provide wine, french champange, and the brits have agreed to give us a free hip hip horray after the third day. Awaiting your timely response - in solidarity I am Barack HUSSEIN OBAMA Alllah uh akbar bro !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377738802612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 21:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377740318241-179</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here's Your #$%$ Moment of the Day...</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377737743653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 20:55:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably another local Republican pseudo-Christian leader.</Msg><Username>jumboyjetski</Username><Timestamp>1377740318241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 21:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377740950834-180</Id><Topic><Title>Atheists havew Killed more people than all Religions Combined</Title><Username>marxbouncers</Username><Timestamp>1377727395352</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dont know about Atilla the Hun but Genghis Khan was a Buddhist Hitler grew up Roman Catholic and became a pagan at least Stalin grew up in the Eastern Rite of the Catholic Church and only left after he became an adult Mao was a Buddhist Pol Pot belonged to an animalistic religeous sect Castro grew up to be a Catholic and is believed to have practiced his religeon in adulthood Che Gueverra grew up to be a Catholic but it isnt known if he continued to practice his religion The American Democrat party may be a majority Catholic and largly practices its religion. The RWNJ'S have opposed abortion at every turn and have brought about the deaths of countless women who have been forced to the back alley abortionist and due to shoddy procedures paid with their lives and their healthl The loonatik RWNJ crowd believe that life begins at conception- but if that is so then it actually begins before conception and masterbation constitutes abortion- which makes 100 percent of the lifers guilty of abortion themselves Modern ethics experts have made it clear that prior to the 24'th week the fetus may be aborted but after that time it is to be considered too near birth and should therefor be allowed to be taken to term and to birth IT ALL BOILS DOWM TO THE FACT THAT PAY4ITYOURSELF IS A LIAR A WANNABE MURDERER HIMSELF AND AN IGNORAMOUS ABOUT THE HISTORY OF LEADERS HE CLAIMS TO KNOW</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377740950834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 21:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377741412250-181</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats - Party of Bigots, Race pimps and Enslavers</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377733182163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:39:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many republican senators were invited to the MLK event?? pay4 you are an evil dishonist rabel rouser that ought to be hauled off to prison before little children hear your propaganda and are influenced to grow up to be mass murderers</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377741412250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 21:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377744721319-182</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats - Party of Bigots, Race pimps and Enslavers</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377733182163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:39:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad day for civil rights. Dr. King would have been shocked to see how the radical left celebrated his day. king was the champion of bringing the races together, and mixed no words about the Black Communities responsibility to seeing that happens. Today'.s gathering looked like a far left Dem convention. Civil Rights laws have been enacted, and laws are not the problem. It is the radical left running the Dem Party that won't address the social issues that are destroying the Black Community.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377744721319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 22:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377746864191-183</Id><Topic><Title>Does Genna Want Obama to Attack Syria?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1377706107689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump for poordumb, who so wishes I'd said something different.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377746864191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 23:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377746961589-184</Id><Topic><Title>deliveries still increasing</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377633107373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-27 15:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG! An OT post on the BA message board. What is the world comming to? Keep it up, we may win yet. Since I retired, I haven't had much real news on Boeing.</Msg><Username>seattle_native_45</Username><Timestamp>1377746961589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 23:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>