<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377407142167-1</Id><Topic><Title>More strange things Louisiana Republicans believe</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377391747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 20:49:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama blames Bush for all these things and even claimed Bush turned him gay.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1377407142167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 01:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377409461762-2</Id><Topic><Title>The right’s black crime obsession</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377389856827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 20:17:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only Loons pick and choose which words someone ELSE chooses to call "well said."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377409461762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 01:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377410091512-3</Id><Title>NY sues big birther</Title><Msg>ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York's attorney general sued Donald Trump for $40 million Saturday, saying the real estate mogul helped run a phony "Trump University" that promised to make students rich but instead steered them into expensive and mostly useless seminars, and even failed to deliver promised apprenticeships. Attorney General Eric Schneiderman says many of the 5,000 students who paid up to $35,000 thought they would at least meet Trump but instead all they got was their picture taken in front of a life-size picture of "The Apprentice" TV star. Sometimes, you get what you pay for! Har har har har</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377410091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 01:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377423211585-4</Id><Title>787-9 rollout</Title><Msg>. EVERETT, Wash., Aug. 24, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing [NYSE: BA] has completed the first 787-9 Dreamliner. The second member of the super-efficient 787 family rolled out of the Everett, Wash., factory today to the flight line, where teams are preparing it to fly later this summer. At 20 feet (6 m) longer than the 787-8, the 787-9 will extend the 787 family in both capacity and range, carrying 40 more passengers an additional 300 nautical miles (555 km). The 787-9 leverages the visionary design of the 787-8 such as its exceptional environmental performance — 20 percent less fuel use and 20 percent fewer emissions than similarly sized airplanes — and passenger-pleasing features. With the second and third airplanes in final assembly, Boeing and the 787-9 are on track. First delivery to launch customer Air New Zealand is set for mid-2014. Neg. K65965_003</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1377423211585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 05:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377423426520-5</Id><Topic><Title>Aug. delivery status</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377381015147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 17:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA is firing on all cylinders!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1377423426520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 05:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377427460079-6</Id><Title>Boeing loves to play dumb!</Title><Msg>When Elon Musk of Tesla called Boeing when they were having problems with their Lithium Ion batteries on the 787, he was trying to help Boeing go to the next level in battery technology. Boeing didn't listen to him because of their arrogance. Well Boeing, TSLA stock is kicking #$%$!</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1377427460079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 06:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377433209615-7</Id><Topic><Title>R.I.P. "waynedickenson961" Yahoo ID</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377239998357</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-23 02:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember how he stuck the landing on touchdown? That was really something to see. The U.S. Olympic Team was so impressed they asked him to try out for the gymnastics team, which of course he made with ease. It turned out that his gymnastic skills were so good, especially on the uneven bars and the balance beam, that they eventually made him team leader. Americans everywhere were ecstatic as he took home not only the individual all-around gold, but led the U.S. team to a gold medal in a stunning, come-from-behind victory over the Soviet Union. If only I had 1% of Wayne's skill and talent, just think where I'd be now. ROFL!!!!!</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1377433209615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 08:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377434375084-8</Id><Topic><Title>The right’s black crime obsession</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377389856827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 20:17:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only Parrots refuse to see the reeking hypocrisy</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377434375084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 08:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377435533574-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Bono Richer than Paul McCartney</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1377206411707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-22 17:20:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll go you one better......Hendrix was Breitbarted, Jim Morrison was Breitbarted, Seal Team six was Breitbarted, Pat Tillman was Breitbarted, Michael Hastings was Breitbarted and Breitbart was Breitbarted.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377435533574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 08:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377435644097-10</Id><Topic><Title>The right’s black crime obsession</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377389856827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 20:17:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only Parrots refuse to see the reeking hypocrisy I had to say that twice ...and with emphasis...just in case you miss it the first time..</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377435644097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 09:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377436425586-11</Id><Topic><Title>The Dream Did Not Come Free</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377300816430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-23 19:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Colin Powell is an embarrassment. Once regarded as a person of high values, and leadership he's caved in, and just another socialist that preaches Black victimization.that continues to destroy Black advancements. 70% of Blacks born out of wedlock, and that more than doubles any other race. And it will get worse with people like Colin Powell representing them.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377436425586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 09:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377436847550-12</Id><Topic><Title>The right’s black crime obsession</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377389856827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 20:17:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why it is rightly talked about, and Black leaders like Juan Williams are constantly talking about it, and they are not Republicans....they are liberals, is because it is dragging down society, and the economy. liberals spending welfare dollars that are tax payer dollars to correct the problem, and only increasing the problem while creating a lot of rich liberal bureaucrats needs to get talked about. Both Jesse, and Al are very wealthy, and they created their wealth at the expense of their race...the lowest form of life...called a hooz lowlife.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377436847550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 09:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377440839835-13</Id><Topic><Title>The right’s black crime obsession</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377389856827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 20:17:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spin it all you want. Fact is, the truth never works out very well for you leftys. That's why you insist on politically correct thought. That's the best way to cover up the truth. People are getting tired of the BS though and maybe you guys have pushed that game too far.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377440839835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 10:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377441082949-14</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing loves to play dumb!</Title><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1377427460079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 06:44:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think they are playing dumb. That's just the way they are.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377441082949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 10:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377441220438-15</Id><Topic><Title>Racism Helps Define The Tea Party</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376611878826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 20:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, They are obviously the real racists.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377441220438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 10:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377441507165-16</Id><Topic><Title>Racism Helps Define The Tea Party</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376611878826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-15 20:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually it does have something to do with Boeing. Boeing is a company loaded with lefty nitwits like this. That's one reason why they are failing.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377441507165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 10:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377441990383-17</Id><Topic><Title>Why You Can't Have a Rational Conversation With the Left</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1377291670835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-23 17:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think of they as children. I think of them as dead bone stupid and totally delusional.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1377441990383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 10:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377442894640-18</Id><Title>DOD Manual now lists Extremist Groups as those who talk about Individual Liberty</Title><Msg>For a few years I thought it couldn't happen here....it IS happening here.. Conservative watchdog group Judicial Watch recently obtained a Department of Defense training manual which lists people who embrace “individual liberties” and honor “states’ rights,” among other characteristics, as potential “extremists” who are likely to be members of “hate groups.” dodmanMarked “for training purposes only,” the documents, obtained Thursday through a Freedom of Information Act request submitted in April, include PowerPoint slides and lesson plans, among which is a January 2013 Air Force “student guide” distributed by the Defense Equal Opportunity Management Institute simply entitled “Extremism.” Judicial Watch’s FOIA request asked for “Any and all records concerning, regarding, or related to the preparation and presentation of training materials on hate groups or hate crimes distributed or used by the Air Force.” As the group notes, “The document defines extremists as ‘a person who advocates the use of force or violence; advocates supremacist causes based on race, ethnicity, religion, gender, or national origin; or otherwise engages to illegally deprive individuals or groups of their civil rights.’” The manual goes on to bar military personnel from “active participation” in such extremist organization activities as “publicly demonstrating,” “rallying,” “fundraising” and “organizing,” basically denying active-duty military from exercising the rights they so ardently fight to defend. It begins its introduction of a section titled, “Extremist ideologies,” by describing the American colonists who sought independence from British rule as a historical example of extremism. “In U.S. history, there are many examples of extremist ideologies and movements. The colonists who sought to free themselves from British rule and the Confederate states who sought to secede from the Northern states are just two examples,” according to the training guide.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377442894640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 11:01:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377443227739-19</Id><Title>Obama moving toward YET ANOTHER Undeclared War in Syria</Title><Msg>Off the World News Desk: Hagel Suggests Pentagon Moving Naval Forces Closer To Syria “ABOARD A MILITARY AIRCRAFT OVER THE PACIFIC -- The Pentagon is moving naval forces closer to Syria in preparation for a possible decision by President Barack Obama to order military strikes, Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel suggested on Friday. Hagel declined to describe any specific movements of U.S. forces. He said Obama asked that the Pentagon to prepare military options for Syria and that some of those options "requires positioning our forces." U.S. Navy ships are capable of a variety of military action, including launching Tomahawk cruise missiles, as they did against Libya in 2011 as part of an international action that led to the overthrow of the Libyan government. "The Defense Department has a responsibility to provide the president with options for contingencies, and that requires positioning our forces, positioning our assets, to be able to carry out different options – whatever options the president might choose," Hagel said.”</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377443227739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 11:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377445954341-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama moving toward YET ANOTHER Undeclared War in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377443227739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 11:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>US Set to Launch ‘Iraq, The Sequel’, in Syria Daniel McAdams Ron Paul Institute August 25, 2013 If you liked the run up to the US attack on Iraq, with the lurid fictional tales of mobile chemical weapons labs and Saddam’s nukes, you will love “Iraq, The Sequel”, currently unfolding in Syria. It is everything the interventionists have been hoping for: a heady brew of Kosovo, Iraq, and Libya all rolled into one. The possibility for an infinitely more toxic conflagration is exponentially higher, to boot, adding for the interventionists much excitement to the mix. Here is the latest: A fourth US warship capable of launching the type of cruise missiles that turned Libya to rubble and paved the way for al-Qaeda affiliates to take control of that country is now rushing to the waters off of Syria, ready to unleash destruction. Chuck Hagel, who some antiwar commentators foolishly believed would put an end to Washington’s military adventurism, is feverishly preparing plans for President Obama to attack. The media worldwide, interventionist to the core, is pushing willing leaders in the US, France, and the UK to finally treat Syria to another devastating “liberation.” What has prompted this sudden dramatic move just over the past few days toward a Western invasion of Syria? A pretext. A claimed chemical attack near Damascus that has produced, according to an estimate from Médecins Sans Frontières, perhaps some 300 deaths. It is unclear whether a bona fide chemical attack has taken place, and it is even more unclear who might be responsible should the attack indeed be the work of some chemical agent. Yet all of a sudden another Washington/Paris/London war is to be set in motion. How banal the triggers for war have become. Almost like a video game. Somehow we are supposed to believe that within 72 hours after the arrival of a UN chemical weapons inspectio</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377445954341</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 11:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377447042216-21</Id><Title>I'm SICK of hearing this excrement about RACE day after day on this board</Title><Msg>...as if this is the PRIMARY problem this country faces.....The country is racing toward another war with Syria and the Bankers are getting to steal our pension funds and the Water and the air and the vaccines and the food is FILLED with toxins (on purpose).....YOU HAD BETTER WAKE UP TO WHATS GOING ON FOLKS</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377447042216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377447399726-22</Id><Title>Bunch of idiots!</Title><Msg>This board has turned into a political forum. Time to stick to the major topic here, BA!</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1377447399726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377447799888-23</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus99991 states Wayne is right TSLA is better than Boeing as an investment here is his quote, TSLA up 423% BA 49%</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377371116943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 15:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991, and yet you refuse to admit that this is you stating a fact, tsla is better than Boeing a clear fact, it has nothing to do with any other statement , your already off topic. as cbx said, go ahead use your spin tactics, take a year and go for it I do not care what you do. first I beat you with apple then acad and now tsla , if you want to move to crapola as if I do not know your moves go for it I have seen your crapola for over 10 years . your an orange county loser only doubling your money while tesla is up 7 times its current value in just over 3 years . facts Boeing sucks, airbus is better both are not as good a apple was , as acad is and as tsla is I am a stock trader and make great calls your are a little man with no stock trade skills so you use story telling to what somehow take something away from how great tsla has done for me and acad too. go for it little man demonstrated your fools folly</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377447799888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377448965470-24</Id><Title>Just got in from kennebunkport</Title><Msg>great weather, fishing, drinks and seafood!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377448965470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377450005753-25</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus99991 states Wayne is right TSLA is better than Boeing as an investment here is his quote, TSLA up 423% BA 49%</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377371116943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 15:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>attention Spartacus 99991, get up, its your turn to spin, the story,! I have a comparison of tsla to boeing for the worst 3 weeks of wall street performance in a long time, it's the results of the past 3 weeks , Boeing lost 2 dollars per share while tesla made 18 dollars per share , now stay on topic har har har and remember back in may you said tesla was better than boeing then and now tesla is up another 100% since then , no changes yet spartacus99991 yoru still a boeing cheerleader and I am still making a lot of money on tsla so much now I cant lose with a stop loss. like with apple I have reached critical mass, I am in and up so far now a 5% hit would mean still I have a huge gain overall and I will never take that much of a loss on any stock• "spartacus99991 • May 28, 2013 11:30 AM Flag o Yes, TSLA and SCTY are better stocks than BA the last month for making money for traders. Happy now?"</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377450005753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 13:00:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377450565142-26</Id><Topic><Title>Spartacus99991 states Wayne is right TSLA is better than Boeing as an investment here is his quote, TSLA up 423% BA 49%</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377371116943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-08-24 15:05:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My turn to spin? So, you've finally admiited that you spin. Caught in your web of lies again. LOL P.S. Have you ever admitted the fact that there are American Airlines 737-800s coming down the line in Renton? You never admit to any of your mistakes.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377450565142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 13:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377452299860-27</Id><Title>TSLA price increase is 20.1 times faster than the S&amp;P 500! boeing is lower than the S&amp;P for 3 weeks</Title><Msg>TSLA's price increased 20.3 times faster than the S&amp;P 500 since the close on Thursday of $157.10. While TSLA was at $161.25 when the alert was fired, up 2.6% for the day, the S&amp;P 500 was only up 0.1%. Additionally, TSLA performed better than its peers who were up 1.1%.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377452299860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 13:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377453598403-28</Id><Title>Tesla moves to trademark "Model E" name for future models</Title><Msg>Tesla Motors Inc, the electric car maker led by billionaire Elon Musk, has filed an application to trademark the "Model E" name to potentially use on future automobiles, clothing and repair service. The name is in keeping with Tesla's style. The automaker now sells an electric sedan called the Model S and next year, it will launch the Model X crossover. Musk's branding strategy is a nod to the Model T, which became the first vehicle middle-class Americans could afford when Ford Motor Co introduced it in 1908. Tesla spokeswoman Shanna Hendriks declined to comment on whether the name would be used for the company's third-generation electric car, which Musk has said would be introduced by 2017. The automaker filed the application with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office on August 5. It is not pending. The trademark filing was first reported by the website VentureBeat. The automaker's third-generation model is expected to cost between $30,000 and $35,000, or about half the price of a Model S, which starts around $70,000 before a federal tax credit. Tesla shares have more than quadrupled this year as Model S sales surpassed expectations. The company said on Monday that the car had received the "best safety rating of any car ever tested." Data from the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration confirmed the Model S achieved the best overall safety score of any vehicle tested for model years 2011 to 2014. NHTSA made the testing procedures tougher for the 2011 model year and has not retested models built for the 1990 to 2011 years under the new standards. Clarence Ditlow, executive director for the Center for Auto Safety, said he would "fall out of his chair if a pre-2011 model did better" than the Model S.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377453598403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 13:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377454213143-29</Id><Title>What Wall street said about the best rated car the Tesla Model S</Title><Msg>"In case you're unaware, is the Tesla Model S. Besides the generous range and truly incredible acceleration, the Model S is most impressive for feeling like a real car from a real auto manufacturer instead of a low-volume special haphazardly slapped together using bits and pieces from other carmakers. That doesn't mean the Tesla is normal, however. An enormous central touchscreen controls almost everything, and for the most part does a good job of it. The trunk under the hatchback (versus the one up front where the engine would be) can be equipped with a pair of rear-facing jump seats. Perhaps most abnormal of all is the way it drives. The only thing that gets up to speed this quietly, effortlessly and rapidly is a magnetically launched roller coaster, while the Tesla's incredibly wide stance and low center of gravity allow it to take corners with similar skill. It's an astonishing vehicle that lives up to the hype and is without question the best electric car on the planet."</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377454213143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377454383766-30</Id><Topic><Title>Wall street went through worst 3 week period since Nov,Boeing lost $2 per share Tesla gains $18 per share</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377449589806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:53:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well I see the boeing storytellers are up with their most dangerous weapon the thumb of rejection for tsla a better stock than boeing sorry Charlie your tuna is not good enough try to get some class and buy tsla and you too Charlie can make more money</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377454383766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377454637078-31</Id><Title>WHATS THE SCOOP WITH DICKWAYNEDICK'S (AKA ELONMUSK),S CLAIM...</Title><Msg>That this tom brown fellow was right...boeing to hit $ 108.00 then down to $ 72.00. what the hell are they smoking?</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1377454637078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377455969564-32</Id><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Msg>• waynedickenson961 waynedickenson961 • 5 hours ago Flag o 2 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 4 o Reply Tom O"Brien on Boeing stock price today and the Boeing advertisement show . Tom O'Brien, is a national stock market expert , who is famous for timing the individual stock prices . Today, Mr. O'Brien covered Boeing , and pointed out that Boeing stock price now is just about "dead on the vine" saying the volume is going down over time. Mr. O'Brien indicated the last time Boeing was a 107 dollar stock was in 2007 and it will now ring the bell at the previous high and maybe get some more but then Boeing stock price will retreat over time to the 71 dollar range . In other words it not going to 130 or 150 it is close to over. For any user of the Boeing financial blog, as you can see there is a core of six Boeing barkers, the doggy, bow wow self proclaimed , Boeing advertisement salesmen, for Boeing who are selling Boeing stock to potential customers. These six people are loud and colorful and like a circus barker stand at the Boeing financial page all day long barking come on in and get some Boeing stocks. Showing news stories and dogging any other opinion with personal attacks For the year to date the competition between the two major competitors, Airbus stock is better .When you have the facts on your side you argue facts, , when you do not have the facts on your side, you pound the table and call names. Airbus is for the year to date up or better than Boeing at a 46% gain to 38% for Boeing, a 7% advantage to Airbus shareholders, For long term investment over the past 3 years , Airbus is better stock gain for their investors by 117%. Remember , the Boeing barkers the doggy bow - wow is to cover their bad position on Boeing , so they pound the table and call names</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377456828096-33</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for the barker, domerrrr update for Boeing now, and Airbus now and Tesla now, Boeing is up 39% year to date, and Airbus has increased its lead over Boeing , now Airbus stock is up over 50% tesla ( tsla) is now up from then on 6-19-2013 then at $103 dollars per share to today $162 dollar rounded up so a gain for me of 60 % on $200,000 that is a gain of $120,000.00 gain im my trader account , in dollars Boeing is flat and a dead cat bounce stock .</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377456828096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:53:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377457111236-34</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>6-19-2013 should be 6-18 213</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377457111236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377457485123-35</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so far boeing is dead on the vine as Tom O;Brien said tesla is up from 103 on 6-18 to 162 boeing went no place , and airbus is up nicely at a gain from 46% toover 505 if you into stocks than do not make much money for any investor airbus is the better of the duopoly domerrr got to eat it as usual !This is Tom O;Brien not me and so fare Tom O;Brien is 100% right Boeing stock for 3 months is dead on the vine, over time does not mean 3 months that is years it will retrace to 71 as Airbus pulls ahead the 747 becomes ded the a380 perhaps becomes a freighter depending upon need, so far 747 or a380 no need fro freighter and boeing has a ned ot zero 747-8 orders airbus has 262 firm A380 orders and over 100 deliveries Boeing has zero and is buying back older 747 and flying each new made 747-8 to the desert and parking them , no way to make money on that deal domerrrr eat it as usual</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377457485123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 15:04:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377457841207-36</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all the typos are for you barkers to have fun with ded is dead, ectera have fun now that is all you can correct so I give them to you for the attention</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377457841207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 15:10:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377458581367-37</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check yourself if you have signs of insecurity: Self-Promoting… Insecure people tend to talk about themselves constantly, as if they feel like they have to prove themselves. Self-promotion is paramount to over-compensation for doubt. A confident person doesn’t need to promote himself. His qualities are displayed naturally by the way he lives his life. Besides, he doesn’t need validation from anyone anyway. Bullying… Insecure people feel threatened by others, and one way to cope with this is to try and squash them. The most threatening person of all to an insecure person is a secure person, because they can sense their power. WORK ON YOURSELF… Insecurity can be highly destructive, especially if you don’t understand it. Many insecure people find scapegoats for their problems, never realizing that they are causing the problems themselves. The beginning of security is learning to laugh at yourself, realizing that no one is perfect. Can’t Enjoy Silence… Some insecure people just can’t deal with silence. They fill every void with meaningless chatter, almost to avoid having to reflect on themselves. The unfortunate consequence is the annoyance of everyone around them, who secretly look for an escape. While a secure person can tolerate, and often enjoys silence. If they are with someone else, they have the ability to let someone else talk without having to interject their own perspective.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377458581367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 15:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377460608949-38</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how much did you lose on SBUX from 2006 to 2009 when it lost 75% of its value? Or did you tell the board then how you got out at 37 and bought back in at 10? How convenient to have omitted that fact. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377460608949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 15:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377461100189-39</Id><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Msg>the real message is buy tsla not Boeing, self doubt go for it, wrapped in a package CBX calls self doubt ,he does not want to discuss that TSLA short term or long term is better investment than Boeing doubt that message CBX !</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377461213976-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't the Kent Raven and his alias</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377449274177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:47:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of the above ..... a slackjawed fat slob on the government dole...and Im not just talking about his wasteline ..Im talking about his fat Slack entitlement attitude.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377461213976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377461378462-41</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991, the topic is TSLAis better than Boeing stay on topic now if you can make an argument for Boeing and against TSLA and remember you already told me my TSLA is better than Boeing in May and that still holds up another 100% Now as you know I purchased the ipo on sbux and since then have not lost a Penney of my investment over time</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461378462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377461481277-42</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the topic is tom Obrien,not insecurity but you spin it,tsla is better than boeing airbus is better than boeing conclusion sell boeing buy tesla or airbus</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461481277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377461840438-43</Id><Title>Automotive Industry on cars ratings and how tesla rates it better boeing on stock price gain too</Title><Msg>The automotive industry has been using internal combustion engines to drive vehicles for more than a century, and the industry was begging to be disrupted by an innovative solution. Some have dubbed electric vehicles the ride of the future, but the likes of Ford's (NYSE: F ) Focus Electric and Nissan's Leaf leave something to be desired. Then something happened – Tesla's (NASDAQ: TSLA ) Model S took America by storm. there's no mistaking that this could be the greatest American-made car ever. Here's why. Performance Tesla's Model S performance delivers in a multitude of different ways. First, it delivers more driving range than the Leaf and the Focus Electric combined. The extended driving range will enable Tesla to build out its supercharger network wider and faster in the months and years to come. In a few short months it will already be possible to drive a Model S between our nation's major metro areas and even diagonally from L.A. to New York. As far as driving performance goes, Tesla's Model S could definitely be considered a sports car, with its top-spec model accelerating from 0 to 60 in 4.2 seconds. To put that in comparison, a 2001 Lamborghini Diablo VT 6.0 does 0 to 60 in the same 4.2 seconds. The Model S is even quicker to 60 mph than Porsche's 2013 911 Carrera, which takes 4.3 seconds. Typically, we don't associate lightning-quick sports cars with being safe -- and that's something that separates the Model S yet again. It recently earned a five-star safety rating from the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, or NHTSA. It topped the list in every subcategory, and its overall Vehicle Safety Score achieved a new combined record of 5.4 stars, according to Tesla's press release. This might not only be the greatest American-made car ever, but it could also be the safest. I'm not the only one insan</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461840438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377461945534-44</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm well aware I can put you and your other 3 or 4 alias's on ignore. BTW, if this is about Tom Abrien, why does TSLA nd irbus keep showing up on this thread?</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377461945534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462033949-45</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"over time" Are those weasel words to losing 75% from 2006 to 2009 and didn't sell? Sort of like SSN? LOL P.S. Are you claiming you bought TSLA over 8 months ago and didn't tell the board at the time but waited until May when it finally started to move?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377462033949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462035891-46</Id><Topic><Title>Automotive Industry on cars ratings and how tesla rates it better boeing on stock price gain too</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461840438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:17:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing on the other hand is flat on stock price, and flat on performance even earning a FAA grounding it its lithium battery powered sky bus the 787 each plane cost the shareholders millions of dollar on each delivery until the break even point in 2021 or longer as the failures mount try that fire on fro size boeing storytellers</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377462035891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:20:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462247194-47</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These are your words from less than 15 minutes ago. how soon we forget the topic is tom Obrien,not insecurity but you spin it,tsla is better than boeing airbus is better than boeing conclusion sell boeing buy tesla or airbus</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377462247194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462272264-48</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so still avoiding tsla and now name calling might as well run in circles and hoot now spartacus99991 that is all you can do with tsla compared to Boeing har har har</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377462272264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462353767-49</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you trying to lend credibility to your statements by using the name of a successful person? Pick another name. Few continue to not recognize the potential of Tesla, so go promote it elsewhere.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377462353767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462411047-50</Id><Topic><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx I am waiting do you want to engage me on tsla compared to Boeing now or later its been all year long tsla better than Boeing and still no response</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377462411047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462589843-51</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said buy it in 3/7/2011 and it dropped over 30% in a week and then several months later you said you really meant not long term (or short, or stop loss, or other weasel words). History can be a #$%$. LOL So, won't answer about TSLA and you maybe buying it 8 months ago?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377462589843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462611036-52</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Topic is Tom Obrien. How soon we forget "For any user of the Boeing financial blog, as you can see there is a core of six Boeing barkers, the doggy, bow wow self proclaimed , Boeing advertisement salesmen, for Boeing who are selling Boeing stock to potential customers. These six people are loud and colorful and like a circus barker stand at the Boeing financial page all day long barking come on in and get some Boeing stocks. Showing news stories and dogging any other opinion with personal attacks "</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377462611036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462682831-53</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>albacucucu, ,my stock tsla and I like it around Boeing a inferior stock,the comparison is good for me and bad for you , put me on ignore if it bothers you but I do not go any place for you so you can forget that order right now</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377462682831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377462767595-54</Id><Topic><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok then, shout and run in circles that is all you can do when it comes to comparing my stock tsla to boeing</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377462767595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:32:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377464533494-55</Id><Title>Good news for Boeing!</Title><Msg>Boeing , Boeing , Boeing! Ever heard that name? What people do not realize is that Boeing is fast becoming the Brand name in the airline industry. Take it to the bank!</Msg><Username>d_proch</Username><Timestamp>1377464533494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 17:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377468930193-56</Id><Topic><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've never said TSLA was not better than Boeing as far as stock price, The only thing to that affect would be when I stated I thought it wa a high risk stock and Boeing was more conservative and then said TSLA was a conservative stock. Perhaps you should "engage" with the real Elon and the author of where this information below came from even if it isn't a comparison to BA like you would discuss "Even TSLA's CEO Elon Musk has hinted/said the stock is overpriced. He seems to be positioning himself (his recent comments) to deflect possible future shareholders lawsuits. These would inevitably follow a significant crash in the TSLA stock price. Such a crash could happen at any time, especially if the overall market reverses significantly. He clearly does not want investors to be able to say he was deceiving them"</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377468930193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 18:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377469386547-57</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I said weasel "word", I wasn't calling you a weasel, although someone with paranoid tendencies might think so and thus respond accordingly. But not you. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377469386547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 18:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377469546541-58</Id><Topic><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The above post should have been "and then YOU said TSLA was a conservative stock"</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377469546541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 18:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377470875342-59</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst Scott Hamilton on Boeings loss and Airbus win especially going forward over time!</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455560817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:32:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all that glory for Allan McArtor but elonmusk909's only kudoo is for his double liplock which he practices on his boyfriend</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1377470875342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 18:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377471587393-60</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx the subject is Boeing the author is Tom O'Brien the topic is Boeing stock price is dead on the vine is his, a better stock is TSLA for this year, last year and the year prior to that, this is s financial message board since Boeing stock price is dead on the vine, a better stock for you is tsla, get it now, or just put me on ignore unless you have insecurity and can not get along without me</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377471587393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 18:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377471759067-61</Id><Topic><Title>I'm SICK of hearing this excrement about RACE day after day on this board</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377447042216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:10:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like you are trying to put al sharpton jesse jackson and that ilk out of well paying jobs !!!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377471759067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377471878358-62</Id><Topic><Title>Tue 6/18/2013 Tom O"Brien said "boeing is dead on the vine" the price will peak at 107 to 110 and go down so far tom is right ,eat it</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455969564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 since your using the word "weasel " on a financial message board you are engaging in this behavior, When you have the facts on your side you argue facts, when you have the stock price TSLA compared to Boeing stock price on your side you argue the stock price, , when you have neither you pound the table and call names. the word weasel is a name ! har har har</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377471878358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377473497573-63</Id><Topic><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx when you said in your original post the tesla shareholder meeting had not occurred ,you are adding information after your comment, that is fraud. As to this new comment you just added about tsla .Elon Musk, standard CEO requirement for a stock that has gone up so much. but it is based on solid performance, meeting and exceeding every milestone and all the shorts getting scared out and buying back to limit their losses. AS you know on May 3, 2013 I told this message board to buy tsla and 15 trade days laterit had gained 100% then spartacus99991 on May 28 decided to say I was right tsla was better than Boeing. spartacus99991 waited for some time and then agreed with me/ Since that 100% -15 day gain it is now up another 100% so I cant lose unless it falls 200% and it blows past my stop loss, not likely. . I also said when the short squeeze was done about 15 days after my call to get into tsla , and to watch it more like a day trade until it broke above the Bollinger band and it did and I went all in at that time. I tell you what I am doing, while CBX at least on this post, you find factual information after the fact and add it to your original post, to make it sound like you were saying it before Elon MusK made a apology style of comment about how fast his company stock has gone up, or a warning to people too late to jump on. I told this message board on May 3 to jump on plenty of time to make 200% that was your choice not to participate. Once more it is not psychology it is you desire to be rid of me because like apple , acad and now tsla I point out much better stocks than you Boeing and you can't stand that . Like airbus stock price is up 50% year to date and boeing is 39% for 3 years Boeing stock price is up 63% and Airbus is up about 160% it varies each day but the trend is airbus is better than boeing for all stock market investors end of the facts now shout and pound the table that is all you can do with those facts .</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377473497573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377473855005-64</Id><Title>Tesla Is Outselling Porsche, Volvo, and Land Rover in California</Title><Msg>California loves Tesla Motors and its Model S luxury electric sports sedan. According to the latest car sales figures reported by the California New Car Dealers Association, Tesla captured 12 percent of the luxury sports car category in the state during the first half of 2013 — enough to surpass the Audi A6 and Lexus GS. Granted the company sold 4,714 Model S’s during the first half of the year, 1,097 of them in June. But that was enough to outsell Porsche, Volvo, Cadillac, Jaguar, Buick and Land Rover during that first month of summer. Impressive. Remember, Tesla is selling only one model of car.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377473855005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377474106173-65</Id><Topic><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Caught again with false information being posted. I have never talked about any shareholder meetings . I think you meant that comment for someone else so your action is fraud agains me. "cbx when you said in your original post the tesla shareholder meeting had not occurred ,you are adding information after your comment, that is fraud." ""</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377474106173</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377475747672-66</Id><Topic><Title>5 most absurd, self-pitying gripes of the Christian right</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377475653276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 20:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sad story is in the deep south there are many racist, bigoted clowns like Hope.....".</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1377475747672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 20:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377477825395-67</Id><Topic><Title>Self doubt, is tesla a better stock than boeing year to date and over time 3 years CBX?</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377461100189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx, you're not the first and won't be the last poster who gets accused by "Elon" of things you never posted. He gets confused easily (trying to remember all his "facts"). I wonder what the term for a person is who thinks everyone is against him? LOL P.S. It's beginning to look like Wayne has settled in on his idol, Elon, as his new ID (identity theft?---- no he wouldn't stoop that low). Goodbye, Sylvia, we hardly knew thee.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377477825395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 20:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377477983281-68</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla Is Outselling Porsche, Volvo, and Land Rover in California</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377473855005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad TSLA is doing the same thing as Boeing with it's current 787 deliveries. Vickrey points out that TSLA made $68 million in Q1 2013 from zero emission vehicles (ZEV) credits. If you take those out of profits, TSLA had a huge loss. TSLA expects their ability to sell these credits will diminish quickly.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377477983281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 20:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377478085039-69</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst Scott Hamilton on Boeings loss and Airbus win especially going forward over time!</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455560817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:32:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He probably gets along with Paul Allen like you said you got along with Morgan Stanley (MS) analyst, Heidi Wood. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377478085039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 20:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377478490206-70</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Wallace Keeps Pushing Disproven Racial Crime Theory In Chris Lane Tragedy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377474376940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:46:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am mystified by these articles that compare Trayvon Martin's killer Zimmerman and those fellows that killed Chris Lane. Just about every one of your posts over the past two years, Hooz, support the idea that Zimmerman was a racist with racist motives - yet the facts that came out in the trial completely dispute that. And, just the opposite. Zimmerman dated, mentored, and helped black people. Only the absurd of this world would count him as a racist. Trayvon, unfortunately, was a racist as Jeantel admitted that in her testimony in court, and that hatred was one factor that led to his death. The young fellows that killed Chris Lane, on the other hand, at least one of them, has spewed lengthy tirades of explicit hatred towards white people. Yet, you post these ridiculous articles that insist that race could not have anything to do with the motives. Why? Because there was a white driver. It was a racist that fired the weapon. Now, I have counted you in the past as someone who operated with a certain level of intelligence - though opposite in philosophy from myself. But these posts are simply stupid.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1377478490206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 20:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377478634839-71</Id><Topic><Title>5 most absurd, self-pitying gripes of the Christian right</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377475653276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 20:07:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under many definitions, gay conversion therapy would be considered torture, and in all cases, regardless of age, anyone should have the right to decline it.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377478634839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 20:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377478888581-72</Id><Topic><Title>Chris Wallace Keeps Pushing Disproven Racial Crime Theory In Chris Lane Tragedy</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377474376940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:46:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have counted you (Hooz) in the past as someone who operated with a certain level of intelligence - though opposite in philosophy from myself. But these posts are simply stupid." They are not SUPPOSED to be intelligent....they are meant to carry on an agenda..and agenda of balkanization of the American people to provoke a race war...Hooz is parroting the agenda from on high...and THAT is the absolute truth</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377478888581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377479333305-73</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla Is Outselling Porsche, Volvo, and Land Rover in California</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377473855005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cbx, the stock price is what counts. CBX, as, far as your Elon Musk's point (after the fact now ) on your conservative argument for Boeing, The statement about the TSLA, the stock price being higher than its value, as a stock trader. If I am worried like you about a pull back, then I will go with a " at the money call" For example, Monday I can buy 100 shares of tsla on a "at the money call" for about $5.85( it will vary a little on Monday with the stock price) and will get the right to sell 100 shares and if tsla. so I control $16,200 dollars of tsla for $585 dollar until Friday, it tsla goes above $167.85( the current price of the stock plus the call at the money cost) by Friday for a very small amount of money I can get the gain on 100 shares or cover $16200 dollars of investment for a maximum loss of $585 dollars. Or I can go with a contract put or call to hedge my longer term TSLa holdings. I am advising you of this, CBX, as your arguments- comments indicate you are concerned about risk avoidanceCBX it's odd , . you fail to see the risk in the 787, which is late, FAA grounded a real bad history, with over budget, no break even until 2021, constantly diverted and emergency landing issues as a safe investment wow that makes no sense, CBX you make little financial sense to me, or do not know how to trade stocks. Boeing is outsourcing engineering, a very risky and failed corporate behavior as seen with MD. Tesla is a winner on time best in class safest car, better dales than its competition,, and your concerned about all the success making it too risky to invest in. Well, CBX, I just told you how to limit your investment risk with a minimal investment of money .. At some point in time you need to learn how to trade a stock. Your arguments do not make sense .</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377479333305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377479754476-74</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla Is Outselling Porsche, Volvo, and Land Rover in California</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377473855005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as far a credits well that is a investment plus that too many shorts did not get right then isn't it !Next what the CEO said is going forward if tsla continues to execute thenthe stock is undervalued, Now he can not say it that way, he had to say what he did for lawsuit issues. Tesla is a target it is number 1 now, for me that means up over 400% I will take the risk of being in the number one stock you can hve the number two stock in a 2 company competition Airbus is number one it is at 50% to 3( % for the year to date and betters boeing by much more at three years 63% to 160% for airbus . CBX your argument is really for a bad stock picke'sr choice and lack of trade skills , no insult intended it is what it is .</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377479754476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377479820168-75</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla Is Outselling Porsche, Volvo, and Land Rover in California</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377473855005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 19:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3 should be 39% for boeing year to date</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377479820168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377481127720-76</Id><Title>armageddon tv coming !!</Title><Msg>Olbermann Set to Return to ESPN and Sports News.. we are doomed !! The whole world and MSM have gone off the rails Since ObUma blames bush or limbaugh for everything - now the Dims will be able to put up Oberslobber as their poster- child. Wonder if he will be able to save the world - or start WW3</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377481127720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377481534767-77</Id><Title>Evidence of Chemical attack use by Syria destroyed...</Title><Msg>How convienient....sounds a lot like Bush and WMD's before Iraq gang... AFP - British Foreign Secretary William Hague on Sunday warned that any evidence of a chemical attack by the Syrian regime may have already been destroyed. "The fact is that much of the evidence could have been destroyed by that artillery bombardment," he cautioned during a press conference after Damascus gave its green light to a mission by UN inspectors.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377481534767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:45:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377481890033-78</Id><Topic><Title>Evidence of Chemical attack use by Syria destroyed...</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377481534767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:45:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course NO one figured out that saddam simply trucked his wmd chemicals over the border to Syria- which was why few were found in Iraq. Next up now that one or two red lines have been croosed- by whom doesn't matter- what will US do ? Whimper- Cry- send a strong memo- ? When will the west learn the only thing those tribal types pay attention to is who has the biggest hammer- and will gleefully negotiate until they have the hammer - or believe the other sides will not use theirs .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377481890033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377481959294-79</Id><Topic><Title>Obama moving toward YET ANOTHER Undeclared War in Syria</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377443227739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 11:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You hair always has to be on fire about Something, Spart. It might as well be this! Harharharharhar But why won't you tell me what John Lennon could do for the opposition that he could NOT do as merela a famous former Beatle?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377481959294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377482110148-80</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst Scott Hamilton on Boeings loss and Airbus win especially going forward over time!</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455560817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:32:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 or like you said you get along with your wife LOL btw what does this have to do with Scott Hamilton's opinion of Boeings loss to Airbus nothing !!!</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377482110148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377482152438-81</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't the Kent Raven and his alias</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377449274177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:47:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you STILL can't make a cased for why the New World Order would want John Lennon dead, can you, Loon? You can eat a mile of my waste line, lunatic.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377482152438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377482283358-82</Id><Topic><Title>Evidence of Chemical attack use by Syria destroyed...</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377481534767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:45:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't assume what you want to believe is the truth. If we knew, with our faultless intelligence, those WMDs were so mobile, why did we send an army to get them?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377482283358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377482455469-83</Id><Title>CBX on Elon Musk and his comment on stock price and the whole article , it was a sound bite that is all</Title><Msg>Elon Musk: Our stock price is obviously far too high Tesla Motors' stock (TSLA) is caught in a wave of hype, leaving Tesla CEO Elon Musk grasping for the best way to describe the company's sky high valuation. The last time we reported on Tesla Motors (TSLA) stock price, last April, it had just broken above $40 a share thanks to good news like posting the first profit in the company's history. Little did we know that today, five months later, the TSLA stock price would be nearing $160 a share, for a 4x gain. Many of us are kicking ourselves for not buying into TSLA at that stock price rally and becoming a Teslanaire. But in a CNBC interview published on Wednesday, Tesla CEO Elon Musk said things about Tesla's stock price that look very bad if taken out of context. Musk really did say to CNBC's Philip LeBeau, "the valuation we have right now is more than we have any right to deserve," and "our stock price is obviously far too high" which surely caught the attention of shareholder class action lawsuits lawyers. But if you listen to his whole statement, rather than the sound-bites, what he said was very reasonable. Theoretically, when the stock market agrees on a stock price, the market is determining a careful and reasoned valuation for a company. Stock price valuation is supposed to be based on a reasoned estimate of future earnings. But in practice the stock market sometimes has darling stocks that fly high based on hype rather than rational valuations. What Elon Musk actually said is that the stock market valuation of Tesla's stock, if taken rationally, means the market believes Tesla Motors is going to succeed beyond anybody's wildest dreams: "I actually think the value of Tesla right now is .. the market is being very generous. And they're obviously giving us a lot of credit for future execution. So we'll do our best to honor the faith the market has placed in us," said Musk. Does Musk believe the valuation for Tesla Motors makes any sense? He can't come right out</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377482455469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:00:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377482743366-84</Id><Topic><Title>CBX on Elon Musk and his comment on stock price and the whole article , it was a sound bite that is all</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377482455469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:00:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(continued from above)So He can't come right out and say something like "hey y'all, you've bid the company up way too high, tone it down a bit" because that would trigger a shareholder lawsuit. What he did say, stumbling around with the words to make sure he said it the correct way, is: "I really feel that the valuation we have right now is more than we have any right to deserve .. so it's not as though I ... I think we need to make sure we knock the ball out of the park in the coming years." Rather than say TSLA is overpriced, he said that Tesla Motors has got to "knock the ball out of the park" in order to live up to the market's expectations. He closed appearing to say that Tesla's stock price is caught up in a hype bubble, and that the price may well fall if or when the current wave of exuberance falls off: "The market obviously goes through these periods of exuberance and depression. That means our stock has a lot of volatility because it depends so much on what people believe our future execution will be. Our stock price is obviously far too high based on historical financials, or even on current financials, ... So the value is very much based on what the future cash position will be like... as that confidence waxes and wanes we'll see fluctuation in the value of the company." For the first quarter of 2013, Tesla posted their first profit ever after many years of posting losses. The profit was based on strong sales of the Tesla Model S, and those strong sales have continued. For the second quarter of 2013, the sales continued strong but because of the way sales have to be accounted with the new lease-like financing program Tesla posted a small loss for the quarter. The company is continuing to show strong sales growth, has started to deliver Model S's in Europe, and in generally really does seem to be knocking it out</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377482743366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377482789948-85</Id><Topic><Title>CBX on Elon Musk and his comment on stock price and the whole article , it was a sound bite that is all</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377482455469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:00:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the park , word for word ,no alterations for my fans</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377482789948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377484194325-86</Id><Topic><Title>CBX on Elon Musk and his comment on stock price and the whole article , it was a sound bite that is all</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377482455469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:00:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please read the article titled "Even Elon Musk Thinks Tesla Stock Is Overpriced" published today at 4:46 (note sure what time zone). Some people may have different opinions on TSLA, (the article is not my opinion nor do I support or debate it), just want to make sure you have read both sides of the coin</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377484194325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377484984182-87</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't the Kent Raven and his alias</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377449274177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:47:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorty belonged to the Eagles which does a lot of charity work. Chris being a comrade, doesn't like anyone but his church of the taxing government doing that kind of stuff. And there are a lot of white people in the Eagles which he hates, because he is one himself and so were his parents, whose generation believed in things like the Eagles.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1377484984182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377485108451-88</Id><Title>White house announces "Burgundy" line crossed ......</Title><Msg>Not "Red". So lets give the Administration a pass here. By my calculations there are at least 5 more shades of red to go according to my Crayola Crayon box, batten down the hatches when the "Melot" is breeched. Getting ready to open a bottle and memorize the shade.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377485108451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377485116419-89</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't the Kent Raven and his alias</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1377449274177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 12:47:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't know me at all, putz. And you don't have to show your ignorance -- we know all about it.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377485116419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 22:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377488206548-90</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst Scott Hamilton on Boeings loss and Airbus win especially going forward over time!</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455560817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:32:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As much as your always bringing up Paul Allen (or Burt Rutan). You do under whsteffanms' sarcasm, don't you? Well, maybe not. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377488206548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 23:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377488301779-91</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst Scott Hamilton on Boeings loss and Airbus win especially going forward over time!</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377455560817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 14:32:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>make that "understand" for my spelling check critics. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377488301779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 23:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377489212365-92</Id><Topic><Title>Evidence of Chemical attack use by Syria destroyed...</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377481534767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 21:45:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ask then other two or three intel agencies - and check with a few special ops people who di find evidence of wmd stuff that had somehow dissappeared . Add to that the typical boast by the local tribes that ' mine is bigger than yours' game and you get the cluster---- that happened.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377489212365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-25 23:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>