<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376021104936-1</Id><Title>Paul is alive</Title><Msg>8/8/69 marks the 44th anniversary of the iconic Abbey Road album cover and about his 51st -60th year in the business but then the RWNJ's have a 65 year old censored50 calling people names like a twelve year old cretin</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376021104936</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:05:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376021200780-2</Id><Topic><Title>Paula Deen More Popular Than MLK Jr. with Georgia Republicans</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1375997072207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incorrect facts? 144K? I am not a JehovWit. The number will be countless, though many, in fact, most will not be there (Matthew 7:13,14). But since you say that you have "no doubts", then you should be happy to share them with me. That is your obligation. Both the Apostle Paul (Romans 10:15) and the Prophet Isaiah (52:7) said, "Blessed are the feet of them that spread the Gospel of peace." What say you?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1376021200780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376021653376-3</Id><Topic><Title>Paula Deen More Popular Than MLK Jr. with Georgia Republicans</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1375997072207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't that what President all about reigning peace upon us all in the name of his Lord, Jesus and God almighty and a couple four drone strikes in yemen on thye heathen...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376021653376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376022043616-4</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives once ridiculed Ayn Rand</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376005088172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 19:38:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Reply but eight thimbs up Sir Paul and sometimes George, John, &amp; RINGO</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376022043616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376022118053-5</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives’ great white hope</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376004848805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 19:34:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol see my previous post concerning No Reply</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376022118053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376022706496-6</Id><Topic><Title>Paula Deen More Popular Than MLK Jr. with Georgia Republicans</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1375997072207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 17:24:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ONE VOTE SHY</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376022706496</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376022926919-7</Id><Title>reougsareliars is leaving out some information so WD will help him out, TSLA is up 355% Year to date minus.9%</Title><Msg>repugsareliars,, you said, TSLA down .09% more than BA in after hours trading , attsa too bad for wd but repugnate, your a liar , by exception. in fact for the year to date TSLA is up still now 353% so with a one day gain of about as much as boeing made in several months there was some profit taking , that is selling at a near term high repugsareliars. IF YOU TAKE ALL THE GAINS BOEIGN HAS MADE FOR THE YEAR TO DATE AND SUBTRACT THEM FROM THE GAINS IN TSLA 353 MINUS 40 YOU MISSED 313% GAIN ON WHATEVER YOU HAVE INVESTED IN BOEING. INOTHER WORDS TESLA STOCK HAS MADE ME SO MUCH MORE THAN BOEING HAS MADE YOU I HAVE A HUGE BUFFER TO NEVER LOOSE MY GAIN TO YOUR BOEING STOCK. but is gets worse so repugsareliars, that is to bad for you LOL Wayne PS the numbers ytd up TSLA stock gain has made me 353% , for 3years TSLA stock gain is 738% that gain betters Boeing up 40% ytd and a pathetic 55% for 5 years. Airbus beats Boeing at 56% year to date( a 15% better and pad against any pullback compared to BA) and 177% for 5 years . so there is no way repugsareliars , that TSLA will be too bad for me, its always going to be a situation that Boeing is too bad for you and your Boeing stock</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376022926919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376023116884-8</Id><Title>WHAT IS 12 TO THE 12TH POWER</Title><Msg>Best Answer: 8,916,100,448,256 X12 X12 X12... SPREAD THE WORD...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376023116884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376023657611-9</Id><Topic><Title>reougsareliars is leaving out some information so WD will help him out, TSLA is up 355% Year to date minus.9%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376022926919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You could BUY 1.44877shares of BA or 33.4606 shares of FTR or one share of TSLA but even I would not do the latter con-sidering the massive RWNJ short storm but the former I would and possibly some of the latter before bitcoins/you pumper if i had a dollar</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376023657611</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376024007203-10</Id><Topic><Title>GOP's Bully: Reince Priebus has a women problem</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376004547615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 19:29:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>11-0</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376024007203</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376024397043-11</Id><Title>Obama is a racists and here is proof</Title><Msg>Pres. Obama is asking public school teachers to “take it easy” on black students who misbehave. On July 26, 2012, Obama signed an Executive Order to create the African American Education Initiative. The order births a new federal bureaucracy and effectively offers black students a green light to misbehave at school. and the horde howls in approval</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376024397043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376024801983-12</Id><Topic><Title>Am I to understand that I will be slandered and taunted until I leave Boeing message board?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1375992816066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sachawk77, let me answer you with a quote of yours " sachawk77 • Jan 9, 2013 9:31 PM Flag 1. You are stupid.....period sachawk77, with not caring here is the same old progress, first the group deny that the stock is any good, now days after repeated great stock's that approach has been pretty much eliminated, my previous stocks were Apple for many years at first the Boeing investors try to deny that my stock is any good, then the usual request is that I go to the message board of that particular stock ie apple, the third phase , which you are on is the denial that I actually have the stock, and the last phase is the slander attack as the stock is too strong to deny bettering Boeing, so the personal attack against me is the final attempt along with please stop mentioning that TSLA is up 353% ytd and 738 % for 3 years . So sachawk77, your in phase three and your welcome to try phase one which you have combined with phase 3 , as you get frustrated with the continued gains for TSLa your welcome to try the slander, here are the usual, I am a fired employee I am a moron, I am a gay person I have no friends, I have no life, and variations of the theme, the problem with this approach is all the boeing investors are taking the time to do this which begs the question if I have whatever personal problem because I constantly mke user comment why are these slander commenter able to take the time if they are also not in the same boat with me. OK then charge on sachawk77 you are combining two phases of the Wayne treatment by the Boeing stock holder. This occurs last year with my 12100 gain on ACAD and will continue this year with my gains and reports on TSLA . I am a stock investor with a MBA and have over 30 years of street smart investing experience. This is part of my legacy, I know all my comments will be here forever, it is a good thing for me . boeing will go bankrupt within 10 years on the MD outsourcing business plan , I guarantee it . Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376024801983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376024846181-13</Id><Title>tis about 10:04 on the left coast and IAM listening to the yotube</Title><Msg>specifically Grateful Dead &amp; Allman Bros ☮ Not Fade Away, 6-10-73 I sure hope Obama don't take it away</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376024846181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376025106416-14</Id><Topic><Title>Am I to understand that I will be slandered and taunted until I leave Boeing message board?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1375992816066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12100 gain in stock price since I mentioned it to sparti who then tried to say he was up 144% in a non existent stock IGZ( its a tool for working on the trader software) on ACAD should be a gain of 1200% correction</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376025106416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376025412440-15</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives once ridiculed Ayn Rand</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376005088172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 19:38:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post. I'm glad to see so many intellectuals agree with me. It's just lamentable that no one mentioned that in Ayn Rand's world, the only way most of her self-interested women can "give themselves" to a man is to be raped. They are far too self-absorbed to think about mutual pleasure. I wonder if Ayn was a submissive or a dominator, a masochist or sadist? What I can't understand is how they got Gary Cooper to "rape" Patricia Neal in the 1949 film version of "The Fountainhead." But it WAS just after the incredible violence of WW2 and alsop, perhaps the stars were short of cash or wanted to be seen as "edgy." This rampant rapism is true even though the railroad baroness Dagny Taggart has a torrid affair with Francisco Domingo Carlos Andres Sebastian d’Anconia (I had forgotten his name but who wouldn't?), apparently because she is so enthralled by his cocktail-party repartee about how money is the root of all good. Since it ran to something like 63 pages in my paperback edition, I wouldn't be surprised if he had NEVER been invited to another cocktail party. Anyway, that was before Dagny met John Galt, the spiritual leader of her leaderless brave new economic world. Small wonder the film versions of Parts 1 and 2 were flops. Ayn Rand's laissez-faire capitalism works. The invisible hand of the marketplace ran them out of town.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376025412440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376025683272-16</Id><Topic><Title>reougsareliars is leaving out some information so WD will help him out, TSLA is up 355% Year to date minus.9%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376022926919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bisbee the problem with your user comment is back on May 3 here on the Boeing message board I called my trade, I said to go into TSLA and it would be a great short squeeze gain . In 15 trade days it made me 100% and then I called it to get out as a hold and go to a day trader plan and gave specific instructions on how to play it until it broke above the Bollinger band that happened today, so if you want go back and read how to play TSLA now . Bisbee, and all my critics know it. Bisbee_angler, you sir are just a after the fact angler not a real stock trader anyone like Sparti can call a stock after the fact. angler, so as many you after the fact players do, your late I make my buys first then post them then keep track of them for you and the Boeing investors to see how badly they are doing in their Boeing investments I did it with apple for years then acad last year and now tsla. Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376025683272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376026118563-17</Id><Topic><Title>reougsareliars is leaving out some information so WD will help him out, TSLA is up 355% Year to date minus.9%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376022926919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you want more based on sound financial principles sounds likje you should be driving a Hummer not aTSLA</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376026118563</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376027295101-18</Id><Topic><Title>tis about 10:04 on the left coast and IAM listening to the yotube</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376024846181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:07:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because then he might have a 'real' fight on his doorstep about nothing/phony RWNJ scandals not fade away</Msg><Username>repugsrwimps</Username><Timestamp>1376027295101</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:48:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376027357359-19</Id><Title>So far so good....</Title><Msg>TSLA drivers suck!</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1376027357359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:49:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376027910251-20</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives once ridiculed Ayn Rand</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1376005088172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 19:38:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me three,,,although this triplicity is starting to con-fuse censored50</Msg><Username>skooterlibby</Username><Timestamp>1376027910251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376028216814-21</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT IS 12 TO THE 12TH POWER</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376023116884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John sir paul matthew mark george and ringo</Msg><Username>skooterlibby</Username><Timestamp>1376028216814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 02:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376028650410-22</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT IS 12 TO THE 12TH POWER</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376023116884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apparently some family ironed-their three-sheet binder-paper and gave me a complete copy of all the answers to chem for the first qtr but that doesn;t mean I don;t have to SHOW YOUR OWN WORK beep...#3 and moving on up... working backwards from waynerdick = 0</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1376028650410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 02:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376029103580-23</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT IS 12 TO THE 12TH POWER</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376023116884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bounced around 1-3-5-7 all yearin chem 179 which included penny what's her face the founder of INTC's daughter the girl with plaques in her braces who was friends with... #' s number'd she married a #$%$ guy?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1376029103580</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 02:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376031574932-24</Id><Topic><Title>tis about 10:04 on the left coast and IAM listening to the yotube</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376024846181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:07:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apparently this old dog has let me sign in once agian using an old Prodigy password just to say thjat it is near 12;04 on the left coast and I have been listening to some early beatles on the youtube including She's A Woman and wondering... how they gonna take my guns away if She;s A Woman who understands</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376031574932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 02:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376031698560-25</Id><Topic><Title>tis about 10:04 on the left coast and IAM listening to the yotube</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376024846181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:07:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary 23016</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376031698560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 03:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376032358819-26</Id><Title>As a young republicon why would I wannbe like</Title><Msg>RMN or RWR aka 666 when I like Ike</Msg><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1376032358819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 03:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376032704826-27</Id><Topic><Title>As a young republicon why would I wannbe like</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1376032358819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 03:12:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Love me do</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376032704826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 03:18:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376032969641-28</Id><Topic><Title>So far so good....</Title><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1376027357359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 01:49:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and TSLA pilots suck twice as much</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376032969641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 03:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376033093375-29</Id><Title>Love, love me BA do</Title><Msg>or Honey Don't select one: Buy</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376033093375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 03:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376042847612-30</Id><Topic><Title>Am I to understand that I will be slandered and taunted until I leave Boeing message board?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1375992816066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slandered and taunted? Awfully full of yourself, don't you think? You repeatedly post things that are, at best, highly inaccurate, others that are patently false, others that are outright lies and still others that are just ridiculous, apparently in some vain attempt to paint Boeing in an unflattering light because of the mountain-sized chip on your shoulder. As a result, you have no credibility, not on this board and certainly not with me. You then complain when people try to set the record straight and criticize you for being a douche bag. You bring it on yourself and have nobody to blame but the guy in the mirror, but you clearly get some kind of sick reward for doing so however or you wouldn't continue to do it. You know, there are plenty of genuine, factually accurate things to be critical of Boeing, its executives and senior management about. There's really no need to make stuff up. As for Airbus ... I know people who have worked for Airbus and have a close friend who did for several years until just recently when she decided to go back to college to get her Phd. Airbus has its own problems and really isn't the flawless machine you like to portray them as. Finally, I have a job at Boeing that I enjoy, that pays me more money than I ever imagined I'd make, with pretty darn good benefits, certainly more than what most people get, working with some really great people, doing fun and interesting things on an almost daily basis that most people never get an opportunity to do. You do not. It's a shame you threw it all away and are now on the outside looking in, unable to let go, unable to accept responsibility for your actions and unable to just move on. You are a bitter, angry, little man, swimming in a sea of misery due to a massive personal problem with no solution anywhere in sight. I am so glad I'm not you.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1376042847612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376044945570-31</Id><Topic><Title>Am I to understand that I will be slandered and taunted until I leave Boeing message board?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1375992816066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It never ceases to amaze me how a person who claims to have made a fortune in the markets spends so much time on a message board.Tell the truth wayne,your in moms basement posting away on cmultiple computers.I feel sorry for you.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376044945570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376045810464-32</Id><Title>Lettuce get the words straight</Title><Msg>NO Snowden No Soschi you can have Snowden</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376045810464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376045854285-33</Id><Topic><Title>Lettuce get the words straight</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376045810464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because your snow SUCKS</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376045854285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376046113088-34</Id><Topic><Title>As a young republicon why would I wannbe like</Title><Username>the_dr_is_in_out</Username><Timestamp>1376032358819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 03:12:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tres bien...</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376046113088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376046349400-35</Id><Topic><Title>Lettuce get the words straight</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376045810464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah well your RWNJ's don't sayu so but we wood and do</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376046349400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376046409098-36</Id><Topic><Title>Lettuce get the words straight</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376045810464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your Snow SUCKS!</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376046409098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376046770423-37</Id><Topic><Title>Lettuce get the words straight</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376045810464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How are we expected to go into the great WHITE north and not drink may cases of beer and then be able to out fish a russian who's snow SUCKS perhaps you wanna play the RWNJ' sissies like #$%$ boil limpballs</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376046770423</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376048265700-38</Id><Topic><Title>Lettuce get the words straight</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376045810464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just to make it clear for our RWNJ's who never fought and their #$%$ pimpled limpballs concerning the other Oilympic Ray-gun boycotted games not much has changed except the koch-suckers think they have control of the SCOTUS and the RWNJ's have more limpballs than a russian peace out</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376048265700</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376049374862-39</Id><Title>Snowden’s Email Provider Shuts Down</Title><Msg>John Keller Lew Rockwell Blog August 9, 2013 Texas-based Lavabit posted a cryptic message as their homepage and has shutdown service. This is the provider that Edward Snowden supposedly used, so it doesn’t take much imagination to guess that some unholy alliance of the NSA, FBI, CIA, and some other alphabet-soup star-chamber despots served them papers including a gag-order. Here is the message in full (emphasis mine): My Fellow Users, I have been forced to make a difficult decision: to become complicit in crimes against the American people or walk away from nearly ten years of hard work by shutting down Lavabit. After significant soul searching, I have decided to suspend operations. I wish that I could legally share with you the events that led to my decision. I cannot. I feel you deserve to know what’s going on–the first amendment is supposed to guarantee me the freedom to speak out in situations like this. Unfortunately, Congress has passed laws that say otherwise. As things currently stand, I cannot share my experiences over the last six weeks, even though I have twice made the appropriate requests. What’s going to happen now? We’ve already started preparing the paperwork needed to continue to fight for the Constitution in the Fourth Circuit Court of Appeals. A favorable decision would allow me resurrect Lavabit as an American company. This experience has taught me one very important lesson: without congressional action or a strong judicial precedent, I would _strongly_ recommend against anyone trusting their private data to a company with physical ties to the United States. Sincerely, Ladar Levison Owner and Operator, Lavabit LLC</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049374862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376052734588-40</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden’s Email Provider Shuts Down</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049374862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:56:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America has fierce terrorist enemies that want to take away our freedoms. To protect our freedoms our government has set up a secret police. The paradox is that this secret police is taking away our freedoms. We need to preserve our freedoms and not allow them to be taken away by anyone.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1376052734588</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 08:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376054715078-41</Id><Topic><Title>Am I to understand that I will be slandered and taunted until I leave Boeing message board?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1375992816066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uniposter76 find one message wher I claim to have made a fortune, your such a liar. Number two real simple, your a Boeing investor and full of slander Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054715078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376054911923-42</Id><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Msg>well remember yesterday TSLa made over 14% and is up over 360% so today it should rest or retreat for profit taking so all it has to do is retreat 320% to be the same gain as Boeing for it to be equal you Boeing investors will never catch up to TSLA today SCTY may gain based on the pre market Boeing has been down all week so far lets see if it makes it for the 5th day down</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376055285675-43</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden’s Email Provider Shuts Down</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049374862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:56:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven likes that............as long as he can keep his Twinkies.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1376055285675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376055362078-44</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you suggesting that it's all down hill from here?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1376055362078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:36:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376055461100-45</Id><Topic><Title>Lettuce get the words straight</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1376045810464</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 06:56:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you hearing voices again?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1376055461100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376055958650-46</Id><Title>for the 5th day in a row Boeing is down Osulinn Boing is not at 110 today is it !</Title><Msg>So far Tom O"brien nailed it, and a boeing hot air investor named osulinn attention your BA is not, like osulinn said going to $110today, osulinn is a hot aired Boeing investor with no stock chart skills as I pointed out yesterday. Osulinn how's that hopey changy thing working for you now ? yesterday osulinn hoped that Boeing would be 110 today, and he is wrong as usual. the 12 prediction in a month off. Osulinn as I told you, learn a skill set above hopie , changie. Boeing has to break its recent high of 107 and hold for two week to go above 107 and for the week it has not been able to hold 106 so you need to learn how to trade then you too can be up over 350% in TSLA for the year to date instead of down for the week on you boeing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376055958650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376056116778-47</Id><Title>to the investors that slander me because you cant get a break on BA ha ha TSLA up over 350% this year</Title><Msg>learn to read a stock chart</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056116778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376056122703-48</Id><Topic><Title>Am I to understand that I will be slandered and taunted until I leave Boeing message board?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1375992816066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW! guess you don't read your own posts</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376056122703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376056405466-49</Id><Topic><Title>Am I to understand that I will be slandered and taunted until I leave Boeing message board?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1375992816066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow goes to show you uniposter you have not shown any proof of your statement that I have said I am rich, you just made a typical slanderous, unsubstantiated claim, your a troll who is angry that your Boeing is not up like my TSLA and your mad at me. Rich is a relative term, Steve Jobs was rich, Paul Allen is rich, Bill Gates is rich unposter76 down from uniposter, your a fool unposter76 and a slanderous liar Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056405466</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376056498247-50</Id><Topic><Title>to the investors that slander me because you cant get a break on BA ha ha TSLA up over 350% this year</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056116778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well well well Boeing is in the 105 range now down from the 107 range look like Tom O.Brien is right for now BA will peak at 107 and retreat to 71 dollars Tom OBrien is a professional stock trader.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056498247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376056565671-51</Id><Topic><Title>to the investors that slander me because you cant get a break on BA ha ha TSLA up over 350% this year</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056116778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one on this board has slandered you. But are we to expect you to continue to libel Boeing?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376056565671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:56:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376056678233-52</Id><Topic><Title>for the 5th day in a row Boeing is down Osulinn Boing is not at 110 today is it !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376055958650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>attention boeing investors who are mad at me TSLA is up this morning your stock Boeing is down how about that losers</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056678233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376056780325-53</Id><Title>DICKWAYNEDICK-FEB...</Title><Msg>Tsla--who cares? Tom o'brien...yeah he is right about $ 70+.... That is after 2 for one stock split.....he forgot to mention the split factor!....</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376056780325</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376056795811-54</Id><Title>osulinn is Boeing at 110 today ?</Title><Msg>osulinn how's that hopey change thing working out for you now eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056795811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376057026111-55</Id><Topic><Title>for the 5th day in a row Boeing is down Osulinn Boing is not at 110 today is it !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376055958650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45 really you now are dreaming of a boeing split when it is going down your a fool domerrrrr45 well maybe a reverse split for boeing if it starts to tank real bad</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376057026111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376057357420-56</Id><Topic><Title>for the 5th day in a row Boeing is down Osulinn Boing is not at 110 today is it !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376055958650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeeveritas Boeing is down for the 5th day in a row that is a fact, you claim that is liable of Boeing? your a fool freeveritas TSLA is up all year long that is a fact not liable get it now your in the wrong stock . I am in the right stock learn to read a stock chart and then you too can make better choices</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376057357420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376057758117-57</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>learn to read a stock chart Boeing trolls Boeing lost the most money of all Dow stocks yesterday it was the dog of the dow, today it is not doing any better you should be in Airbus or TSLA</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376057758117</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376057831174-58</Id><Topic><Title>for the 5th day in a row Boeing is down Osulinn Boing is not at 110 today is it !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376055958650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O'brien has n't nailed anything dimbag wyane...is boeing $ 70? Still trading above $ 100...actually jerry o'shea predicted boeing to hit $ 130+ in next 12 months and jerry has a great track record....</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376057831174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376057939895-59</Id><Title>DICKWAYNEDICK-FEB TESLA....</Title><Msg>Who cares, who cares about tesla in boeing boards...go gloat in teslaland! Moron!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376057939895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376058380594-60</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That period of time was one of the worse times in this country for the working man 1890`s being the worse and if it were not for slaves and many Chinese working for next to nothing our rail roads would of not been able to be built. also this is 2013 like over a hundred years of passed we need to move forward not backwards sorry.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1376058380594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376058640889-61</Id><Title>so I expect TSLA to pull back or go flat for a while after earings but I just made 3 dollars per share and sold on a day trade</Title><Msg>Boeing investors when was the last time you could make 3 dollars per share on Boeing in less than a hour ? never ! you keep up that hopey changey thing and I will read a stock chart I just made $3000 in a less than a hour trade on TSLA if you read my user comments on May 3 I told you to buy TSLA and 15 days later at a 100% gain I said sell and go with day trading until it breaks out of the Bollinger band that happened yesterday now you know what to do if you follow me. However, today was right after a earning report and a big up side gain so there are always traders late to the show who will run it up in the morning . I just took their money. Its real simple to learn how to trade just spend 30 years on the street learning to develop your skill set Never follow a guy like osulinn who has made several hot air predictions always that Boeing will be up on a certain date or for the year there are several like barbing who say trust her she works for Boeing it will be 120 by a certain time that time cam and went these people are fools</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376058640889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376058763744-62</Id><Topic><Title>for the 5th day in a row Boeing is down Osulinn Boing is not at 110 today is it !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376055958650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets bump this for domerrrrr45 freeveritas and osulinn all boeing investors not TSLA investors way to go, fools</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376058763744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376059030955-63</Id><Title>New investor on Board... Came in a few weeks back to day trade a bad day for BA and decided to stay long..</Title><Msg>I have been playing many stocks and after digging into the financials ,ect this is the only decent stock I have come across that has a solid future... Others seem to be the latest fad compared... I think I hit on a good one here with many years of orders under their belt already... 120.00 before years end ...gl</Msg><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1376059030955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376059500074-64</Id><Topic><Title>New investor on Board... Came in a few weeks back to day trade a bad day for BA and decided to stay long..</Title><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1376059030955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welcome aboard. Just be aware that the wayneker will call you a loser and a hack if you only make 14% in 5 months.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376059500074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376059875976-65</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You rock, star.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376059875976</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376060082743-66</Id><Topic><Title>New investor on Board... Came in a few weeks back to day trade a bad day for BA and decided to stay long..</Title><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1376059030955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have already read some posts ..I always abuse my ignore button upon entering a new board and often have to update it when new ID's are made... That aside..... I can't believe their isn't more interest in BA...Did I hear right that they have a 29 yr work load? and a new factory...</Msg><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1376060082743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376060115550-67</Id><Topic><Title>so I expect TSLA to pull back or go flat for a while after earings but I just made 3 dollars per share and sold on a day trade</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376058640889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeveritas you just accused me of liable against Boeing and in the same breath you welcome someone to the board and single me out that is slander I have had nothing to say to the guy and your making a liable statement about me , a double standard nope, your just a liar boeing boy " 1 Reply . Welcome aboard. Just be aware that the wayneker will call you a loser and a hack if you only make 14% in 5 months. Define loser, freeveritas is is a person who makes 3 dollars in TSLa today on a hour trade over 350% gain in TSLa this year to date or a guy like freeveritas who has miss and followed me with apple , acad and now tsla and not be able to connect the dots and made any money</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376060115550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376060318588-68</Id><Topic><Title>for the 5th day in a row Boeing is down Osulinn Boing is not at 110 today is it !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376055958650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets bump this for freeveritas who just liabled me with a " new to the board guy" less than an hour after freeveritas claimed I liabled Boeing so double standard , nope freeveritas is jealous of me, as he been following me for the miss he made on Apple then ACAD and now tsla , you cant teach stupid freveritass</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376060318588</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376060769374-69</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is a racists and here is proof</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376024397043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 00:59:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The initiative says nothing of the kind, nice try racist.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1376060769374</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376060908823-70</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeveritass you just liabled me with a "new to the board" guy and yet you are mad at me for allegedly libeling Boeing. freeveritass the crapola contributor, is this a double standard? freeveritass, nope your a Boeing investor who did not follow me on apple and then did not follow me on acad and now has not followed my on tsla and your just a angry guy at your poor choices that is your fault if you weren't stupid you would follow me on my next pick but you cant make the connection Wayne said buy apple until Steve jobs died , you missed thousands of percent gains , wayne said buy ACAD it went up 1200 last year, your friend sparti said buy IGZ ,IGZ is a symbol but it is not a real stock, it does not exist as a stock it is a software testing tool, Wayne said on may 3 buy TSLA in 15 days it gained 100% you just are too stupid to learn freeveritas that is not laible it is a fact I define being stupid as any person that can not learn from good stock pick suggestions and then is unable or unwilling to be connecting the dots . experiences should teach you same for domerrrrr45 I bub you curlie and sicne domerrrrr45 is real mad , he is dubbed Moe and I dub osulinn as larry</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376060908823</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:08:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376060970571-71</Id><Topic><Title>so I expect TSLA to pull back or go flat for a while after earings but I just made 3 dollars per share and sold on a day trade</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376058640889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO CAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARRES!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376060970571</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376061237239-72</Id><Topic><Title>New investor on Board... Came in a few weeks back to day trade a bad day for BA and decided to stay long..</Title><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1376059030955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:37:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dmorgan2151 please tell us more on Boeing, we may all be unable todo any research on Boeing. Next dmorgan2151, you seem to be almost ready to tell us investors more about why you think Boeing is a great investment did you realize Airbus has bettered Boeing by gaining in stock value much more than boeing ? I am not impressed , dmorgan2151, you have the support of the other Boeing pumpers already, and you just signed on, wow just like you people are planning this welcome ha ha ha hit he ignore button now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376061237239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376061336056-73</Id><Topic><Title>for the 5th day in a row Boeing is down Osulinn Boing is not at 110 today is it !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376055958650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:45:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets bump this for the , ha ha ha new board member , who just loves Boeing stock wow and he is supporeted by the Boeing pumpers too , imagine that ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376061336056</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376061456695-74</Id><Topic><Title>so I expect TSLA to pull back or go flat for a while after earings but I just made 3 dollars per share and sold on a day trade</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376058640889</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 10:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>domerrrrr45 I thought you had better things to do and I was a loser for posting all day on the Boeing message board, how does that work again domerrrrr45 you follow me all day and your ok? LOL</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376061456695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376061551364-75</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets bump this for larry , moe and Curlie aka osulinn, domerrrrr45 and freeveritass</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376061551364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376061603360-76</Id><Topic><Title>osulinn is Boeing at 110 today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056795811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>calling out osulinn</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376061603360</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376062156312-77</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOUR MOTHER IS SERVING US WELL....TY TY TY MOM!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1376062156312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376062530933-78</Id><Topic><Title>osulinn is Boeing at 110 today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056795811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try singing a line from "Indian Love Song".</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376062530933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:35:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376062637058-79</Id><Topic><Title>osulinn is Boeing at 110 today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056795811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction; Make that "Indian Love Call'.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376062637058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376063494411-80</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only for you illegal aliens like you floyd</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1376063494411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376063565392-81</Id><Title>for 5 days Boeing down 2.87% TSLA up almost 12% that explains TSLA up for one year 427%</Title><Msg>so TSLA stock price is up a great old Boeing number 747% for 3 years at 12% per week that would be about 600% for the year gain , not going to happen but TSLA may be, most likely, a real growth stock for some time. I watch the stock chart and trade accordingly. until I see anything that indicates a change its TSLA for me . I saw the Apple change , it was easy, Steve jobs died and had no person to take his place. Right now Elon Musk of TSLA is still in charge , very simple , next watch the stock chart. Boeing not so good a failure at GE, named James McNerney, sent packing by th famous Jack Welch, crash landed on Boeing. James Mcnerney was a a mediocre MMM executive and way overpaid at Boeing , so he has no incentive to do anything for the Boeing shareholders . Elon Musk, makes his money by making and selling his companies like paypal he made it and sold it for 1.5 billion. James McNerney has never made anything, but failure and mediocre performance . He was hired by a temporary man , no airplane experienced as temporary CEO of Boeing, Lewis Platt was a very poor person to make a choice, Lew Platt. . If it were a HP style company then Lew Platt could have made a informed choice as he was the HP CEO that is not airplane making .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376063565392</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376063730184-82</Id><Topic><Title>osulinn is Boeing at 110 today ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376056795811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when heckling works for stock selection I will give it a try</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376063730184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376064227616-83</Id><Topic><Title>for 5 days Boeing down 2.87% TSLA up almost 12% that explains TSLA up for one year 427%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376063565392</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 11:52:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump this for freeveritass who is heckling me now go freeveritass if heckling makes you feel better and sooths your heart when you look at how much better TSLA is than Boeing and you could have followed my May 3 suggestion to buy TSLA you would have made 100% gain in just 15 trade days and now much much more , but you didn't you stuck with Boeing that was your choice ,now man up and live with it</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376064227616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376064994315-84</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tsk, tsk. First, floydian isn't a illegal citizen and second I'm surprised that someone like you would use such demeaning language. Undocumented citizen if you would, please.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1376064994315</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376065830409-85</Id><Title>Every time a red candle with a long tail shows up after running down... It has a nice run..</Title><Msg>So far it's looking good for that to show up on the yearly chart.... On avg 3 to 4 bucks...</Msg><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1376065830409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376066114271-86</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And there were bank panics on a regular basis: 19th century Panic of 1819, a U.S. recession with bank failures; culmination of U.S.'s first boom-to-bust economic cycle Panic of 1825, a pervasive British recession in which many banks failed, nearly including the Bank of England Panic of 1837, a U.S. recession with bank failures, followed by a 5-year depression Panic of 1847, United Kingdom Panic of 1857, a U.S. recession with bank failures Panic of 1866, Europe Panic of 1873, a U.S. recession with bank failures, followed by a 4-year depression Panic of 1884, United States and Europe Panic of 1890, mainly affecting the United Kingdom and Argentina Panic of 1893, a U.S. recession with bank failures Australian banking crisis of 1893 20th century Panic of 1907, a U.S. economic recession with bank failures Great Depression, the worst systemic banking crisis of the 20th century People grew weary of losing their money and demanded more stability hence the Federal Reserve, oh wait they had a Federal Reserve in 1930 it's just that under Hoover and Carnegie they thought their job was to keep the supply of money low. That didn't work out very well, hence the modern version that took us through the time when the U.S. became THE economic superpower of the world but it reverted to a free market model under Greenspan, that didn't work out very well.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1376066114271</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376066160790-87</Id><Title>slow start to August</Title><Msg>Thru Thursday only 9 planes have been delivered. 1 787 and the rest 737's. But the amount of predelivery test flights out of everett has risen significantly and includes all planes in the BA family. What has been puzzling is the lack of air activity at Charleston. There are a lot of 787's ready for delivery and they need to open that spigot.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376066160790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376066682532-88</Id><Topic><Title>how many of you think BA break 110 this Friday?</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1375986793640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 14:33:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>burrrrrp</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376066682532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376067090350-89</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you're leaving out of the equation is the (for a time) limitless national resources easily extractable by new technologies, and a policy of optimized immigration bringing in a docile workforce to fill the factories and farm the plains.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376067090350</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376072254495-90</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wayne said buy apple until Steve jobs died" Can you point to any of your posts (near Jobs death) that said you were getting out of Apple? Didn't think so.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376072254495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 14:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376072433201-91</Id><Topic><Title>slow start to August</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376066160790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see the news has they just won a big military contract ..I guess it's ho hum for any excitement over it....The stock barely moved..It just follows the dow... Needs to detach itself from it..</Msg><Username>dmorgan2151</Username><Timestamp>1376072433201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 14:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376072993777-92</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty can't see those bust cycles through his loon-colored glasses. Ain't libertarianism wonderful?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376072993777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 14:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376073009074-93</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Steve" Jobs (February 24, 1955 – October 5, 2011) waynedickenson961 2814 posts | Last Activity: 2 hours 23 minutes ago Member since: Aug 30, 2012 Just facts here</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1376073009074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 14:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376074605134-94</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He needs to review the "cross of gold" speech one more time.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376074605134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 14:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376074650125-95</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to mention Irish.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376074650125</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 14:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376074977016-96</Id><Topic><Title>how many of you think BA break 110 this Friday?</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1375986793640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 14:33:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MFI confirms. The MFI at the recent peak, low relative to the MFI at the early July peak, is a bearish sign.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1376074977016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 15:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376076005397-97</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This probably doesn't belong on the BA message board, but interesting to me.and maybe others(these are just rough numbers so don't get upset if they aren't exact) 10/11 AAPL $425 8/12 AAPL $600 10/12 AAPL $700 Today AAPL $454</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1376076005397</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 15:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376076857739-98</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven may have many aliases, but he is still one DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1376076857739</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 15:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376079468520-99</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You cannot libel a person by stating facts, since truth is an absolute defense in libel cases. His facts about you are good; your facts about Boeing and other posters are nonsense.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1376079468520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 16:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376083638958-100</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991, you said," spartacus99991 • 3 hours ago Flag 3 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 2 Reply . "Wayne said buy apple until Steve jobs died" Can you point to any of your posts (near Jobs death) that said you were getting out of Apple? Didn't think so." How does that work you ask me a question and then answer it like I can not prove it, what kind of dirty trick is that? Tell me again about IGZ as long as your making up your own answers . The answer is yes I did say that once Steve jobs died that the replacements were paid huge money and he worked for only 1 dollar per year the rest was on stock price gain, so the Apple company like Boeing is not going to be any good going forward and I said it several times</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376083638958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 17:27:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376083650191-101</Id><Topic><Title>wayne#$%$ on Airbus engineering failures</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1375997733488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 17:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how he never talks about airbusts failures.How about the wing cracks on the a380?</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376083650191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 17:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376083767626-102</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take a break.After your posting frenzy this morning.</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1376083767626</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 17:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376085062526-103</Id><Title>spartacus99991 on WD not mentioning that apple would not be good after jos died,</Title><Msg>"spartacus99991 since you said that TSLA was better on may 28 than Boeing I looked it up after the 15 day 100% gain I called on may 3 to buy TSLA it had already made a 1005 gain prior to may 28 and went up a lot more but lets make a point here . Using your statement and going only from may28, , to Friday the last trade day7/12/2013 , tesla is up another 16.92% from closing on May 28 to Friday TSLA it went from $110.33 to $129 that is a gain of another 16.92% spartacus99991 your arguing with me , just like with ACAD now, spartacus99991, your still a fool and can't trade Boeing is not a good stock since may 28 Boeing has gone from 100.11 to Friday 101.87 a gain of only 1.18% now since the reason I told you Boeing is a bad stock is they have a MD style business plan , that has already been proven to end in bankruptcy, you worked for MD that is your problem and might be why you hate me . Md -Boeing it will never be any good, the whole stock run upfor Boeing in the last 4 months is based on the 4 month grounding and stock buyback and that can only go on so long, eventually like MD- Boeing is going to go bankrupt. Why because like the MD management , the 747 fix, it failed the 737 MAX based on MD business plan will fail and the 777 X will fail for the same reason you can't think right spartacus99991 , so you will never get it Hart- Smith was right and it applies to all Boeing planes not just the 787.I told you that Apple was done a long time ago once Steve jobs died, he and Elon Musk are very similar they both don't work for big up front money , they earn it like I did each day.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376085062526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 17:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376085814491-104</Id><Title>you missed Tesla now pay attention Elon Musk on the Hyperloop, August 12 , 2013 start reading, sell Boeing</Title><Msg>The fevered speculation about billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk's mysterious "Hyperloop" transport system is about to come to an end. Musk, the visionary behind electric-car firm Tesla and the private spaceflight company SpaceX, has said he will unveil a Hyperloop design on Monday (Aug. 12), after teasing the world about the superfast travel technology for more than a year. The solar-powered Hyperloop would allow passengers to get from Los Angeles to San Francisco in less than 30 minutes, Musk has said, meaning it must travel at speeds greater than 600 mph (966 km/h). The system would be cheap and convenient, he added, with tickets costing less than a seat aboard a plane or train and Hyperloop vehicles departing frequently from their various stations. Though we don't know exactly how the Hyperloop will work or what it will look like, Musk has dropped some hints since first disclosing the concept in July 2012. For example, this past May he described the Hyperloop as a "cross between a Concorde and a railgun and an air hockey table."</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376085814491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 18:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376088951781-105</Id><Title>Executive Orders to protect black school childred from discipline. Obama is a racist</Title><Msg>Obama Tells Teachers Not To Reprimand Black Pres. Obama is asking public school teachers to “take it easy” on black students who misbehave. On July 26, 2012, Obama signed an Executive Order to create the African American Education Initiative. The order births a new federal bureaucracy and effectively offers black students a green light to misbehave at school. Advertisement Obama asked public school teachers to reduce the number of disciplinary actions taken against black students. Specifically, it calls on schools to “not rely on methods that result in disparate use of disciplinary tools.” The order, however, does not include any suggestions to improve black students’ inappropriate behavior. Members of the new bureaucracy will work to pressure public school systems into complying with the president’s order. To do that, public schools must utilize a quota system. That’s right, a quota system. The U.S. Department of Justice’s Bureau of Justice Statistics reports, “There is a huge crime rate disparity between blacks and other racial groups.” So, wouldn’t it make sense that black students were discipline more frequently? DOJ’s report shows that homicide rates in black communities are nine times higher than in white communities. Subsequently, 93 percent of black homicide victims are killed by black perpetrators. But Obama argues that disciplining black students isn’t fair because they “lack equal access” to quality education. Let’s look at the facts. Washington, D.C. spends the highest amount on average per student of any U.S. state or territory. D.C. public schools also “educate” more black students than anywhere else in the country. Despite D.C.’s “overfunding” public schools, they are “widely touted as the worst performing schools in the entire industrialized world.” Obama’s motives for this initiative are clearly flawed but isn't it flawed in every aspect of his p</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1376088951781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 18:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376093434188-106</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you link to a post (around October 2011, when Jobs died) where you said you were out of Apple? Not something much later where you say you got out before the big drop. If not, then you're doing it in hindsight. Prove me wrong.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376093434188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 20:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376093846750-107</Id><Topic><Title>spartacus99991 on WD not mentioning that apple would not be good after jos died,</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376085062526</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 17:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't trade individual stocks. Most of my investments are not in the stock market. I had met Hart-Smith in Long Beach in the 80s and I've read and agree with his paper. BTW, BA closed today at 105.33. What's this 101.87 nonsense?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1376093846750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 20:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376094927677-108</Id><Topic><Title>how many of you think BA break 110 this Friday?</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1375986793640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 14:33:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zero.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1376094927677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 20:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376096206696-109</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I noted earlier, that will be difficult to provide something from 2011. Again, as Joe Friday would say on Hawaii 5-o, "just the facts ma'am" .) waynedickenson961 2814 posts | Last Activity: 2 hours 23 minutes ago Member since: Aug 30, 2012 I'm sure I'll get slammed for using facts on this post</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1376096206696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 20:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376096715066-110</Id><Title>Great that Boeings ScanEagle one of the first two approved for US use UAV's</Title><Msg>Very nice as they predict that by 2020 the UAV industry will be a forget---its either 11 billion or 22 billion. Will try and find which one now, but either number is nice and large</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376096715066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 21:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376097140400-111</Id><Topic><Title>Great that Boeings ScanEagle one of the first two approved for US use UAV's</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376096715066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 21:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its 11.4 Billion market by 2022 was the prediction</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376097140400</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 21:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376097712299-112</Id><Topic><Title>slow start to August</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376066160790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe with all the new products coming they need to open up more lines for the 737 and 787. We have a little while for the tanker. Maybe the lack of air activity is due to additional and perhaps redundant quality checks and the effect of the Honeywell story. Boeing needs to reduce their backlog and have shorter delivery schedules. If that means more lines, than so be it. Waiting 5-7 years for some new planes if ridiculous. More lines---address customer delivery requirements better. A penny saved could lose market share by not being robust enough with delivery. Think of Northrop in WWII spitting out those planes daily at an incredible rate. Its possible.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1376097712299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 21:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376098676759-113</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday Boeing lost the most money of all 30 stocks on the Dow</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1376054911923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 09:28:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Above post should have refered to Dragnet, not Hawaii 5-o, that would have been "book em Dano".</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1376098676759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 21:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376101722946-114</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bust cycles are required ...its part of the ebb and flow of Capitalism....Hey did you notice before the Fed...that there was virtually NO inflation for our entire nations history...</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376101722946</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 22:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376101836777-115</Id><Topic><Title>This black MD angered Obama at the National Prayer Breakfast</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1375973825972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 10:57:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O'Bama isn't too bright . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376101836777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 22:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376101923533-116</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Marxists tell NFL NO celebrating TD's.......</Title><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1375997102053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-08-08 17:25:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberal Marxists can kiss my Obama . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1376101923533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 22:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376101972444-117</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should review the Documentary's "the Secret of Oz" or "The Money Masters" It does not matter if money is backed by Gold or Silver or even sticks with shavings in them (as was the case in William the Conquerer's time) ...but Fiat money..BACKED BY NOTHING ALWAYS FAILS AND ALWAYS WILL THROUGHOUT HUMAN HISTORY...just because youbelieve it has not totally failed or WILL not fail in America, is "normalacy bias" ...it CAN AND IT WILL</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376101972444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 22:32:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376102424874-118</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not romantacising that period. Each period has its good points and bad. But per capita there was a huge surge in small business...Are you arguing that the slavery they left in China was any better then the so called slavery they got in America ? Or that the Potato famine Irish left in Ireland was a BETTER standard of living ? There was a REASON immigrants came to America? When you figure it out why let me know.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376102424874</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 22:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376103946409-119</Id><Topic><Title>slow start to August</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376066160790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rumor has it that there are quality issues with the Charleston planes.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1376103946409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 23:05:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376104966535-120</Id><Topic><Title>slow start to August</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376066160790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 12:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It appears that the delivery issues have nothing to do with either production or quality issues. It seems that has more to do with cutomers and delivery dates. There are 737 first flights every day. The planes sitting on the flight line in Charleston are there due to customer issues. These seem to be almost over. July started slow and finished up quite well. So I believe that these isues will start to fade in the last of August/ start of September. Only time will tell.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1376104966535</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 23:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1376105041936-121</Id><Topic><Title>The Best time in Human history happened without a Federal Reserve and No IRS.</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1376049017080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 07:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WRONG, the worst inflations in our history occured in the 1740s, 1780s, 1790s, 1815, 1865, 1920s with lots of deflation in between. Fun times 20%+ inflation followed by deflation. Much worse inflation than the worst in the post Fed period during the early 1970s and there were no deflationary years except possibly 2008 after the Greenspan debacle.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1376105041936</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 23:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1376106522609-122</Id><Title>Letter from Boeing today</Title><Msg>I opened it with gleeful anticipation. This would be the invite and tickets to the Family Day. Hey! whats this, its not tickets but its an invite. An invite to give them my email address and they promise to send me news releases on whats happening. Well if that don't just take the cake. Listen James or whoever is running that place I have a pretty read on whats going on up there, in fact if you follow my post, you will find out things that you didn't know. You could let us know what those technical issues are that the 787's keep returning to field for. Hope those tickets get here soon.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1376106522609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-08-09 23:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>