<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358053862051-1</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BITE-ME AND HIS SILVER FOOT IN MOUTH</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358034415368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so which group will he target next ?</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358053862051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 00:11:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358056663916-2</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BITE-ME AND HIS SILVER FOOT IN MOUTH</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358034415368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Says he is shooting for tuesday. But his things shoot out of both ends so there is no sure victim. The ricochets may get em. He aims to target any of conservative values. Says he has mining roots, but those coal miners would have kicked his #$%$ out of the mine the first day. Have we triggered all of the redflag words yet?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358056663916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 00:57:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358058870791-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's kids schools has 11 armed guards</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358039461020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:11:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most news reports said Sidwell school already had 11 armed guards before the addition of the normal complement of Secret Service agents. Many Washington DC politicians and newsmen (like David Gregory) send their children there.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1358058870791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 01:34:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358059638799-4</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BITE-ME AND HIS SILVER FOOT IN MOUTH</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358034415368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have we triggered all of the redflag words yet? Well- the killer word would be to call him a a a a re pub li can !</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358059638799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 01:47:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358062786251-5</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BITE-ME AND HIS SILVER FOOT IN MOUTH</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358034415368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:46:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In any case the trigger man or hit man. To say sharp shooter would be wild shot.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358062786251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 02:39:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358063766747-6</Id><Title>Think outside the box when replacing search planes, bidders urge Ottawa</Title><Msg>Boeing trying to lure Canada into their web. Goes on then saying the v-22 can conduct rescues. (water rescues) it can't of course. Pay attention Canada, these dirt bags are lying to you.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358063766747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 02:56:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358065528992-7</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With respect to the 787, Boeing management went with the McDonnall logic of off load everything. The engineers said it didn't work for Mac and it won't work for the 787 and that proved to be correct. Armies of Boeing engineers, at mind boggling costs, were sent to the vendors to fix problems that never would have occurred had management listened to the engineers to begin with. Once again Boeing and to some degree the Speea union don't really understand that the labor troubles with the engineers isn't really over money.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1358065528992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 03:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358066636580-8</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>phantomfield, Sadly you are a victim of Boeing Chicago management spin. Let me help you with your misperception. The 787 outsourced planes cost an extra 30 billion that is 25 billion more than SPEEA could have engineered the 787 and got it to the customer on time. 2. Phantomfield, you seem to think Boeing paid engineers are greedy, ,did you know the CEO of Boeing has no problem taking huge amounts of money from the Boeing shareholders for himself? Chief Executive Jim McNerney earned a total compensation of almost $23 million in 2011, up 16 percent from $19.7 million in 2010, according to the company's annual proxy filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).The Boeing shareholders are being robbed now by the Boeing executives, you know the MD executives that run Boeing now after bankrupting MD with the same business plan. So look at the McNerney pay and the other executives of Boeing . The executives at Boeing are robbing the shareholders of Boeing before they take the company into bankruptcy.. . Boeing will become bankrupt over the next 10 years.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358066636580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 03:43:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358073604018-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama arms the Muslim Brotherhood.......</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033206593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So which one are you?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358073604018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 05:40:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358073752023-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you claiming to be a normal American? You sound like another DFC to me.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358073752023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 05:42:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358074075348-11</Id><Topic><Title>Mony people on here have asked Why Democrats Hate Freedom so Much?</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1358027642023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:54:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= Don't forget more government means less freedom..= Says who?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1358074075348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 05:47:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358076361533-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>= What terrifies normal Americans is the thought of paranoid freaks like Spartaloonkook being armed.= You are 100% right about that... Study spartakook's posts here and you'll understand what made Tim McVeigh tick. And, you'll understand what needs to done to PREVENT such mass murders.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1358076361533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 06:26:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358084736214-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary, wondering what the latest BA Blog had in store, while I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a yapping, As of some one gently yapping, yapping like a bloody bore. Tis the loser from Kent," I muttered, "yapping like a bloody bore - Only this, and nothing more.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358084736214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 08:45:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358084841956-14</Id><Topic><Title>An Administration that could stage "Fast and Furious...</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033942580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:39:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358084841956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 08:47:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358084957465-15</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"rely on better men than themselves to make a living and protect them, that's why they crave big governemt" Some don't work at all...or were fired from their last job</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358084957465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 08:49:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358085070157-16</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of Taking the Hypocritical Oath...did you see where Piers Morgan is calling for killing Alex Jones....with a Semi-Auto.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358085070157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 08:51:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358085459270-17</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here come the ignorant attacks on the messenger not being able to contest one point of contention! Remember, ignorance can be overcome..idiocity is one's for life. I'm afraid most leftists on this thread are stuck with their condition.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358085459270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 08:57:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358086299403-18</Id><Title>Thank GOD....</Title><Msg>for the gun control issue that Obama seeks to take advantage of crazies commiting mass murders, and now wanting to take away good citizens guns, and circumvent the 2nd Ammendment. Obama, and the left have created millions of new gun owners...shops sold out of guns, and ammo. In Arizona where the govt set up a buy back of guns, 200 clunkers were bought back at tax payer expense, and gun dealers setup booths not far away, and bought back guns that worked!! This is going to cost congressional democrats bigtime in next years midterms. HAHAHAHA</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358086299403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 09:11:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358087008948-19</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also share the sentiment that a handful of top executives are ripping off the company. But they can justify their actions in a court of a law because that's what the market bears for senior executives at Fortune 100 companies. That does not justify thousands of engineers trying to rip off the company as well. It is not a valid excuse that because several can get away with ripping off the company thousands should be able to do the same. That attitude will ruin Boeing.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358087008948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 09:23:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358089949886-20</Id><Title>Charlie Daniels: Precedent shows...They want ALL of your guns</Title><Msg>When the Supreme Court, or any other court for that matter, makes a ruling in a case they first look for precedent, in other words to see if there has been a court decision rendered on the same subject in the past and usually defer to the old decision in ruling on the case. The greatest teacher in life is experience; it only takes one time of burning your fingers on a hot stove to know that you never want to touch another one. The next greatest teacher is observation, paying attention to someone else's experiences and profiting from their wins and losses, trials and errors. In my generation I have seen the rise and fall of fascism, communism, different experiments in socialism and the kind of downright social and fiscal foolishness that leads to what has recently happened in Greece. There is an old saying that those who do not learn from history are doomed to repeat it. There is at this time a huge debate in our nation about the private ownership of firearms. The president and the anti-gun crowd claim they do not want to do away with private ownership, that they only want to modify the existing laws having to do with assault weapons -which can be construed as anything in your gun cabinet of any heavy caliber - and clips for semiautomatic weapons holding more than 10 bullets. I submit to you that what is going on here is the first assault on private gun ownership They will take what ever they can get now and continue to chip away until all you can legally own to protect your family with is a baseball bat. Did you know that one of the major reasons the Japanese did not attempt to land troops on the American coast during World War Two is because they knew that Americans owned guns and would fight tooth and nail for every inch of shore line. Hitler disarmed Germany, Stalin disarmed Russia, and Mao disarmed China. The mainstream media is quick to report any kind of gun violence but omit the stories where lives have been saved by legally owned guns in the hands of good citizens and the stories are many and varied all across the country. Let's look at some precedent: In 1997, many Aussies were forced to give up their privately owned firearms. Over 630,000 were turned in to be destroyed as part of a "buyback plan" by the Australian government. Total cost of the buyback? $500,000,000. One year later, here were the results: Homicides nationwide: Up 6.2% Assaults nationwide: Up 9.6% Armed robberies nationwide: Up 44% In the state of Victoria alone, homicides with firearms went up 300%. Five years later, a "continued modest decline" in homicides was noted, but what has gone up in the land down under over the past few years is the number of assaults. Overall, assaults are up 40% and sexual assaults are up 20%. Across the pond, Great Britain passed a handgun ban in 1998. Ten years later, many British "bobbies" are armed for the first time because of the amount of illegal guns in the hands of criminals. Have you read about gun bans resulting in more gun violence or seen it on the television news? Do you think it's newsworthy? America, no matter what Obama, Biden, Pelosi, Reid and the rest of the far left in America say, they want your guns. They want them all. Don't just wait and see. What do you think? Pray for our troops God Bless America Charlie Daniels</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358089949886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 10:12:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358094710094-21</Id><Title>Cars Leaking Fuel???</Title><Msg>If a new car was leaking fuel, they have a major recall. If a new jetplane leaking fuel, no big deal? just saying</Msg><Username>oneshotcarson</Username><Timestamp>1358094710094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:31:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358095267227-22</Id><Topic><Title>America Needs Government but Who Should say fir it.......</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1358008972712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:42:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only in Mir(de)-world is three references to something a "typo." Must be tough to be this handicapped. A total fraud and sloppy prevaricator.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1358095267227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:41:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358095359890-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's kids schools has 11 armed guards</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358039461020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:11:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Many Washington DC politicians and newsmen (like David Gregory) send their children there." In others words, multiple kids there are high profile targets. It is a private school with lot's of kids of wealthy parents (who, by the way, PAY for those guards), not particularly compareable to a public school.</Msg><Username>rividiot</Username><Timestamp>1358095359890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:42:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358095709099-24</Id><Topic><Title>Charlie Daniels: Precedent shows...They want ALL of your guns</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358089949886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 10:12:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you suppose the Liberals/Progressives/Communists/Marxists/Nazis hate Charlie Daniels so much?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358095709099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358095820590-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama arms the Muslim Brotherhood.......</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358033206593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:26:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, who should be armed?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358095820590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:50:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358096304981-26</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They sit at home collecting their welfare checks while stuffing their face with Twinkies and posting about the benefits of Communism.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358096304981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:58:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358096366918-27</Id><Title>It's A Fact, Teabaggers Still Eating The Most 'Gummit' Welfare Cheese.</Title><Msg>Just google "teabaggers" and "welfare cheese"</Msg><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1358096366918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:59:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358096848050-28</Id><Topic><Title>It's A Fact, Teabaggers Still Eating The Most 'Gummit' Welfare Cheese.</Title><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1358096366918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:59:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need more something, but probably not vacation.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1358096848050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:07:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358097331051-29</Id><Topic><Title>Charlie Daniels: Precedent shows...They want ALL of your guns</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358089949886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 10:12:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because he represents Bedrock American values. Its not about Guns ...its about control</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358097331051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:15:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358097428997-30</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is very true. I find libs to be very creepy! Its hard to believe that people can be so twisted like they obviously are. I guess it's the result of living under continuous propaganda. They lie as easily as they breath, and like breathing, they usually don't even notice they are doing it.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1358097428997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:17:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358098713455-31</Id><Topic><Title>VERY SOON A 787 WILL CRASH !</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1357937337312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 15:48:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, It's COST first, SCHEDULE second, and QUALITY someplace near the end. It's a good short term business strategy, but long term it doesn't work too good. That's not the way Boeing used to be, but that's what they have now, and actually ever since Condit took over years ago. Mulally tried to keep things going, but the politics were set against him. The current leaders of Boeing won that battle. It will be interesting to see how this will all play out. Its sort of like watching an ultra slow motion train wreak!</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1358098713455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 12:38:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358100370414-32</Id><Title>The good news is it makes the plane lighter when the fuel leaks out....</Title><Msg>less weight cheaper to fly I think that is what BA must be thinking. Unless they run out of fuel half way across the Atlantic Ocean but still should be ok every body has a life vest right !</Msg><Username>craigcrrd</Username><Timestamp>1358100370414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:06:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358103390140-33</Id><Title>Ho do you maintain Air Worthiness certification with leaking fuel?</Title><Msg>YOU CAN'T!</Msg><Username>captain_of_truth</Username><Timestamp>1358103390140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:56:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358103495994-34</Id><Title>A New Class of Boeing Employees</Title><Msg>There is a new breed of Boeing employees with a positive outlook. They actually see themselves as Boeing career persons. They find working at Boeing interesting and exciting. They are satisfied with their pay and the family lifestyle it affords. They have team spirit and take pride with every airplane produced. They want Boeing to be prosperous, successful and number 1 and they certainly do not want to stand in the way of Boeing. They believe job security comes from Boeing successes. They want their union to work both for themselves and for Boeing. They are telling their union settle, settle settle with Boeing we have what it takes to succeed. We do not want a strike.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358103495994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:58:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358104603005-35</Id><Topic><Title>Cars Leaking Fuel???</Title><Username>oneshotcarson</Username><Timestamp>1358094710094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:31:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depends. Did you ever overfill your car's tank and have some gasoline run down the side. Did you report that to the authorities for a recall?</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1358104603005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:16:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358104939057-36</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"will become bankrupt over the next 10 years." Someone on this board said it would be 5 years. Good to hear that there's another 5 years for workers to get to retirement.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1358104939057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:22:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358106320981-37</Id><Topic><Title>A New Class of Boeing Employees</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358103495994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:58:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you mean "WE" ( mbfield ) - Boeing does not build, assemble or do significant airplane work in New York NY !!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358106320981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:45:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358106394534-38</Id><Topic><Title>Ho do you maintain Air Worthiness certification with leaking fuel?</Title><Username>captain_of_truth</Username><Timestamp>1358103390140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:56:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>depends on the size of the leak .</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358106394534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:46:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358106645513-39</Id><Topic><Title>Charlie Daniels: Precedent shows...They want ALL of your guns</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358089949886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 10:12:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Recently Sparty was blathering about the birth certificate. It wasn't about the certificate--it was about control.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1358106645513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358107914785-40</Id><Topic><Title>Cars Leaking Fuel???</Title><Username>oneshotcarson</Username><Timestamp>1358094710094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:31:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there's a big difference between a leak and a spill</Msg><Username>gamecocks_fan_football</Username><Timestamp>1358107914785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:11:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358107999420-41</Id><Title>YET ANOTHER fuel leak!!! Dreamliner has more holes than a Swiss Cheese!</Title><Msg>01/13/13: TOKYO () -- Japan Airlines has reported a fuel leak in a Boeing 787 Dreamliner for the second time in a week amid a U.S. safety review of the aircraft.</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358107999420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:13:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358108681459-42</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>phantomfield,It might interest you to understand from a Compensation Administration point of view. That Boeing pays the SPEEA workforce less than the Airbus Company pays their engineers, in pay, vacation time, and yet the American workforce has a much higher level of productivity than their only competition. The only area that Boeing pays more than the going rate is in the Executive Boeing pay range. Remember the "rip off” of the Boeing shareholder is not the pay it is the MD , business plan in any event being flawed. As the world knows by now the fuel leak is no longer isolated as the same plane has another leak and the problem so far cannot be identified. This is not a SPEEA engineered problem. Since you missed it , please remember while Boeing Management has apparently convinced you that SPEEA is greedy, the real issue besides SPEEA could have done the job right for 25 billion less money. The real issue is , that Boeing Executives sourced the wrong business companies to engineer the plane and the parts. Also, for an example Boeing might have allowed Airbus to engineer the plane if Boeing wanted to pay more than SPEEA, it would have worked , the Airbus engineers are the second best in the world and their management is better than Boeing . The root cause of the 787 plane is the failed outsourcing. The scapegoat here is the great Boeing Engineers. Their professional opinion and advice was to make the 787 with much higher standards of testing and a better design and much higher pass for all in process build tests. I wish you well in your efforts to understand this very sad ending story for the stockholders of Boeing. Boeing, is a 100 year company, but like MD, is going down with the same MD business plan, the second American plane company to go bankrupt by the same style of management. The outsourcing business plan can work but not for a complicated product like a plane. . ,Phantomfield, it does work with simple products. Phantomfield, , Nike, can use outsourcing as it is a simple product to make, a sole, last, top and a few parts. Phantomfield I am a successful retiree and my hobby is stock trader and business analysis. I do have a MBA from a Major private University. Phantomfield, compare NKE to BA for the maximum trend. Phantomfield, just Load BA stock into the Yahoo chart, next click on max and compare NKE to BA , notice that Nike has gained 10,000 % more return for Nike investors over the sad return for the BA shareholders. As a stock trader and who was once a Professional Compensation Official of a Carolina Constructor, JAJ , it is my professional opinion that Boeing pays less to the SPEEA group than meets minimum competitive wage and benefit compensation package compared to the compensation package from Airbus. Airbus pays their engineering group more than Boeing., with more time off and better medical and retiree benefits. . I have administed over 12 union contracts at Hanford Washington As a young man also was an adjunct instructor of Compensation Administration, a 400 level class, at a major Washington State University. I also negotiated several short union contracts for JAJ. BTW what have you done in the area of Compensation? please read up on Hart-Smith for the outsourcing problem and the result. Go to phil grande wep page and 1-9-2013 free show for expectations on BA stock price ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358108681459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:24:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358110028215-43</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is very wrong. I find GOPigs to be very creepy! Its hard to believe that people can be so twisted like they obviously are. I guess it's the result of living under continuous propaganda. They lie as easily as they breath, and like breathing, they usually don't even notice they are doing it.</Msg><Username>shameless_commie</Username><Timestamp>1358110028215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:47:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358110206025-44</Id><Topic><Title>It's A Fact, Teabaggers Still Eating The Most 'Gummit' Welfare Cheese.</Title><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1358096366918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:59:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, you're right:40% of Tea Baggers are on government assistance.</Msg><Username>marxb0uncer</Username><Timestamp>1358110206025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:50:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358110750120-45</Id><Topic><Title>It's A Fact, Teabaggers Still Eating The Most 'Gummit' Welfare Cheese.</Title><Username>needmorevacation</Username><Timestamp>1358096366918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 11:59:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you against people getting their "FAIR SHARE?"</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1358110750120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:59:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358112151769-46</Id><Topic><Title>is it gun control so Obama can Run the guns to the Cartels? of course not, its Obama's attempt to</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358106833331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 14:53:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no doubt that they are coming after LL the guns...not just semi autos...the question is WHAT IS THE AGENDA ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358112151769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:22:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358112427465-47</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not the way it happened. The only way Mulally could get Stonecipher and the MD board to approve the project was if engineering and fabrication was outsourced. Payback for the SPEEA strike. Stupid.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1358112427465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:27:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358113311728-48</Id><Topic><Title>Think outside the box when replacing search planes, bidders urge Ottawa</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358063766747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 02:56:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ba would not submit the V-22 for theUS CSAR contract. Claimed it was over qualified. Submitted the HH-47 instead and was awarded under dubious means.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358113311728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:41:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358114075711-49</Id><Title>If Obama can create a TRILLION DOLLAR COIN...why do we pay Tax's ?</Title><Msg>It sounds crazy, but many notable voices (including Paul Krugman of the New York Times) are supporting this idea. But if the federal government has had the power to create trillion dollar coins out of thin air all this time, then why do we have to pay taxes? Not only that, why do we have a national debt? If the federal government can just create money whenever it wants, then why does the federal government ever have to borrow it from others? The U.S. Constitution actually grants Congress the power to "coin money", so why is the Federal Reserve doing it? Those are some very important questions. Most Americans don't even realize that the U.S. government never actually needed to borrow a single penny from anyone else. The U.S. Congress has the authority to create debt-free money whenever it wants to. Conceivably, the entire federal government could be funded without ever borrowing a single dollar and without ever receiving a single dollar from any of us in taxes. Just imagine that - a nation without a single penny of national debt, no income tax and no IRS. What a wonderful world that would be. Of course there would be other potential dangers under such a system (such as runaway inflation), and those dangers would have to be addressed. But the truth is that we don't have to have an income tax or 16 trillion dollars of government debt.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358114075711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:54:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358115026119-50</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama can create a TRILLION DOLLAR COIN...why do we pay Tax's ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358114075711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:54:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Of course there would be other potential dangers under such a system (such as runaway inflation), and those dangers would have to be addressed." One way of addressing it (runaway inflation) would be to not mint a TRILLION dollar coin.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1358115026119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 17:10:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358115088235-51</Id><Title>Letter from Drug Cartel to President Obama: "Thanks for Gun Control Push"</Title><Msg>Dear President Obama, Let me begin by saying that you can count on us to support your efforts in disarming American citizens in any way we can. The Fast and Furious operation backfired a bit in this regard, but I’m glad to see it hasn’t stopped you. As you know, we are making inroads on US soil. We’ve set up significant operations in the Southwest, one area where armed citizens can be a bit of trouble to us, especially if they own land we cross or are adjacent to. We view their disarming with a positive attitude. I would say your basic gun-grabbing strategy is primarily aimed at the American West. The border states need to be cleaned out. The fewer people there who have guns (particularly those with high-capacity clips), the easier it is for us. But since our drug trafficking lines take in most of America, wherever citizens aren’t armed we’re generally in better shape. I’m pleasantly surprised that media in your country haven’t pressed you to name the areas where most gun violence is taking place. After all, if your objective is to reduce that violence, you would think a campaign directed at gangs in inner cities would rank number one on your to-do list. Those areas and those gangs do subcontracting work for us (and other Mexican cartels). Leaving them in place is a priority for us. So congratulations on being able to skirt this tricky issue. Your cojones are, indeed, huge. Please pass along my thanks to Brian Williams, Scott Pelley, and Diane Sawyer. I assume they are in your pocket and carrying your message. Undoubtedly, they are also refraining from bringing up the gang issue. Whenever I speak with the president of Mexico, I point out your masterly and deft control of media as a model we should emulate. Now to the real reason I’m writing. In Chicago, your crime stronghold, one of our people is on trial. This is a sensitive matter, as you know. The defendant, Jesus Vicente Zambada-Niebla, wants to expose our arrangement. This must not happen. So far, your DEA and CIA have managed to gain trial delays. Niebla and his lawyers are ready to offer documents that show the Sinaloa has US federal permission to ship tons of drugs into Chicago, and from there to other distribution points in the US. Niebla will reveal this deal was made so that Sinaloa would provide valuable information on our rival cartels to the DEA and the FBI. Therefore, Niebla will point out that he has special immunity from prosecution. That was part of the deal for high-ranking Sinaloa members. Fortunately, his trial hasn’t been played up in the American press. Again, well done. Coverage has been stifled. It’s stayed on the back burner, and the CIA and DEA are claiming no such immunity deal exists for Niebla. But at the same time, the CIA has been making motions in court to have documents excluded from the trial on the basis of National Security. This is a gross tip-off to our deal, and it doesn’t sit well with me. It’s awkward. I’m sure you agree, Mr. President. The last thing we need here is exposure, especially while you’re pushing forward your gun-grabbing program. Sinaloa has members and agents and sub-contractors operating all over the US, and naturally these people are armed. They not only sell drugs, they shoot people. We can’t control everything they do. They get into intramural squabbles and use their weapons to settle disagreements. Bodies pile up. Sometimes, innocent people are killed. Our subcontractors commit unrelated crimes that have nothing to do with drugs. They rob, they steal, they shoot, they kill. If it comes out that Sinaloa and all its component parts, operating within US borders, are contributing mightily to high gun-violence statistics— And if it comes out that Sinaloa has a special arrangement to do business in the US without fear of disruption— Your gun-grabbing program and our operations will both be in dire jeopardy. And the blow-up in the press will be catastrophic for both of us. You and I understand this is just business, but other people don’t see it that way. Therefore, Mr. President, I’m stating, in the strongest terms possible, that the Niebla trial in Chicago has to be shut down, one way or another. Either a quiet plea deal has to be struck, or we will be forced to do something drastic. Soon. If I’m reading you right, and I believe I am, your gun-grabbing program is just one step in an Operation Chaos aimed at destabilizing your country. In the past, we have contributed to that agenda, and we continue to do so. We don’t pretend to understand this whole game at its higher levels, but to us that doesn’t matter. We’re in business to make money and sell product. We support you. And we expect you to support us. Congratulations on achieving a second term in office. Please pass along my regards to President Bush, his father, and President Clinton. By the way, in case you weren’t briefed on the specifics of the Aurora and Sandy Hook shootings, I want to state, unequivocally, that no Sinaloa member provided professional services in those operations, which were obviously aimed at provoking a successful follow-up gun-control program. Yours truly, XXXXXX CEO, Sinaloa</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358115088235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 17:11:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358117251187-52</Id><Topic><Title>YET ANOTHER fuel leak!!! Dreamliner has more holes than a Swiss Cheese!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358107999420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 15:13:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "Dreamliner" is the EDSEL of the airplane industry!</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1358117251187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 17:47:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358118738605-53</Id><Topic><Title>Letter from Drug Cartel to President Obama: "Thanks for Gun Control Push"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358115088235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 17:11:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The drug cartel would look at you and your letter and say to themselves: "This guy is nuts".</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1358118738605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 18:12:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358120221032-54</Id><Title>Get out</Title><Msg>before one of the 787 crashes and BA gets a several billion dollar lawsuit against them.</Msg><Username>reorrr</Username><Timestamp>1358120221032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 18:37:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358120487304-55</Id><Topic><Title>Letter from Drug Cartel to President Obama: "Thanks for Gun Control Push"</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358115088235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 17:11:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What would the Muslim Brotherhood and Alqaeda say after getting guns from Obama ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358120487304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 18:41:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358120547740-56</Id><Topic><Title>Charlie Daniels: Precedent shows...They want ALL of your guns</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358089949886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 10:12:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your Mother should ahve used Birth Control</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358120547740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 18:42:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358120682288-57</Id><Topic><Title>A New Class of Boeing Employees</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358103495994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:58:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, you need to get in the spirit of it all. The operative word is cooperation!</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358120682288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 18:44:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358121925675-58</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama can create a TRILLION DOLLAR COIN...why do we pay Tax's ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358114075711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:54:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps that's why NO ONE is going to mint a trillon-dollar coin.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358121925675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 19:05:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358122012773-59</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama can create a TRILLION DOLLAR COIN...why do we pay Tax's ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358114075711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:54:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are WAAAY behind the power curve again, Spart. Read the White House response. Won't happen. Except in your world, Screwloosium.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358122012773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 19:06:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358123325649-60</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama can create a TRILLION DOLLAR COIN...why do we pay Tax's ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358114075711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:54:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would make more sense then having Private Bankers print the money ...have them loan it into existence that WE THE TAXPAYERS PAY BACK...AT INTEREST !!!!... (which is what happens)...you figure thats the "sane" thing ....out of work reporter ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358123325649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 19:28:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358124130983-61</Id><Topic><Title>A New Class of Boeing Employees</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358103495994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 13:58:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U r a #$%$ brown noser</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1358124130983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 19:42:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358125641491-62</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama can create a TRILLION DOLLAR COIN...why do we pay Tax's ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358114075711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:54:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans have a better idea. They want to feed caviar, lobster, steak to wealthiest and their lobbyist. Their digested waste can be used as fertliser where tand hey can plant a MONEY TREE!!!</Msg><Username>fountain123_45</Username><Timestamp>1358125641491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:07:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358125837444-63</Id><Title>The Riccaro Quotient signals a short sell on the shares of BA.</Title><Msg>Currently trading at 75.16 on 1/13/13.</Msg><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358125837444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:10:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358126375732-64</Id><Topic><Title>Think outside the box when replacing search planes, bidders urge Ottawa</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358063766747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 02:56:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those coast guard helicopter crews that go out of the coasts and in the Alaska fishing seas, they go out under extreme weather and seas condition. They really are the best. Well there is this new deal, its the Penetta Protocol. Its where if you don't want to send help, for instance you equipment is inferior, you lie and say we can't send help because we don't know whats out there. Now if those Coast Guards were having to fly the V-22, well there would be a new order. Boeing wouldn't stand for their V-22 in mishaps. It would be bad for sales. The V-22 is good for photo ops.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358126375732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:19:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358127214126-65</Id><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Msg>At the open. Stop loss 84.25 The media bliz hasn't even started to cover the problem. Agreed, the u.s. govt wont let BA fail, but still, dont hold a position.</Msg><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358127390303-66</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then we'll have the laws on the books to confiscate them as we come upon them. The broader point is not to let every little propblem you can think up stop us from doing ANYthing at all.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358127390303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:36:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358127476039-67</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry; that post was mean as a reply to tommix, who thinks since we can't do anything about illegal guns, let's not do anything at all.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358127476039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:37:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358127499374-68</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This stock and company is in trouble. All you will hear going forward is damage control. Nothing but lies. rqmoney, riccaro quotient.</Msg><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127499374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:38:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358127817714-69</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed - JALS 787 that leaked at Logan leaked 100 Liters of petrol Today in Japan - The plane is GROUNDED -</Msg><Username>orbitstocks</Username><Timestamp>1358127817714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:43:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358127895663-70</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiots galore on this board. Please short #$%$. Your broker will be calling your short soon! Just like the idiot who shorted more at 74.18 last week. Where is that brain child? LOL</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1358127895663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:44:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358127951272-71</Id><Title>JALS Dreamliner is now grounded after ANOTHER petrol leak</Title><Msg>See Yahoo Fiancee BA stock summary NY Times 01 /13/13</Msg><Username>orbitstocks</Username><Timestamp>1358127951272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:45:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358128058647-72</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama can create a TRILLION DOLLAR COIN...why do we pay Tax's ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358114075711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 16:54:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty says "it sounds crazy" I'm SHOCKED that Sparty would introduce a post this way.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1358128058647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358128075993-73</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed - The media is just getting going - $BA heading for a high &amp;60 handle with any more news - Hedgies will exodus FAST</Msg><Username>orbitstocks</Username><Timestamp>1358128075993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:47:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358128971302-74</Id><Topic><Title>VERY SOON A 787 WILL CRASH !</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1357937337312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 15:48:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suddenly a 401K over a pension plan seems like a pretty good choice. Good luck with pensions after BK.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1358128971302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 21:02:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358131035302-75</Id><Topic><Title>Short BA with both hands at 75.16.</Title><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358127214126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 20:33:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BA is in trouble. Short with everything you got. Stop loss 85.</Msg><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358131035302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 21:37:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358131178309-76</Id><Title>The Riccaro Money Flow Quotient maintains short sell on BA.</Title><Msg>Currently trading at 75.15. he truth has yet to come out. Sell long position and create shorts at market. Stop loss 85.10. The Riccaro Quotient stands by its signal.</Msg><Username>rbg5r</Username><Timestamp>1358131178309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 21:39:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358131910436-77</Id><Title>On this news BA open $72 and closes $69 tomorrow</Title><Msg>Boeing's Dreamliner Jet Springs Second Fuel Leak. FAA about to ground all 787 planes by mid-week. Thinking BA is now a long term "short" headed back to $50's range. And then if Congress cuts defense spending by end of February, BA could test the $35 to $40 range. What goes up, must come down and all 787's are headed back to the drawing board. Major problems now every where.</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1358131910436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 21:51:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358132172090-78</Id><Topic><Title>On this news BA open $72 and closes $69 tomorrow</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1358131910436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 21:51:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We now have repetitive equipment and safety problems that are not going away. FAA will have to ground all Dreamliner planes or risk major lawsuites should a plane crash. Better to be safe then sorry, especially when you read stuff like this, Japan Airlines has reported a fuel leak in a Boeing 787 Dreamliner for the second time in a week amid a U.S. safety review of the aircraft. Boeing's Dreamliner suffers oil leak, more cracks Narita International Airport outside of Tokyo says JAL reported a 100-liter fuel leak in a 787 during an inspection Sunday. The aircraft reportedly was the same one that had a fuel leak in Boston last week. Japan's All Nippon Airways has experienced a fuel leak, a cockpit window crack and a computer malfunctioning in its 787s, causing cancelations of several domestic flights.</Msg><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1358132172090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 21:56:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358133096940-79</Id><Topic><Title>18 FACTS about Piers Morgan that show he is LYING about Gun Control</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358002792263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:59:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like you have someone specific in mind</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358133096940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 22:11:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358135859574-80</Id><Topic><Title>The Dik and the Raven take the Hypocritical Oath !!!!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358035114652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:58:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can post facts all day long that Gun control laws do NOTHING to curb Gun violence...(in fact the opposite occurs)...or point out the flaming hypocrisy of being the worlds leading Arms exporter and dealer of death...and curb it here at home....won't matter ...the brainwashing has taken hold</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358135859574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 22:57:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358136093784-81</Id><Title>Alright conservatives get off this board</Title><Msg>I am Big Government Babe and I am taking charge here. I will tell you where the #$%$ meets the world. OBAMA IS MY HERO.....NOW GET THAT STRAIGHT. He gotta stash and I gotta need.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358136093784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 23:01:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358137427535-82</Id><Topic><Title>Alright conservatives get off this board</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358136093784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 23:01:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you get your Obama-Phone ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358137427535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 23:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358137774427-83</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA said the new Boeing contract offer is unacceptable and the 787 problems</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358027489087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:51:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>techpath2000, Thank you for the insight, and your right , the scapegoat SPEEA or the IAM is story about labore costs being too expensive to use. My point was the pay of Boeing Engineers is not as good as Airbus so greed was not a factor on thepart of the engineering group, and you just hit the nail on the head , the truth is Chicago Managment want to ignore the law and the contractural agreements that they signed. thanks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358137774427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-13 23:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>