<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363752572954-1</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the stats were misleading but her speech was simply a "speech" - I would not call anything she does "major" you can get her, Palin and Trump together as a package and say you would pay them only $1,000 per show and Fox News still wouldn't want to book 'em...Red Eye will stay put</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1363752572954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 00:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363754310608-2</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I trade day trades for as much as 25%" "any one should be making at least 25 percent" So, "as much as" means anything (including negative) up to 25 percent, whereas "at least" means nothing below 25 percent. Wayne changing his story when he gets called on it. Par for the "coarse". P.S. Gonzaga must be a jock school. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1363754310608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 00:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363759880898-3</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparticus99991 lets see you have several posts all of them to me or your other names for me, are you obsessed with hate because i can show that Boeing is nota good invetment stock , yes your a Boeing hack , lets look at your 100% only obsession with me eply to sparticus9991 ownes 6,123,457 shares of Boeing so that is your motivation to discuss Boeing problems by waynedickenson961 •Mar 9, 2013 3:12 AM spartacus99991 • Mar 9, 2013 9:31 AM 2users liked this postsusers disliked this posts8Reply Well, I guess Wayne is trying to change my previous post into something that it wasn't so he could exercise his calculator and write some more nonsense. He didn't notice (maybe the rage in his eyes clouded his vision) that there was a decimal between the "3" and "4" . So all his minute calculations... More Reply to Dell's Challenge from 2 years ago (3/7/2011) by spartacus99991 •Mar 7, 2013 8:28 PM spartacus99991 • Mar 8, 2013 1:19 PM 2users liked this postsusers disliked this posts4Reply Still no comments from Dell (or anyone who claims that Dell was his old nick). Reply to Boeing hacks another trade proof that your full of BS not years ago but this month by waynedickenson961 •Mar 7, 2013 11:58 PM spartacus99991 • Mar 8, 2013 12:54 PM Flag 1users liked this postsusers disliked this posts4Reply Actually, Dell theoretically made $3871 (3.871 percent) over the last 2 years. It was just $10,479 less than BA over that same time period. He made the challenge (its in his posts) and I followed thru. Whatever your trading gains recently are don't change the fact that Dell's 10 picks did not do as... More Reply to Boeing hacks another trade proof that your full of BS not years ago but this month by waynedickenson961 •Mar 7, 2013 11:58 PM spartacus99991 • Mar 8, 2013 12:33 AM 0users liked this postsusers disliked this posts4Reply Dell made the challenge. I accepted it and have posted the results after 2 years. What don't you like about facts? Dell is down over $10,000 (lucky for him it's only a means of keeping score). I never said you were fired. I believe you when you say you retired in 2003. These are the facts. Reply to Dell's Challenge from 2 years ago (3/7/2011) by spartacus99991 •Mar 7, 2013 8:28 PM spartacus99991 • Mar 7, 2013 11:03 PM 1users liked this postsusers disliked this posts7Reply "so when and if you can prove me wrong go for it" Seems like Dell made the challenge with that statement, or are you admitting that you are really Dell? Still behind by over $10,000 no matter how you want to spin it in hindsight. LOL Reply to Dell's Challenge from 2 years ago (3/7/2011) by spartacus99991 •Mar 7, 2013 8:28 PM spartacus99991 • Mar 7, 2013 8:59 PM 4users liked this postsusers disliked this posts6Reply BTW, when Dell (Wayne, Fred, Veronica ?) was losing the challenge in 2011 he said he really meant that some stocks should be long and some short and he would tell us later which are which. "Spin" never seems to go out of style. 5users liked this postsusers disliked this posts4Reply Dell's Challenge from 2 years ago (3/7/2011) by spartacus99991 • Mar 7, 2013 8:28 PM Dell hasn't been posting to the BA board for a while. Maybe he's moved on to other endeavors, or has a new nick (I wonder), or maybe he just lurks and doesn't care to respond. ... More</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363759880898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 02:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363760794104-4</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparticus9991 lets look your obsession , as a Boeing hack in play, see your so angry as the MD engineer who goes by several user names , with me as you own Boeing stock and would do anything to promote your stock value in Boeing you hate it that I show how much better Airbus is for any investor to make money and that is all this is about, remember BA is up per CNN money stock chart YTD 13% while Aribus (eadsy) is up 35% and for 3 years BA Boeing is up only 17% while Airbus is up 163% both stocks as of the end of today trade session. My math is not a factor that is a world wide CNN Money stock chart calculator and as to my personal investments you can spin and twist all you want , I use your extremely silly arguments to put my topic on the top of the Boeing message board and want to have other readers see how ridiculous your comment are thanks and here are more of your garbage comments AKA spin ' partacus99991 27 posts | Last Activity: 1 hour 34 minutes ago Member since: Apr 5, 2008 1 2 3 months Sort: Newest | Oldest | Highest Rated Expand all messages Reply to sparticus9991 ownes 6,123,457 shares of Boeing so that is your motivation to discuss Boeing problems by waynedickenson961 •Mar 9, 2013 3:12 AM spartacus99991 • Mar 9, 2013 9:31 AM 2users liked this postsusers disliked this posts8Replyn Well, I guess Wayne is trying to change my previous post into something that it wasn't so he could exercise his calculator and write some more nonsense. He didn't notice (maybe the rage in his eyes clouded his vision) that there was a decimal between the "3" and "4" . So all his minute calculations... More Reply to Dell's Challenge from 2 years ago (3/7/2011) by spartacus99991 •Mar 7, 2013 8:28 PM spartacus99991 • Mar 8, 2013 1:19 PM 2users liked this postsusers disliked this posts4Reply Still no comments from Dell (or anyone who claims that Dell was his old nick). Reply to Boeing hacks another trade proof that your full of BS not years ago but this month</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363760794104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 02:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363762019257-5</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus for 3 years is up 167% Boeing stock for three years up 17.59%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633031168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 14:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>duffymagoo have you heard of them now har har har</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363762019257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 02:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363762403316-6</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seem like institutional shareholders and Boeing PR are the ones responsible for the 10% increase in stock price since Dec 2012. If you study the movement of BA stock price and events unfolded day by day , you could see how BA tried to calm public panics by manipulate the stock price . Look at volumes one and two days after 787's grounded. They pump 20 millions shares in each day . That's the different between political sciences and physical sciences. In political sciences , money talk, if you could read chart , you'll make big money. In physical science, money is not the governing force. Not enough hydraulic force, landing gear won't open nor close. Advance electrical system required large and fast movement of energy , battery will baked. In natural science, pigs can't fly. Murphy's law is if anything go wrong, it will go wrong. Any thing go wrong will cost you more and longer than you thought. Bad feng shui will result in bad luck. For example, Chinese believed # 4 as bad luck, death , look at Apollo 13=4, 787=22=4, emergency on runway 22 ???. Now think of # 7s in 7E7 series, as wings of an air plane, and the middle number as body of an airplane. Think of airplanes as birds. All the 707, 717, 727, 737, 747, 767, 777 , all doing fine, because as with flying birds , they all got wings much larger than bodies, Now look at 787. the # 8, represent the body, bigger than #7 represent wings . think of the penguin. can they fly?? . That is my opinion. I hope BA will get over this soon. Good luck.</Msg><Username>hoiinca</Username><Timestamp>1363762403316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 02:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363762632144-7</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne takes the bait and reproduces all my latest posts showing the fallacy in his math and predictions and that bumps it to the top where the board can see his obsession with changing other's posts to fit his "facts" and his "at least 25 percent per week" that nets him $109M per year. Spin away, Wayne. Archives are a #$%$. BTW, who wants an MBA from a jock school?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1363762632144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 02:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363763095363-8</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the flying business of Big Birds, they use all senses, they must be very alert at all times, not sleepy nor dreaming about lines nor circles. May be E RAPIDO or GLOBAL RAYA a better name for 7E7's . Best of luck to BA.</Msg><Username>hoiinca</Username><Timestamp>1363763095363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 03:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363765026111-9</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hoiinca, Boeing has the PR machine going with the 787 will be flying soon and the fix excuse for not finding the cause 2. Boeing has a large amount of stock buy back to manipulate the stock price, Boeing holds airplane orders secret( for competitive reasons ) is their claim. Boeing gives a discount to the airlines to not release the purchase agreement until Boeing gives the OK, this is done to influence the stock price to lower the stock price during the one day the union bonus pay is determined. and , to pump the stock price for the excessive short standards used to determine long term management bonus stock price threshold( 20 trade days ) above a determined threshold price). Boeing has considerable political power and uses friendly analysts to pump Boeing stock price. Political power is considerable Boeing is almost a government company they sleep together Boeing used uncle Norm, a Washington lawmaker to create a single factor on the 767 tanker ,less fuel to operate after Airbus won the contract. In return uncle Norm is now , guess what paid aerospace consultant to Boeing har ! So short term Boeing does manipulate stock price. However over time as i point out to the Boeing hacks Boeing sucks for investors compared to its rival Airbus for the eyar to date Boeing stock price has gained only 13.4% while airbus has gained 35% use CNN Money and their chart set to ytd and then to 3 years . For 3 years Boeing stockholders returns in this huge up market is pathetic only 17.8% while airbus is up 163%. the DOW JONES average of which BA is a part is up 33% for three years so are the Sand P 500 and the NASDAQ so Boeing to the absolute anger of the Boeing hacks is not a good stock past present or future !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363765026111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 03:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363766082622-10</Id><Title>Why these numbers 13 and 17 seem to make Boeing at leas 6 stock holder's angry &amp; enrage or provoke?</Title><Msg>Boeing STOCK GAIN ytd is 13.%while Airbus is 35% In the last 3 years Boeing stockholders return is a pathetic 17.8% Airbus is up 163%. Next compared to the higher risk of a single stock how did Boeing do compared to all the good and bad stocks for the past 3 years ? DOW JONES average is up 33% so are the Sand P 500( 32.7%) and the NASDAQ(34.82%) TO VERIFY GO TO CNN MONEY AND USE THEIR STOCK CHART. BA , Argus symbol is eadsy, , the dow S &amp; P and nasdaq are icons</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363766082622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 03:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363767456214-11</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you in the wrong message board. A sorrowed soul try to analyze politic . Go take your prozac.</Msg><Username>hoiinca</Username><Timestamp>1363767456214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 04:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363779381459-12</Id><Title>Target raised..</Title><Msg>LMAO.. 120$..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363779381459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 07:36:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363781562788-13</Id><Title>Hey, Jim Crxmer, buy BA, instead of CAT.</Title><Msg>will you?</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363781562788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 08:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363782305030-14</Id><Title>You know BA is going to break all time high, right?</Title><Msg>it is matta of time.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363782305030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 08:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363787960319-15</Id><Topic><Title>BA rumored to be bought out!</Title><Username>smith.frank7</Username><Timestamp>1363260989034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 07:36:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>interesting predictions!</Msg><Username>rodrigez_mm</Username><Timestamp>1363787960319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:59:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363789079721-16</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The TSA has become little more than another dumbo jobs program, minorities / m uslims preferred, education optional.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363789079721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363789948045-17</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i expect chrissie n spart are double dippers, welfare AND dumbo/mobro jihad payments... from the weekly standard... "According to the Census’s American Community Survey, the number of households with incomes below the poverty line in 2011 was 16,807,795," the Senate Budget Committee notes. "If you divide total federal and state spending by the number of households with incomes below the poverty line, the average spending per household in poverty was $61,194 in 2011." This dollar figure is almost three times the amount the average household on poverty lives on per year. "If the spending on these programs were converted into cash, and distributed exclusively to the nation’s households below the poverty line, this cash amount would be over 2.5 times the federal poverty threshold for a family of four, which in 2011 was $22,350 (see table in this link)," the Republicans on the Senate Budget Committee note. To be clear, not all households living below the poverty line receive $61,194 worth of assistance per year. After all, many above the poverty line also receive benefits from social welfare programs (e.g. pell grants). But if welfare is meant to help bring those below the poverty line to a better place, it helps demonstrate that numbers do not add up. As for the welfare programs, the Republicans on the Senate Budget Committee note: A congressional report from CRS recently revealed that the United States now spends more on means-tested welfare than any other item in the budget - including Social Security, Medicare, or national defense. Including state contributions to the roughly 80 federal poverty programs, the total amount spent in 2011 was approximately $1 trillion. Federal spending alone on these programs was up 32 percent since 2008. Related Stories Ten Welfare Programs to Cost $8.3 Trillion Over Next ... Welfare Spending Now Largest Budget Item Record High Enrollment for Food Stamps: 46,681,833 46,609,072 People on Food Stamps in 2012; Record ..</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363789948045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363790683829-18</Id><Topic><Title>Elizabeth Warren: Why Isn’t the Minimum Wage Triple What it is Today?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363786051213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:27:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh hopyiedoppy you should lay off the Propaganda the talking heads feed you everyday you make no sense and just spew partisan nonsense endlessly. what I call more empty space. or you could just say gone coo koo!!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1363790683829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363790842230-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why these numbers 13 and 17 seem to make Boeing at leas 6 stock holder's angry &amp; enrage or provoke?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363766082622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 03:54:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good morning Boeing hacks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363790842230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:47:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363791069736-20</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chrissie err spaz err spart err dumbo err fascistcensoredmobro err jihad err spaz err bumpie-poo</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1363791069736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363791104861-21</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err spaz err dumbo err censoredspaz err fascist err spazmo</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1363791104861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363791192023-22</Id><Topic><Title>Elizabeth Warren: Why Isn’t the Minimum Wage Triple What it is Today?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363786051213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:27:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roksta takes his cues from frauds, phony injuns/lawyers, dumbos elevated by virtue of affirmative action/EEOP, n tsleazy lawyers</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363791192023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363791293694-23</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty's having another sissy fit, he doesn't like it when dumbos are called out for being dumbos</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363791293694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363791540605-24</Id><Title>ANA wants cash payment for 787 failure compensation !</Title><Msg>Sorry Boeing investors, All Nippon Airways wants to be paid in cash for the 787 planes’ failure to perform, in violation of the air worthiness certification guarantee. Boeing would prefer to pay for their failure with the customers accepting discounts on future aircraft purchases this would allow Boeing to spread any reimbursement costs over several years. Airlines, though, see cash compensation as a quicker way to make up for their losses. Boeing declined to comment on compensation issues, no surprise there ! Boeing is reported to have already faced billions of dollars in fees for three years of delays in getting the 787 into service because of problems with a global production system.This is why Airbus stock is up 167% in the past 3 years while Boeing s investors have only made 17% in three years , all the plane orders and deliveries mean nothing with these huge costs . JAL President Yoshiharu Ueki said on Tuesday the 787's grounding could knock 1.1 billion yen ($11.6 million) off the airline's operating profit for April-May, taking the total hit since the grounding to 1.8 billion yen. In October-December, the company had an operating profit of 46 billion yen.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363791540605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:59:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363791580777-25</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty doesn't like being called a freeloader, much less double dipper, even when he's double n triple dipping welfare pot, social security (disability) pot, n the ACORN/mobro s*** pot</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363791580777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363791708887-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't Democrats ever Answer Question about their Looney Ideas?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363184496035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:21:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They won't answer because the smart ones can't let the dumb ones know how utterly stupid they are for believing the idiotic nonsense the spew to get their votes.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363791708887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363792416405-27</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do Democrats have anything to do with that situation? Maybe what we need is more intelligent TSA workers, and to get them, their wages would have to be increased. And you and your ilk would certainly not want that, correct?</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1363792416405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363792759144-28</Id><Title>INFLUENCE GAME: Congress quiet on Dreamliner woes, or hide in" plane" sight</Title><Msg>Jim Hall, a former NTSB chairman, has misgivings about Congress relying solely on private briefings. On the 787 failure and potential safety of flight issues and does not like the Boeing political use to cover up a open investigation and public hearing on the disaster that is the 787. "Where is the public responsibility, where is the public accountability in those types of meetings?" he asked. The NTSB has been unable to establish a root cause for the Boston fire, and its investigators are also looking into the process by which the FAA certified the 787 as safe for flight in August 2011. In recent years, the FAA has increasingly delegated responsibility for testing the components and systems of new Boeing's testing indicated the likelihood that a battery would emit smoke was 1 in 10 million flight hours. Instead, there were two smoking batteries less than two weeks apart, when the entire 787 fleet had recorded only about 52,000 flight hours. The FAA is conducting its own review of the design, manufacture and assembly of the 787, but that isn't expected to be completed until later this year. In Short Boeing has all the players under their control. Here they are , The chairman of the panel's aviation subcommittee, Democrat Maria Cantwell, is from Boeing's home state of Washington. Asked about the possibility of a 787 hearing, she was noncommittal. She'd prefer to have hearings on the importance of "aviation manufacturing and how do we maintain a robust workforce because the U.S. industry is facing great competition from China, Brazil, and others that want to be in the business," Cantwell said. BTW-The company's political action committee and its employees have contributed $107,200 to Cantwell's political campaigns since 1992 Washington's other senator, Democrat Patty Murray, chairs the subcommittee of the Senate Appropriations Committee that oversees the FAA's and the NTSB's budgets And lets put the best spin on the 787 disaster so this is the idea hide the issues as best as possible “Rep. Nick Rahall, the senior Democrat on the transportation committee, said he and some other committee members are concerned a hearing might create "an unnecessary scare when there is no grounds for it," resulting in air travelers refusing to fly the planes. Yah think!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363792759144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363793045319-29</Id><Topic><Title>INFLUENCE GAME: Congress quiet on Dreamliner woes, or hide in" plane" sight</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363792759144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:19:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and more for the Boeing hacks to hide from, As Boeing, its airline customers and federal safety regulators struggled over the past two months to solve problems with the new 787 Dreamliner's fire-plagued batteries, one player has been strangely silent: Congress. Despite the plane's grounding and the safety issues raised by its cutting-edge technology, there have been no congressional hearings or news conferences focusing on the problems, and little commentary from lawmakers who normally pounce at the first sign of trouble. Because this is an issue of huge significance in both economic and safety terms, you would think it would be a natural for Congress," said Norman Ornstein, an expert on Congress at the American Enterprise Institute, a think tank. Why? Simple The aircraft maker has spent more than $83 million on lobbying over the past five years, according to disclosure reports. It fielded 115 lobbyists last year, both on its own payroll and at some of the best-connected lobbying and law firms in Washington. About three-quarters of those lobbyists had previously worked for Congress, the White House or federal agencies, according to the political money and influence tracking website OpenSecrets.org. The FBI- friends , brothers and In-Laws continue to do their thing , President Barack Obama appointed McNerney to chair his President's Export Council, which operates as an advisory committee on international trade. Obama's former commerce secretary, John Bryson, was a member of Boeing's board of directors before joining the government.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363793045319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363793163544-30</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What language is that?</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1363793163544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363793261790-31</Id><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Msg>Then Make Everyone pay a 23% consumption tax on everything they purchase at the retail level.......no exemptions no deductions. Everyone pays exactly the same amount of Taxes on what they consume from then on. Tax only what people consume, not what they produce. Stop all welfare, subsidies, entitlements and any other form of government transfers. There would be no need for these things.....everyone would be millionaires......at least they would until they started consuming more than they produced. The government can do this......they have the presses that can print the money. Just print the money and give it to the people. Then make it against the law for any politician to spend more than $200 to get elected to office and require congress to balance the budget. Oh, I'm aware low IQ people will call me names and hurl insults because this would stop the government's ability to take from producers and give to nonproducers.....Progressives (Marxists) would lose power and purpose if that ever happened.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363793414873-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intellectuals and Race</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363788227353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:03:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is odd since many of the left's heroes like Margaret Sanger were Eugenists and Darwinists who accepted the science of natural selection and wanted to eradicate those she saw as unfit. "As part of her efforts to promote birth control, Sanger found common cause with proponents of eugenics, believing that they both sought to "assist the race toward the elimination of the unfit."[83] Sanger was a proponent of negative eugenics, which aims to improve human hereditary traits through social intervention by reducing reproduction by those considered unfit. Sanger's eugenic policies included an exclusionary immigration policy, free access to birth control methods and full family planning autonomy for the able-minded, and compulsory segregation or sterilization for the profoundly #$%$." - Wiki These beliefs are still very prevalent in the Liberal elitist class. A good example is Mayor Bloomberg who insists that he knows how you should lead your life better than you do. In a way many liberals believe that African American's are 'unfit' in the way Margaret Sanger views the term, and as such liberal Democrat elites are should in fact run the lives of African Americans which is a circular process that keeps African Americans 'unfit' in society. You're a racist if you dare challenge the notion that African Americans can compete with anyone without help from Democratic Party elites that view them as 'unfit' and unable to compete.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363793414873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363793428504-33</Id><Topic><Title>BA rumored to be bought out!</Title><Username>smith.frank7</Username><Timestamp>1363260989034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 07:36:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great one!</Msg><Username>webbj</Username><Timestamp>1363793428504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363793554854-34</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe we don't need the TSA or homeland security, particularly if they're not allowed to enforce our borders and/or discriminate/profile...i know we don't need em if they're not going to do the job for which they were hired we'll hire hire private sector companys, who can hire and fire who they please, able to use their judgement AND discriminate without threat from ACLU #$%$.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363793554854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363793833863-35</Id><Topic><Title>Leaked BA buy out report!</Title><Username>dennis.jacksonny</Username><Timestamp>1361970587265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 08:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great one!</Msg><Username>webbj</Username><Timestamp>1363793833863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363793973957-36</Id><Title>March delivery update</Title><Msg>As of yesterday, BA has delivered 25 planes. 18 737's. 2 747's. 5 777's BEAerospace (BEAV), a BA supplier, has been on a roll for some time and hit an all time high this morning. It provides interiors and components to a number of plane builders. It has gone from the high $30's to just under $60 since last August.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363793973957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363794041630-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The embracers of Eugenics will fight anything that prevents them from controlling others. That's why. Their system is designed to only reward those that do what the elite wants them to do. Freedom of choice for Eugenicists is deplorable concept. To run your own life as you see fit means they have no power over you. People like Hooz and Genna want to be controlled because they have bought into the idea that they are 'unfit' (see my post on Margaret Sangers idea of what is unfit) to make decisions. Hooz admitted to me years ago that the reason he doesn't post his own ideas is that he is not as smart as the people he copies and pastes. Instead of becoming more knowledgeable and thinking for himself, Hooz continues to remain a useful idiot of the followers of Eugenics who believe only they should be able to run everyone else lives. He is a poster boy for unthinking fanaticism.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363794041630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363794151296-38</Id><Topic><Title>Elizabeth Warren: Why Isn’t the Minimum Wage Triple What it is Today?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363786051213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:27:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah--Fascist//Bumper's monthly screed about various folks. Fascist probably lost a lawsuit and is even more bitter than otherwise. Poor bumper.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1363794151296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363794833918-39</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>████████████LOADS A KEY STROKE LOGGER!!! ████████████████████████████████████████████████████████ ██████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████████</Msg><Username>thatsmrmorontoyou</Username><Timestamp>1363794833918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795033878-40</Id><Topic><Title>INFLUENCE GAME: Congress quiet on Dreamliner woes, or hide in" plane" sight</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363792759144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:19:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uncle Norm how much will the taxpayer be paying you on retirement ? "really, a monthly check from the U.S. taxpayers for $8,939 why uncle norm you making more on retirement than those pesky Boeing worker make working 40 hours per week. any new job uncle Norm, no kidding your now a consultant tot he Boeing company what a sweet(heart) deal for you, I bet you just lucked into that job right ! . Attention Boeing Hacks who are concerned about the high wage of Boeing union employees this is more than a worker gets in a year. On average, congressional pensions are two to three times as generous as those offered to workers in the private sector with similar salaries, said Pete Sepp, the executive vice president of the National Taxpayers Union And as usual , Boeing officials were not immediately available to comment on the company's relationship with uncle norm</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363795033878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:57:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795174298-41</Id><Topic><Title>ANA wants cash payment for 787 failure compensation !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363791540605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 10:59:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so money up front that will cost Boeing eh !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363795174298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795317184-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why these numbers 13 and 17 seem to make Boeing at leas 6 stock holder's angry &amp; enrage or provoke?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363766082622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 03:54:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep the facts really hurt Boeing hacks 13 and 17 gains compared to Aribus of 35 and 167% and the 3 major averages of 35% or greater for 3 years in stock price appreciation show Boeing company stock price to be a huge loser right on Boeing hacks have at it then tell me all about it now , what was that ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363795317184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795370411-43</Id><Topic><Title>Cheney Marks Tenth Anniversary of Pretending There Was Reason to Invade Iraq</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363737765635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They should be hanging in effigy. Cheney and that carpet licker #$%$ daughter of his are the scourge of planet earth.</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1363795370411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795459417-44</Id><Topic><Title>Cheney Marks Tenth Anniversary of Pretending There Was Reason to Invade Iraq</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363737765635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>drudge was reporting they may have been some o dem pretend reasons in syria yesterday sparty and it's looks like chrissie (please forgive the confusion, i'm still not convinced spart is not hooz, if hooz is indeed chrissie, they're both freeloaders/marxists, both enemy friendly), always give the enemy the benefit of the doubt, even when there is none.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363795459417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795473062-45</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear she gives great headola. Yahoooooooooooooooooooooooooo</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1363795473062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363795488934-46</Id><Title>Simple way for Republicans to win</Title><Msg>Be more like Democrats, it`s not freaking rocket science folks.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1363795488934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795555036-47</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You stupid NRA #$%$ Fox fool. Go back and screw your daughter loser.</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1363795555036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363795597156-48</Id><Title>Dreamliner to be cleared</Title><Msg>End of April is the latest prediction by BA. Yahooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1363795597156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795736079-49</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i expect she prefers real men, as opposed to gay and/or dumbo pretenders</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363795736079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363795802908-50</Id><Topic><Title>Simple way for Republicans to win</Title><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1363795488934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:04:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we''re all tapped out ahkmed, the golden goose is on it's last leg</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363795802908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363796021734-51</Id><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Msg>"A top company engineer said the necessary certification tests should be completed by Boeing in 'the next week or two' and that afterward he expects 'timely' FAA approval of the fix." Liar, liar, your pants are on fire.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363796352294-52</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So they didn't get inside and never saw the safe or its contents. And this qualifies as a "raid" by the "gestapo" how, exactly? It couldn't be that the gun #$%$ are getting a bit shrill, could it? Well, anyway, we can see that you are.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363796352294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363796720868-53</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds like gestapo to me, the parents / kid did NOTHING wrong, all of a sudden the Politically Communist police are at their door. chrissie are you n spart different idiots, or one n the same. if not are you hooz, or is it sparty?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363796720868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363796803318-54</Id><Topic><Title>BA rumored to be bought out!</Title><Username>smith.frank7</Username><Timestamp>1363260989034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 07:36:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>important information !</Msg><Username>lloyd_m82</Username><Timestamp>1363796803318</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363796854908-55</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They did the right thing.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363796854908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363796907374-56</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sounds like gestapo to me" What doesn't?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363796907374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363796930485-57</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Define timely. LMAO.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363796930485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363796931911-58</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your idea is an excellent one. The real reason progressives would never go for such a plan is that it gives the masses way too much freedom to make their own choices and suffer the consequences of those choices. The whole concept of Marxism/Communism/Statism/Colectivism/Democratism is that the masses are just too stupid and dumb to live in freedom and make their own choices and that’s why they need elitists to govern them and to make life’s necessary choices for them. Never mind that these so-called elitists can’t even come close to making decisions that will even remotely begin to approach the kind of benefits to mankind that individual liberty and free markets produce. These brilliant elitist are the ones that have got us $17 trillion in debt, confiscated the hard earned money of working people and redistributed it to wealthy donors, unions and non-producers. They have virtually destroyed the black family with their plethora of laws made every single American a criminal. They have convinced people they are too dumb to make their own choices of what they eat, buy, wear or should get for their labor. What’s ironic is that more and more members of the masses seem to be agreeing with them.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363796931911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363796974937-59</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"i expect she prefers real men" You mean like Lindsay Graham?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363796974937</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797130636-60</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What’s ironic is that more and more members of the masses seem to be agreeing with them." What is even more ironic is somebody who is constantly telling us that he is in the Cayman Islands posts on a yahoo message board every day. Can't help but wonder why.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363797130636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797189571-61</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well done</Msg><Username>nadya.lekki</Username><Timestamp>1363797189571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797412174-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think your IQ is borderline delusional. where do you come up with the ruffly $320,000,000,000.000.00 it would take to do that ? there is this thing called reality you must deal with.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1363797412174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797431784-63</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissie.....I suppose you also think "threatened to take his kids" is not a "gestapo" type action either.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363797431784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797750695-64</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not in the Cayman Islands today but if I were, I would still be able to post on here every day. You must be one of the masses that admits they're too dumb to live in freedom. I can see why you're also too dumb to know there is internet on the Caymans.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363797750695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363797943285-65</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will the Raven defend this veteran....or will he defend this tyrannical department of an increasingly tyrannical government?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363797943285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363798152735-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't Democrats ever Answer Question about their Looney Ideas?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363184496035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:21:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have answers for everything but the questions.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363798152735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363798218748-67</Id><Title>737 milestone</Title><Msg>SEATTLE, March 20, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing (BA) has delivered the 7,500th 737 to come off the production line to Malaysia-based Malindo Air. Malindo Air is a joint venture by Jakarta, Indonesia-based Lion Air and Malaysia's National Aerospace and Defence Industries. Malindo Air is using the Next-Generation 737-900ER to launch its low-fares service.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363798218748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363798251989-68</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just print it! That's what we do now and since deficits don't matter it's doable, right?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363798251989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363798486442-69</Id><Title>Live with it</Title><Msg>Iraq war veteran's open letter to Bush, Cheney: "I write not because I think you grasp the terrible human and moral consequences of your lies, manipulation and thirst for wealth and power. I write this letter because, before my own death, I want to make it clear that I, and hundreds of thousands of my fellow veterans, along with millions of my fellow citizens, along with hundreds of millions more in Iraq and the Middle East, know fully who you are and what you have done. You may evade justice but in our eyes you are each guilty of egregious war crimes, of plunder and, finally, of murder, including the murder of thousands of young Americans—my fellow veterans—whose future you stole."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363798623338-70</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you want to be that absurd about it just go pick the money off some trees.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1363798623338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363798998049-71</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama continues with the same 'war crimes' as Bush and Cheney. Is this veteran upset with Obama too?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363798998049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799233033-72</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the entire TSA structure, which has insinuated itself into almost every aspect of our lives and builds bonfires with our tax dollars, has been an insult to democracy ever since it was created by George W. Boxarox Bush. And to think the only power it derives is from the mind-numbing FEAR of wussie Americans that was fed off by the FEAR-mongers of the Neocon movement. Since 2001, we have been running out of specially hot places in hell where we can book reservatrions for these plutocrats.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363799233033</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799331200-73</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Democrats are refusing to deal with the reality of a 17 trillion dollar debt and huge deficits as far into the future as one can see, why is it anymore unrealistic to create 320 trillion dollars out of thin air when creating money out of thin air is one of the very few things they're really good at?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363799331200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799337657-74</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it like the threats you imply when your exhort your fellow right-fringers to stock up on precious metals like lead and brass?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363799337657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799349688-75</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are more in favor of eugenics than you allow yourself to be aware of you phony bootlicking skrewball</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363799349688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799410633-76</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363799410633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799435641-77</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you study up on economics especially money and banking and see if you yave to ask the same question again. For a quick answer ask an economist</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363799435641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799487189-78</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you sound just like the people who think that the way we print money now and raise deficits now, is absurd. ;-) I've seen videos of people talking about getting their share of Obama Money. I bet if you told them Obama Money came from a tree they would believe it.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363799487189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799571298-79</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you should read a little history, mirror games. The gestapo would simply have taken the kids. If you bozos knew what you were creating, you'd stop.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363799571298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799635485-80</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Government Police Raid Family's Home over Facebook Photo of Child’s Rifle</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787075165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"when the people fear the government there is tyranny. When the government fears the people there is liberty." What's wrong with stocking up on on precious metals like lead and brass? It only seems threatening if the government is the only ones that do it.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363799635485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799704638-81</Id><Topic><Title>You Gotta Love Michele Bachmann</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363732540871</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 18:35:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>genna's jealous</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363799704638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799733908-82</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why won't the Democrats abolish it?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363799733908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:15:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799735867-83</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you were NOT a righty-tighty, you would know that there's no need to be an apologist for the neocons Future World Leader Breeders..</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363799735867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799824613-84</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You only asked what *I* thought, brainless. But why indeed. I can't wait for it to come to a vote on the floor of the House of Reps. Harharharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363799824613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363799978839-85</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you trying to say?.....er avoid trying to answer? The question is, "is this veteran upset with Obama too?" Chrissie are you?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363799978839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800004584-86</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissie, Have you bought in to the mobro doctrine, as our POS n Chief, his CIA Chief, Injustice Head, Homeland Security Operative,....and Sparty</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363800004584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:20:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800036016-87</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I am not in the Cayman Islands" That was implied. There used to be a TV show called "Lifestyles of the Rich and Famous." You live as though you are in a trailer park, not a VIP on that program. You are certainly not going to sway anybody with your opinions until you live like a man in power. If you are not persuading anybody to adopt your political philosophy, then really, all you will accomplish is to look like a fool.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363800036016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800063798-88</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey yeah- those boxcutters are pretty inefficient for killing people. considering the gun loonacy in this country why don't we just open it up all the way and allow passengers to take anything they like abord airplanes and abololish the TSA 100%- now that makes a lot of sense to people like censored hope4 and mir rogains</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363800063798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800095490-89</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have... and so have the majority of the American people. Deal with that, too.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363800095490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800197072-90</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>most likely the event describited by the hate merchant hope4whitepeople never happened or if it did it has been greatly exaggerated by thishate merchant and liar without peer</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363800197072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800401504-91</Id><Topic><Title>March delivery update</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363793973957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:39:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A 777 for air china and a 747 (for korean air?) are in the air today.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363800401504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800500705-92</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans think Iraq War was a mistake: Poll</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363740706217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, What's your point? New poll out today shows most Americans think re-electing Obama was a mistake.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800500705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:28:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800831686-93</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read the whole story, brainless, and you will see he signed up to go after the 9/11 terrorists in Afghanistan. He was sent to Iraq, and that was what he thinks is a war crinme. Oddly enough, that is exactly how Ialways thought about the war in Iraq, and Obama has done what he can as fast as he can to end that war. I too supported going after our avowed enemies in Afghanistan -- until recently, when I decided that the puppet regimes we have tried to set up over there are just as ban an enemy. Remember Diem! Putz. I can be upset with Obama for delaying the end of our involvement in Afghanistan without screaming hatred and dripping acid like a dead battery, as you do.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363800831686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363800872380-94</Id><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Msg>Dubya did some dumb things and I feel no compulsion to defend those things. However, Obama has done many more dumb things that are harming the country but Chrissy feels an Obligation to defend him.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800890263-95</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: "... just as BAD and enemy."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363800890263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363800968347-96</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong. I defend the institutions of our government. As I swore in an oath once.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363800968347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:36:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801046114-97</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans think Iraq War was a mistake: Poll</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363740706217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He can't see through his dogma, hooz. But after all, I heard that a mission to Mars is being planned where the crew's dogma will be used to block cosmic rays.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363801046114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801135902-98</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans think Iraq War was a mistake: Poll</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363740706217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which might mean something if those people got to vote every couple of months, but they don't they get to vote for prez every 4 years. That's why Boxarox got so long to screw everything up.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363801135902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801333062-99</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans think Iraq War was a mistake: Poll</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363740706217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and people disliked being lied into a war with Iraq" You expressed your outrage with this "lying" I bet "Earlier today, I ordered America's armed forces to strike military and security targets in Iraq. They are joined by British forces. Their mission is to attack Iraq's nuclear, chemical and biological weapons programs and its military capacity to threaten its neighbors. Their purpose is to protect the national interest of the United States, and indeed the interests of people throughout the Middle East and around the world. Saddam Hussein must not be allowed to threaten his neighbors or the world with nuclear arms, poison gas or biological weapons." William Jefferson Clinton - Dec 1998</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1363801333062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801449782-100</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is the TSA one of the "institutions of our government" you defend?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363801449782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801582114-101</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes; and I will vote against it the first chance I'm given. Perhaps you've read my posts where I screech and whine and putt out my hair and rend my garments about the TSA. In an effort to be like mir! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363801582114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801622256-102</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you had enough brain cells to comprehend an answer, I'd respond to your question.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363801622256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801671230-103</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: "...and PULL out my hair ..." I think I need to run and get more coffee. Tata Putz.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363801671230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363801862472-104</Id><Topic><Title>BA rumored to be bought out!</Title><Username>smith.frank7</Username><Timestamp>1363260989034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 07:36:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very nice article!</Msg><Username>clark_w44</Username><Timestamp>1363801862472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363802197230-105</Id><Title>Obama Keeps All His Promises :-)</Title><Msg>Cut the deficit in half by 2012, close GITMO, troops out of Afghanistan by 2011 -- he did that right? he said he would</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1363802197230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:56:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363803255711-106</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>También se la llama doble obras para la contratación externa"</Msg><Username>hoiinca</Username><Timestamp>1363803255711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363803650719-107</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You obviously took an oath different from the one I took when I entered the Marine. ""I, mir_rguns, do solemnly swear (or affirm) that I will support and defend the Constitution of the United States against all enemies, foreign and domestic; that I will bear true faith and allegiance to the same; and that I will obey the orders of the President of the United States and the orders of the officers appointed over me, according to regulations and the Uniform Code of Military Justice. So help me God." I don't see anything in there about defending "the institutions of our government." Especially if they're not constitutional.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363803650719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363803850103-108</Id><Topic><Title>787 fix, sounds like Boeing is dictating " Timely FAA approval of the fix."</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363633836490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 15:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>somnolent encore ? accueil à la zone crépusculaire.</Msg><Username>hoiinca</Username><Timestamp>1363803850103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363804434804-109</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mining _PhD and you can bet your britches on that one too ! Wayne !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363804434804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363804636159-110</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My aunt died on the ValueJet crash in the Florida everglades. That was due to a onboard fire. The never recovered her body.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363804636159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363804699581-111</Id><Topic><Title>Why these numbers 13 and 17 seem to make Boeing at leas 6 stock holder's angry &amp; enrage or provoke?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363766082622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 03:54:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So for the Boeing hacks, liar liar pants on fire and the number 13 and 17 really get you all hot under the collar too !!!!! I see smoke but no fire and is that some kind of enclosure to contain the Boeing hacks ----Feeling or showing anger; incensed or enraged i see white hot feeling emitting from the Boeing hack department now.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363804699581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363804917194-112</Id><Topic><Title>INFLUENCE GAME: Congress quiet on Dreamliner woes, or hide in" plane" sight</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363792759144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:19:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow the Boeing hacks are hiding, wonder why / they are just too angry to reply now eh I i see smoke but no fire and a containment enclosure might be teh answer, to the Boeing hacks anger, yes it is anger when the truth about Boeing is listed here - Feeling or showing anger; incensed or enraged is the only response because the truth is just too hard to bear !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363804917194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363805708001-113</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's essentially the oath I took, freely and without mental reservation or purpose of evasion. The Constitution you took an oath to support and defend enumerates the institutions of our government, and since no one appointed you to the Supreme Court, you don't get to pick and choose which institutions are constitutional. Those 9 cats in robes do that. On the other hand, you also swore to obey the orders of the president, which for right now is Barack Hussein Obama. (I see that no one asked you to LIKE them.) So what's your "out," again?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363805708001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363805776037-114</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And I enjoyed doing it, hooz. But I'm back now.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363805776037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363806128619-115</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mining_phd, I am sorry for your loss my uncle died in a hellcat in WWII the plane did not recover from a dive on a Japanese freighter it was mechanical error or worse, a friendly fire deal , he was too good a pilot not to pull out of a strafe family death is hard to take for any reason .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363806128619</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363806342507-116</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans think Iraq War was a mistake: Poll</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363740706217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I expressed my outrage: I oppose Dubya's War by: Chris_Genna (M/Kent, WA) 03/16/03 02:48 am Msg: 218294 A U.S.-only pre-emptive invasion of Iraq will result in hundreds of Americans being killed, if we're lucky and if the Vultures' wishful thinking is correct. Each is as good as person as anyone posting here, with hopes for the future as good and valid as any of ours. I know some of them; some are the kids of guys I flew with. I support them and I honor them for their loyalty and their dedication to doing the job they are ordered to do. I wish their leaders were as commendable. It will result in the deaths of thousands of innocent Iraqis and each will have a couple of relatives who will decide it will be worth his life to kill a few dozen Americans. But cowards die many times," and this would not deter me if there was any chance such a war would bring peace or even stability (a stable level of turmoil) to the region. It will not, not unless we are prepared to remain there for years and turn Iraq into a military/police state. If you do not believe this, check out the history of ANY region at ANY time that was "pacified" by a superpower -- Afghanistan (or even India) under the Brits, Northwest Africa (or Lebanon) under the French, etc. The weaponry has changed but human nature has not. So why do it? Like Epistemophile, I have lost track of which rationalizations have been justified by which lies. It has been said Saddam has weapons of mass destruction; no one believes this. So it became that he was developing weapons of mass destruction. Drones have turned out to be toy airplanes; attempts to purchase plutonium have turned out to be forgeries. Every other nation (and there are a score or more) who have developed weapons of mass detruction have learned pretty quickly that ownership beings a kind of responsibility. That includes China back when it was OK to call them "Red China." Career diplomats have quit in disgust at our gunslinging, simplistic (MORE</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363806342507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363806412954-117</Id><Topic><Title>Most Americans think Iraq War was a mistake: Poll</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363740706217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CONT view of the path to "peace." The Vultures say Saddam has to go. Fine. Does it take an Army and Navy and Air Force to get that done? Those who complain loud and often that I'm a Democrat take note: When Ronald Reagan decided Moammar Gadhafi had to go (and the French wouldn't agree, by the way) Reagan had the good sense to launch an air strike aimed at Gadhafi. He missed (too bad) but Gadhafi sure was quiet after that. Maybe it would work with Saddam. We don't know because we aren't going to try it. It does not fit with our administration's plans to get control of those Iraqi oil well heads. Now that the strike force is in position, we could retaliate against any attack on our jets in the no-fly zones. This too is dismissed. It's as if we need to show the world we don't need a reason. A pre-emptive strike will establish the principle as legitimate (just as an attack using poison gas would legitimize that tactic -- and why do you think no one tried it in WW2?) Do we want to set an example for the rest of the unpleasant people in the world that pre-emption is a valid reason to fire missiles? Can't you think of any other regimes paranoid enough and capable enough to do this? How about North Korea? Oh, right, we're going after them next, right? Or is it after Iran? Or the French or the U.N. (in N.Y.)? No one should want to establish the principle of pre-emption. Even the state terrorism-supported Stalin regime would not open hostilities with Hitler! When the Israelis used pre-emption in the 1967 war, they had to spend the next two years tring to justify it, and had so little success at it that they had to get caught with their pants down in 1973. Most important to me: Going into Iraq alone or largely alone negates the best credit this nation ever had in the world, and perhaps the only credit we have left -- that we're the good guys; that we don't start wars, but finish them. We show the world what it means to be free; what it means to be *SELF*-determinant. We wh</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363806412954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363806645488-118</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rummy said 6 days maybe 6 weeks and surely less than 6 months even as they ignored Afghanistan. Gen Powell resigned and would not continue to serve under bushJr. Mr Obama Voted Against the Iraq involvement. bushJr WAS C and C / POTUS and too many went along w/o proper investigations. I am still ashamed for our collective prejudicial Islamaphobia and for bushJr allowing American troops being used as Saudi mercenaries. Any soldier and ESPECIALLY one that was Wounded in Combat, has the Right and Duty to tell the Truth as they see it. Wannabees that weren't there will have to #$%$ and listen with Respect... Many Veterans wake each day and go to sleep (try) with the results of our many misguided Wars, and many have given all and are just #$%$ DEAD. Pretty high prices in Blood and Treasure that will be with us for at least generations. I agree with this Veteran's opinions.</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1363806645488</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363806874822-119</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are mighty right, TC.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363806874822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363807181384-120</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mining phd that was the ValuJet Flight 592 was a domestic passenger flight between Miami International Airport, Miami, Florida, and William B. Hartsfield Atlanta International Airport, Atlanta, Georgia that crashed into the Everglades on May 11, 1996 as a result of a fire in the cargo compartment killing all 110 people on board a DC-9 plane I remember it well.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363807181384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363807354354-121</Id><Topic><Title>Rename for 787's</Title><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1363706703643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:25:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thumb-downers obviously don't work on the 787......</Msg><Username>mocking_heads</Username><Timestamp>1363807354354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:22:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363807422492-122</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mir rogain if you hadn't flunked out of the 3rd grad you might be capable of learning something but that opportunity was lost long ago. Be satisfied with what you are- a sub 70 IQ critter who cant even find a decent bridge to sleep under</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807422492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363807496961-123</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or discuss it with Paul Allen</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363807496961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363807695147-124</Id><Title>5 experimental 787 aircraft flew for 2 years no battery problems</Title><Msg>5 experimental 787 aircraft flew for 2 years wo battery trouble proving that the design works- The japanese airlines had problems indicating that the problem is with Japanese airlines not the Boeing 787</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807695147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363807757259-125</Id><Topic><Title>Rename for 787's</Title><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1363706703643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:25:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought it was funny.</Msg><Username>duane_460</Username><Timestamp>1363807757259</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363807788770-126</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about Dell George's boy friend</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807788770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363808286093-127</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>`father, you are asking that folks get answers from the experts?...you, a leftist? Had you just followed your own advice you'd be a normal decent thinking conservative today.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1363808286093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:38:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363808450407-128</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whstllefanms I mean father zosima you need to run that by your boy friend Paul Allen too, ans father whistleffanms careful with your inelecto uaall discshon with rockstar both of you need to be very careful not to blow your nose if anyof that IQ that leaks out it may make both of you unable to continue your boring intelecual dsh gust shon wow ee like if only Einstein were here , they he could explain the relativity of your appeal to anyone in the past , present or future please your way too inet ltectual for us lower people so why not pay another visit paul Allen on your real big boat once you leave your estate in the apartment in Everett , you know the smaller room that you share in your mothers home.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363808450407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363808542717-129</Id><Topic><Title>Rename for 787's</Title><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1363706703643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:25:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>firestarter</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363808542717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363808546411-130</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing to warn for 1st Quarter</Title><Username>bankrdude10</Username><Timestamp>1363699961093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 09:32:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, there are rumors but nothing substantive. Note that the "fix" Boeing is offering is a relatively cheap option and if they can get the FAA to buy it they will have gotten away without a lot of incremental production costs. But that still leaves the extra inventory carrying costs of the 87s sitting around, the reduced cash flow from delayed deliveries, and potential penalties to the airlines. Your logic on there being extra costs is good but given the miracle of Boeing accounting practices it may get hidden away in the footnotes or spread out over ten years or so. Another associated factor is that McNerney is going to retire in a year or two and wants to go out on a high note with maximized bonuses.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1363808546411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363808622015-131</Id><Topic><Title>Rename for 787's</Title><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1363706703643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:25:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well it flies in the corporate board room just not in Everett or the rest of the world that would be a nightmare liner</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363808622015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363808845483-132</Id><Topic><Title>Rename for 787's</Title><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1363706703643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:25:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the flying firebox a double redundancy airplane with a box containing a fire inside a 600 MPH box with several hundred passengers who are kindling wood once the containment box can not fail, can not fail, can not fail, shut off the back box power is off now and the plane has crashed due to pilot error sorry we don't know what happened and the back box is 3 mile down in the ocean and we cant find it so sorry</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363808845483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809076436-133</Id><Topic><Title>Rename for 787's</Title><Username>inwestminsterca</Username><Timestamp>1363706703643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 11:25:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when you get the thumb it is from the 6 Boeing hacks that try try try to convince investors that Boeing is a good investment compared to airbus lets see BA stock price is up up 13% for ytd while airbus up 35% for 3 years Boeing is up up up 17% while airbus is up 163%so conclusion sorry Boeing hacks , nope nope nope, Boeing hacks, liar liar pants on fire BA is not as good as airbus for any investor</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363809076436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809121635-134</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Given all the hype about having a test plan in place and ready to go it's puzzling that neither one of the flight test aircraft (5 and 272) have taken to the skies yet since getting the go ahead.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1363809121635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809204662-135</Id><Topic><Title>5 experimental 787 aircraft flew for 2 years no battery problems</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807695147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and yet all the 787 the planes are grounded? father, we need your guidance here , what happened father explain it to us we all want to observe your genius at work !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363809204662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809320205-136</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I actually had flunked out of the 3rd grade I still would have been far more educated than you and I would have had some common sense which you totally lack.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363809320205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809380377-137</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>techpath2000 it is much better to talk a good game on the 787 than to fly the fire starter any time soon good comment BTW and only one test flight planned , Boeing sure does not want to chance too much air time in the plane do they !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363809380377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:56:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809435474-138</Id><Topic><Title>BA rumored to be bought out!</Title><Username>smith.frank7</Username><Timestamp>1363260989034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 07:36:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lots of information, worth seeing!</Msg><Username>w_matt74</Username><Timestamp>1363809435474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363809822968-139</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These American citizens, who lost their lives, have a small plaque that is off the highway and cannot be seen be the traveling public in the everglades. They are Americans. They are not foreigners, who lived and died on foreign soil. I think they deserve a Holocaust memorial on Pennsylvania Blvd in Washington DC. It should be taxpayer supported. Some Americans pay homage to a group of folks who were not American citizens, did not fight for America ( most fought on the side of the Communists in the Spanish Civil War 1936-1939) , were not killed by Americans and did not die on American soil, yet they have a $175,000,000 museum of victimization, which costs taxpayers $45,000,000 per year to operate. Mr President, remove the Holocaust museum to some land off American soil. It is an affront to every nationality in the world, and most every Veteran.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363809822968</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363810274673-140</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the business of air travel does not want to advertise the death of airplane passengers it is bad for business, the Spokane Military graveyard is a mile east of medical lake about 8 miles east of Spokane , this is the new one, in the middle of a wheat field so isolated . whine i visit my fellow friends the second thing about the sadness is how far away the government plants them as used assets they are ignored for their life The military grave site for 100 year or older is close but then Spokane was a smaller town and has expanded. So in a 200 years medial lake will have a close grave site to visit your great grandfather who gave his life for america , not much thanks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363810274673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363810360166-141</Id><Topic><Title>**** TEN MEDIA HOAX'S ****</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1363320052209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 00:00:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You believe in those fairy tales if that is how you cope in life. If you think the hoax is real, produce proof of one gassing, and win a $100,000 prize. As George Bush would say, you are either with the truth or you are with the hoaxsters.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363810360166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363810528021-142</Id><Topic><Title>Budget deadlock squeezes military members seeking education</Title><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1363462980542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judaism, religion of porn. You chickenhawks never served because you are too yellow.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363810528021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:15:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363810681749-143</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't Democrats ever Answer Question about their Looney Ideas?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363184496035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:21:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because they're like a deer caught in the headlights when anyone points out how stupid their ideas are.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363810681749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:18:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363811073729-144</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's certainly more logical than a minimum wage.....or socialized medical care.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363811073729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363811116955-145</Id><Topic><Title>Budget deadlock squeezes military members seeking education</Title><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1363462980542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you directed this slur at me. Yes, I have Jewish ancestry, both sides killed off the other and I am what's left. Wrong on MY Service to OUR America. You are a candy a$$ed Wannabee, truth. You must feel so secure to write this and You're welcome for OUR sacrifices that allow your vile puking (speech). Thesevenfingeredgimp VFW Post 81, member...</Msg><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1363811116955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:25:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363811133057-146</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With just a little effort you will be able to find and read numerous articles by Iraqi war veterans who are proud of their service and consider what they did to be a just cause to include once recent aricle by female Marine officer who lost a leg.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1363811133057</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363811503606-147</Id><Topic><Title>Budget deadlock squeezes military members seeking education</Title><Username>tcmoiba</Username><Timestamp>1363462980542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>98% of you ribbon wearers sat a a desk or served soup in some kitchen on a boat or tent and parade around like you are Gen Patton. Oh, I forgot, Judiasm religion of porn, the ad hominem and usary. Your trinity.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363811503606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:31:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363811654628-148</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying this is not a government of the PEOPLE, by the PEOPLE and for the PEOPLE? I took that oath too but I'm no longer bound by it because I'm no tin the military. If the president doesn't keep his oath of office then why should anyone else?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363811654628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363811941113-149</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A most intriguing scenario. I wonder how long it would take today's government dependents to get back in the same financial shape they are today and be screaming "we need a level playing field?"</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363811941113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363812079679-150</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the Devil</Title><Username>otto_pilot_blow_me</Username><Timestamp>1363811539445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most sane people already knew he is the devil.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363812079679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363812390966-151</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the Devil</Title><Username>otto_pilot_blow_me</Username><Timestamp>1363811539445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sane people know that the Devil is nothing more than a paranoid delusion.</Msg><Username>barking_dogmas</Username><Timestamp>1363812390966</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363812469884-152</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Raven: Did you google "uss liberty veterans association" like I asked you ?</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1363494722637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 00:32:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crissie is like a good little #$%$ soldier. He says he doesn't have the right to refuse to Obey the C in C as long as the supremes agree with him. Most of us think there is a higher power that pulls rank on the President and the supremes.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363812469884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363812855494-153</Id><Title>DHS Official: Fine, Maybe We Could Have Cut Costs Without Releasing Aggravated Felons</Title><Msg>Democrats' sequester tower of terror continues to collapse, floor by floor. Amidst the media fact checks and stomach-turning posturing, Republican members of Congress are using hearings to hold bureaucrats' feet to the fire over the claims and actions of their departments. Rep. Andy Harris (R-MD) blew the cover off of the administration's duplicity on supposed cuts to pediatric vaccinations a few weeks ago; yesterday, it was South Carolina Congressman Trey Gowdy's turn at bat. Watch as he grills a Department of Homeland Security Under Secretary as to why his team released ten "level 1" aggravated felons from federal custody, supposedly due to sequester cuts: GOWDY: "There was nothing else [you] could do as a cost savings measure. Is that your testimony?" BORRAS: "No, that is not my testimony." My personal favorite exchange was the bit where Gowdy "asks" Borras how long the department had to prepare for sequestration, knowing exactly what the correct response would be: More than a year and a half. And yet they were hoping the American people would simply accept the notion that they couldn't spare $1,200 bucks to keep violent felons locked up, ostensibly because of small across-the-board federal spending reductions. Not cuts, reductions in the rate of growth. Remember, the president proposed and signed this law, then attempted to pawn off its supposed ill-effects onto Republicans -- hoping to count on the credulous media the spread the distortions. When the GOP wouldn't cave, the administration mobilized to set the vast apparatus of the federal government to work against the interests and well being of the American people in order to justify their hysterical predictions of widespread misery. I'll leave you with the infamous quote that sums up this deeply cynical and reckless approach to governance: "It is our opinion that however you manage that reduction, you need to make sure you are not contradicting what we said the impact would be."</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363812855494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363813246303-154</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so the thumbs count is is 20 thumb down, a real indicator of the Boeing Hacks are all hacked off . and with no argument,so Boeing hacks, it is l hard to argue the facts. lets give the anger inducement engagement comparison Boeing compared to Airbus as found on cnn money . today BA YTD is up , up up 13% , Airbus (eadsy) is only 35% up YTD and then airplane delivery and sold orders hacks, it gets worse for all you Boeing investors or as you opinion for yourself the investors of the the number one airplane company, Boeing and your point is ? for who? not the shareholders investment anyway! so today's updated comparisons for the end of the trade day . Hold your breath now and prey, oh so sorry, hacked off Boeing investors , the DOW and p and P 500 and nasdaq compared to the Boeing e year gain of a pathetic fire starter 787 failure is only up up up in smoke, but not fire , at only of 17% while airbus is still up 162 % as of today.not too close a race between number one Boeing adn number two airbus eh !And how does Boeing do compred to the average it belongs to the Dow , terrible, is the only answer. over the last three years are all twice Boeing pathetic performance Dow up 33.74% s and p 500 is up 34% and the NASDAQ average of all good and bad stock up 36%so tell me why you think Boeing is the "plane " maker or a business investment plan that would make any investor any good gains compared to the overall stock market let along the miss on 162% with Airbus</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363813246303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363813269636-155</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a dumb idea... really.. the poor and middle class, as a percentage of their income, spends more on consumption than the rich. So, why are you giving the heaviest tax burden on the people who can least afford it?</Msg><Username>android_shopper</Username><Timestamp>1363813269636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363813387342-156</Id><Title>Experts: House Budget Spurs Growth, Senate Version Spikes Debt</Title><Msg>The House of Representatives is expected to take up Paul Ryan's budget today, as the Senate begins debate on Democrats' first fiscal roadmap in nearly four years. The House GOP version balances in ten years, without raising taxes, by reducing the rate of spending growth and reforming entitlement programs. Senate Democrats propose $1.5 trillion in tax increases and hundreds of billions in phony savings, yet their ledger never approaches balance. The president's offering is still nowhere to be found. Ryan's plan would shave $4.6 trillion from deficits over ten years, compared to the current spending path; the Reid/Murray approach actually raises overall spending by hundreds of billions. As these contrasting paths forward are discussed on Capitol Hill, read through this Wall Street Journal op-ed by two Stanford University economists. They argue that their thorough analysis suggests that the House budget would boost the economy and inspire confidence in American employers, investors and creditors: According to our research, the spending restraint and balanced-budget parts of the House Budget Committee plan would boost the economy immediately. With the Budget Committee's proposed tax reform included, the immediate impact would be even larger. The entire plan would raise gross domestic product by one percentage point in 2014, equivalent to about a $1,500 increase for each U.S. household. Ten years from now, at the end of the official budget horizon, we estimate that the entire plan would raise GDP by three percentage points, or more than $4,000 for each U.S. household... The long-run economic gains from restraining government spending would not, despite what critics claim, harm the economy in the short run. Instead, the economy would start to grow right away. Why? First, the lower level of future government spending avoids the necessity of sharply raising taxes. The expectation that tax rates won't need to rise provides incentives for higher investment</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363813387342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:03:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363813854359-157</Id><Title>This will be at 80.00</Title><Msg>Anyone doubt that?</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363813854359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363813955889-158</Id><Topic><Title>This will be at 80.00</Title><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363813854359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:10:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a short on as of today. We shall see. Ran up too fast on negative news. It will be a classic sell the news when the turd is back in the air</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363813955889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363814299892-159</Id><Title>Lets hope for another strike</Title><Msg>80.00 on its way.</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363814299892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363814454611-160</Id><Title>NOW MY SHORTS GET PAID</Title><Msg>took a few days off from bashing. now still sitting with 400 shares short at abg close to 81, explaining in my last post any mis step and this priced for perfection stock will plummet. it may not be as fast as i like or thought as it clips down a little each day but with the recipients of 787 clammer for cold hard cash we ought to see the slow and steady decline i'v anticipaTED. in addition for another mis step i'm sure lurking around the corner. everyone thinks rally on for the indicies but i think too many sailors on one side of the boat now and individual issues like BA ready to bring it down as soon as something like a little more delay in 787 testing or gov't backlash fearing catastrophy if they move too fast. helped of course by customer wanting cash. i'm also ready to double on margin if ti miracously cruises into the 90's for a total of 800 shares short. see ya in the green by weeks end, if not months end, haha, lol</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1363814454611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363814511110-161</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Progressive taxation is a dumb idea. The more you produce the more you're punished. A consumption tax is much more fair. With a consumption tax people who can afford to spend the most will pay the most. Although slightly different, a sales tax and no income tax works well in states. These states have no income taxes. Alaska Florida Nevada South Dakota Texas Washington Wyoming Compare their economic performance with states that the highest personal income taxes: California New York New Jersey Connecticut These states are also losing populations as producers move to states with lower tax burdens. Producers - the people that actually pay taxes......are voting with their feet.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363814511110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363814653717-162</Id><Topic><Title>Chrissie's Hypocrisy</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1363800872380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not for me to question whether legality. I was only following Mein Fuhrer's orders.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1363814653717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363814749079-163</Id><Topic><Title>NOW MY SHORTS GET PAID</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1363814454611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smart man,</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363814749079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363814783721-164</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you hate freedom?</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1363814783721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363814813121-165</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the Devil</Title><Username>otto_pilot_blow_me</Username><Timestamp>1363811539445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was trying to get Jesus to take food handouts but Jesus refused. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363814813121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815010575-166</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the Devil</Title><Username>otto_pilot_blow_me</Username><Timestamp>1363811539445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yea.......you obviously haven't been paying attention to Obama.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363815010575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815167404-167</Id><Topic><Title>NOW MY SHORTS GET PAID</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1363814454611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You wil make money. Fact.</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363815167404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:32:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815226672-168</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“We cannot continue to rely only on our military in order to achieve the national security objectives that we’ve set. We’ve got to have a civilian national security force that’s just as powerful, just as strong, just as well funded.” Barrack Obama</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1363815226672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:33:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815312687-169</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you read anywhere in my post that I considered his opinion universal, then you are a knee-jerking Right-fringe howler whose hair catches fire whenever anyone says boo!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363815312687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815382551-170</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for another strike</Title><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363814299892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those union guys really threw a curve ball at Boeing. Management didn't get the strike that lil' wayne said Boeing was trying to get in order to catch up on supply orders and avoid delay penalties.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1363815382551</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363815392155-171</Id><Title>Going down</Title><Msg>Anyone doubt that???????????</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363815392155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:36:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815444701-172</Id><Topic><Title>**** TEN MEDIA HOAX'S ****</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1363320052209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 00:00:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For me, the ultimate test is this, Reinhard: Who would benefit from the halocaust being found to be lie? "By their fruits you will know them." Sieg heil!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363815444701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363815479801-173</Id><Title>Will Chrissie Defend Veterans or will he Defend the CIC's insanity.</Title><Msg>American’s are now three weeks into the sequester and even though Obama’s administration has since withdrawn their apocalyptic government warnings, questionable spending cuts continue to persist. Earlier this week Fox News reported that the administration had approved $37 million in foreign aid for Pakistan at the expense of a tuition assistance program for veterans. Rep. Ted Poe, R-Texas, plans to introduce a bill that will stop foreign aid funding until military tuition is restored: “Why are we funding education programs for [Pakistan] when we can't fund -- or don't fund -- the education for our military? And to Pakistan of all places, where hatred for America is at its highest. Washington should watch its spending and prioritize.” Poe went on to defend the program, claiming that: “The cost of the program is .1 percent of the Defense Department's budget, and one that has helped graduate 50,000 individuals. The Marines spent roughly $47 million from the program last year”. Veteran unemployment already hovers around 9.4%, almost two points above the national average. And despite the president’s assurance last year that “no one who fights for this country overseas should ever have to fight for a job”, the elimination of this program tells a contradicting story. Various departments have already made multiple cuts to make Americans feel the effects of the sequester, though as previously reported, the reasoning is purely political. The news comes two weeks after Secretary of State John Kerry announced another foreign aid package of $250 million for Egypt. These promises of foreign aid are particularly complexing when factoring in the results of a Pew Research Poll conducted a week before the sequestration deadline, which found that “[f]or 18 of 19 programs tested, majorities want either to increase spending or maintain it at current levels. The only exception is assistance for needy people around the world.” Unfortunately it appears as if Democrat spending will continue to go unchecked. Money that could be allocated towards supporting troops is being spent on countries that haven’t always had America’s best interest in mind. Yet another example of how far the government is willing to go to fabricate sequester pains.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363815479801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815515759-174</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read "Refusal to mourn the death by fire of a child in London." Then try to grow up.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363815515759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815632858-175</Id><Topic><Title>Lets hope for another strike</Title><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363814299892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good. More bad news</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363815632858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363815690774-176</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosima....Instead of making one of your normal stupid comments you could have checked it out and you would have know it happened just as hope4 reported. He's obviously much, much smarter than you.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363815690774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816063013-177</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't think of a thing in that statement that strikes fear in me. He doesn't say secret police or gestapo. Why does it strike fear in you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363816063013</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816107853-178</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is the Devil</Title><Username>otto_pilot_blow_me</Username><Timestamp>1363811539445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tee hee.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363816107853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816327731-179</Id><Topic><Title>Will Chrissie Defend Veterans or will he Defend the CIC's insanity.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363815479801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:37:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We do know without a doubt obama and the left do not want big govt spending reduced. Obama makes the ignorant statement that he "is not worried about the debt, that problem is over"..when his own plan has us headed towards $20,000,000,000,000 in debt (with a "T") in a few short years. Now Harry Reid lies about Marines dying in his state of Idaho during training "because of the budget cuts"...The Marines called Harry, and told him he was lying.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1363816327731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363816363801-180</Id><Title>Would the Raven Have Joined the Rebellion against King George in 1776?</Title><Msg>....or would he have remained loyal to the King?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816363801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:52:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816496521-181</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is your President.</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363815177091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But unlike in years gone by, Americans have accepted who their President was. This President is so bad for the country, a high percentage of Americans do not accept him as their President. Almost 1/2 the country thinks that way, and views BO as a huge mistake having been elected by ignorant folks, and the far left kooks that number around 20%.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1363816496521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816560710-182</Id><Topic><Title>Will Chrissie Defend Veterans or will he Defend the CIC's insanity.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363815479801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:37:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry's state is Nevada...but Harry is insane.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816560710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816822439-183</Id><Topic><Title>Going down</Title><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363815392155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going down like a #$%$ on a meat popsicle</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1363816822439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816833303-184</Id><Topic><Title>a road map to a much brighter America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816753055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Sparty might say, "People are waking up."</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363816833303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816858416-185</Id><Topic><Title>Could Michael Jackson still do the moonwalk if he were alive?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816581759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its a very TRENDY question...very trendy...very liberal...very Non Racist</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1363816858416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816876911-186</Id><Topic><Title>Could Michael Jackson still do the moonwalk if he were alive?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816581759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will little Chrissie be able to squeeze out a rational thought before the hypothetical question hour ends?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1363816876911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816948960-187</Id><Topic><Title>a road map to a much brighter America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816753055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds more like a road map to China by way of North Korea.................</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1363816948960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816981019-188</Id><Topic><Title>Will Chrissie Defend Veterans or will he Defend the CIC's insanity.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363815479801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:37:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe everything you post when you talk about Harry Reid's state, Idaho. Hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363816981019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363816993050-189</Id><Topic><Title>a road map to a much brighter America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816753055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HE SHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOTS..............................................HE SCORRRRRRRESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1363816993050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363816994557-190</Id><Title>Is Harry Reid Punch Drunk?</Title><Msg>Harry Reid's profession boxing record of 3 and 27 is a good indication why he gave up boxing to become a politician but leaves little doubt that the sport left him with an acute form of dementia.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816994557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817065665-191</Id><Topic><Title>Going down</Title><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363815392155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup.</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363817065665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:04:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817136530-192</Id><Topic><Title>Would the Raven Have Joined the Rebellion against King George in 1776?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816363801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:52:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven would have been the King's boyfriend............</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1363817136530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817209256-193</Id><Topic><Title>a road map to a much brighter America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816753055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What, no attribution? Harharharhar At least you aren't saying that about yourself. Or are you?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363817209256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817236049-194</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A quote that is entirely more appropriate: "Sparty is truly insane." Sammy</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1363817236049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:07:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817795444-195</Id><Topic><Title>a road map to a much brighter America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816753055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Genna I beg to differ. Poor Sparty represents IN NO WAY any known state of wakefulness.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1363817795444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817837170-196</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah...you just WISH I were insane...If Im not...then you're entire parallel Universe is bogus....right Raven?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1363817837170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817841683-197</Id><Topic><Title>a road map to a much brighter America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816753055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have a problem with people learning about past and current events?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1363817841683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363817894529-198</Id><Topic><Title>a road map to a much brighter America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816753055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Colorado has a head start on becoming the dope smoking nitwit capital of America. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363817894529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363818035798-199</Id><Topic><Title>Dremliner to fly soon or not ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1363796021734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A truly dirty, nasty, filthy, stinking, vile, obscene post.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1363818035798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:20:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363818288706-200</Id><Title>White House hoses tourists who went to see the peoples House</Title><Msg>But Senator Tom Coburn, Republican of Oklahoma, failed to win passage of his proposal to take $6 million from the National Heritage Partnership Program, which runs a wine-tasting train in Ohio, a Celtic celebration in Wheeling, W.V., and a Salem Witch Hunt program in Massachusetts, and use it to force President Obama to keep White House tours operating. The White House opposed it, and Democrats fell in line.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1363818288706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363819176568-201</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most folks don't wish any form of insanity on anybody. In your case, you MAY have enough resources to go get help. Take your list of conspiracies to the nearest mental health counselor and see if he stops you once you get past the first several dozen. IF he lets you go to 5 dozen or so, he is probably simply too amazed to speak. Your life can be good. Get help.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1363819176568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363819325685-202</Id><Topic><Title>BA rumored to be bought out!</Title><Username>smith.frank7</Username><Timestamp>1363260989034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 07:36:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks just received the report</Msg><Username>mike.sanch7</Username><Timestamp>1363819325685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363821483849-203</Id><Title>Another satellite launch</Title><Msg>Boeing (NYSE: BA ) and Lockheed-Martin’s (NYSE: LMT ) space-launch joint venture, the United Launch Alliance, or ULA, successfully launched its third rocket of 2013 into orbit yesterday. An Atlas V rocket carried a Space-Based Infrared System satellite into orbit on behalf of the U.S. Air Force, the second such satellite to be deployed after the first reached orbit in 2011.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363821483849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 19:18:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363822756967-204</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hunter is a pathetic wimp. He got his job because his dad was a Congressman with the name spelled the same. Hunter kisses butt for the military and bows to Israel. He is a disgrace to america.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363822756967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 19:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363825238577-205</Id><Topic><Title>NOW MY SHORTS GET PAID</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1363814454611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's up with all the thumbs down, truth hurts? Oh I know pointing the way the stock is headed. Everyone will be headed for the hills prior to earnings release knowing lost revenue on straight up cash give backs, and the future growth trimmed for the large discounts needed to off load these pigs. I've got a great idea for a new business AIRPLANEFAX. It works like car fax, pull a report on a plane and see if its been in any battery fires or clipped wings of parked runway aircraft due to drunken pilots. Hahahahalolhaha</Msg><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1363825238577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363825806520-206</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nancy Pelosi and Hillary Clinton supported the removal of Saddam Hussein. The Dems all supported Bush going to war in Iraq Chrissie. It doesn't matter how deep you bury your head in the sand and deny the truth, you can't prevent others from knowing the truth. This veteran is ill informed just as you are.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363825806520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363826531671-207</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The responsibility for the war lies with the leaders which, in this case, were Cheney and Rumsfeld. Bush was willing to do whatever they wanted to do. Cheney entered office in 2001 with the intent of going to war with Iraq. As Secretary of Defense, he wanted to take out Saddam while we were ther. Besides, if you want to talk about hypocrisy, when Bush was wearing his flight suit, declaring Mission Accomplished, and saying "America and her allies have prevailed in Iraq", Bush, Cheny, and Rumsfeld were riding high and saying "We did it!" It wasn't until Bush admitted we aren't winning, but we're not losing either, and we need the surge that it became the Democrats war too. The Democrats insist they were not given complete information from Cheney/Rumsfeld, and the American people believe them.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363826531671</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363826758703-208</Id><Topic><Title>Michele Bachmann runs away from reporter</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363825753374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:29:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who was he reporter?...from the mainstream mediaa?...lookin to trap Backmann with a loaded, leftist question?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1363826758703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363826912036-209</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raven, why does The Flight Suit bother you so much? Do you still suffer from jet jock envy?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1363826912036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:48:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363827150856-210</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are all on tape claiming Saddam had WMDs and Hillary and Pelosi are on the record claiming the need to take out Saddam. I can't help that Democrats lie and people don't know the truth and are too lazy to do the fact finding. Obama is already committed his own war crimes and again if people choose to be blind and stupid it's on them. Many honest intelligent liberals, the ones that haven't swapped their moral compass for a thrill up their leg, have acknowledged Obama's war crimes.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363827150856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363827397356-211</Id><Topic><Title>Michele Bachmann runs away from reporter</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363825753374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:29:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody could trap Bachmann with cheese, a bucket, and a piece of string.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363827397356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:56:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363827419245-212</Id><Title>Reid used military deaths to push his spending addiction today</Title><Msg>What a complete #$%$. Reid was eviscerated by the military for his use of dead service men to push his political agenda.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363827419245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:56:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363827525410-213</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, based on the lies of Rumsfeld and Cheney. It's the Republicans' war, and always will be.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363827525410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 20:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363827958678-214</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was advised by his lawyers to create legal separation from Bush on the Iraq war and they outlined how he could accomplish that. Obama chose not to take that advice. Thus from that point on Obama was complicit, supportive and responsible for the war. You can bury your head in the sand next to Chrissie.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363827958678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363828260078-215</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama ended the war on December 18, 2011, in his first term. It will always be a war started by Republicans and ended by the Democrats.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1363828260078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363828320298-216</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The flight suit bothers me because Bush served almost none of his time in the reserves. He got extensive excused absences to serve on his Dad's campaign. He never really earned the right to wear that flight suit.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1363828320298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363828356137-217</Id><Title>787 flight tests possible by end of this week.</Title><Msg>SEATTLE/WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Boeing Co (BA.N) plans to conduct two flight tests of its revamped 787 battery system, possibly as soon as the end of the week, according to three sources familiar with the matter. The 787 flights, the first since February, mark another step toward Boeing's recently announced goal of returning the grounded jet to service in a matter of weeks, not months.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363828356137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363829079135-218</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My response was to the veterans accusation of war crimes and Obama and the Dems have also committed war crimes. Clinton started the extraordinary rendition/torture program in the 1990s. It is on the ACLU web site if you are ignorant of the facts. You're ignorance and holier than thou attempts make you look foolish and lying to yourself when the Dems have blood on their hands and are guilty of war crimes too, doesn't alter facts. Again I suggest that you bury your head deep in sand next to Chrissie.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363829079135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363829173356-219</Id><Topic><Title>Live with it</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1363798486442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:54:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could of told you all this in 1990 and 2000 and 2001 and 2003, but the cult of republicanism otherwise known as fascism never listens. they think WAR on innocents is proven your patriotism. It is proving you are a bully with no regard for the welfare of others. War is a SCAM designed by WEALTHY elites. All WARS.</Msg><Username>mining_phd</Username><Timestamp>1363829173356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:26:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363829850173-220</Id><Topic><Title>White House hoses tourists who went to see the peoples House</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1363818288706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:24:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah know, it is obvious to many people that supporters of this president have a hard time dealing with this president's past. All of them refute it or are not willing to except common facts as a denial of this president's past, present or future ideology. They behave like alcoholics in denial. They're content in living this convenient lie to satisfy their egos. After all, it is difficult to except ones gullibility in exchange for the truth.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1363829850173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363830188088-221</Id><Title>Uber Liberal Chomsky - Obama is worse than George Bush and Tony Blair says Noam Chomsky</Title><Msg>Look at the record, says Chomsky: Obama is in many cases worse than George Bush and Tony Blair -- on Afghanistan, Pakistan, Israel, Egypt -- and would be indicted for war crimes if the Nuremburg principles were applied. BA board progressive who have sold their morality and their souls for the thrill up their leg they feel for Barry, continue to lie to themselves. The list of honest Liberals who feel like Chomsky continues to grow.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363830188088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363830320992-222</Id><Title>starting tomorrow BA will start selling off...........</Title><Msg>hedge funds don't want to own it during the test.....</Msg><Username>dimebag_eddie</Username><Timestamp>1363830320992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:45:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363830861609-223</Id><Topic><Title>Uber Liberal Chomsky - Obama is worse than George Bush and Tony Blair says Noam Chomsky</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363830188088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ralph Nader says Obama is a war criminal.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363830861609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363830944424-224</Id><Topic><Title>NOW MY SHORTS GET PAID</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1363814454611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe that is a good call.?</Msg><Username>ronjancewicz</Username><Timestamp>1363830944424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363830994944-225</Id><Topic><Title>starting tomorrow BA will start selling off...........</Title><Username>dimebag_eddie</Username><Timestamp>1363830320992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:45:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have already completed 90 percent of the testing. The test flight is simply to record data during flight.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363830994944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363831187859-226</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: We’ve been lying all along</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363818711407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:31:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>approaching crazy?? They most certainly are crazy! Boehner is no prize either. It seems there are many nut cases running around DC.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1363831187859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363831396582-227</Id><Topic><Title>a road map to a much brighter America</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363816753055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 17:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we can all agree that the dope smoking nitwit capitol of America would have to be one of the blue states.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1363831396582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363831531644-228</Id><Topic><Title>Is Harry Reid Punch Drunk?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816994557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder who the three people he beat were.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1363831531644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363831742532-229</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight tests possible by end of this week.</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363828356137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:12:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing needs to conduct only one test flight with the proposed fix on ZA272 (LN 86, SP-LRC) according to the NCY787 blog. Two will make sure they cover all the bases.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363831742532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363832574711-230</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: We’ve been lying all along</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1363818711407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:31:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, Here is the difference between Republicans and Democrats: Republicans lie to themselves Democrats lie to everyone else. The chief liar is Obama. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1363832574711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363832724616-231</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dell George weve long known that your single skill in life is your double lip lock and your ability to swallow</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363832724616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363832740384-232</Id><Topic><Title>Is Harry Reid Punch Drunk?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816994557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good ole canvasback harry- sounds like more then one blow to many- the lights are on but nobodys been home for years</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1363832740384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363832834040-233</Id><Topic><Title>Is Harry Reid Punch Drunk?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816994557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>probably the high school will not release the names !! maybe it was one of the patrons in the cat house across from the school in searhlight ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1363832834040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363832874179-234</Id><Topic><Title>Why Won't the Government Just Give Every Man, Woman and Child a Million Dollars?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1363793261790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 11:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you don't know sh.t about economics, politics or engineering. You are like dell George- the only thing you know is how to suckk</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363832874179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363833058814-235</Id><Topic><Title>Uber Liberal Chomsky - Obama is worse than George Bush and Tony Blair says Noam Chomsky</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363830188088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Father Zosima says ali infested is a wannabe war criminal</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363833058814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363833174284-236</Id><Topic><Title>Gestapo Democrats Allow TSA to Humiliate Injured Marine</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1363787556786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 09:52:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have to worry about anything you say- 9 times out of ten it is one of your hate lies</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363833174284</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363833266711-237</Id><Topic><Title>Is Harry Reid Punch Drunk?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816994557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does it strike anyone odd that Reid cancelled the gun control law that was being pushed by Feinstein? After all, Obama was "hot" to make this happen because of all of his crocodile tear support of the Sandy Hook parents. Didn't he say that this was a "priority" of his administration? And, equally weird is Obama's trip to Israel. For four years he has done EVERYTHING in his power to UNDERMINE Israel's security and blowing off its leadership. Why the turn-about now? Well, it is related to Reid's throwing Senator Feinstein under the bus: the 2014 election. Obama is no dummy. Israel and gun control are two issues that the Democrats do not want to deal with in their re-election or their challenge to Republican incumbents for the house. I previously pointed out the proclivity of Democrats to lie. This is just another lie. When the Dems fully take over the Congress in 2014, there will be nothing standing in their way of taking down the Constitution and the country.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1363833266711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363833300836-238</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight tests possible by end of this week.</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1363828356137</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:12:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing wrong with the battery , they knew it. 787's design require heavy use of electrical , too much energy going through the cable caused it to get hot and baked. The problem is very simple but to fix it require redesign the electrical system which very costly . The only thing they did is reenforced the battery. It will bake again soon.</Msg><Username>meinfdia</Username><Timestamp>1363833300836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363833817087-239</Id><Topic><Title>5 experimental 787 aircraft flew for 2 years no battery problems</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363807695147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 15:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dell George I bet you are missing another tryst with your boyfriend</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1363833817087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363834322391-240</Id><Topic><Title>this is like msft and beta testing too bad its an airplane and not a peice of #$%$ software</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1363833858379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry your pretty little head over this. Stuff like "electricity" and "electrons" can be pretty scary at times to you, eh?</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1363834322391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363836125081-241</Id><Topic><Title>Uber Liberal Chomsky - Obama is worse than George Bush and Tony Blair says Noam Chomsky</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363830188088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 21:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cornel West says Barry is a war criminal. The list keeps growing.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1363836125081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 23:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363836392255-242</Id><Topic><Title>Is Harry Reid Punch Drunk?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1363816994557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 18:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The D folks don't need made up issues they way you are stretching. They have campaigners like you.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1363836392255</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 23:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363836506296-243</Id><Topic><Title>this is like msft and beta testing too bad its an airplane and not a peice of #$%$ software</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1363833858379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:44:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Flight Sim Lab . . . Project Manager and flew some of them in the similator. . . ." Now we know exactly what is wrong with Boeing.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1363836506296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 23:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>