<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365670094523-1</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said!</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1365670094523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 04:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365673392226-2</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul tries to outrun history at Howard</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365643332328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rand Paul: Size 10 1/2 shoe, size 12 mouth. Hey! He's flexible!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365673392226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 05:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365673469301-3</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well that's the whole point, Chrissy . Stuff this into your pointy, bald head; even a small fire arm puts any person on equal terms with the biggest badest felon in the hood . Up to ten felons, but no more, per the dimbulbs . . . . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1365673469301</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 05:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365673598939-4</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul tries to outrun history at Howard</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365643332328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and your aliases are at it 24-7...........why is that?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365673598939</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 05:46:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365673991966-5</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365673991966</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 05:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365676896632-6</Id><Title>Boeing is up 6% for five years in stock price Airbus is up 116% in fiveyears is the decertified 787 flying paaengers"?</Title><Msg>Boeing has really been flying high with constant stock price gains it is now up from 5% to 6% return on investment for 5 years ouch and bark! For the arrogant Boeing Management clones that populate this sight, Attention Boeing hacks the latest's news on the 787 the decertified and passenger less experimental lemon that cost an extra 33 billion to outsource and another almost 4 years late now . Mr Head the CEO what is his first name ? Is it Richard Head? Boeing Hacks that sounds about right or is descriptive of his job to date. Lets look a the e decertified 787 now 1.Boeing needs the FAA to end a Jan. 16 grounding order so deliveries can resume from an order book valued at almost $190 billion. Politics, not just safety, will weigh on the agency as it reviews the Dreamliner’s battery redesign and test-flight data, said John McGraw, an aerospace consultant. That is 4 months Boeing Hacks not fast or quick. 2Another NTSB hearing starts today on the use of lithium-ion batteries in transportation, and next week, the Dreamliner probably will come up when the Senate Commerce, Science and Transportation Committee holds a hearing to discuss the FAA’s progress on safety initiatives. That is not a fast deal and its political !3One challenge for Boeing is that it’s betting everything on one solution to the battery faults, said Richard Aboulafia, an analyst at consultant Teal Group in Fairfax, Virginia. An FAA rejection would be a major setback, he said. “Even if there’s only a 5 or 10 percent chance that it won’t satisfy the FAA, that’s a big risk especially if there isn’t a backup plan,” he said. 4 Boeing stock on buy back has gone up 13% in the 4 months but that gain only puts long term investors up 6% for 5 years CNN money, Use their stock chart and compare to eadsy up 116%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365676896632</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 06:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365676986917-7</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If youre not a pro lifer...you're a pro deather</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365676986917</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 06:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365677109189-8</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does chris_genns defend Obama's attraction to communism unless.....</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1365622239175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The liberal-socialist agenda has REASON and that is TOTAL DESTRUCTION OF EVERYTHING GOOD… It’s interesting sometimes to read about the last days of past civilizations. It’s hard not to notice during these readings that those last days were filled with completely irrational ideas and behaviors that could not be explained in any way outside of a mass collapse of reason. And boy, are we seemingly there. You know, most societies die of suicide, not attack. Most societies wipe themselves out and it’s interesting to read about their last days.. You’ll note that the last days of past civilizations were filled with idiotic, irrational ideas and behaviors that couldn’t be explained by reason.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365677109189</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 06:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365677130038-9</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing now 21st most shorted stock and the NTSB will hold meeting on why the lithium batteries suck</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365605185186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:46:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LaHood, 67, a former seven-term Republican member of the U.S. House of Representatives from Illinois, has played a prominent role since the Dreamliner’s batteries came under scrutiny with a Jan. 7 fire on a Japan Airlines 787. At a Jan. 11 news conference, he and FAA chief Michael Huerta declared the plane safe. Less than a week afterward, an ANA 787’s battery began smoldering and spewing vapor above Japan, prompting an emergency landing and then the grounding. LaHood’s involvement in the 787 decision escalates pressure on the FAA, said John Nance, a Seattle-based aviation-safety consultant and former commercial pilot. “The FAA is totally risk-averse,” Nance said. “This is an intolerable situation.”</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365677130038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 06:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365677478758-10</Id><Title>Smaller toilets on the 737</Title><Msg>This does not go far enough !. Do away with toilets alltogether. Instead just have a pipe sticking up from each seat extending down to the outside of the plane. Then when the pressure differential kicks in, everyone gets a power assisted dump, the plane gets lighter (fuel efficiency !), and, if correctly routed, farmers below will get a free fertilizer program. We need more visionaries on the design team !!</Msg><Username>dunrovin76</Username><Timestamp>1365677478758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 06:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365678392207-11</Id><Title>Is this boeing Hack credible ? jjovaz</Title><Msg>jjovaz jjovaz • Feb 13, 2013 6:39 PM Flag1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 7 Reply How soon we forget! I remember not too long ago when IAM rank and file members cut wiring harnesses on 737's awaiting delivery in Renton during contract negotiations and it made national news! also, a couple of homes were burnt down in the Enumclaw area by an IAM member because another Ba employee crossed the picket line. Bring the law suit on!! I will bury you with the FACTs. the repl;y was you could prove nothing , the Boeing Company and investigators said Boeing workers are very loyal and no person was found to be guilty or even accused, the company has many guests who can come on any airplane and look around so your claim is as good as your character flows , here is what another user said about you jjovaz remember "Wow jjovaz, you manage to accuse 2 different unions of sabotage - so let me be blunt, you're nothing but an anti-union POS Regarding the boeing company being the 21 largest short now that was a quote and nothing more, you spun your story to satisfy your depth of escape from reality , I know your will bury me with the facts again woo hoo a arrogant Boeing Mangment clone want to be .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365678392207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 07:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365678625366-12</Id><Topic><Title>Smaller toilets on the 737</Title><Username>dunrovin76</Username><Timestamp>1365677478758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 06:51:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>run that by foulmoutharbor and his boy friends , the Boeing Hacks , they are arrogant enough to look into if for you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365678625366</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 07:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365682065567-13</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great report.</Msg><Username>clinekate341</Username><Timestamp>1365682065567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365683772245-14</Id><Title>THE FAA: How Corruptible is it ?? OPINE NOW !!!!</Title><Msg>Express serious intelligent opinions, if you have any here for the record. Thank You</Msg><Username>analyticanalysis</Username><Timestamp>1365683772245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365684710561-15</Id><Title>'Very High' Chance North Korea Will Fire Missile, US and South Korea Say</Title><Msg>U.S. defense officials are "highly confident" that North Korea is planning the imminent launch of a medium-range missile. http://www.cnbc.com/id/100632779</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1365684710561</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365684758690-16</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does chris_genns defend Obama's attraction to communism unless.....</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1365622239175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whose calling everyone gay? Just because someone calls a gay person gay doesn't mean the call everyone gay. Hooze you need to realize you're unique.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1365684758690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365686498056-17</Id><Topic><Title>Why Does chris_genns defend Obama's attraction to communism unless.....</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1365622239175</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 15:30:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's the tactic of your Messiah...he bullied his party members to support ObamaCare. Broke ol congressman Nelson down for being forced to support it, and then go home to Nebraska to face his constituence that didn't want to support it..Nelson retired in shame, and that isn't the only example. Bully tactics are the tactics of your far left folks.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365686498056</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365686626351-18</Id><Title>Precious Metals</Title><Msg>Back in January I recommended buying gold but also said the most precious metal you could buy was brass and lead. I have a personal armory as do most Louisianians and Texans. My ammo stock filled a small storage room. Gun shops in town have begged me to sell them some so I did......at double my cost. I still kept plenty for target practice and taking care of critters on the property. I will replace what I sold latter in the year as supply exceeds demand. However, if Democrats are stupid enough to keep pounding on gun control more and more people law abiding citizens will become armed to the teeth. Someone in the U.S. buys a gun every 39 seconds and the Gun Dealers Association has named Obama as their salesman of the year.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365686626351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365687107068-19</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice stuff!</Msg><Username>hargreaves_leo</Username><Timestamp>1365687107068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365687232079-20</Id><Topic><Title>Paul McCartney Still UK's Richest Musician</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365685170425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:59:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rich guys like myself don't waste our time and energy being jealous of people who may have more money. That's the job of losers, socialists, communists, Democrats and other societal leaches. PS: Carlos Slim is far richer than McCartney and doesn't have to sing for his his supper.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365687232079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365687562712-21</Id><Topic><Title>House GOPer: Biblical flood proves climate change isn’t man-made</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365643500594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:25:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did the last Ice age occur because of industrialization? Was their a carbon tax on mastodon grazing?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365687562712</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365687764476-22</Id><Title>air france delays A380 deliveries on fnancial woes</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - Air France-KLM said it is finalising talks with planemaker Airbus about postponing deliveries of the next A380s it has on order by several months as it tries to rein in spending and reduce debt. The Franco-Dutch carrier operates a fleet of eight of the $400 million superjumbo aircraft, after taking delivery of two more last year, and has a further four on order. The bulk of the agreed price is typically paid on receipt of the planes. "Discussions are still in progress with Airbus to define new dates regarding deliveries of the next A380s still on order," Air France-KLM said in its latest annual registration document. Air France-KLM is seeking to return to profit and cut debt by 2 billion euros ($2.6 billion) by the end of next year after being battered by soaring fuel costs, a worsening cargo business and tough competition from Gulf and low-cost carriers.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365687764476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365688279277-23</Id><Title>$90's here we Come$$</Title><Msg>Boeing knows the 787 will be flying shortly so the Short Sqeeze will be kicking in$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365688279277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365688344312-24</Id><Title>BIG SIS ORDERS BAGPIPES</Title><Msg>Yesterday DHS ordered a new supply of musical instruments including bagpipes and drums. There is music writing software included in the order as well as the many small parts that go into caring for bagpipes. I guess Napolitano didn’t get the memo. We are supposed to be saving money here! How exactly are we “securing the homeland” with bagpipes and drums? The problem here is, that Democrats keep saying that the sequester cuts were too much and that we weren’t going to be able to continue life as we know it without this money. Well obviously, that’s just not true. Maybe Obama administration should look at how their departments are spending funds and do a little audit. The scare tactics aren’t going to work when there is hypocrisy coming from within the administration and officials the president appointed. Until the President looks more closely at how money is being spent from within the government, he cannot preach about how raising taxes is the only way out of this recession. Uh Oh.....Update: BIG SIS CANCELLED BAGPIPES ORDER. Once you shine the spotlight on these cockroaches they they head for the safety of not so transparent hiding places.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365688344312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365688364584-25</Id><Topic><Title>air france delays A380 deliveries on fnancial woes</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365687764476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read it this Morning, Poor Air bus!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365688364584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:52:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365688501878-26</Id><Topic><Title>Paul McCartney Still UK's Richest Musician</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365685170425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:59:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Rich guys like myself don't waste our time and energy being jealous of people who may have more money." MAY have? People who work at McDonald's may have more money than you. I definitely do.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1365688501878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365688593067-27</Id><Title>new high</Title><Msg>BA hit 88.84 this mornng as shorts scrambled to cover. Airbus was down.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365688593067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365688956310-28</Id><Topic><Title>Paul McCartney Still UK's Richest Musician</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365685170425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 08:59:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You definitely work at McDonald's? That's surprising......why have they lowered their hiring standards.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365688956310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:02:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365689190891-29</Id><Topic><Title>THIS DOG GOT NO LEGS</Title><Username>genesisautos</Username><Timestamp>1365601165111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:39:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you shorts, looks like another great day, are you all heading toward the exits?</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1365689190891</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365689292253-30</Id><Title>Elvis far Greater Singer than Paul MCartney</Title><Msg>According to the R.I.A.A., the governing body that certifies Gold, Platinum, and Multi-Platinum Record Sales, (Recording Industry Association of America) the Leading all time Artist in Record Sales is ELVIS PRESLEY. Elvis is the leading sales artist for both Solo Artist or Group. Elvis has sold over 2.5 Billion Records Worldwide. ( A Billion is 1 Thousand Million). Elvis has been on the charts more times than any other artist or group. Elvis has the most hits in the Top 100, the Top 40, The Top 10, and has had 32 Number 1 Records. Elvis is the only artist inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, The Country Music Hall of Fame, The Gospel Music Hall of Fame, and The Rythm and Blues Hall of Fame. Elvis was nominated for 41 Grammy Awards, but won only 3... all for Gospel Music. John Lennon said: "Before Elvis there was nothing". Bruce Springsteen said: "There are pretenders and contenders... but their is only one King". Elton John said: "There is no one greater as an artist on this earth, Elvis was my inspiration... he is the Man. Period." Paul McCartney said: "Elvis has always been on Top... His records always made me feel good. I thought the Beatles had gold records, until I had a private tour of Graceland... the hall of Gold says it all... Elvis has the most Gold, Platinum, and Multi-Platinum sales of all of us.... amazing man... simply amazing".</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365689292253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:08:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365689372451-31</Id><Title>NICE AND EASY DOES IT !!!!</Title><Msg>Might get 90 today if the market keeps going up ;-) UP YOURS AIRFRANCE !!! ;-)</Msg><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1365689372451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:09:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365689761625-32</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>up early today our ceremonial president/disaster is gonna meet with fwank dodd forum then conspire with useless nations... 10:15 AM The President and the Vice President receive the Presidential Daily Briefing 11:00 AM The President meets with members of the Financial Services Forum 11:30 AM Press Briefing by Press Secretary Jay Carney 12:05 PM The President holds a conference call with more than 100 local elected officials to discuss summer and year-round pathways to youth employment 2:10 PM The President awards Chaplain (Captain) Emil J. Kapaun, U.S. Army, the Medal of Honor; the First Lady also attends 2:55 PM The President meets with United Nations Secretary General Ban Ki-moon</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365689761625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365690021589-33</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very helpful report!</Msg><Username>garner_nicole</Username><Timestamp>1365690021589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365690571421-34</Id><Topic><Title>Revealed: Another Abortion House of Horrors</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365689881995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:18:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a preview of commiecare</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365690571421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365690889523-35</Id><Topic><Title>Elvis far Greater Singer than Paul MCartney</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365689292253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:08:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post. We've identified two of us who have far more money than you ever will.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1365690889523</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:34:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365691229833-36</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC's Harris-Perry Doubles Down on Communist Ads</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365688753695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do conservative folks that come off as total #$%$ always interpret words and twist them into some sick fantasy they have ? it`s getting rather sickening listening to the lies, propaganda, hate and total garbage that is spewed on a daily bases by these ideologues.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1365691229833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365691702200-37</Id><Topic><Title>Elvis far Greater Singer than Paul MCartney</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365689292253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:08:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does it feel to be part of the mediocre class, mir?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1365691702200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365691982639-38</Id><Topic><Title>new high</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365688593067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>90 is around the corner. Dell will have to go back on suicide watch.</Msg><Username>mrstock52</Username><Timestamp>1365691982639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365692033455-39</Id><Topic><Title>By the time battery issue is resolved., BA is at 100</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1363361940809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just kidding..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365692033455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365692054134-40</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC's Harris-Perry Doubles Down on Communist Ads</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365688753695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every time someone exposes the absurdity of the left-wing lunatic collectivists the sure get upset.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365692054134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365692233662-41</Id><Topic><Title>Elvis far Greater Singer than Paul MCartney</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365689292253</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:08:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>instant_karma48....if you ever rise tho the level of mediocrity, you'll find out for yourself.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365692233662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:57:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365692285413-42</Id><Topic><Title>Your Kids Aren’t Your Own - More anti family progressive BS on MSNBC</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1365602033890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor old Marx- has to take a bashing from the lowest of the low this morning- namely Sparticus</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365692285413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365692379843-43</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1365692379843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365692568852-44</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Besides, it was less to do with the kitchen and more to do with razor blades used in x-acto knives.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365692568852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365692590223-45</Id><Title>Disability Ranks Continue to Surge Under Obama</Title><Msg>Oh, I know......it's George Bush's fault but.......Almost as many people signed up with the federal government's permanent worker disability program as got jobs in March, according to two sets of government data, continuing a troubling trend throughout the Obama recovery. Last month, 81,804 workers left the workforce to join the Social Security Disability Insurance program. So far this year, nearly a quarter million workers have joined the program. Over the past four years, 4 million left the workforce to go on disability. Even after accounting for those who dropped out of the program because of death or retirement, the ranks of the disabled have shot up more than 1.4 million under Obama.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365692590223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365692769360-46</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err spaz err dodd err useless human being fascist bumper err spaz</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1365692769360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365693184122-47</Id><Title>90+ today.</Title><Msg>Gold rush.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365693184122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365693202542-48</Id><Title>LWNJs Get Extremely angry at Obama's failure being Exposed</Title><Msg>Record unemployment, Obama Commiecare disaster, record deficits, corrupt attorney general he won't replace, class warfare, unkept promises, unparalleled hypocrisy and lie after lie. When these things are specifically pointed out the left becomes extremely angry and fire up the name calling, insults and bazaar denials.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365693202542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365693434854-49</Id><Topic><Title>90+ today.</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365693184122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We might tap that but tomorrow its going to fly$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365693434854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:17:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365693454265-50</Id><Topic><Title>White House Schedule</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1363270937569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>calm down sparty, it's only a schedule, who knows what the #$%$ is really doing...it's a show, like his parties...anyone find out what he was doing while his charges were being murdered in Benghazi?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365693454265</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365693490592-51</Id><Topic><Title>new high</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365688593067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Wayneker's rants are a lost cause.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1365693490592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:18:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365693632858-52</Id><Topic><Title>new high</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365688593067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short squezze will take the price too the low $90's by tomorrow on experation$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365693632858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365693724736-53</Id><Topic><Title>NICE AND EASY DOES IT !!!!</Title><Username>cutthemoffnow</Username><Timestamp>1365689372451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 10:09:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>airbus is soo screwed with the frencies canceling (so-called delay) thier orders$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365693724736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365693895369-54</Id><Topic><Title>LWNJs Get Extremely angry at Obama's failure being Exposed</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365693202542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's biggest failure is - he is a black man -</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365693895369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:24:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365693910878-55</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes 500 Rich List Acquiring BA Shares!</Title><Username>james.tingle</Username><Timestamp>1362414215788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 11:23:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting report!</Msg><Username>tommyunknow</Username><Timestamp>1365693910878</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365693911820-56</Id><Title>Last time Jim Crxmer sold QCOM, QCOM took off</Title><Msg>This time Jim Crxmer sold BA, BA lifts off</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365693911820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365693952432-57</Id><Topic><Title>new high</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365688593067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is an inspired interpretation of his name.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1365693952432</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365694785470-58</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK...</Title><Msg>HOW ARE YOU? SHORT BOEING OK?</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1365694785470</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:39:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365694911902-59</Id><Topic><Title>LWNJs Get Extremely angry at Obama's failure being Exposed</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365693202542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zosima is race baiting LWNJ, among other things despicable</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365694911902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365695094586-60</Id><Title>120$.. No seller remorse, no more.</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365695094586</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365695488271-61</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul tries to outrun history at Howard</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365643332328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>=You and your aliases are at it 24-7...........why is that?= Because they're NOT his aliases, stupid one. (Kinda answered your own dumb question, eh?)</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1365695488271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365695943198-62</Id><Topic><Title>LWNJs Get Extremely angry at Obama's failure being Exposed</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365693202542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama's biggest failure is - he is a black man" Obama's biggest failure is not being black, it is being the first black president who is ensuring that it will be a long time before we have another. So much potential to finally begin uniting the U.S. but, instead, he has been very ineffective and, if anything, divisive. Quite a shame and loss!</Msg><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1365695943198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365696200577-63</Id><Topic><Title>LWNJs Get Extremely angry at Obama's failure being Exposed</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365693202542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry #$%$ lib / race baiters only defense.... "he is a black man" course his record has nothing to do with being a self absorbed America hating enemy useful idiot</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365696200577</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365696484052-64</Id><Topic><Title>LWNJs Get Extremely angry at Obama's failure being Exposed</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365693202542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is being black now an excuse for failure? Maybe you should tell all the successful black men they're supposed to be failures.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365696484052</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365696916850-65</Id><Topic><Title>LWNJs Get Extremely angry at Obama's failure being Exposed</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365693202542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the base of today's R Party: Confederacy.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1365696916850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365697300477-66</Id><Title>Don't Forget</Title><Msg>On October 2, 2007 Boeing was at 107.15. It is a far better company now.</Msg><Username>john37p</Username><Timestamp>1365697300477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365697655570-67</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul tries to outrun history at Howard</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365643332328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Millionaire Randpaul owes his daddy for all those $millions. Payback for him is dedication to the same slimy crock he learned at his daddy's knee. His daddy once proclaimed secession” was "a deeply American principle". The students at Howard have a right to be insulted but they were not fooled by this lying hypocrite .</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1365697655570</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365697874807-68</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul tries to outrun history at Howard</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365643332328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no need to change IDs just for us Sparty</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365697874807</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365698259784-69</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul tries to outrun history at Howard</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365643332328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 21:22:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blacks lost track of history when dumbos destroyed their families, huh hoozDIK our not so great socialists created the "who's your daddy?" epidemic, our statists rushed in to fill the parental void with their re-education programs</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365698259784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365699074377-70</Id><Topic><Title>new high</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365688593067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:56:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>89.46 at about 1130am.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365699074377</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 12:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365700542789-71</Id><Title>Five Decades of Lies Help Dems Create Monolithic Black Vote</Title><Msg>By Larry Elder As recently as 1956, nearly 39 percent of blacks voted Republican in that year's presidential election. After the Civil War, Abe Lincoln's Republican Party easily carried the black vote -- where blacks were allowed to vote. Unwelcome in the Democratic Party, most blacks voted Republican and continued to do so through the early part of the 20th century. It wasn't until 1948, when 77 percent of the black vote went to Harry Truman, who had desegregated the military, that a majority of blacks identified themselves as Democrats. Yet, as a percentage of the party, more Republicans voted for the passage of the Civil Rights Act of 1964 than did Democrats. For his key role breaking the Democrats' filibuster and getting the act to pass the stalled Senate, Republican Sen. Everett Dirksen, a conservative from Illinois, landed on the cover of Time magazine. President Lyndon Johnson called Dirksen "the hero of the nation." The Chicago Defender, then the country's largest black daily newspaper, applauded Dirksen's "generalship" for helping to successfully push through the bill. Older black voters sometimes explain they're opposed to Republicans because of the "racist" Southern strategy. But Richard Nixon speechwriter Pat Buchannan, credited with inventing the "Southern strategy," considered the Democratic Party the party of the racists. Buchanan said: "We would build our Republican Party on a foundation of states' rights, human rights, small government and a strong national defense, and leave it to the 'party of [Democratic Georgia Gov. Lester] Maddox, [1966 Democratic challenger against Spiro Agnew for Maryland governor George] Mahoney and [Democratic Alabama Gov. George] Wallace to squeeze the last ounces of political juice out of the rotting fruit of racial injustice.'" But before that, another pivotal event occurred that helped the GOP-as-racist meme. In 1960, during the presidential campaign, Martin Luther King Jr. was arrested following a sit-in at a segregated lunch counter in Atlanta. Hundreds of other protestors were released, but King was jailed on a trumped-up probation violation for failing to have a Georgia driver's license. King's aides reached out to then-Vice President and Republican presidential candidate Richard Nixon. They also reached out to the Democratic nominee, John F. Kennedy. Bobby Kennedy called the Atlanta judge handling the case. Shortly after that call, the judge released King. Nixon, according to Harry Belafonte, a King supporter, "did nothing." Is that true? Nixon, it turns out, had a much closer relationship with King than did Kennedy. In the Nixon Presidential Library in Yorba Linda, Calif., records show considerable handwritten notes and correspondence between Nixon and King. This includes a 1957 letter from King acknowledging their previous meetings, which thanked Nixon for his "assiduous labor and dauntless courage in seeking to make the Civil Rights Bill a reality," and praised him for his "devotion to the highest mandates of the moral law." But in 1960, on the eve of the election, Nixon was in a tough spot. Nixon's public silence might be misconstrued as acceptance of King's arrest. On the other hand, as a candidate for his boss's job, Nixon worried about the political costs of appearing ungrateful if he chastised President Dwight Eisenhower for not taking stronger action. Eisenhower, however, was content to let the Justice Department handle the matter. According to historian and presidential biographer Stephen Ambrose, while Nixon made no public comments, he telephoned Attorney General William Rogers to find out if King's constitutional rights were being infringed, thus opening the door for federal involvement. Nixon, a lawyer, was concerned about the ethics of calling a judge to get him to release someone. Nixon, writes Ambrose, told his press secretary: "I think Dr. King is getting a bum rap. But despite my strong feelings in this respect, it would be completely improper for me or any other lawyer to call the judge. And Robert Kennedy should have known better than to do so." That Bobby Kennedy, also a lawyer, nevertheless made a phone call to the judge did not alter the issue of whether it was appropriate. In retrospect, an easy call, but not at the time. Two million pamphlets titled, "'No Comment' Nixon Versus a Candidate With a Heart, Senator Kennedy," were distributed in black churches. Never mind that in 1956 Nixon revealed he was an honorary member of the NAACP. Or that Nixon pushed for passage of the '57 civil rights bill in the Senate. Or that Time magazine wrote that Nixon's support for civil rights incurred the wrath of one of his segregationist opponents, Sen. Richard Russell, D-Ga., who sarcastically called Nixon the NAACP's "most distinguished member." But the GOP-is-racist meme can be heard nightly on MSNB-Hee Haw and in political science and history classes all over the country. Actor Morgan Freeman calls the tea party racist. Democratic National Committee Chair Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz, D-Fla., tells us that the GOP wants to "literally drag us all the way back to Jim Crow laws." Keeping blacks ignorant of history remains crucial to this caricature of the Republican Party -- and to the monolithic Democratic black vote. Not so black and white, is it?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365700542789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 13:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365701102525-72</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, dumbo; that's how I see you, too. Facing down 10 miscreants in the hood, armed with only your innate goodness, your superior courage, and your trusty Beretta. I'll bet there's a pretty girl, someone like Sandra Locke, lying at their feet with her clothes torn when you show up, too. Harharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365701102525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 13:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365701608627-73</Id><Topic><Title>Gee, another look at African-Americans voting for Democrats</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365701233035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 13:27:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what was the explanation?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365701608627</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 13:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365702280077-74</Id><Title>Boeing thins out Puget Sound workforce</Title><Msg>As mentioned in press releases some months ago, layoff notices went out to over 900 production workers and a number of Manufacturing engineers are included as work winds down on the retrofit of early 787 builds. 787 and 747-8 production lines have stabilized and need fewer people. Other work leaving the Puget Sound area includes the informaton technology support moving to St. Louis and South Carolina and the pilot training to Miami. Boeing has committed to help those who cannot find work elsewhere in the company to find other employment.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365702280077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 13:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365702343528-75</Id><Title>Hey Black Ameicans, how''s the Democrat Government Plantation Working out for You?</Title><Msg>Black Unemployment twice the national rate (Black unemployment used to lower that that for whites). Blacks with 12.5% of the population now are 49 % of the welfare recipients, incarceration rate six times the national average, HS dropout rate 63% higher than whites, College dropout rate is 58%, median income 62% of whites and an illegitimate birth rate of 73%. After all those good Republicans died freeing your ancestors from their Democrat slave masters, but you decided to trade your freedom for government dependency and new massas. What a pay-off!</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365702343528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 13:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365702445753-76</Id><Topic><Title>LWNJs Get Extremely angry at Obama's failure being Exposed</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1365693202542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 11:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the down? Not even thinking about paying for it.</Msg><Username>prybarbq</Username><Timestamp>1365702445753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 13:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365702524690-77</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gun nuts are masters of the false equivalency -- the fine art (?) of using anything which might cause a death as the same thing as a gun, which has no other purpose than to kill people when it has a 30-round magazine and/or easy conversion to automatic fire. In Oregon, you can use a SEMIautomatic rifle to hunt deer, but only if it has a magazine capactiy of 5 rounds or less. That's because people in my home state want to give deer a chance to escape. Yet gun nuts are perfectly happy giving 6-year-olds only 1/6th to 1/20th the chance of escape and survival Oregonians give deer. Even more absurd is that they want to make everyone think that the slightest, most reasonable regulation is a total attack on their rights (Pronounce it "rats") and a confiscation. As if it is not already illegal to own a silencer. As if the state has no right to pass anti-defamation laws that regulate their free speech or probable cause rules to search you without a warrant.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365702524690</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 13:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365703430232-78</Id><Title>Don't Worry Black American......</Title><Msg>.....there will always be plenty of white liberal bigots to tell you you shouldn't think for yourself, that their white elitists will think for you. And if the white liberal bigots don't convince you, there will always be their back-up chorus of race and poverty pimps like Al Sharpton, Jessie Jackson and the Congressional black caucus. Don't worry about those few blacks that escape the government plantation and go on to build successful lives making you look like failures. There will be plenty of black race pimps and white liberals to call them names and degenerate them for daring to escape the government plantation. Just look at what they're doing to men like, Benjamin Carson, Charles Payne, Herman Cain and Clarence Thomas.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365703430232</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365704306455-79</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chrissie......don't you believe a person should be able to defend his life, property and family?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365704306455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365704599311-80</Id><Title>Facts Gun Control Nut Don't Want you to Know</Title><Msg>According to the FBI, in 2011, 1,694 were murdered with knives, 726 with hands or feet, 496 with clubs or hammers, 323 with rifles of any type. But Obama wants to ban semi-automatic rifles?"</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365704599311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365704921772-81</Id><Title>Donald Trump bough BA.</Title><Msg>You are fired if you sold early.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365704921772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365705047582-82</Id><Topic><Title>Donald Trump bough BA.</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365704921772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:28:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me bought @70, 3-5$ lower than him Me bought BAC @ 5+ still smarter than him and WB..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365705047582</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365705619492-83</Id><Title>Biggest airplane breakthrough since 747...</Title><Msg>Only cellular phones can come close to it... Do you get it? Stop trading.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365705619492</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365706215841-84</Id><Title>Sheila Jackson Lee - Democrat Representative</Title><Msg>Sheila Jackson Lee, the dumbest woman, mammal and oxygen breathing lifeform in Congress, is there to serve as an example to the dumbest of Americans. A role model that proves that even if you can’t tell the difference between Mars and the Moon and think that the United States won the Vietnam War and that hurricanes should be named after black people… you can still have a rewarding career saying stupid things. Jackson Lee suggested lawmakers should take inspiration from President Lincoln’s leadership during the Civil War. “I stand here as a freed slave because this Congress came together. Are we going to be able to do it today to free America?” Sheila Jackson Lee may well have ended up mentally challenged due to her oxygen supply being cut off for an extended period of time after choking on a deck of race cards she’d accidentally ingested, but she’s still not afraid to play with that deck: " And I thank you professor very much. I’m going to be engaging you with those very powerful numbers that you have offered on what the tea party recognizes, uh, or is recognized as. Might I add my own P.S.? All those who wore sheets a long time ago have now lifted them off and started wearing [applause], uh, clothing, uh, with a name, say, I am part of the tea party." Next we find out that Jackson Lee hasn’t had a refresher course in geography since at least 1975, if ever: Democratic Rep. Sheila Jackson Lee — who once famously asked where she could find photos of the American flag that Neil Armstrong planted on Mars — yesterday insisted, in stark defiance of basic facts of history, that “today we have two Vietnams, side by side, North and South, exchanging and working. We may not agree with all that North Vietnam is doing, but they are living in peace.”</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365706215841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365706851275-85</Id><Title>There no Way a White Man Could Outrun a Black Man.....</Title><Msg>.....as long as there's a Democrat waving a welfare check at the finish line.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365706851275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365707210597-86</Id><Title>Boeing the numbers</Title><Msg>BA up YTD -17% Airbus up 26%, for 3 years BA up 25% Airbus up 153% bark and ouch for BA stock holders, For 5 years BA up now a whole 7% bark and ouch Airbus up 116%. If your a Boeing long you have lost huge to the stock market and if your a Boeing short you have made next to nothing conclusion stay out of Boeing stock and do not listen to the Boeing Hacks that populated this message board with the Boeing Company line that is you foulmoutharbor and your boye friends who use typical Boeing management style arrogance to criticize mu user comments . Yes the decertified and over 3 year late firebomb with a containment vessel is flying now and because the root cause can not be found the boeing Company wants to put passenger lives at risk we all know that is going to happen. It has been 4 months and the FAA and the NTSB are worried that this flying firebomb may crash that is the truth.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365707210597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365708232559-87</Id><Topic><Title>Facts Gun Control Nut Don't Want you to Know</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365704599311</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:23:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why do Democrats insisting on trying to take a speck oot of the eyes of law abiding citizens when they have logs in their own eyes?</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1365708232559</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365708625020-88</Id><Title>Boeing company and the Boeing Hacks</Title><Msg>we all know who you are sprit and your various names remember this post today ACAD is up 65% in one day, 182% YTD, 700% for one year and 689% for 3 years and 52% for 5 years , not that I would buy and hold this stock. anyway sparti hows not following me working for you now ."2users liked this postsusers disliked this posts1Reply ACAD compared to IGZ by waynedickenson961 • Mar 21, 2013 3:57 PM Flag a well known Boeing hack attempted to keep up with me on my stock picks after I answered his debate style of the regular 25% gain with a demonstration not with words but in the few days it took me to make that gain on ACAD. I made 26% on ACAD this morning and am out. This certain Boeing hack claimed a stock IGS was up 144% so what was my point. har har har ?a certain Boeing hack without knowing how to trade stocks picked the wrong stock IGZ is not a stock , never was a stock, and never will be a stock it is a symbol used to test the trading platform, So a certain person who is a Boeing hack should probably use one of his other names now as he has just fooled himself sorry Less</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365708625020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365709080062-89</Id><Title>Would Liberals Vote for a White Man with the Same Record of Failure as Obama?</Title><Msg>Probably......as long as they were confident he was a communist.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1365709080062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365709210359-90</Id><Title>April deliveries to date</Title><Msg>15 planes. 13 737, 1 747, 1 777. A very slow start to the month. But there are a number of planes which have completed first flight and are out for painting. They need to get those 747's and 777's into customers hands by month end. The big question is whether we will see any 787 deliveries this month and next. They certainly have a number of them in or ready for flight test. How fast they can retrofit them with the battery related fix while upgrading the fleet already sold is questionable.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365709210359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365709861492-91</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing company and the Boeing Hacks</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365708625020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so sparti in just 19 days I made over 60% on ACAD while you pretended to show me up with a stock you thought was a real stock and it is a symbol used to check out the trade platform. Once more I remind you BA is not a buy or sell short, it is a poor stock investment compared to Airbus eadsy or the general stock market averages . Boeing sucks because the Boeing management is incompetent .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365709861492</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365710544244-92</Id><Topic><Title>April deliveries to date</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365709210359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The NK rocket has been raised for firing. Markets getting very skittery. This could be the start of the pull back we were talking about. Tomorrow should be an interesting day.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1365710544244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365710958139-93</Id><Title>Gotta love these market record highs</Title><Msg>I'm glad to say I'm finally looking forward to paying taxes on my market profits in 2013 and 2014. It's about time I had some! Its true about a rising tide raising all ships, and all this maket joy in the face of North Korea's threat.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1365710958139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:09:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365711414932-94</Id><Topic><Title>Gotta love these market record highs</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1365710958139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:09:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same here I have Siri 90% gain now Boeing +45% my Tax lady said I will need more Losses$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365711414932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365711501131-95</Id><Topic><Title>April deliveries to date</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365709210359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wear how many times has that jerk gone thru this all wants is Money!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1365711501131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365712109900-96</Id><Title>"More Employers Dropping Insurance: Study" ... What A Boon for Corporate Profits!</Title><Msg>By Jonathan Block, Posted: April 11, 2013 - 12:01 am ET Rising premiums have driven a steady decline in employer-sponsored health insurance since 2000, according to a Robert Wood Johnson Foundation study released today. In 2011, the number of Americans with employer-sponsored insurance stood at 159 million, a decline of 11.5 million from 2000. The 2011 figure represented 59.5% of the U.S. population, a drop of 10 percentage points from a decade earlier. According to the report, 47 states had a statistically significant decline in employer-sponsored coverage from 2000-2011, with 22 states experiencing declines of at least 10 percentage points. Michigan saw the biggest percentage drop—15.2 percentage points—over the period, while North Dakota saw the smallest drop, less than one percentage point. To hack healthcare costs, employers (The other Big Brother) can now track how you grocery shop. “Employers continue to shoulder about the same percentage of costs for employees' health insurance as they did 10 years ago, but everyone's costs have increased dramatically,” RWJF President and CEO Risa Lavizzo-Mourey said in a written statement. “Higher costs naturally translate into fewer employers offering insurance coverage, and fewer employees accepting it, even when it is offered.” Between 2000 and 2011, the average annual employee-only premium more than doubled to $5,081 from $2,490. And during that period, the amount employees contributed toward premiums also skyrocketed, to $1,056 from $435. However, the one demographic that saw a rise in employer-sponsored coverage was adults between the ages of 19 and 25. That was attributed to a provision in the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act that allows this those under 26 to remain on their parents' insurance policy. When the Affordable Care Act's state insurance exchanges open in 2014, only 46% responded they definitely would continue sponsoring health benefits.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1365712109900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:28:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365712447086-97</Id><Topic><Title>April deliveries to date</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365709210359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have been thinning out my holdings to be ready for a pull back. I agree the market is jittery but as long as that nut job does not launch an attack on the south, it will turn into a "boy who cried wolf" situation and no one will worry about him. Unfortunately that is when he will be the most dangerous.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1365712447086</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365712549177-98</Id><Topic><Title>"More Employers Dropping Insurance: Study" ... What A Boon for Corporate Profits!</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1365712109900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:28:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Adios for the big paper processing middle man, the health insruance ccompanies. They just became to greedy and mean spirited. Now instead of you being dropped by your health insurer for having a corn on your foot, the public can now drop them. 'Bout time!</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1365712549177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365712847556-99</Id><Topic><Title>Gotta love these market record highs</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1365710958139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:09:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this keeps up I might be able to write off all of my Bush economic train wreck losses while I am still alive.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1365712847556</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365714207177-100</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing HACK VALUE SHARP SHOOTERS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364675266684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne "make at least 25 percent a day" doesn't know when markets close and he calls himself a trader? He should be embarrased. HarHarHar</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1365714207177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365714547182-101</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing HACK VALUE SHARP SHOOTERS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364675266684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waynedickenson961 • Mar 28, 2013 5:10 AM Flag3 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 4 Reply BA will hit 90 by Friday.. the stock market closes early thrusday and is not open friday-osulinn get a clue</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1365714547182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365714808063-102</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did I say that, hopealong? To believe I did, you have to imagine things were said that were not said. Imagined them. Like your friends.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365714808063</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365714885954-103</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Worry Black American......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1365703430232</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 14:03:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Hermie Cain is one of your models of integrity and intelligence, you need say no more.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365714885954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365715491256-104</Id><Topic><Title>Is BA Poised For A Huge Win?</Title><Username>williemeadows695</Username><Timestamp>1365712695191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 16:38:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think your right fundamentals are the way to go. Like it</Msg><Username>shermandoyle147</Username><Timestamp>1365715491256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365716677695-105</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do all your aliases agree with your radical Communista dogma?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365716677695</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365716724842-106</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He thinks the state should do that.........</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365716724842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365717589499-107</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing HACK VALUE SHARP SHOOTERS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364675266684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he is an idiot....</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1365717589499</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365718339454-108</Id><Topic><Title>Your Kids Aren’t Your Own - More anti family progressive BS on MSNBC</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1365602033890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would answer you Spartaloon, if you wouldn't just ignore what I say as you have in the past; and if you stood for anything yourself, other than: * the principle that ALL government officials lie ALL the time, * that "libertarians" like the nutty gnome from nowhere has the only lock on the truth, * that our nation has already been shipped to hades in a handbasket and there is therefore no hope for it, and * that anyone who doesn't agree with you all the way on everything is a minion of Satan or at least MUCH less of a manly man than you are by dint of your 25 years in uniform. I think I have about covered your professed belief system, but let me know if I forgot anything -- Oh, like how David Crockett was defending America from illegal Mexican immigrants at the Alamo. But that's awful specific, and if I went in to specifics of every one of your insane perversions of logic, we'd be here all day!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365718339454</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 18:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365720264400-109</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing HACK VALUE SHARP SHOOTERS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364675266684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 , the difference is your are a critic, not a stock market trader and yet you keep attempting to put me in your critic slam opinion place by ignorant statements . Like you can show me up with IGZ, the difference is I do trade and I do make what I say I do and I did trade and called my acad trade for 26% and then just waited for 19 trade days to once more point out that you are a critic and a Boeing hack. sparticus999991 you called it on IGZ not me . As far as your continued arrogant crapola you will not stop, as a critic and a time waster your comeback childish statement of LOL crapola claiming that the stock Market was not closed on thrudsay and somehow that is important to you then ?sparticus99991, once more your spinning, the comment by me was to another of your boye friends who keeps claiming without looking that the stock BA would be up on what thrusday or Friday, very hard to do since the stock market was closed, I used to compare BA to appl until Steve died and you had 15 years to get in, then I gave you some stocks to look at and your attempt was to make it a forever stock comparison, in fact even with it being a then time deal most of them did beat Boeing , Why because Boeing is a bad stock to invest in,bad managment . the only rreal gain is in the CEO pay over 5 years he had made about 100% but to make any real money you needed to be in Airbus for 5 years and your investment would be up over 100% not the 7% that Boeing shareholders have made. I do not go long or short on Boeing it is not a money maker. I do day trades , swing trades and long term investments al of them beat boeing . Sparticus99991 as you know I was in Apple for 15 years and you dogged me all the way. I hope you continue to play the critic I am making money and do not like the Boeing Hack people spinning the boeign managment Company dogma ouch and bark it is a doggy stock BA sucks</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365720264400</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 18:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365720373401-110</Id><Topic><Title>Your Kids Aren’t Your Own - More anti family progressive BS on MSNBC</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1365602033890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Poor old Marx" ...yeah Im sure Hitler and Genhas Khan are on your list of collective heros as well....Little clue...Authoritarian tyrants are Anti American</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365720373401</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 18:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365720532536-111</Id><Title>Italian Senate blames Bilderberg for terrorist attacks</Title><Msg>Honorary President of the Supreme Court of Italy and former Senior Investigative Judge Ferdinando Imposimato, the man who prosecuted the case involving the assassination attempt against Pope John Paul II, has sensationally accused the Bilderberg Group of being behind terrorist attacks in Europe. Italian Supreme Court President Blames Bilderberg For Terrorist Attacks 110413it Ferdinando Imposimato. Image: Flickr In an interview with the ArticoloTre website, Imposimato, who was also involved in the case involving the kidnapping and murder of former Italian Prime Minister Aldo Moro, said that he “found a document that left me appalled” implicating the Bilderberg Group in conspiring with the far right organization Ordine Nuovo to commit terror attacks. Speaking of unsolved murders in Italy and the document in his possession, Imposimato stated, “When it comes to slaughter it also speaks of the Bilderberg Group. I believe this document. I did some tests and I can say that behind the strategy of tension and the slaughters there is also the Bilderberg group, a sort of Big Brother is over, maneuvering, using terrorists and Masons. “ The “strategy of tension” refers to a policy under the auspices of Operation Gladio, a NATO cold war “stay behind” project that sought to create an expedient political climate in Europe by having its agents carry out terror attacks which were then blamed on both far left and far right political groups. Gladio was designed to demonize political opposition and “force the public to turn to the state to ask for greater security,” according to the testimony of former Gladio agent Vincenzo Vinciguerra. In 2000, an Italian parliamentary investigation found that the 1980 Bologna train bombing, which killed 85 people, was carried out by “men inside Italian state institutions and … men linked to the structures of United States intelligence.”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365720532536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 18:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365721156859-112</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing HACK VALUE SHARP SHOOTERS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364675266684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is not a critic. He is a kook. In fact, he is the President of the Kookdom Weirdo Conspiracy Theory Around Every Corner Freako Weirdo Group.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1365721156859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 18:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365721279790-113</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing company and the Boeing Hacks</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365708625020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so sparti you asked me to stop poining out that your a very poor critic and I used your ignorant claim about a stock you offered to criticize my 19 day ago 26% acad gain. ? First of all sparti , you started the crapola yars ago with me and now you want to cry uncle? Why would I stop , you have been dogging me for years , you could have moved on or actually made some real money off my stock suggestions at the time they were apple for 15 years , you dogged me about it for 15 years as you claim it is spirited dialog, nope your a Boeing Hack not a very good on at that. Sparti, I have been pointing out now thad Airbus long term is far better than Boeing and ACAD is a great swing trade stock, did you follow ACAD or Airbus , nope your a Boeing Hack not a good one . so once more and as usual for you listen up, acad just made me another 67% today just 19 trade dasy after you tried to slam me with a bogus stock , get it how ? sparti, and instead of listening twice as much as you talk, you keep on mouthing up to me. So sparti, how is that working for you now? sparti are you up another 67% on acad on top of another 26 that I am today? sparticus99991. Boeing is not a good stock to trade long or short it has bad management the only 100% gains is to the pay of the CEO over his 6 years with Boeing, the shareholders have made 7% as of today , Airbus shareholders have made over 115% in 5 years get it now sparti , stop being a Boeing Hack there is no money in it roll your IRA inot a self directed portfolio and make some money stop hope and pray for BA learn to read a stock chart or more bark and ouch will keep cumming to you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365721279790</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 19:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365721717427-114</Id><Topic><Title>Your Kids Aren’t Your Own - More anti family progressive BS on MSNBC</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1365602033890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Raven alias blowing smoke up Raven's but.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365721717427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 19:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365721830064-115</Id><Topic><Title>Your Kids Aren’t Your Own - More anti family progressive BS on MSNBC</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1365602033890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those are all Ravens heroes you are making fun of........now he and his army of aliases will go ballistic.....</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365721830064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 19:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365723272469-116</Id><Topic><Title>Italian Senate blames Bilderberg for terrorist attacks</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365720532536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 18:48:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typically, Sparty turns one loony soulmate into the "Italian Senate." Anyone have a count of how many times the Loon has done this. Silly me. Too many times to count.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365723272469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 19:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365725008533-117</Id><Title>BA probably this only strong growth stock in DJ...</Title><Msg>in the next few years.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1365725008533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365725600939-118</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The difference is almost every mass killing has happened in a gun free zone. Gifford is the only exception.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1365725600939</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365726577256-119</Id><Topic><Title>Italian Senate blames Bilderberg for terrorist attacks</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365720532536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 18:48:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My post did not even mention 9-11....amazing how you sneak things in but ok..............................................................9-11, Bilderberg and operation Gladio and the attempted assassination of the Pope...what did they ALL have in common ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365726577256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365726921215-120</Id><Topic><Title>Precious Metals</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1365686626351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 09:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Im looking for Gold to take a short term pullback to coil for new highs by next year......Central Banks of the world are hoarding Gold while telling everyone to sell.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365726921215</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365727164871-121</Id><Topic><Title>Its time we got tuff on Kitchen Cutlery !</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365649448863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shooting a 30 rd clip is a blast, like taking a hot rod to the drag strip or track. They sell beer in cases of 24 and if you drank all 24 you could drive and kill someone, should we reduce a case of beer to 3 cans? Of course libs with 30 rd clips &amp; fully auto guns (payed for by hard working taxpayers), like to sell them to Mexican drug lords so they can blame gun owners and call it a cool name like Fast &amp; Furious.</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1365727164871</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365727550931-122</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come you defend Minorites that are a different color or Homosexuals that are a different sexual persuasion but make fun of people with horrible degenerative diseases ? Are you some sort of Ultimate hypocrite ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365727550931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365728061014-123</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but clearly agreed with the sentiment...</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365728061014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365728269042-124</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus boy is not smart enough to assess that</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1365728269042</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365728677188-125</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz...its embarrassing·to have to kick your hind end on hear on a daily basis...at least preserve what little dignity you have left and forego changing IDs to try to defend yourself.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365728677188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:04:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365728899544-126</Id><Topic><Title>Your Kids Aren’t Your Own - More anti family progressive BS on MSNBC</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1365602033890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now that our illegal immigrant president has won a second term all the communists are coming out of the shadows. Let's see, take the second amendment away, then ship us off to a Fema Camp. If you're a democrat and have the mark, you're safe.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1365728899544</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365729540372-127</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven uses 2 computers to post simultaneous posts from 2 different aliases in a pathetic attempt to be clever. He likes that.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1365729540372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:19:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365729598719-128</Id><Topic><Title>Your Kids Aren’t Your Own - More anti family progressive BS on MSNBC</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1365602033890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 09:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Now that our illegal immigrant president has won a second term all the communists are coming out of the shadows."...exactly...the pundits at the Collapborator state run media are even saying Obama has a mandate for communism and so the Narrative is to PUSH a commie agenda at all costs.....A backlash is brewing bigger then most of us imagine</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365729598719</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365729697163-129</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven likes to paraphrase the Air Force recruiting motto...Aim Low...its a great Waste of life !</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365729697163</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:21:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365729760683-130</Id><Topic><Title>What Margaret Thatcher Really Meant to England and the World</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365728813475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:06:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because of the incredible respect, and success she had recovering England's economy for one by promoting good capitalist market measures rather than the big govt socialist failing direction Obama has taken us, Thatcher is a thorn in liberals side...something they either don't want to talk about, or attack if they do.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365729760683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365730147404-131</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing HACK VALUE SHARP SHOOTERS</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1364675266684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne, the" trader", who still won't admit that he gave out misinformation by claiming the market would close EARLY on Thursday, the day before Good Firday.</Msg><Username>jshade19</Username><Timestamp>1365730147404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365730652855-132</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing company and the Boeing Hacks</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365708625020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't owned BA for many years. Did you sell your $28M worth of AAPL when it was over $700, or did you ride it down a ways?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1365730652855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365731446484-133</Id><Topic><Title>Will the Christian right flee the GOP?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365726209039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:23:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hope they flee the R party. The country needs two (2) sane parties.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1365731446484</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365731485514-134</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quote of the Day: "Put The President On A Leash,Please!"</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1365731485514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365731517684-135</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing company and the Boeing Hacks</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365708625020</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 15:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, how's that SSN stock you touted as going to beat BA "going forward" on 3/7/2011 when it was $4.53? Today it closed at $0.49. Good pick. HarHarHar. I know, you're a "trader" who doesn't know when the markets close early or not.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1365731517684</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:51:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365732397870-136</Id><Topic><Title>Can a Hacker Hijack a Plane With an Android App?</Title><Username>spcrash</Username><Timestamp>1365732180755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 22:03:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Research what ACARS is and does and get back to us. Sheesh.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1365732397870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 22:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365732531095-137</Id><Topic><Title>Can a Hacker Hijack a Plane With an Android App?</Title><Username>spcrash</Username><Timestamp>1365732180755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 22:03:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you google "9-11 Operation Home Run" you know that planes can be remotely hacked and become long distance drones and guided into very big buildings.......................google "9-11 Operation Home Run"</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365732531095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 22:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365732828515-138</Id><Title>in 2007, 31.5 million Americans were on food stamps</Title><Msg>.......................... In 2010, it was 40 million. In 2013 it’s up to 49 million. Clearly, there has been “no recovery” of any sort (obviously).</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365732828515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 22:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365736316745-139</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is it that a "sensitive liberal" such as yourself would devolve into crass use of tragic health issues for humor?</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1365736316745</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 23:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365736415662-140</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365725725935</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 20:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, it's not funny. You know better that this.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1365736415662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 23:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365736496574-141</Id><Topic><Title>Pro Abortion, Anti 2nd Amendment Democrats are Screwballs</Title><Username>bapsychdept</Username><Timestamp>1365545317964</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-09 18:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If youre spartacus you are a pro deather- a drag on Western Civilization who has never contributed anything to society except his paranoia</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365736496574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 23:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365736671148-142</Id><Topic><Title>in 2007, 31.5 million Americans were on food stamps</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365732828515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 22:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hope you get some help soon. You need much of it.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1365736671148</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 23:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365737014096-143</Id><Topic><Title>in 2007, 31.5 million Americans were on food stamps</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365732828515</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 22:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The deception on unemployment dropping slightly is the fact there are not the jobs even available anymore since Obama took over....gone, vanished. When you have far fewer jobs even available naturally the unemployment number for the available jobs drops. And many have now gone years without a job, and they drop of the rolls, and end up on food stamps to survive.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1365737014096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 23:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365737210297-144</Id><Topic><Title>What Margaret Thatcher Really Meant to England and the World</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1365728813475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 21:06:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey dumbsas liberals will be glad to talk about the evils of Thatcherism any time or any place and dont you forget it</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1365737210297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 23:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>