<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-08-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377058702739-1</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Rev. Al to step up</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1377040004654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 19:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3rd looks like hybrid</Msg><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1377058702739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 00:18:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377062514508-2</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Rev. Al to step up</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1377040004654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 19:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, what's new? BRUNSWICK, Ga. -- A Georgia woman said Friday a teenager trying to rob her at gunpoint asked "Do you want me to kill your baby?" before he fatally shot her 13-month-old son in the head. Race not mentioned but De'Marquis Elkins was arrested and charged...hmm.</Msg><Username>yb4itohitsfree</Username><Timestamp>1377062514508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 01:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377067263760-3</Id><Title>B-1B</Title><Msg>All this time and I can't believe there's been no mention of the latest B-1B crash or the new dog in the White House.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377067263760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 02:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377083358474-4</Id><Title>Obamacare, tepid US growth fuel part-time hiring</Title><Msg>U.S. businesses are hiring at a robust rate. The only problem is that three out of four of the nearly 1 million hires this year are part-time and many of the jobs are low-paid. http://www.cnbc.com/id/100977130</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1377083358474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 07:09:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377089549085-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama al Queda on the run, to closing all Embassys in N Africa and else where. Now the Saudi's side with Egypt</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377048673570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 21:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama supplies AlQaeda with guns...this is now confirmed....he may be the biggest liar to ever to inhabit the White House but he follows orders for his Globalist handlers well</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377089549085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 08:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377089979670-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama al Queda on the run, to closing all Embassys in N Africa and else where. Now the Saudi's side with Egypt</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377048673570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 21:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Connect the dots....ObamaCare won't cost you a dime to I've got Al Queda on the run to I am all for border protection and no Amnesty for illegals, to I don't want to take away your guns....Whatever he says the opposite is true. You will be right every time.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377089979670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 08:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377090287488-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare, tepid US growth fuel part-time hiring</Title><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1377083358474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 07:09:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That isn't even really true. There are less jobs now than when BO took over. But figuring out the fact that business is not going foot the bill for lousy ObamaCare doesn't take someone smarter than a liberal. Even liberals should have been smart enough to figure that one out. 92% of Fed employees do not want it. Ever wonder why?</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377090287488</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377090997912-8</Id><Title>Air India</Title><Msg>It appears that the air india 787 delivery scheduled for Monday did not occur. The airline continues to be a problem. At some point they should lose their slot (and maybe their deposit if they paid one). There are plenty of other customers who would take the planes in a heartbeat.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377090997912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377091198102-9</Id><Title>33 Shocking facts which show how badly the Economy has tanked since Obama became President</Title><Msg>The following are 33 shocking facts which show how badly the U.S. economy has tanked since Obama became president… #1 When Barack Obama entered the White House, 60.6 percent of working age Americans had a job. Today, only 58.7 percent of working age Americans have a job. #2 Since Obama has been president, seven out of every eight jobsthat have been “created” in the U.S. economy have been part-time jobs. #3 The number of full-time workers in the United States is still nearly 6 million below the old record that was set back in 2007. #4 It is hard to believe, but an astounding 53 percent of all American workers now make less than $30,000 a year. #5 40 percent of all workers in the United States actually make less than what a full-time minimum wage worker made back in 1968. #6 When the Obama era began, the average duration of unemployment in this country was 19.8 weeks. Today, it is 36.6 weeks. #7 During the first four years of Obama, the number of Americans “not in the labor force” soared by an astounding 8,332,000. That far exceeds any previous four year total. #8 According to the U.S. Census Bureau, the middle class is taking home a smaller share of the overall income pie than has ever been recorded before. #9 When Obama was elected, the homeownership rate in the United States was 67.5 percent. Today, it is 65.0 percent. That is the lowest that it has been in 18 years. #10 When Obama entered the White House, the mortgage delinquency rate was 7.85 percent. Today, it is 9.72 percent. #11 In 2008, the U.S. trade deficit with China was 268 billion dollars. Last year, it was 315 billion dollars. #12 When Obama first became president, 12.5 million Americans had manufacturing jobs. Today, only 11.9 million Americans have manufacturing jobs. #13 Median household income in America has fallen for four consecutive years. Overall, it has declined by over $4000 during that time span.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377091198102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377091248593-10</Id><Topic><Title>33 Shocking facts which show how badly the Economy has tanked since Obama became President</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377091198102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#14 The poverty rate has shot up to 16.1 percent. That is actually higher than when the War on Poverty began in 1965. #15 During Obama’s first term, the number of Americans on food stamps increased by an average of about 11,000 per day. #16 When Barack Obama entered the White House, there were about 32 million Americans on food stamps. Today, there are more than 47 million Americans on food stamps. #17 At this point, more than a million public school students in the United States are homeless. This is the first time that has ever happened in our history. That number has risen by 57 percent since the 2006-2007 school year. #18 When Barack Obama took office, the average price of a gallon of regular gasoline was $1.85. Today, it is $3.53. #19 Electricity bills in the United States have risen faster than the overall rate of inflation for five years in a row. #20 Health insurance costs have risen by 29 percent since Barack Obama became president, and Obamacare is going to make things far worse. #21 The United States has fallen in the global economic competitiveness rankings compiled by the World Economic Forum for four years in a row. #22 According to economist Tim Kane, the following is how the number of startup jobs per 1000 Americans breaks down by presidential administration… Bush Sr.: 11.3 Clinton: 11.2 Bush Jr.: 10.8 Obama: 7.8 #23 In 2008, that total amount of student loan debt in this country was 440 billion dollars. At this point, it has shot up to about a trillion dollars. #24 According to one recent survey, 76 percent of all Americans are living paycheck to paycheck. #25 During Obama’s first term, the number of Americans collecting federal disability insurance rose by more than 18 percent. #26 The total amount of money that the federal government gives directly to the American people has grown by 32 percent since Barack Obama became president.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377091248593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377091271600-11</Id><Topic><Title>33 Shocking facts which show how badly the Economy has tanked since Obama became President</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377091198102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#27 According to the Survey of Income and Program Participation conducted by the U.S. Census, well over 100 million Americans are enrolled in at least one welfare program run by the federal government. #28 As I wrote about the other day, American households are now receiving more money directly from the federal government than they are paying to the government in taxes. #29 Under Barack Obama, the velocity of money (a very important indicator of economic health) has plunged to a post-World War II low. #30 At the end of 2008, the Federal Reserve held $475.9 billion worth of U.S. Treasury bonds. Today, Fed holdings of U.S. Treasury bonds have skyrocketed past the 2 trillion dollar mark. #31 When Barack Obama was first elected, the U.S. debt to GDP ratio was under 70 percent. Today, it is up to 101 percent. #32 During Obama’s first term, the federal government accumulated more new debt than it did under the first 42 U.S presidents combined. #33 When you break it down, the amount of new debt accumulated by the U.S. government during Obama’s first term comes to approximately$50,521 for every single household in the United States. Are you able to pay your share?</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377091271600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377091655294-12</Id><Topic><Title>Well, The Asteriod Missed by 17,000 Some Miles</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360983644903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 22:00:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, can't do it . Chrissy has gotten the less than, and greater than keys banned by the Yahstoppo . He has personal issues with less than, and greater than . Most Liberals do .</Msg><Username>cluck_head_00</Username><Timestamp>1377091655294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377094806342-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama al Queda on the run, to closing all Embassys in N Africa and else where. Now the Saudi's side with Egypt</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377048673570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 21:31:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama care does not negate my health care cost libturd. The company sent a letter out saying it increases it and it does. That fact is nothing but the truth..co pays doubled, deductible doubled, coverage 100% to 80% two years now and not one uninsured American has benefited, Obama now delays it. If enough dumb idiots are watching they will recognize the idea of free healthcare was an election ploy, now we see the poor can't afford it. Instead of just being stupid, got read up on the subject before you connect that dumb idiot brain of yours to your fingers.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377094806342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 10:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377098504989-14</Id><Topic><Title>Another busy day for the Occupier</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377097138904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 10:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The joke is you thinking you know something, or that your post has any value or relevance. You prove the opposite here every day.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1377098504989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 11:21:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377099584371-15</Id><Topic><Title>Lee Daniels: Americans are Showing ‘True Colors’ in Anger at Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377096042659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 10:40:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's true the Obama and his supporters are the most bigoted people in the recent history of America. The are still the party of slavery and the same party that started the KKK......just using different tactics today.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377099584371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 11:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377099889617-16</Id><Topic><Title>might sell</Title><Username>lucyduffy8</Username><Timestamp>1377035222682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 17:47:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>congrats man i’m definitely gonna sell. and wait till that next alert , it’s supposed to be here pretty soon.</Msg><Username>melisabradbury</Username><Timestamp>1377099889617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 11:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377100199947-17</Id><Topic><Title>Another busy day for the Occupier</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377097138904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 10:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is having drinks with the 72 dolphins while you endless repeat propaganda on a yahoo message board . I would say the Jokes on you fool .</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1377100199947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 11:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377100801703-18</Id><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Msg>If I go to the grocery store and buy a loaf of bread, my fair share is what is charged for the bread. If I go to a Ford dealer to buy a new pick-up, my fair share is what ever the dealer will charge for the pick-up. It doesn't matter if I'm going to share my bread with someone I'll give some one else a ride in my pick up, I still have to pay my fair share. If Libtards want socialized medicine, they should pay their fair share......the full cost of it and leave every one else the h*** alone. If libtards wellfare for people in need.....why don't they pay their fair share (the full cost) and quit stealing form everyone else.</Msg><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377101388476-19</Id><Title>FLST</Title><Msg>FuelStream will soon be trading in the dollars again. New contracts worth 250M, just waiting on financing to go through to make an announcement. The current market cap is less than $2M, going to be way undervalued soon.</Msg><Username>soonergirl9572</Username><Timestamp>1377101388476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377101474242-20</Id><Topic><Title>33 Shocking facts which show how badly the Economy has tanked since Obama became President</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377091198102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377101474242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377101568045-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is going to make Republicans even more rabid about trying to shut down Obamacare before the health insurance exchanges launch Oct. 1: A survey by USA Today of 19 states finds that their estimates of how many uninsured residents will sign up for insurance on the exchanges far outstrips the federal government's estimates. Those 19 states estimate a combined 8.5 million uninsured people enrolling on the exchanges. The government had estimated 7 million for all 50 states. California alone is expected to enroll 5.3 million. This is potentially huge for the program. First of all, more of the currently uninsured will be getting access to health care. More people means more healthy people in the system, which means premiums can be kept lower for everyone. "For the most part, that's a very good thing," said Paul Ginsburg, president of the Center for Studying Health System Change. "First, these are people who need health insurance. And second, the scenario that only sick people will enroll is less likely." [...] The states said they made their estimates based on how many individuals are uninsured and aren't likely to become insured by an employer, what insurers in their states expect and conversations with HHS about reasonable goals. "It's not a positive development for the Republican opponents who would like to see this fail," Ginsburg said. "But it's still very early in the process." It is early in the process, but nonetheless extremely encouraging, at least for supporters of the program. But it is very bad news from Republicans, who are still doing their damnedest to convince young, healthy people that they should be sacrificing their own health for the goal of defeating President Obama. Expect the defund crowd to get increasingly shrill and increasingly unhinged with this news.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1377101568045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377101756388-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People like hoozdik, rockstar and zosima are 3rd. generation welfare people. The idea of paying their fair share is foreign to them. They believe they have a right to what other people earn........so do most thieves.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377101756388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377102054072-23</Id><Title>Sharpton and Obama Silent on Murder of White Baseball Player By Three "Bored" Black Teenagers</Title><Msg>Three teenage boys were charged in the killing of an Australian university student in Oklahoma "for the fun of it," prosecutors said on Tuesday Christopher Lane, of Melbourne, was found dead of a gunshot wound on Friday, according to police in Duncan, Oklahoma, about 80 miles south of Oklahoma City. “They followed him, shot him in the back and drove off,” Duncan, Okla., police chief Danny Ford said yesterday. “When asked why he [a 17-year-old suspect] did it, he said, ‘We were bored and decided to kill somebody.’ ” According to police, Jones admitted that the teens decided to kill someone "for the fun of it." Charged with first-degree murder are Chancey Allen Luna, 16, and James Francis Edwards Jr., 15. Michael Dewayne Jones, 17, who allegedly drove the vehicle carrying the other suspects, was charged with use of a vehicle in the discharge of a weapon and accessory to murder after the fact, according to the Stephens County District Attorney's office. Police said Jones named Luna as the gunman. Lane was out jogging during a visit to his girlfriend and her family in Duncan on Friday, when he was shot in the back, police said. He attended East Central University in Ada, Oklahoma, where he was on a baseball scholarship. Not surprisingly, Al Sharpton and Barack Obama, who quickly opined on the George Zimmerman self-defense case against Trayvon Martin, are silent. Not only should they be publicly condemning the alleged killing, which is now an international incident, but they should be asking why the hell these teenagers were "bored" in the middle of the day. Where were their parents? Where is Sharpton when it comes to condemning young black men joining gangs, as these three did? If Obama had a son, would he look like Chris Lane?</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377102054072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377102095976-24</Id><Topic><Title>Another busy day for the Occupier</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377097138904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 10:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I found censored's post quite valuable and thank goodness Obonzo has lots of staff to help with this heavy work load because</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377102095976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377102399846-25</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you think the asking price for anything is fair? The only time I've ever paid asking price for a vehicle was for an ad car that was about $8000, or 30% less than the others like it.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377102399846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377102548056-26</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Rev. Al to step up</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1377040004654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 19:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's OK because the baseball player can not be Obonzo's son. We are only interested in those that could be Obonzo's son.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377102548056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377102788214-27</Id><Topic><Title>Another busy day for the Occupier</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377097138904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 10:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got that right. She is trying to get fat people to lose weight but the concept is foreign to her when it comes to her own need to slim down of her use of taxpayer money.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377102788214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377102851791-28</Id><Title>Surprise: State Department Reinstates Officials 'Disciplined' Over Benghazi</Title><Msg>No Arrests, No Firings, Two Promotions......same old Obama M.O.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377102851791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103021924-29</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People like pay4ityourself repeats the same BS fact less opinionated propaganda that they have been spoon fed by talking heads selling commercial time for far too long. They would not know what paying their fair share was if it fell from the sky and hit them in the face rebounded off Rush`s mouth, bounced of his pill bottle and somehow ended up back in payfityourselfs ear.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1377103021924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:37:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103181929-30</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you and idiot liberal......he didn't say anything about the asking price.....he said "what ever the dealer will charge." His point is that libtards only want to do their good deeds with other people's money. Remember, a Democrat will never accuse you of greed for wanting to spend someone else's money.....only for wanting to keep your own.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377103181929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103227558-31</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise: State Department Reinstates Officials 'Disciplined' Over Benghazi</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377102851791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:34:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many folks were disciplined over the invasion of Iraq and the thousands upon thousands of Americans lives lost for what ?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1377103227558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103303979-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ do you know? you sit on a yahoo message board 12 + hours a day repeating yourslef endlessly.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1377103303979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103313802-33</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise: State Department Reinstates Officials 'Disciplined' Over Benghazi</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377102851791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:34:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incompetent executives tend to reward incompetence until they bring the organization down in flames. Obonz's combination of incompetence and arrogance is unsurpassed.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1377103313802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103346083-34</Id><Topic><Title>Lee Daniels: Americans are Showing ‘True Colors’ in Anger at Obama</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377096042659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 10:40:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have had similar controversies in every presidency since the first, but in this case the attacks and derision on Obama manifest themselves as 'communist' or 'socialist' or 'muslim' or 'occupier'. Why? Because all those things are more politically correct to say than to say he is black, or the more colorful versions of saying he is black. For centuries there have been people who wanted to send all black people back to Africa, as if any of them had ever been there, and some people of this generation wish to do the same by making much of the fact that Obama's father is from there.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377103346083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103604327-35</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Rev. Al to step up</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1377040004654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 19:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blacks have Al Sharpton while Whites have Pee Wee Herman.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1377103604327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:46:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103773794-36</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you pay to cross a bridge, you don't pay for the whole bridge, you pay the same toll everyone else pays.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377103773794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377103977103-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you want to live in a Banana Republic, why don't you move to Belize?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377103977103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377104130324-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Censored, leeching off the Military Industrial Complex is a public service. With enough leeches we could shut the whole slimy thing down.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1377104130324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377104132132-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>government actually spends a relatively small amount of its budget on assisting the poor. It actually spends an extraordinary amount of money handing the already-rich even more money. Here’s five ways that Republicans use government to give even more money to the already-rich (who finance the party): 1. Supporting The Oil Subsidies: The newest line among Republicans is that they despise “crony capitalism.” But House Republicans have voted unanimously time and time again to give billions of dollars to the oil industry. Paul Ryan’s budget maintains $40 billion in subsidies for Big Oil over ten years. The oil industry is giving approximately ten times as much cash to Republicans this year as it is giving to Democrats. 2. Providing Federal Funding For Rip-Off For-Profit Colleges: The for-profit college industry has abused students and veterans while ripping off taxpayers, while getting $32 billion in federal aid every single year. The Obama administration moved to cut off funding to schools with the worst performance, but every single House Republican voted to block these reforms. The industry gives twice as much money to Republicans as Democrats (unfortunately many members of both parties serve the for-profit college agenda). 3. Protecting And Subsidizing The Drug Industry: The big pharmaceutical companies have one of the best deals in the country. First, the government lavishly funds the industry’s research. It then artificially boosts prices by banning the re-importation of drugs from Canada while at the same time barring Medicare from negotiating for drug prices. Most Republicans have supported this arrangement (although there are a few dissenters like Senator David Vitter). Slightly more industry money goes to Republicans (far too many Democrats do the drug companies’ bidding as well). 4. Boosting The Insurance Industry’s Profits: Romney likes to peddle the misleading claim that Obama severely cut Medicare to finance the Affordable Care Act. But what Obama’s health care law actually does is cut back on private insurance subsidies through the Medicare Advantage program. What’s more, Romney and Ryan also want to hand the entire Medicare program to the health insurance industry, which would cost seniors an extra $60,000 for their health care. The insurance industry has given almost twice the dollars to Republicans this cycle. 5. Bailing Out The Big Banks And Then Failing To Regulate Them: Although a number of congressional Republicans did not vote to bail out the banks, Mitt Romney heartily supported the bailout programs. And both Romney and almost all Republicans in Congress opposed the Dodd-Frank financial reform law and are working to repeal large sections of it in the future. In the current campaign cycle, the Big Banks have shifted their giving to the Republicans, and have donated almost twice as much money ($81 million) to them as compared to the Democrats. Americans shouldn’t fall for the false dichotomy of one party wanting to use government to help people and the other wanting to rely only on the free market. As bold progressive candidate Elizabeth Warren said, “Republicans say they don’t believe in government. Sure they do. They believe in government to help themselves and their powerful friends.”</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1377104132132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377104656657-40</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Rev. Al to step up</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1377040004654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 19:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Zimmerman was a white-latino, why isnt the 3rd person listed as white - xx ? Instead- the spin is on gun control - and why no mention of the internet postings of the two blacks and being enamored of the crips ?? Couldn't both of them or possibly all three be ObUma sons ???</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377104656657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377105917627-41</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored I mean fascist I mean bumper I mean roksta i mean chrissie/spart I mean community agitator i mean parasite I mean brain damage spaz I mean censored I mean bumper I mean spaz I mean fascist I mean islamospaz</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1377105917627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377106202133-42</Id><Topic><Title>UPS to drop 15,000 spouses from insurance, cites Obamacare</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377104601334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:03:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This just shows how bad a company UPS is. They're only doing that to non-union workers and illustrates the value of union membership.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1377106202133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377107048324-43</Id><Topic><Title>Why don't liberals ever Want to Pay thier Fair Share.</Title><Username>rebel2rouse</Username><Timestamp>1377100801703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:00:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most excellent and to the point post, rockstar.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377107048324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377107521805-44</Id><Topic><Title>UPS to drop 15,000 spouses from insurance, cites Obamacare</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377104601334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:03:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Company sponsored healthcare is not an invention of unions. It was created by a physician to support dam construction workers and then adopted by the Kaiser manufacturing company. Unions took it over as a bargaining chip as time went on, and a lot of the bargaining power is leaving that chip. Now unions will bargain for higher wages or safer working conditions or job security in lieu of medical coverage. Look for these changes at a shop near you.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377107521805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377107820570-45</Id><Topic><Title>UPS to drop 15,000 spouses from insurance, cites Obamacare</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377104601334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:03:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just ask yourself why the percentage of union jobs in comparison to the work force is just a fraction of what it was in the early 50's? Then ask yourself where all the union jobs have gone to?</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377107820570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377108087271-46</Id><Topic><Title>Well, The Asteriod Missed by 17,000 Some Miles</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360983644903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 22:00:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's funny, 'cause it depends entirely on the size of the room, now doesn't it ? Maybe you should take your own advice .</Msg><Username>ticolow50s</Username><Timestamp>1377108087271</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 14:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377108446143-47</Id><Topic><Title>"Just for the record, Australia has had zero gun massacres since 1996"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377107671886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why are you here fomenting racial discord.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377108446143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 14:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377109692935-48</Id><Topic><Title>B-1B</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377067263760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 02:41:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Figured some of you would be all over that new dog thing. Pundits rate a new pet very high as an indicator of bad news for the president.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377109692935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 14:28:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377109882667-49</Id><Topic><Title>Air India</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377090997912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mexico for one.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377109882667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 14:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377110990291-50</Id><Topic><Title>"Just for the record, Australia has had zero gun massacres since 1996"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377107671886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Chicago tribune: Researchers at the University of Melbourne, however, found no such improvement as a result of the new system. "There is little evidence to suggest that it had any significant effects on firearm homicides or suicides," they wrote. Howard says the country has had no mass shootings since 1996. But mass shootings are such a tiny share of all homicides that any connection may be purely a matter of chance.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377110990291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 14:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377111072540-51</Id><Topic><Title>Well, The Asteriod Missed by 17,000 Some Miles</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1360983644903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 22:00:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1.) Yeah, sure . They are always to blame, always . They're under your bed, too . 2.) Whatever keeps the nut in the bag .</Msg><Username>cluck_head_00</Username><Timestamp>1377111072540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 14:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377111215466-52</Id><Topic><Title>Air India</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377090997912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right. THey had 100 on order</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377111215466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 14:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377111673063-53</Id><Topic><Title>UPS to drop 15,000 spouses from insurance, cites Obamacare</Title><Username>censored53</Username><Timestamp>1377104601334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:03:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why? Because corporate management has no loyalty to their workers. I doubt they care much about this country except to the extent it generates profits for them.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1377111673063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377111720401-54</Id><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Msg>Boeing stockholders , to us the comparison, my apple is better than your orange ! Tesla has built a car that is better than any other car based on award and is the past accident tests wtith the highest rating possible. per car testing . Boeing 787 has failed to deliver , the 787, broke down,, caught on fire twice, grounded by FAA, leaks jet engine oil, has bad wiring for fire suppression, well you get the point . You better own land in Orange county , but then your not up over 660% in 3 years . A thumb down is a vote for tesla and a get rid of Boeing, for any smart stock investor , sparti must be a angry land ower ha ha</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112016727-55</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a BOZO!!!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377112016727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112098161-56</Id><Topic><Title>Air India</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377090997912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All in Due time. Raising the prices was great$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377112098161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112218588-57</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are being to kind.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377112218588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112576756-58</Id><Topic><Title>B-1B</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377067263760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 02:41:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary hasn't been elected yet.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377112576756</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:16:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112586792-59</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla up 7% Bowing ony 3% which is better, told yah next is ethics now your gone ha</Title><Username>gsylvia16</Username><Timestamp>1377047478332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 21:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Wayne. I see you got yourself a new ID. You can change the label, but you can't change the crazy. No. We're all still here and doing fine, as I'm sure VN is as well. From what I've seen, he's able to back up his claims and has never been anything other than completely honest, which is a claim you cannot make. I'd expect he's just the type of employee a company like Boeing would want (e.g. ethical, honest, truthful, trustworthy, etc). Perhaps that's why he still works for Boeing and you do not. It certainly makes one wonder. Have a nice day! .</Msg><Username>waynes_correction_tape</Username><Timestamp>1377112586792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112666840-60</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems someone on this board (Sylvia?) is accumulating new IDs so "thumbs" up or down will have great meaning. P.S. How's the mobile home you said you bought recently? LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377112666840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112721609-61</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"to kind" freferitass to compensate for the wrong to too two , I added and deleated some of your Bozo name , ha ha and , har har har tesla is up to 150 not 104 like boeing, har har har tesla from the start of this year to now wennt from 35 to 150 , not like boeing what a loser you are only a few dollars, ha ha 75 to 104 har har har your in the wrong stock and I am being too kind</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377112721609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112866573-62</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow 13 thumbs down on correection tape means the boeing stock holders are mad at me ,har har har har har they do not like people seeing how much better tsla is and moving to that stock har har har har</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377112866573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377112928755-63</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Elon, why are you obsessed with spelling. Don't you have enough to do with your new hyperloop? Or are you waiting for Mr. Rutan to give you advice too?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377112928755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377113056350-64</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.......".your" in the wrong. You're in the wrong.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377113056350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377113064578-65</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am parking it on your condemed orange county property now , it's next to your fantasy world of orange coounty property, next to Disneyland btw DIS disney stock is much better than BA too, har har har har thanks for the plug sparti buy DIS not BA</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377113064578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377113190653-66</Id><Title>sparti just pointed out disney is a better stock than Boeing too thanks sparti</Title><Msg>DIS over time beats BA their dumbo does not crash like the 747 jumbo</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377113190653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377113232132-67</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least it's "not down by the river", if you get the reference (which you won't). LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377113232132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377113243888-68</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, using your instead of you're is the same mistake that waynerker always make.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377113243888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377113457516-69</Id><Topic><Title>Tesla started out 2013 at $35, today $150, BA stared out at $75 now $104, TSLA builds safe cars BA builds unsafe 787</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377111720401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes me wonder if waynerker's invention was used on Fosset's plane.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377113457516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377113475617-70</Id><Topic><Title>sparti just pointed out disney is a better stock than Boeing too thanks sparti</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377113190653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>starting at two yearsto 5 years and beyond disney beats BA stock price by at least 20% and then accelerates higher than a airbus leaving a 787 on the ground and on fire. har har har</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377113475617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377113584799-71</Id><Topic><Title>might sell</Title><Username>lucyduffy8</Username><Timestamp>1377035222682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 17:47:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ya just got an email from them that its this week</Msg><Username>daisystock2</Username><Timestamp>1377113584799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377114518834-72</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Rev. Al to step up</Title><Username>cw60521</Username><Timestamp>1377040004654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 19:06:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm worried that Obama and Michelle no longer have time for white concerns. Did Obama take Acting in school? He plays a pretty good part about not caring about anything but his own personal needs. childhood behavior with someone that has been denied love and attention to them can manifest itself into adulthood as also not caring about those around him. As Michelle once stated that her husband was married to his religion but not to others around him like Michelle and their children or anyone in his sphere of influence.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1377114518834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377114561227-73</Id><Topic><Title>"Just for the record, Australia has had zero gun massacres since 1996"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377107671886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just for the record, our commie pinko Hooz poster is here following pinko central orders, and pushing for gun control again. When the murder occurred, I said here come da pinko on the BA board again pushin for gun control.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1377114561227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377114957925-74</Id><Topic><Title>sparti just pointed out disney is a better stock than Boeing too thanks sparti</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377113190653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to be graced with Elon's presence on this board. Had me fooled all along that he was just using an alias of Wayne all this time. Are you really working on the hyperloop with Burt Ruton?</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1377114957925</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:55:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377115263656-75</Id><Title>Did Australia have an AG that Massacred People like ours Did at Waco?</Title><Msg>.....and you might want to look up Ruby Ridge. Take the guns away from the government before you take them away from citizens.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377115263656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377115359334-76</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Really Helping People with our Money or Are they Just Buying Votes?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377114865270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously a rhetorical question sort of like ' . . . . or is the pope catholic ? " they are against voter registration as they will lose the cadaver vote</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377115359334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377115547158-77</Id><Topic><Title>sparti just pointed out disney is a better stock than Boeing too thanks sparti</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1377113190653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, that was my line. Something about great minds...</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377115547158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377115666569-78</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Really Helping People with our Money or Are they Just Buying Votes?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377114865270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or, as it use to be: "Is the pope Italian?" Never mind.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1377115666569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377115999055-79</Id><Title>Progressives and Blacks</Title><Msg>Sometimes I wonder when black people will reject the patronizing insults of white progressives and their black handmaidens. After CNN's Piers Morgan's interview with the key witness in the George Zimmerman trial, he said: "Rachel Jeantel is not uneducated. She's a smart cookie." That's a remarkable conclusion. Here's a 19-year-old young lady, still in high school, who cannot read cursive and appears to be barely literate. Morgan may have meant Jeantel is smart -- for a black person. Progressives treat blacks as victims in need of kid glove treatment and special favors, such as racial quotas and preferences. This approach has been tried in education for decades and has revealed itself a failure. I say it's time we explore other approaches. One approach is suggested by sports. Blacks excel -- perhaps dominate is a better word -- in sports such as basketball, football and boxing to such an extent that blacks are 80 percent of professional basketball players, are 66 percent of professional football players and, for decades, have dominated most professional boxing categories. These outcomes should raise several questions. In sports, when have you heard a coach explain or excuse a black player's poor performance by blaming it on a "legacy of slavery" or on that player's being raised in a single-parent household? When have you heard sports standards called racist or culturally biased? I have yet to hear a player, much less a coach, speak such nonsense. In fact, the standards of performance in sports are just about the most ruthless anywhere. Excuses are not tolerated. Think about it. What happens to a player, black or white, who doesn't come up to a college basketball or football coach's standards? He's off the team. Players know this, and they make every effort to excel. They do so even more if they have aspirations to be a professional player. By the way, blacks also excel in the entertainment industry -- another industry in which there's ruthless dog-eat-dog competition. Seeing as blacks have demonstrated an ability to thrive in an environment of ruthless competition and demanding standards, there might be some gains from a similar school environment. Maybe we ought to have some schools in which youngsters are loaded up with homework, frequent tests and demanding, top-notch teachers. In such schools, there would be no excuses for anything. Youngsters cut the mustard, or they're kicked out and put into some other school. I'm betting that a significant number of black youngsters would prosper in such an environment, just as they prosper in the highly competitive sports and entertainment environments. Progressives' agenda calls for not only excuse-making but also dependency. Nowhere is this more obvious than it is in their efforts to get as many Americans as they can to be dependent on food stamps; however, in this part of their agenda, they offer racial equal opportunity. During President Barack Obama's years in office, the number of people receiving food stamps has skyrocketed by 39 percent. Professor Edward Lazear, chairman of the president's Council of Economic Advisers from 2006-09, wrote in a Wall Street Journal article titled "The Hidden Jobless Disaster" (June 5, 2013) that research done by University of Chicago's Casey Mulligan suggests "that because government benefits are lost when income rises, some people forgo poor jobs in lieu of government benefits --unemployment insurance, food stamps and disability benefits among the most obvious." Government handouts probably go a long way toward explaining the unprecedented number of Americans, close to 90 million, who are no longer looking for work. This is all a part of the progressive agenda to hook Americans, particularly black Americans, on government handouts. In future elections, they will be able to claim that anyone who campaigns on cutting taxing and spending is a racist. That's what Rep. Charles Rangel, D-N.Y., said in denouncing the Republican 1994 call for tax cuts. He said, "It's not 'spic' or 'n****r' anymore. (Instead,) they say, 'Let's cut taxes.'" When black Americans finally recognize the harm of the progressive agenda, I'm betting they will be the nation's most conservative people, for who else has been harmed by progressivism as much? W. Williams</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople2</Username><Timestamp>1377115999055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377116414644-80</Id><Topic><Title>B-1B</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377067263760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 02:41:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOD ONE Free!!! LMFAO!!! WOLF$$ Go BOEING$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377116414644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377116475034-81</Id><Topic><Title>"Just for the record, Australia has had zero gun massacres since 1996"</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377107671886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 13:54:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then get the F out!!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1377116475034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:21:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377116896569-82</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Really Helping People with our Money or Are they Just Buying Votes?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377114865270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Few democrats care. Few republicans care. Tea Party members of Congress and grassroots Americans who follow are serious about government overspending and government growth, government overreach in the Constitution, as well as supporting a strong National Defense. America without physical power would easily become a victum to foreign intrusion. Having a safe and secure border to stop the foreign invasion of America is another concern for Teabaggers, like myself. Keeping the elections honest is a grave concern for Teabaggers as well as it should be for anyone else. These are all common problems that America is dealing with that should be of concern for everyone. Everyone!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1377116896569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377117477745-83</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Really Helping People with our Money or Are they Just Buying Votes?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377114865270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who`s money do Republicans use to buy votes?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1377117477745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377117573912-84</Id><Topic><Title>Are Democrats Really Helping People with our Money or Are they Just Buying Votes?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377114865270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 15:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cadaver vote has been a political staple since the beginning.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377117573912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377117645005-85</Id><Topic><Title>Did Australia have an AG that Massacred People like ours Did at Waco?</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377115263656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:01:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waco was basically self immolation.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377117645005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377117929014-86</Id><Title>NSA COLLECTED 1000S OF INTERNET COMMUNICATIONS WITH NO TERROR CONNECTION</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) -- The National Security Agency declassified three secret U.S. court opinions Wednesday showing how it scooped up as many as 56,000 emails and other communications by Americans with no connection to terrorism annually over three years, how it revealed the error to the court and changed how it gathered Internet communications. Director of National Intelligence James Clapper authorized the release Wednesday. The opinions show that when the NSA reported that to the court in 2011, the court ordered the NSA to find ways to limit what it collects and how long it keeps it.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople2</Username><Timestamp>1377117929014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:45:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377118226628-87</Id><Title>GALLUP: Unemployment Spikes to 8.9%...</Title><Msg>Outside of the federal government's Bureau of Labor statistics, the Gallup polling organization also tracks the nation's unemployment rate. While the BLS and Gallup findings might not always perfectly align, the trends almost always do and the small statistical differences just haven't been worthy of note. But now Gallup is showing a sizable 30 day jump in the unemployment rate, from 7.7% on July 21 to 8.9% today. This is an 18-month high. At the end of July, the BLS showed a 7.4% unemployment rate, compared to Gallup's 7.8%. Again, a difference not worthy of note. But Gallup's upward trend to almost 9% in just the last three weeks is alarming, especially because this is not a poll with a history of wild swings due to statistical anomalies. Gallup's sample size is a massive 30,000 adults and the rolling average is taken over a full 30 day period. Gallup also shows an alarming increase in the number of underemployed (those with some work seeking more). During the same 30-day period, that number has jumped from 17.1% to 17.9%.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeople2</Username><Timestamp>1377118226628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377119467656-88</Id><Topic><Title>Sharpton and Obama Silent on Murder of White Baseball Player By Three "Bored" Black Teenagers</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377102054072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>two black- one white ( driver of car )</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1377119467656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 17:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377121758378-89</Id><Topic><Title>GALLUP: Unemployment Spikes to 8.9%...</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople2</Username><Timestamp>1377118226628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 16:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it was invented by Boxarox's crew.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1377121758378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 17:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377123784706-90</Id><Topic><Title>Sharpton and Obama Silent on Murder of White Baseball Player By Three "Bored" Black Teenagers</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377102054072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the kid didn't look like him or all the convicts that look like him. This president is a racist. I got black friends that tell me he is a racist. A president weighing in on local crime. Its crazy.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377123784706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 18:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377124351712-91</Id><Title>Second Amendment saves Iowa Couple</Title><Msg>BEDFORD, Iowa —Law enforcement authorities said Tuesday that an Iowa couple shot and killed an escaped inmate after being held in their home for four hours. Authorities: Iowa couple shot, killed escaped inmate A couple shoots and kills an escaped inmate in their kitchen after he held them for four hours. More Iowa Division of Criminal Investigation Special Agent Mitch Mortvedt said Rodney Long forced his way into the couple's home at 2609 Highland Avenue about 10:15 p.m. and held them for the next four hours. Jerome and Carolyn Mauderly said Long was armed with a semi automatic handgun. He had also taken their phones. Jerome, 71, and Carolyn, 66, decided to defend themselves, Mortvedt said. Jerome shot Long with his shotgun. They were not seriously hurt in the incident. About 2 a.m., the couple called 911 to report the shooting. An Iowa State trooper was on the road nearby and responded immediately to the home. The trooper found Long dead face down on the kitchen floor of the couple's home. "As the trooper made entry into the residence they found Rodney Long lying face down on the kitchen floor. He secured the situation and obviously checked on the wellbeing of Mr. and Mrs. Mauderly," said Mortvedt.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377124351712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 18:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377125781975-92</Id><Topic><Title>Ron Paul to be keynote speaker at anti-Semitic conference</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377125427535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 18:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Figures. Paul is even more tone deaf than we thought.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1377125781975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 18:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377126146792-93</Id><Topic><Title>B-1B</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377067263760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 02:41:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, but it's a virtual certainty. The R guys are even more weird today than they were yesterday.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1377126146792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 19:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377129199865-94</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare foe Rick Perry suddenly wants Obamacare funds</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377127068569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 19:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, Perry has a lot to brag about. Notice he's trying to supplement elder care rather than anyone else. The elderly already use the lions share of health related services and by a certain age are guaranteed a certain amount of health insurance. Perry feels it's safe to support the elderly because none of them are going to ask for an abortion.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377129199865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 19:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377129317377-95</Id><Topic><Title>Sharpton and Obama Silent on Murder of White Baseball Player By Three "Bored" Black Teenagers</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1377102054072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 12:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President OBAMA appears to have a racial bias at least. We heard him call the Trevon Martin case a racial issue even though the jury said not guilty". Now we have two African Americans and another man we do not (or care) his background who seem to have killed an Australian man because they were bored. Where is the outrage for this obvious RACISM. I guess it is a one way street in the Presidents view.</Msg><Username>lovestoread41</Username><Timestamp>1377129317377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 19:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377129610487-96</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare foe Rick Perry suddenly wants Obamacare funds</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1377127068569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 19:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like it or not it is the trough that we have to go to.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1377129610487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 20:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377130381657-97</Id><Topic><Title>My Impersonation of HoozdikHertz</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1376876757320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-08-18 21:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Ever since the Garden of Eden, the serpents have been relegated to slithering on the ground ....."...speaking od serpents... I see where Oliver Stone called Obama a Snake....a snake that had to be turned on...</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1377130381657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 20:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377130862005-98</Id><Title>hoozdik_hertz_557 vision of America</Title><Msg>The Spawn of liberal american parents gunning down people out of boredom, and blaming responsible gun owners. You will probably be a victim one day by the very same electorate and fellow party voters. The country is at a tipping point, there will come a time when the country will rise up and fix the Rash of Red/ Blue state liberals and their children gunning down innocent citizens and blaming it on everybody else.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377130862005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 20:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377131753588-99</Id><Topic><Title>B-1B</Title><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1377067263760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 02:41:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>29% of Republicans blame Obama for the Hurricane Katrina response. 28% of Republicans blame the existing President then, W. We are dooooooomed.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1377131753588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 20:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377132432578-100</Id><Topic><Title>Air India</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377090997912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 09:16:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Things may be ready to loosen on Air india;s pursestrings. With todays flight of an air ndia 787 out of charleston (I believe it was at least a B2 flight aince it was airborne a few days ago), there are two air india planes rthat should be ready for delivery. IF air india was not going to take them soon, they woudl not have bothered to expend the fuel and time.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1377132432578</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 20:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377138283190-101</Id><Topic><Title>hoozdik_hertz_557 vision of America</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1377130862005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 20:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I knew Hoosesuk would be doing that even before I logged on . I must be psychic . It's hillarious that the unemployable think they've got the smarts to run the world . You can't make this stuff up . Y.T. Jumbojetski</Msg><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1377138283190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 22:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377138796286-102</Id><Title>NO MORE DICKWAYNEDICK?</Title><Msg>PHEW.....</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1377138796286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 22:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377139199536-103</Id><Topic><Title>might sell</Title><Username>lucyduffy8</Username><Timestamp>1377035222682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 17:47:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow man i cant believe you made that much</Msg><Username>kristiewatanabe</Username><Timestamp>1377139199536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 22:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377139819517-104</Id><Title>Snowden for president and hooz off to Bengazzi to pose as President Obama</Title><Msg>Snowden is a hero, hooz is a hoozdick</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377139819517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 22:50:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377143072692-105</Id><Title>WGN TV chicago black baby 5 month old missing Saw a picture Looks just like Obama</Title><Msg>but the baby wasn't smoking dope.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377143072692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 23:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1377143216011-106</Id><Topic><Title>WGN TV chicago black baby 5 month old missing Saw a picture Looks just like Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377143072692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 23:44:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And has a birth cert</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1377143216011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 23:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1377143375558-107</Id><Title>WGN TV Chicago 5 murders gang related. Now gun hatters will scream, but I bet you illegal guns. These #$%$</Title><Msg>want us to believe the person is beautiful, guns are bad, but even Obami was hunting with white boys his first term. Back in Hawaii wasn't Obama the leader of a gang, posing while smoking a joint?</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1377143375558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-21 23:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>