<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362292480708-1</Id><Topic><Title>Jay Leno retire but does it matter? Not to me I stoped watching when Obama made fun of Sara Palins mentally disabled son</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1362272746124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 20:05:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are totally wrong, as usual. I can't decide it you know it's a lie you cynically repeat over and over again or if you are just too stupid or too much a True Believer to know you are being fed lies.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362292480708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 01:34:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362292585112-2</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God for Gun Safety Courses</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244642830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Such vitriol over a little chortling. We must have cut close to the bone! Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362292585112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 01:36:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362295407376-3</Id><Title>Regulators Wary of Boeing's Plan to Fix the Dreamliner</Title><Msg>Japan's preponderance of Dreamliners means that even though Boeing is an iconic American company, Japanese regulators actually have far more clout than US regulators in determining when and how the 787 gets back in the air. For Boeing, the opportunity is absolutely massive. However, the company's execution problems and emerging competitors have investors wondering whether Boeing will live up to its shareholder responsibilities. While the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration is not yet ready to allow test flights , Japanese regulators aren't even ready to admit that the battery itself is the problem, , Japanese transport minister Akihiro Ota called Boeing's plan a "starting point" and indicated that his ministry would need to take some time just to evaluate the proposal to see if its satisfactory. If Japanese regulators don't accept that the battery is at fault, and require Boeing to go back to the drawing board for a more comprehensive fix, resuming flights by April would look very unrealistic.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362295407376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 02:23:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362295640927-4</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing’s apology tour</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1362098624997</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 19:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don, sometimes when you cant fix a dog or a cat the situation requires they be put down, its a sad day, but sometimes it spares a lot of grief on the pet owners part or shareholders of BA</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362295640927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 02:27:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362298086520-5</Id><Title>Good-by Boeing dictator, SEC orders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman roles maybe !</Title><Msg>To those who argue the board should decide its own management structure, all I can say is "How's that been working' out for you?"The documents between BA and John Chevedden and the SEC are interesting reading ,The typical BA response is right out of the cookbook used by Perkins Coie and sometimes even Boeing Counsel offices. Boeing must let investors vote on splitting the roles of chief executive officer and chairman to strengthen oversight, the Securities and Exchange Commission said. Chevedden’s plan would require that an independent director lead Boeing’s board instead of the CEO, according to SEC documents. The proposal gives the company the option to put off separating the roles until McNerney, 63, leaves. Boeing shares have climbed 2.5 percent this year, trailing the Dow Jones Index by 6.5 percent and the Dow Jones average , as Dreamliner’s woes mounted. Through Thursday, the stock has lagged by over 11% percent of the whole average of good and bad stocks since McNerney took over as CEO in July 2005, compared with 27.1 gain percent for the S&amp;P 500.Boeing has also trailed the Dow by a wide margin since the CEO took over Boeing. One major problem besides the wrong man for the job, the wrong man has both the Chairman and CEO jobs, which is like being the dictator of North Korea. Boeing has sought to block a vote, messages to the SEC show.. Before shooing McNerney out the door, there are 2 other GE alumni on the Boeing board of directors. It would be no surprise if they are McNerney's CEO 'backups' Boeing and the friends brothers and in-laws who hold large institutional shares will fight this vote with everything they have in the false and misleading tool box. What you want to make the CEO responsible to the Board of Directors? Why. Why, John Chevedden statement “There is a direct link between the behaviors that led to this financial collapse and the short-term compensation programs so common in financial services companies( and other companie</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362298086520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 03:08:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362298554968-6</Id><Topic><Title>Good-by Boeing dictator, SEC orders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman roles maybe !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362298086520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 03:08:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a direct link between the behaviors that led to thisBoeing short t erm reward and the log time failure called outsourcing and the short-term compensation programs that the executives set up for themselves. This is so common most companies like Boeing that reward short-term gains and short-term stock price increases with extremely generous pay levels” O.f Executives bonus called long term like 20 days is long term like right to work state really means no union protection fire at will . . Boeing CEO got a 34% pay raise last year for example while the workers had to fight to get up to 5% and a loss of future retirement for new hires . All While Boeing is in the right place at the right time to sell, but not make flyable airplanes that are fuel efficient (787). Four years late and grounded and 34 billion dollars above the budget for building the 787 is failure by the CEO and the Board of Directors this is Boeing's future and it is a 100% fail. The workers just put them together the executives hire the contractors to make the parts and they failed the shareholders .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362298554968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 03:15:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362311686874-7</Id><Title>The dreamliner is all lyies and deception</Title><Msg>This plane has so many problems it will NEVER fly passengers again. Electrical problem is an unkown 8 years after desighing it. Gas leaks all over the plane. Boeing is knows the plane is hoseed up but is used to BSing the Pentagon. Nobody will fly on it. If it did fly it would be within a year one would crash.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1362311686874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 06:54:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362311772143-8</Id><Title>Dreamliner problems: Getting wors in everyway everday !</Title><Msg>No progress is being made. Only more questions to be sweprt under the rug.</Msg><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1362311772143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 06:56:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362319511009-9</Id><Topic><Title>Good-by Boeing dictator, SEC orders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman roles maybe !</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362298086520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 03:08:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see the Boeing loser investor and Boeing PR jerks have given me a thumbs down, how does it sit with you Boeing monitors and stock market losers who give a thumbs down to a newspaper report! ha ha ha This is what is clear to any person who compares Boeing stock price to the Dow or the NASDAQ or the S and P 500. Now because of the terrible performance of Boeing 2.5% compared to Airbus up 15% the shareholders are finally getting angry and a rich guy is starting to take action against Boeing , to get rid of the good old boy MD -GE failure at the top of Boeing. It is a long time off, but eventually with continued new program failure Boeing will fail completely or be saved by returning to a engineering company that build airplanes by designing them in the USA. Next you losers that lick the CEO bottom, get lost , Boeing needs to bring work back to the USA. After 100 years of taxpayer support Boeing should have a lot more loyalty to the taxpaying people of America and make as much of the plane as they can in America. The argument that labor is cheaper overseas is total BS.. The only country that makes parts for Boeing that is cheaper is Mexico and that country makes very few parts. So the only real reason is Japan will buy a lot of Boeing planes if Boeing gives them work like the battery for the 787.The wing for the 787. was outsourced to Japan, that was the dumbest decision of all time. These CEO's who sell off the golden egg, the wing technology secrets will be used by Japan to conquer the American airplane indusutry it was greed of the executives that caused that . there should be a required oath of Allegiance to t he USA for all CEO in America. Canada will not allow any worker to obtain a job in their country unless no Canadian citizen is qualifired . You can only immagrate to Canada if you have enough money to live there and you can only set up a company if you have the money and you must hire Canadian citizens</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362319511009</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:05:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362319583944-10</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God for Gun Safety Courses</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244642830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the war zone that leaves people dead everyday in places like Democrat Central in Chicago is fine with the Hooz. All the stringent gun control laws in Chicago are really working in the absent mind of the Hooz.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1362319583944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:06:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362319608700-11</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing’s apology tour</Title><Username>lasertech_3d</Username><Timestamp>1362098624997</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 19:43:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lazertech you should be the CEO of Boeing good job</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362319608700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:06:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362321306551-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why was the 777 such a great success?</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1362275149784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 20:45:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope Phil Condit, led the team that launched the wide-body Boeing 777 airplane under the direction of T A Wilson. , defense junky, get your facts straight. Allan Mulally was part of the problem, he was the guy who started the sonic cruiser which formed into the dreamliner, and Mulally would not listen to reality . no airline company wanted a fuel sucking airplane that made just a little more speed . So from one extreme to another new skin, new outsoruced engineering, the guy acts like a bipolar mental case not a smart and wide director with other people investment money while he was at Boeing . He wasted 5 years failing. . Mulally got wise when he was shown the door at Boeing, he said it was a fight to the death and if the other guy won (James McNerney) he would leave. Like he had a choice, be a loser for the end of his career or move on to Ford. Mulally would much rather had the Boeing job, but he was too stupid to get over himself and the mantra of unions are bad and all that stinking thinking. He learned to work with unions at Ford as he had no choice. Now if you read his retirement package he is taking a huge deal with him. I sure hope he will never get back to Boeing. the last good CEO was T A Wilson he was responsible for all the great planes. So after he retired the great Boeing planes 1943 to 1987 from B-52 to the 777 , nothing since Wilson retired has Boeing been any good. Wilson assumed the role of chairman emeritus and continued to serve as a member of the board of directors until April 1993.. . On December 8, 1989, Boeing began issuing offers to airlines for the 777.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362321306551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:35:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362321762569-13</Id><Topic><Title>Concern and Canceled Flights as Airlines Wait for 787</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362195112586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:31:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>averyed510 glad your sure they will get the 787 flying again, but will it crash and burn too ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362321762569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:42:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362321860052-14</Id><Topic><Title>The BA BATTERY flamethrower</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587230282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the idea that a fix is a containment for a planned fire is just a bad fix.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362321860052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:44:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362321946183-15</Id><Topic><Title>YTD , DOW up 6%, but BA lags at 2%,how many 787 are flying now ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1361976788268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice for me to read a newspaper has figured out that Boeing stock sucks compared to the three major averages , only took them abut 3 years to find that fact .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1362321946183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:45:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362321952159-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner problems: Getting wors in everyway everday !</Title><Username>food_stamp_nation</Username><Timestamp>1362311772143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 06:56:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We just don't know what progress is being made. I am especially disappointed being a member of the 787 design team. Boeing provided us a special web site to keep us updated on progress, but has instead decided to keep mum.</Msg><Username>mbfield</Username><Timestamp>1362321952159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:45:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362322228687-17</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA leaders wave the white flag</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1362246005124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:40:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's time to realize that the world has changed big time over the last several years. There are still many people out of jobs and would love to have a job at Boeing with all their benefits. This is not the time to get greedy. Boeing is one of the last companies in America that makes a difference in the world!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1362322228687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:50:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362324231200-18</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God for Gun Safety Courses</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244642830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These are Obama loving Democrats Hooz so I would be a third wheel as I'm not in love with Obama like you, so I would just drop you off after dark and leave. Here's a suggestion for an itinerary for your visit: I figured first you could go door to door looking for law abiding citizens that have guns, like retired cops and security officers, and demand that they turn in their weapons to you and vaGenna by convincing them that it is what Obama wants and it would be much safer if only criminals had guns. This WILL work and I believe they will give you their guns because they were stupid enough to vote for Obama and obviously have #$%$ for brains just like you and vaGenna. lol After you've confiscated all the legal guns, you and vaGenna can get to the drug dealers by trading the confiscated guns to drug dealers for drugs. You and vaGenna can then get stoned out of your minds to show your support for the progressive movement to make drugs legal and available to everyone. Next, while still stoned (you'll have more street cred being stoned), you can distribute some of those new DHS shooting targets, that contain pictures of White pregnant women and White children, to criminals in the hood. Educate them that Democrats will soon take weapons away from all law abiding citizens and that Democrats are fine with criminals killing innocent people, as long as they don't appear to be racist about it. The targets of White pregnant women and White children will encourage them to shoot more White people and not just Black people and remove the racist element found in the current murder rate statistics. This is the Progressive Democrat's approach to making neighborhoods safer and fight racism and I know that you and vaGenna are good little Progressive Democrat Obama lovers, so here's your chance to shine. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362324231200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 10:23:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362324416537-19</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm #$%$ Hertz... and I just enrolled in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362321428454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:37:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BrokeDik: "fulfilled all the requirements for being a "REAL" man" When YOU fill the requirements of being a Man...you and "Trendy" PAUL MCCartney will let us know</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362324416537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 10:26:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362326351601-20</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very helpful report , thanks !</Msg><Username>godfrey.hilary</Username><Timestamp>1362326351601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 10:59:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362326411100-21</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm #$%$ Hertz... and I just enrolled in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362321428454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:37:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can we get Barry into class #2? He's an attorney with big ears that could be confused for large bird wings, so he would be a perfect addition to the course. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362326411100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362327188670-22</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm #$%$ Hertz... and I just enrolled in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362321428454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:37:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz, it is clear that progressive Democrats think REAL men have memberships to Man's Country Chicago and have beards. ROTFL</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362327188670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:13:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362327649305-23</Id><Topic><Title>Willard Re-emerges From Mansion Seclusion</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1362240295589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 11:04:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Willard recently said he was "shellshocked" by his election loss. He was almost as "shellshocked" as when he received his draft notice immediately after returning from cheerleading another war rally. He had to move "offshore" for three years to recover. He fled from the sound of the guns to the sounds of the Folies Bergere.</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1362327649305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:20:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362327780993-24</Id><Title>SNL Nails Barry's Whiney Little Spoiled Brat Act</Title><Msg>It was hilarious and the YMCA joke poking fun at Barry's sexuality probably went over most viewers heads but I was ROTFLMAO.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362327780993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:23:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362327896708-25</Id><Topic><Title>Cupcakes and Flu Shots for Syria</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1362162559586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world's most dangerous WMD stockpile is inside dJubmot's so-called brain.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1362327896708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:24:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362328612796-26</Id><Topic><Title>Cupcakes and Flu Shots for Syria</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1362162559586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about ali's lice-infested brain? I nominate that one.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1362328612796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:36:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362328692735-27</Id><Topic><Title>Conundrum</Title><Username>hrosenldgt56a</Username><Timestamp>1362234914144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 09:35:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If today's price is low, where do you think it "should" be? How do you analyze the "should"? Thank you.</Msg><Username>hrosenldgt56a</Username><Timestamp>1362328692735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:38:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362329030044-28</Id><Title>47% Of Americans Support Incompetent Wannabe Dictator</Title><Msg>Barry has been channeling his inner Stalin and it doesn't seem to be working yet, but I encourage him not to give up. ;-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362329030044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:43:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362329430788-29</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores! --Chris Genna</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362329430788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:50:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362329794832-30</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Definitely Harvard. Ever see the front student area of Harvard? Looks like Haight Ashbury. Crudy looking students crawling all over the place. Make sure you've been vaccinated if you ever get near the place if you are conservative. Liberals should have no health problems. And we do know Obama appointed his good friend Van Jones.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1362329794832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362329827084-31</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a DFC would try to use a famous saying from hockey night in Canada and pass it off as your own. What a PUTZ!!!!</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1362329827084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362329886291-32</Id><Title>Union or Job</Title><Msg>Union---give me, give me, give me! I worked for Hyatt Clark Ind. Inc. in Clark New Jersey, which was formerly New Depature Hyatt Roller Bearing a divison of GM. When GM sold the plant to the employees it became HCI. The company turned it around and the quality went from 63% to over 84% with the same machinery. What happened that the company collapsed- the company closed. It was the UAW which we joined. "THEY" the UNION, the UAW, told everyone to stage a slowdown. Well Stupid, you can't have a slowdown against yourself just because you disagree with management. If you don't make the bearings then GM your only customer wont get there product and will go else where. See, management didn't want to give out the profits for the year. OK, so put it back into the company, yes. But management should have given 25% of profits to workers. HCI was a profit sharing company. Ok, but you don't tell your union brothers to slowdown. SO, GM said that if we couldn't resolve our difference it will buy their bearings some where else. Well they did. Why, because the UAW is so hard headed that it can't see past their own greed. I WOULD RATHER HAVE A JOB THAT PAYS A BIT LESS THEN WHAT I'M RECEIVING AND PAY 40% FOR MY HEALTH PLAN AND HAVE A JOB,---THEN NOT HAVE A JOB! STUPID #$%$_KEN UNION! THEY ARE GOOD FOR THE WORKER BUT THE UAW WILL ULTIMATELY BE THE WORKERS DEMISE. I say strong sell because GM is going down at the hands of the UAW!</Msg><Username>daninjersey732</Username><Timestamp>1362329886291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:58:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362330088099-33</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only did Foster Hewitt coin the phrase that little Chrissy thinks is his own, it was also a movie title from 1995. Google "he shoots, he scores" and see that little Chrissy didn't make that up.................</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1362330088099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:01:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362330167414-34</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm #$%$ Hertz... and I just enrolled in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362321428454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:37:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's just a DFC and probably card carrying too.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1362330167414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:02:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362330338011-35</Id><Title>UNION- Give-me Give-me Give-me</Title><Msg>I wrote these two letter on GM message board some three yrs ago. HOW TRUE IT IS! WE need to make America strong. Be glad you guys have jobs. If you guys screw with BA then you are only giving jobs to Airbus by your neglect and bickering. How is it that the UAW thinks that GM should pay all expensive of health plan? Union workers, as management workers work for GM 8hrs a day, right. So your #$%$ is home away from GM 16hrs a day. That is 1/3 the time at GM. GM can at times be hazardous at some of the work stations and there by be responsible for some of the health plan cost. BUT!! Your #$%$ sits home ---SMOKING, DRINKING, DRIVING your car, working around the house, using chemicals cleaning your house, EATING LIKE A PIG and getting fat and you guys are saying you shouldn't pay for any of your health plans coverage! "You" and I'm sorry to say this, Want,Want,Want Americans are making me sick! I'm an American and if you guys think that you can live high on the hog and buy this and buy that and eat this and smoke that you guys are fooling yourselves. You guys UNION, have lost your own jobs by the Want,Want,Want, GiveME, GiveMe, GiveMe, attitude. STRONG SELL</Msg><Username>daninjersey732</Username><Timestamp>1362330338011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:05:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362330509161-36</Id><Topic><Title>The BA BATTERY flamethrower</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587230282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No it's an excellent #$%$</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1362330509161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:08:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362330923618-37</Id><Topic><Title>Cupcakes and Flu Shots for Syria</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1362162559586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jumbo, The "Russian" angle had not occurred to me. And the Russians are certainly not inclined to do anything to undermine Obama's "after the election I will have more flexibility" status as well as the fascination that many Americans seem to have with left-wingnut-isms. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1362330923618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:15:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362331009443-38</Id><Topic><Title>SEC SEC orders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman rolesorders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman roles</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1362193716634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:08:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are now suffering the backlash of when H.Stoneceipher was the CEO. and so are the workers there. i.m.o.</Msg><Username>loftndude2000</Username><Timestamp>1362331009443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:16:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362331571994-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why was the 777 such a great success?</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1362275149784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 20:45:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's pretty delusional. You must be one of the clowns that designed the 787. The team that designed the 777 was totally different than the team that designed the 787. That's just the truth. Mulally lost the political battle to the MD idiot managers that Condit let take over the company. Stonecipher gave Mullaly an impossible job to do. That forced him out of Boeing. That's what I saw.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1362331571994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:26:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362332106781-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why was the 777 such a great success?</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1362275149784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 20:45:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>put to the point !</Msg><Username>loftndude2000</Username><Timestamp>1362332106781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:35:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362332551698-41</Id><Topic><Title>47% Of Americans Support Incompetent Wannabe Dictator</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362329030044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:43:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gallup Poll shows an 11 point drop in Barry's job approval since late December 2012 and now he has become argumentative with the press corps which I'm sure Barry would prefer to be a press corpse like most other dictators enjoy. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362332551698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:42:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362332977155-42</Id><Title>The 787 disaster</Title><Msg>Yes, I put total blame on the Douglas management that runs Boeing. McNurdy needs to go and the entire Boeing management needs a major overhaul!</Msg><Username>morons_finder</Username><Timestamp>1362332977155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 12:49:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362334618433-43</Id><Topic><Title>SEC SEC orders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman rolesorders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman roles</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1362193716634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:08:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting - Why, when I post the boeing argument against part of the proposal- in which Boeing LOST ( as copied from the SEC documents ) people turn thumbs down ?? I would think most would be in favors of BA losing such that the proposal wil appear intact, and give a few a chance to query McNearney at the shareholders meeting. Maybe it just my fans ??</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1362334618433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:16:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362334769385-44</Id><Title>If you are a TRUE design engineer</Title><Msg>The problem with the 787 was the way the program was managed from day1! Total outsourcing is a total joke. You need to keep total control of the engineering process until you identify the materials and companies that will produce the parts to the specifications that are required! Another words, you keep all the design in house until you feel it is time to outsource. Boeing screwed up big time on the 787.</Msg><Username>morons_finder</Username><Timestamp>1362334769385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:19:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362335106018-45</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did he go there then. Should have gone to Liberty University. Must not be too smart</Msg><Username>mr_cut_and_paste</Username><Timestamp>1362335106018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:25:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362335106857-46</Id><Topic><Title>47% Of Americans Support Incompetent Wannabe Dictator</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362329030044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:43:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy, you got that right! 47% is a lot of ignorant people that don't have a clue as to what's taking place in those sacred halls in Washington.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1362335106857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:25:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362335400613-47</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good job</Msg><Username>stevens_roger</Username><Timestamp>1362335400613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:30:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362335454669-48</Id><Topic><Title>47% Of Americans Support Incompetent Wannabe Dictator</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362329030044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:43:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would not get wedded to that 47% business. It cost Romney the election and not everyone who voted against him is #$%$. A lot of them knew it was flat WRONG and thought it would be dangerous to have a man who talked like that be at the head of our government. Romney's 47% included military retirees. Do you think Sparty, who has told us over and over about his 25 years in various uniforms, would agree that all 47 percent are shiftless losers who never contributed? Romney's 47% included Social Security beneficiaries, so ask your grandma if she's a parasite and hope you don't get your mouth washed out with soap.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362335454669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:30:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362335676411-49</Id><Title>What Now</Title><Msg>It looks like the sequester crisis is pretty much played out. So what new fiasco is president Obama and the Dems going to lead us into? We shouldn't have to wait long to find out.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1362335676411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:34:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362335743882-50</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to get over it, floyd. Your obsession about Foster Heitt is making you the kind of guy who never gets invited to parties. You spurt ... You bore! --Chris Genna</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362335743882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:35:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362335828846-51</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What a putz"? Who did you steal THAT from???? Harharharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362335828846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:37:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362336077542-52</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its very funny when you have your aliases stick up for yourself.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362336077542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:41:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362336119377-53</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm #$%$ Hertz... and I just enrolled in</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362321428454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 09:37:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you a card carrying one?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362336119377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:41:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362336195842-54</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you claiming putz too? What a putz!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362336195842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:43:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362336288736-55</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great work</Msg><Username>august_whelan</Username><Timestamp>1362336288736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:44:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362336328027-56</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It must really irk you when others out your BS. hahahahahaha.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362336328027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:45:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362336985361-57</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>amywatts82</Username><Timestamp>1362336985361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 13:56:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362337978901-58</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for sharing!</Msg><Username>helen.hereford</Username><Timestamp>1362337978901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 14:12:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362338165304-59</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whooosh, Miss Aim. Whoosh. I was pointing out that 3-4 English words -- put together to express a single, simple thought -- cannot be copyrighted. If they could, someone would have copyrighted "Have a nice day." Now I know you're wondering why I'm replying to a putz who is a sad joke on intelligence. I found that by having you and floyd on ignore, I was missing 90 percent of the humor on this board, which I my main reason for showing up. But I've decided I only really need floyd's humor. You can go back on ignore. I mean that in a nice way. But when you post 4 messages in row all responding to me, you show yourself to be a dangerous stalker and possibly sex offender. (If I was really worried, I'd report you to Yahoo! (tm :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362338165304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 14:16:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362338406062-60</Id><Topic><Title>Thank God for Gun Safety Courses</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244642830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:17:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362338406062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 14:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362338603546-61</Id><Title>Here's what the 47% got Romney</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney says it "kills" him that he's not president. But he doesn't blame Superstorm Sandy, New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie or anything else on his loss to President Barack Obama--except his campaign's failure to connect with minority voters. “I lost my election because of my campaign," Romney said in an interview broadcast on "Fox News Sunday," his first television interview since his November defeat. "Not because of what anyone else did." The former Massachusetts governor refused place blame on Christie, who some Republicans say gave Obama a last-minute lift in his embrace of the president in the wake of the storm. Romney said his inability to win over black and Hispanic voters--and the damage done by those disastrous "47 percent" comments--ultimately derailed his White House bid. [So keep at it, right-fringers. Soon you'll ALL be able to join mittens in a giant cry-in-your-beer garten.]</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362338603546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 14:23:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362338826564-62</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google it? Who would bother except a hateful little nothing-but-nonsense twerp like you? Hahahahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362338826564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 14:27:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362339189804-63</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>tasha_cook</Username><Timestamp>1361981972208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:19:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>richardkelly728</Username><Timestamp>1362339189804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 14:33:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362339985243-64</Id><Topic><Title>You have to love ted cruz</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_567</Username><Timestamp>1362244478187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:14:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you hung over or still drunk? You sound very angry and kind of weird.</Msg><Username>justshutupnfish</Username><Timestamp>1362339985243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 14:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362340887638-65</Id><Topic><Title>Here's what the 47% got Romney</Title><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362338603546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 14:23:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I voted for Romney. He wasn't my first choice, and I did not vote for him in the primaries. He still would be a much better leader for this county than Obama. I agree with the explanation for him losing the general election as his "47 percent" comments. I'm not sure who put those ideas into his head, but I think it may have been a well laid out trap from the left and he fell for it, hook, line, and sinker. The democrats always go for the throat if the Republican candidate is a successful and wealthy businessman, as though there has never been a rich and super wealthy democrat. Dems always label Republicans as the party of and for the rich. Mitt gave them a good target to do just that.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1362340887638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362342190304-66</Id><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Msg>In particular, he says a Google search of the terms “Hitler Gun Control” produce so-called “research studies” claiming that “either these atrocities never really occurred (such as the Jewish Genocide) or that the facts are wrong,” Fight4Freedom says. “No matter what, the idea is to use FALSE statements and FALSE information to continue to gain momentum in calling for disarming of the American People,” he wrote. “The most fundamental question is why should what happened in #$%$ Germany have any bearing on calling for Gun Control in the U.S.? They are not related. It is merely a propaganda tool. Our God given right to self-defense, backed by the U.S. Constitution is all that matters.”</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362344027832-67</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btdt100 over on the MO board advocates the same nonsense that the Holocaust never happened.</Msg><Username>dogshitforbrains</Username><Timestamp>1362344027832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:53:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362344760460-68</Id><Title>SEQUESTRATION .. what will happen to BOEING ???</Title><Msg>.. Lay off coming.. or what ..?????</Msg><Username>hq_2004</Username><Timestamp>1362344760460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 16:06:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362344857618-69</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are correct, once again. There is no denying that gun grabbers are always on the wrong side of history and join the ranks of Fascists and Communists. There is almost nothing more anti American.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1362344857618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 16:07:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362345404419-70</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The show is down 27% in total viewers and 38% in the demo from its debut in Jan. 17th, 2011. Piers Morgan Tonight also had the lowest demo in its time slot and was even beat by HLN’s Dr. Drew (with 208,000).</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362345404419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 16:16:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362347827467-71</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Piers Morgan has been schooled by several real Americans lately. Nobody watches his show.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1362347827467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 16:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362348099668-72</Id><Topic><Title>The BA BATTERY flamethrower</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587230282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not an elegant solution.</Msg><Username>fmrdownestr</Username><Timestamp>1362348099668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 17:01:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362348897673-73</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alex Jones the President of Gun Owners of America and The Moter City Madman ripped him a new #$%$...and EASILY...always happens when you have th estatistics and the truth on your side</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362348897673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 17:14:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362349070160-74</Id><Topic><Title>47% Of Americans Support Incompetent Wannabe Dictator</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362329030044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:43:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"47% Of Americans Support Incompetent Wannabe Dictator"...but 55 percent of the voting machines support the Dictator too....its not who votes that matters...its who COUNTS the votes</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362349070160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 17:17:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362350722953-75</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you find significant about his ratings?? I mean, you get way more thumbs down than thumbs up, and it nas no noticeable effect on your spouting lunacy.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362350722953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 17:45:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362354263863-76</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even Dwight Yoakam ripped him a new one............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362354263863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 18:44:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362354360488-77</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lose again, grabber wannabe. You may find China more to your liking,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1362354360488</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 18:46:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362355837539-78</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More appropriately, google "Sparty weirdo conspiracy theorist freak Orly Taitz insane kook Holocaust Denier" and take note of the 1,627,389,566 hits.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1362355837539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 19:10:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362357647782-79</Id><Topic><Title>SEC SEC orders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman rolesorders vote to split Boeing CEO, chairman roles</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1362193716634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 22:08:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is good for a bump OP</Msg><Username>loftndude2000</Username><Timestamp>1362357647782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 19:40:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362358025909-80</Id><Topic><Title>The BA BATTERY flamethrower</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1361587230282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 21:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember Boeing sold their wing technology to Japan ma few years ago. Also for many years Boeing has lobbied for China to have fair trade with the rest of the world and China got it. Now Boeing and Airbus better look out! they will be number One in a few years I beleive.</Msg><Username>loftndude2000</Username><Timestamp>1362358025909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 19:47:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362358353843-81</Id><Topic><Title>47% Of Americans Support Incompetent Wannabe Dictator</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1362329030044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:43:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But just in case, ali lice infested continues to campaign for the R Party. Keep up the good work and we'll be saying "President Clinton" all over agin.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1362358353843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 19:52:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362358793808-82</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when big planes had 4 engines?</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361554988926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:43:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I remeber when 4 engines were the mode. Now the planes are going to a fiber type body.Well atleast Boeing did but soon Airbus will follow</Msg><Username>vnvpenbis</Username><Timestamp>1362358793808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 19:59:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362360708950-83</Id><Topic><Title>Are the Media Waking up to the Fact they Have Been Used as Useful I*D*I*O*T*S ????</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1362066370191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 10:46:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What gives me great hope is the ratings at CNN..they are in the toilet (check out Piers Morgans ratings)...people ARE waking up to the fact that the Mainstream Dinasaur Collaborator Media is like the Vichy French and Bagdad Bob all rolled into one.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362360708950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 20:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362360830856-84</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True but the DIFFERENCE is that the CNN ratings are NOT based on out of work Reporters logging in several times ...are they ...Hmmmmm ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362360830856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 20:33:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362360867721-85</Id><Topic><Title>SEQUESTRATION .. what will happen to BOEING ???</Title><Username>hq_2004</Username><Timestamp>1362344760460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 16:06:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see much of any effect from it this year or next. They may actually get more defense work supporting/upgrading existing pentagon assetts. Their dorne products should see a lot of interest.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1362360867721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 20:34:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362361285835-86</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when big planes had 4 engines?</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361554988926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:43:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the Red Baron had three wings.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1362361285835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 20:41:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362361904650-87</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when big planes had 4 engines?</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1361554988926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-22 12:43:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is also a big difference between internal combustion engines and jet engines. Similar to the difference between a refrigerator and an ice box.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1362361904650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 20:51:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362362054133-88</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA leaders wave the white flag</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1362246005124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 12:40:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phantom.. There is a lesson to be learned for the unions, for the states and for our country of the ongoing challenge for businesses located in non-right-to-work states. If our own government is willing to give a defense contract to a foreign-owned entity over multiple, capable U.S.-owned entities - including one that incumbently held the previous contract - because of pricing, other entities will be focused on pricing too. States that continue to prioritize union ideology over the need to be competitive may end up with no work at all. Case in point: the contract to replace the old issue M4 rifles with the newer M4A1 worth $77M. Colt and Remington bid but lost out to A Belgian government owned company, FN Herstal. Herstal will build the rifles in a non union facility in South Caroline. Colt was going to build them at their union plant in Connecticut and Remington was going to build them at in its union plant in Ilion, N.Y., facility.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1362362054133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 20:54:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362363666196-89</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't seperate a loon from his delusions.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1362363666196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 21:21:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362366250445-90</Id><Topic><Title>Son in-law, how soon we forget, $1.83 when Obamu took office now the son inlaw is going to be happy when the local refineries resume full</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1362267690547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-02 18:41:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gReGtOmdOOfusCHECKN is blissfully unaware that the US is a net petroleum product exporter. Fits the doofus profile perfectly.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1362366250445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 22:04:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362366563672-91</Id><Topic><Title>Cupcakes and Flu Shots for Syria</Title><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1362162559586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-01 13:29:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Neither are the Russians inclined to upset the apple cart of Obama's and the other 47%'s delusion regarding his ("methinks the man doth protest too much") notion of "I am NOT a dictator" - though the opposite is apparently true: 1) this is the most "transparent" administration in history; 2) "I was told not to discuss the (obviously overt) drone program" (Robert Gibbs, former Obama Press Secretary); 3) what we are doing in Libya is a "kinetic action" and does not require Congressional approval; 4) what happened in Benghazi "is the result of a video"; 5) "we do not have a spending problem"; 6) "I will uphold the Constitution of the United States" ..... etc). The Russians, the Iranians, and the North Koreans do not need to do anything. The President and his team are doing it for them.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1362366563672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 22:09:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362366591747-92</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Grabbers are Holocaust Deniers</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1362342190304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 15:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Constitution is everything to me! Why do the President and Politicians feel otherwise? Gun manufacturer will be airlifting weapons and munitions into Colorado before Colorado Democrats enact severe new anti weapons ban. Manufacturer claims this is their America's Berlin Airlift.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1362366591747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 22:09:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362370189779-93</Id><Title>737 Max Plane ?</Title><Msg>Haven't heard much about the new 737 MAX plane that was all the talk, about 2 years ago.I remember the state of washington and the Union were smooching Boeing in keeping the work in that state. Not due for production till 2016 but Boeing is taking sale orders now. Will it be built where?</Msg><Username>vnvpenbis</Username><Timestamp>1362370189779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 23:09:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>