<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-09-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380169090168-1</Id><Topic><Title>Cokie Roberts Nails It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380155686529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 20:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hate to tell you this ali_infesto but she nailed it.....the lady has seen this country and the world and she nailed it.........mark her response and re-read it 3 yrs from this date......some couldn't accept a damn thing from Obama even it he agreed 100% with any of their beliefs strictly because of his background and skin color</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380169090168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:18:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380169301962-2</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus Alabama is hiring while Boeing Washington state is laying off Charleston is a failure so far</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380139338700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 16:02:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing stock has done OK in my book.......can't time everything perfectly but so far, the stock is a big winner this year</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380169301962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380169380565-3</Id><Title>Remember when Obama said he was bipartisan and pay half the debt in 2 years. I know so many lies you have to get ready for the next</Title><Msg>the media use to count the lies. Interesting how the media became his friend. Clinton too, lied to all Americans I did not have relations with that woman. Just a #$%$ while Hillary was in another room in the White House. Then we had Obama verses Larry Sinclair in court of which Larry won and published his book. Obama is a non reciprocation oral sex homosexual. Larry won in the courts then the media turns its back on the truth. Earmarks a Mississippi Senator wants a freeway in California then years later we learn Pelosi had investment property in the same location. Idols of America's Democrap liberals</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380169380565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380169775360-4</Id><Topic><Title>now in 57 days tesla is up 57% boeing not so good still 16% Airbus soaring with airplane orders</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380137770222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:36:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll take that as a no. P.S. I was responding to Elon. Forget to switch ids? LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380169775360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380169821079-5</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Congressman on Ted Cruz: “He’s a fraud”</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380155178994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 20:26:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cruz is a damn good circus barker and that's it........nothing more</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380169821079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380169934959-6</Id><Topic><Title>Airbus Lines Up $15 Billion in Asian Orders, boeing not so good, customers unhappy with chicago management</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380150518453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 19:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please report when Boeing sticks a double digit billion dollar win......it does happen on this side of the street too you know</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380169934959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380169939037-7</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing prepares for a tongue lashing on the 787 from a customer on poor quality 787 dreamfailure outsourcing plane</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1379962400495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-23 14:53:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ooh, we have a board monitor who sets rules for posting. Take that stuff to the 6th grade, you bigot. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380169939037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380169939356-8</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz and Snowden are partriots, Obama shames the country running guns to cartels and al Qaeda and disses the flag for Americans to see</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380157515694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 21:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect once Obama can't hide behind Executive Orders Obama will be going to prison after the longest felony pardon list in our nations history. This hood has used the IRS as his personal execution squad</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380169939356</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380170011495-9</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Obama said he was bipartisan and pay half the debt in 2 years. I know so many lies you have to get ready for the next</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380169380565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all lies</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380170011495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380170111242-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama running guns to the Cartels and al Qaeda Obama's hands runs blood and murder to hide it</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380157066338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 20:57:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see 6 he got hooked up with here on the board.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380170111242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380170150349-11</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz and Snowden are partriots, Obama shames the country running guns to cartels and al Qaeda and disses the flag for Americans to see</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380157515694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 21:05:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turn around and look at the short line of people behind you, lining up if they believe those 2 are patriots.......now look at that long line that wraps around city blocks.......that's the line of people who completely disagree with your assertion</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380170150349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 00:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380174217640-12</Id><Title>shorts get ready</Title><Msg>this is just one of a handful of stocks that I will short on monday</Msg><Username>qqq4422</Username><Timestamp>1380174217640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 01:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380175738884-13</Id><Title>Bernstein Raises BA Valuation to $146</Title><Msg>Per Reuters press release</Msg><Username>vegacolony1</Username><Timestamp>1380175738884</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 02:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380176347726-14</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing prepares for a tongue lashing on the 787 from a customer on poor quality 787 dreamfailure outsourcing plane</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1379962400495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-23 14:53:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile Airbus still scratching its head for two years now on why its wing cracks occur. ROFL</Msg><Username>vegacolony1</Username><Timestamp>1380176347726</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 02:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380188283854-15</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking: Whistleblower Reveals U.S. State Dept. Ships Arms Directly to al-Qaeda</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380148493233</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 18:34:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Raven parrots talking points from loons.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1380188283854</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 05:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380188368477-16</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking: Whistleblower Reveals U.S. State Dept. Ships Arms Directly to al-Qaeda</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380148493233</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 18:34:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares what you find? No run along a go find your Twinkies.............</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1380188368477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 05:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380192177564-17</Id><Topic><Title>LOT 787 issue</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380133309546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 14:21:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where are the "shop travelers" with for example repair instructions in order--if a temporary double inspection of all Dreamliners would stop this then so be it. Boeing Quality Control is failing its task--its getting too much already</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380192177564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380192576624-18</Id><Title>Boeing Quality Quality Assurance is failing on the Dreamliner---if a shake up is necessary so be it</Title><Msg>Sometimes a fresh managment approach is needed as this is going to start affecting order capture. These so called "centers of excellence" need to get going on overtime. Boeing is an important symbol of American engineering and quality. So come on----my bosses would not take this. Sorry. I am long Boeing but this is on everyones mind. Norway had enough and called in Boeing upper managment--good----if that what it takes. They will get hit with liquidated damages if this delivery issue of compliant product continues</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380192576624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380192840208-19</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the quality issues SC or Wash?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1380149823806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 18:57:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing Q.C. needs to really stop this. Double or triple inspections and hold people accountable and back to training. When things calm down, things can go back to normal q.c. level of inspection. I would like to see the "shop traveler" to see if the box was checked off "replacement filtered installed"--if it was signed the employee needs training or if it continues.....fill in the blank</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380192840208</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380192942144-20</Id><Topic><Title>Order builds momentum for the 787-10</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1380109075480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 07:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, first the order is announced then eventually finalized and the order recieved at Boeing when the contract is recieved--not before. Your incorrect</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380192942144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380193078667-21</Id><Topic><Title>Missing low pressure fuel filters!.........really?</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1380133213539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 14:20:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shake up needed in Q.C. sorry. Too many failures. No excuses--this is flight hardware. They should not be demoted but removed from Q.C. this is tarnishing Boeing</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380193078667</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380193114473-22</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Quality Quality Assurance is failing on the Dreamliner---if a shake up is necessary so be it</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380192576624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380193114473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380193211738-23</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Quality Quality Assurance is failing on the Dreamliner---if a shake up is necessary so be it</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380192576624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is upper management?? Does Q.C. report to anyone in Boeing and why are they still at Boeing---this is for stupid stuff that is inexcusable</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380193211738</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 07:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380193371057-24</Id><Topic><Title>Missing low pressure fuel filters!.........really?</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1380133213539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 14:20:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So do I where is the source inspection for these suppliers before they encapsulate with plastic or encase a part that can't be looked at later---those items must be bought off before further assembly--this is 101 stuff--once again long on Boeing but getting concerned plus</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380193371057</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 07:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380193975166-25</Id><Topic><Title>Cokie Roberts Nails It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380155686529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 20:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doc - If Roberts said what you wrote THE WAY THAT YOU WROTE IT, I would agree but that is not what she said. You are either missing her error or you don't want to accept that her statement THE WAY SHE SAID IT, IS NOT LOGICAL NOR PLAUSIBLE. Reread exactly what she said. She's an old lady and her mind is probably not as sharp as it once was.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380193975166</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 07:12:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380195262290-26</Id><Title>7th Graders suspended for playing with TOY Gun...AT HOME</Title><Msg>Last week, in the wake of the Navy Yard shooting in Washington DC, we predicted that we’d see another wave of knee jerk overreactions to anyone doing anything with any object that even remotely looks like a gun – sadly we were right. The latest incident occurred in Virginia, where a seventh grader and his friend have been suspended from school for playing with a toy gun, in the boy’s own front yard, outside of school hours. WAVY-TV reports that while waiting for the school bus, the boys were fooling around with an airsoft replica handgun, shooting plastic pellets at a target attached to a tree, with a safety net rigged up to catch any off target pellets. A neighbor saw them and called in a complaint to police. The caller even acknowledged that the gun wasn’t real, telling the 911 dispatcher “This is not a real one, but it makes people uncomfortable. I know that it makes me (uncomfortable), as a mom, to see a boy pointing a gun.”</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380195262290</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 07:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380195380505-27</Id><Title>UN Treaty and Fast &amp; Furious —Tools of Gun Control</Title><Msg>It was just a few days ago that Henry Porter of the London Observer said: This has reached the point where it has ceased to be a domestic issue. The world cannot stand idly by. The UN has been working for a long time on tactics to disarm and control Americans. The purpose of the UN Arms Trade Treaty (UN-ATT) is to regulate the transfer of guns. That obviously requires that all guns be registered and tracked by governments — which is really about registering and tracking gun owners. To get the ATT ratified, a watered down version is offered as a Trojan Horse with just a passing reference to “small arms”. Once it’s ratified, it can easily be changed and expanded with only 75% of UN countries voting for changes. That won’t be difficult considering it passed nearly unanimously, with only 3 countries (Iran, Syria and North Korea) voting against. FALSE FLAGS &amp; PUBLIC OPINION The history of the UN-ATT is intertwined with false flags. Fast &amp; Furious was supposed to lay the groundwork to scare the public about arms crossing the border. Even the NY Times pointed out that the purpose of our government shipping guns to Mexico in the “Gunwalker” programs was to scare the public about arms moving across borders and get the public to cry out for protection. And the UN-ATT was the legislation they had already prepared to offer as a solution. The UN-ATT was originally scheduled for a vote last July. But Fast &amp; Furious had been exposed and was in full blown controversy because the GOP wanted to use it for political gain — not because they wanted to end the BATF abuses or send anyone to jail for criminal behavior. The “Gunwalker” programs had been run under Bush prior to Obama. Exactly one week before the UN was to vote on the UN-ATT, the Aurora, CO shooting was staged to try to energize gun control, take away attention from Fast &amp; Furious and get American public opinion to support UN-ATT passage.</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380195380505</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 07:36:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380195618932-28</Id><Title>List of typical Tweets on exploding Obamacare costs</Title><Msg>Get the picture? I had to stop there because this webpage simply couldn’t handle the amount of tweets that were coming in. My Twitter account is now completely overloaded with people complaining about soaring Obamacare costs. Where are the “millions of Americans” who can now afford health insurance thanks to Obamacare, according to Kathleen Sebelius? I am struggling to find any. Here’s a collection of comments from a Facebook thread in response to the question, “Will your costs be increasing or decreasing under Obamacare?” “Mine have already increased.” “Mine has significantly increased.” “INCREASING!! PLUS I ALREADY GOT DROPPED FROM MY DOCTOR!!” “Mine’s going up 65% I have no choice but to completely drop it.” “Already have increased by about 200%.” “Increasing for sure.” “Increasing at my work.” “My boss is eating the costs. Def increasing.” “Catastrophic increases!!” “Everyday reports are coming in and telling a grim picture. Costs are going up. My son, who is single, will be $300 per month poorer. Thanks Obama.” “Mine doubled.” “Speaking as someone working in the health insurance industry, i can verify that this year alone premiums have skyrocketed – and because of the “affordable care” act.” “Increasing..no to obamacare.” “Already went up! Just what we needed.” “Increasing by at least $7,000 per year on average.” “Per my employer they are doubling.” Out of hundreds of responses, barely a handful said their costs would be decreasing. A generous estimate would be that around 1% of respondents said their costs would drop thanks to Obamacare. So while the media is busy parroting the claim that Obamacare costs are largely dependent on where you live, the overwhelming consensus from Americans who live all over the country is that the new regulations are not “affordable” at all but in fact a huge financial burden</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380195618932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 07:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380198203705-29</Id><Title>LOT 787 issue.........................</Title><Msg>Seems to me like GE built those engines not Boeing</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380198203705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 08:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380201761899-30</Id><Topic><Title>Citigroup Raises PT on The Boeing Company</Title><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1380161016961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 22:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I`m a Big Buyer..........I see $150.00 in the next two years. Go Boeing</Msg><Username>thesilverarrowflies</Username><Timestamp>1380201761899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 09:22:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380202807055-31</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Quality Quality Assurance is failing on the Dreamliner---if a shake up is necessary so be it</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380192576624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Upper management is detached from the actual operations. They spend their time in Chicago or Washington DC, pushing paper and lobbying the government. The commercial aircraft division got fat and lazy living off the cash flows of the 777 and 737 programs. The levers in their business were jockying with the unions and lobbying for more and more support for ExIm loans to 3rd world customers. In the mean time, they forgot how design new airplanes. The company is now run not by engineers but by MBAs, lawyers, and lobbyists. Graduate degrees in finger painting would be as relevant to their jobs. Boeing coasted for decades on legacy programs, now they will suffer for decades for lack of stewardship. Strong buy</Msg><Username>ba_hard_landing</Username><Timestamp>1380202807055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 09:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380203479957-32</Id><Topic><Title>List of typical Tweets on exploding Obamacare costs</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380195618932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 07:40:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing has put the screws to employee health care costs. 100% is now 80%, deductable doubled, copays doubled and higher for specialists</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380203479957</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 09:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380203690205-33</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking: Whistleblower Reveals U.S. State Dept. Ships Arms Directly to al-Qaeda</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380148493233</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 18:34:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He quotes a source and you attack the messenger. So you are not interested in facts. A very stupid person</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380203690205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 09:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380203748438-34</Id><Topic><Title>LOT 787 issue.........................</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380198203705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 08:23:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All LOT planes are fitted with RR Trent 1000 engines, But the point is valid unless the filters were removed by boeing and then not replaced as claimed by another poster. We will have to wait and see what the investigation reveals.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380203748438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 09:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380203853850-35</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing prepares for a tongue lashing on the 787 from a customer on poor quality 787 dreamfailure outsourcing plane</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1379962400495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-09-23 14:53:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The A380 wing cracks were serious, embarrassing, and more difficult to fix than originally anticipated. But the cause was found, existing aircraft were retrofitted, new builds incorporated the re-design, and the problem did not recur. Boeing never gave a satisfactory answer for why that 787 had an inflight electrical fire that nearly crashed the plane in November 2010. They built "superboxes" around the batteries, which should contain any future battery fires, but never explained why those fires happened when they had claimed such a failure mode was impossible. And despite the widely reported story that the Honeywell ELT was responsible for the Queen of Sheba fire, that investigation is ongoing. Strong buy</Msg><Username>ba_hard_landing</Username><Timestamp>1380203853850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 09:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380204037295-36</Id><Topic><Title>LOT 787 issue.........................</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380198203705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 08:23:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I contend that most of the squawks on the 787 are due to the airlines themselves. The maintenance personnel are so incompetant they cant maintain an oxcart or the airline itself has exterior motives for throwing the proverbial monkey wrench into the deal to get consessions from Boeing. That goes for the battery problem also</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380204037295</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380204323805-37</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Quality Quality Assurance is failing on the Dreamliner---if a shake up is necessary so be it</Title><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380192576624</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 06:49:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The issue needs resolution but first we need to know if the filters were originally installed in the RR Trent 1000 engines and then removed (and not replaced) by BA mechanics or they were missing when received from Rolls Royce. Then BA can take the appropriate action to fix the issue. If RR shipped the engines withut the filters, they own a large piece of the liability.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380204323805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380204473442-38</Id><Title>liberals are stupid</Title><Msg>A guy posts a source of facts and a lib attacks the messenger with insults. So facts for a liberal means nothing. Libs live in a land of lies, race, hate and rage.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380204473442</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380205261688-39</Id><Title>Obama said he was going to cut the debt 1/2 in two years 2008 to 2010</Title><Msg>But in truth he has doubled it and wishes to triple it. He is not only a liar but a big liar.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380205261688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380205918743-40</Id><Title>Deliveries</Title><Msg>As of 9-25, BA has delivered 44 planes. Airbus has delivered 33. 5 days to go till End of Month/Quarter.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380205918743</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380206182906-41</Id><Title>Ted Cruz is proof the GOP is the Party of Idiots !</Title><Msg>the Ted Cruz fraudabuster has become a moment of truth. No one in their right mind thinks that speech was anything other than a colossal humiliation of not only the speech-giver, but of the party he purports to represent. It is not every day that the troll under the bridge broaches the broad daylight and sprays his derangement into the air for all to see and hear, but there was Ted with his bare face hanging out, giving a clinic on just how preposterous the modern Republican Party has allowed itself to become.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380206182906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>19</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380206618043-42</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thou reprints right-wing lies daily and is calling me a plagiarizer.... ha ha ha</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380206618043</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380207024981-43</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Committing Suicide !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379707421629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 16:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if that's true... they're not very good at it</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380207024981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380207202803-44</Id><Topic><Title>liberals are stupid</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380204473442</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:07:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahhh poor me! Greg you should know more than anybody about attacks with insults it`s about all you can do. your post is nothing but the same thing you are whining about lmao are you not even smart enough to see that?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1380207202803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380207310536-45</Id><Topic><Title>LOT 787 issue.........................</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380198203705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 08:23:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are RR not GE. Boeing assumes responsibility for the mechanical condition of the engines when they are installed, checked out and flight tested</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380207310536</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380207458334-46</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Committing Suicide !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379707421629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 16:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup... Fear mongers fueling their impotent flock ...</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380207458334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380207679452-47</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Committing Suicide !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379707421629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 16:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now that the GOP is going to become defunct you will be free to consider joining the NSDAP- maybe even get the svastika back eh doubledumbsass</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380207679452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380207774828-48</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Committing Suicide !!</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1379707421629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-09-20 16:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you and your fellow zombies have had your chance and you blew it- next the GOP goes extinct and all you troglodytes will have to start over again-- hopefully on another planet</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380207774828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380207854845-49</Id><Topic><Title>LOT 787 issue.........................</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380198203705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 08:23:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>after delivery too?</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380207854845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380208075866-50</Id><Topic><Title>shorts get ready</Title><Username>qqq4422</Username><Timestamp>1380174217640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 01:43:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lots of luck....u will need it bad!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1380208075866</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:07:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380208521372-51</Id><Topic><Title>LOT 787 issue.........................</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380198203705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 08:23:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Certainly the carriers themselves are responsible for maintenance. An it's unfortunate for Boeing if some sloppy carrier with lousy maintenance makes the whole program look bad. But many of the 787 problems have been with brand new planes. Those Norwegian planes are two of the newest in service, and the JAL fire in Boston was on a plane that had been delivered just a few weeks before. For brand new planes to have so many problems is a design issue or a manufacturing issue, not maintenance. And we can benchmark against other programs. How many fires have there been inside a 767 or 777? How many of those aircraft have been written off due to damage (not related to pilot error or terrorism)? The 787 looks terrible in comparison. Strong buy</Msg><Username>ba_hard_landing</Username><Timestamp>1380208521372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380208895529-52</Id><Topic><Title>LOT 787 issue.........................</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1380198203705</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 08:23:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up to the first maintenance cycle which is where they found out about missing filters. That forced them to check out the rest of the fleet. This is embarrassing and needs to be rectified ASAP.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380208895529</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380210207431-53</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dr. Seuss was a writer and poet most widely known for children's picture books. Yes, sick.man's poetry is geared for his target market intellectual level. Now, Spartacus's Raven is a true board classic.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1380210207431</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380210288150-54</Id><Title>The Lessons of Romneycare</Title><Msg>So let’s look at the polls for Romneycare, the Massachusetts health-care law and model for Obamacare. What do the Bay State polls say? When it went into effect seven years ago, polls showed a skeptical, if not hostile, view of Romneycare. Now you couldn’t pull the health plan out of the people’s cold dead hands. The latest Massachusetts Medical Society poll has 84 percent of state residents happy with their health coverage, versus national polls showing only 67 percent of Americans so content. Like Obamacare, the Massachusetts plan caused some confusion at first. Kinks needed to be ironed out and were. Forgive this brief foray into policy. Warnings that Romneycare would lead Massachusetts businesses to drop their workers’ coverage did not come to pass. On the contrary, employers offering insurance rose to 76 percent, from 70 percent before the reforms. Obamacare is more fiscally conservative than was the original Romneycare. It does more to control costs. For example, Obamacare proposes bundling payments for a medical condition. That basically means one check is written to cover soup-to-nuts treatment for an ailment, such as a broken foot. That removes incentives to order more X-rays, office visits or other care not needed. And it rewards providers who do a good job the first time around. Massachusetts offers subsidies to those earning less than 300 percent of the federal poverty level. In this, the federal government is more generous, starting subsidies at 400 percent of the poverty marker. The fiscally conservative Massachusetts Taxpayers Foundation praises Romneycare. The program’s sharpest critics, the group says, are from out of state or single-payer advocates on the left.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380210288150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380210370902-55</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're FOS. I provide data and sources for my comments. I gave you the Harvard study on gun control for instance. You have no fact based rebuttalsto anyone that disafgrees with you on this board and you make up a lie about me to protect your ego. The only person who believes you on this board is you.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380210370902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380210748669-56</Id><Topic><Title>Cokie Roberts Nails It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380155686529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 20:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then again maybe she is trying to get her own program on the OWN channel.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1380210748669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380210790668-57</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stick_putz is upset I pointed out that he did not write the poem. Instead of giving credit to the true author he uses a technique known as "deflecting" in order to avoid admitting that he plagiarized (gave no credit to the person who actually wrote it). You notice he did not refute my claim and say that he was the one who wrote the poem though.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380210790668</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380211125010-58</Id><Title>ACAD up 909% in past 12 months new 52 week high BA 787 not so good ,</Title><Msg>ACAD rose 3.57% to a new 52 week high of $25.55. During the last 52 weeks, ACAD's price has ranged from $1.80 on November 15, 2012 to today's high of $25.55. Additionally, over the last 12 months, ACAD has increased 909.88% while its peers in the Biotechnology industry increased 55.59%.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380211125010</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380211304238-59</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the quality issues SC or Wash?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1380149823806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 18:57:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need to wait till the investigation finds the facts. Adding more QC checks was abandoned by the auto industry some time ago. They made the hands on workers responsible for thier work. Too many times things were not done correctly/completely because workers felt It was ok because QC will catch it before it ships. They started making the workers check themselves/each other.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380211304238</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:01:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380211824928-60</Id><Topic><Title>The Lessons of Romneycare</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380210288150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I strongly disagree. My healthcare costs increased 15% a year each year here in Mass.. Blue cross. Glad I was finally eligible for medicare or I would have been in real difficulty. Even then I had to switch from Medex gold to Medex Bronze and still every year it goes higher.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380211824928</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380211838037-61</Id><Title>seems to me you are in the wrong stock</Title><Msg>for the second day in a row elon's reached a new 52 week high why are you arguing about a lot 787 ground crew being responsible for a new 5- new 787 not working that is silly father is a very poor con artist elon's stock is now up is now up 575 percent over twelve months and boeing is not very simple you are in the wrong stock airbus beats boeing too.</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380211838037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380212109913-62</Id><Topic><Title>7th Graders suspended for playing with TOY Gun...AT HOME</Title><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380195262290</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 07:34:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who wrote this whiny philippic? Surely YOU didn't</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380212109913</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380212231078-63</Id><Topic><Title>The Lessons of Romneycare</Title><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1380210288150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 11:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One huge problem is that you can not be a part of it, and wait till you get sick, then join which is why we don't have 100% of the people covered.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1380212231078</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380212352413-64</Id><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Msg>Boeing Trails Airbus In The Race For New Commercial Airplane Orders By Trefis, September 12, 2013, 02:12:43 PM EDT Boeing ( BA ) is trailing its European rival, Airbus, in new commercial airplane orders in the year-to-date period. Through August, Boeing received orders for 786 commercial airplanes compared to 902 received by Airbus. Airbus SAS booked sales valued at more than $15 billion on a single day from Asia, underscoring the region’s role in driving global demand for commercial jets. The deals, once confirmed, will bring Airbus beyond the 1,000 aircraft orders the company has predicted it can garner this year. In the first eight months, Airbus had already secured 942 firm orders, with Lion Air Inc.’s purchase of 234 jets in 2013.</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380212581741-65</Id><Title>777</Title><Msg>The air cargo business is not flourishing, but that isn’t stopping Lufthansa Cargo from upgrading its cargo fleet in the Trans-Atlantic, where it will bring in new Boeing 777 freighters starting in November.The carrier will begin operating the 777F in November on trans-Atlantic routes from Frankfurt to Atlanta, Chicago and Newark. It will take delivery of two aircraft this year, two in 2014 and one in 2015. List price is $270 million; major airlines pay generally pay about half of list price, analysts say.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380212581741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380212963162-66</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Qatar and Lan 787's are flying again today out of Charleston (9-26)</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380212963162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380213328243-67</Id><Title>wednesday DOD contracts</Title><Msg>Textron's joint venture with Boeing, known as the Bell-Boeing Joint Project Office, won contracts for: •$20.5 million: a delivery order to upgrade 15 Marine Corps and 8 Air Force V-22 Osprey tiltrotor aircraft training devices to the MV-22 Block C2.02, and CV-22 Block 20.2.01 configurations, respectively. This work is to be completed by September 2016. •$9.5 million: a modification to a previously issued delivery order from the U.S. Marine Corps, instructing the company to perform non-recurring engineering and flight test aircraft modifications to incorporate the Joint Allied Threat Awareness System and APR-39D(V)2 radar warning receivers into MV-22 Osprey tiltrotor aircraft by March 2016.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380213328243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380213690920-68</Id><Topic><Title>777</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380212581741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:23:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact that it is not flourishing is all the more reason to become more fuel efficient, for now and into the future.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380213690920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380213754863-69</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do we suspect these planes are under modification or rework?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380213754863</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380214161783-70</Id><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in stock price gain for the day, year and over time 155% to 78%</Title><Msg>for 3 years Airbus stock betters Boeing gaining 155% Boeing still at 78% source; CNN money stock chart which calculates from the entry day(now) going back , for year to date Airbus betters Boeing 60% to 58% and today Airbus betters .71% Boeing up .59% as of right now</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380214161783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380214563601-71</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>easy to understand Airbus has more airplane orders and makes more profit per plane, Airbus stock betters Boeing the fact that the huge cost and investment in the Boeing 787 is not working as planned due to outsourcing and you have Boeing, a plane maker in long term trouble Boeing is not a good investment over time Airbus is up 155% in 3 years Boeing is up 78%.</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380214563601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380215025569-72</Id><Title>over 17 % gain on this stock in little over a month with no pullback</Title><Msg>wow</Msg><Username>cshupirate86</Username><Timestamp>1380215025569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 13:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380215186432-73</Id><Topic><Title>over 17 % gain on this stock in little over a month with no pullback</Title><Username>cshupirate86</Username><Timestamp>1380215025569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 13:03:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Join the party and get long baby. Get in!</Msg><Username>cunyhound</Username><Timestamp>1380215186432</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 13:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380217199912-74</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Artists copy each others' work and steal each others' ideas all the time. Cruz probably didn't announce the author's name when he read the poem, either.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380217199912</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 13:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380217402769-75</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, they are recent production and have no known rework issues.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380217402769</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 13:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380217530678-76</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. Do you know if they repaired or brought home the jet that had the fire issue?</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380217530678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 13:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380219581089-77</Id><Topic><Title>Cokie Roberts Nails It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380155686529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 20:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think that all of the painfully obvious lies and wildly stupid policy decisions and his lack of being held responsible for any of his many failures and crimes might account for some of the anger against the failure-in-chief. Oh yes, I almost forgot. It's very irritating that he plays the race card every opportunity that comes along. That's not helping to bring us all together. LMAO. What a joke this creepy guy, and the blind media hacks that follow him are.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1380219581089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 14:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380220147191-78</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is Sparty's "customizing" of Edgar Allen Poe's poem any different from stick man's alteration of Theodor Geisel's work? Your whine wouldn't be politically motivated at all, would it, vinoveritas?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380220147191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 14:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380220397589-79</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not plagiarism since he used different words in every line. If he adopted Theodor Geisel's style, that's not plagiarism (in this case, it's genius -- though not quite at the level of my adaptation of the Supremes' "Love Child" lyric to the Supreme Court selecting Boxarox to be our president :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380220397589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 14:33:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380220423127-80</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy there, sonny. You don't have to campaign this hard quite yet. Hillary will benefit from your blather, but it's not necessary for a little while. Carry on.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1380220423127</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 14:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380221165142-81</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's hard to sit comfortably at his keyboard when one's so badly chapped where he is.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380221165142</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 14:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380221578008-82</Id><Topic><Title>over 17 % gain on this stock in little over a month with no pullback</Title><Username>cshupirate86</Username><Timestamp>1380215025569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 13:03:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zacks has this at HOLD so they expect a pull back. I have stayed the course and expect to add huge on the pull back...more on UNP. Awaiting the fall. Dems are selling out the next two generations on the debt. Remember when Obama said he would pay back half the debt in two years?</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380221578008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 14:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380221729860-83</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you mean the plane that had the fire caused by the emergency transponder, I have no idea. I will see what I can find out.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380221729860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 14:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380221751877-84</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The rules and legalities of plagiarism are not what most think. They are more in regard to ill gotten gain, like getting a grade or degree or earning a paycheck, or winning an award.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380221751877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 14:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380222202946-85</Id><Title>why isn't Obamacare good enough for Obama, Congress or Federal workers?</Title><Msg>Then how can a guy making $10.50 per hour afford $144.00 a month for Obamacare. Nobody ever explains why. Why is corporate America on part time to avoid it. Its like Obama is trying to fool Americans</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1380222202946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380222628960-86</Id><Title>elon one year ago and boeing today and facts</Title><Msg>One year ago, Tesla (NASDAQ:TSLA) Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk told Fox News that there was a “tsunami of hurt coming for those holding a short position“ on the company’s stock. (up in the year 584% for 12 months) On September 13, 2012, the day his interview aired, shares of the electric vehicle maker’s stock closed at $28.28.Compare with Boeing CEO James McNerney who has missed each of his 7 predictions about Boeing 787 meeting deadlines , the failed 787 Dreamliner earned the nickname “7-Late-7” for three years of delays in entering commercial service. The razzing may continue into the customer failure future from the production delay past, so far many complaints LOT ANA, Norwegian Air , and other customers have serious concerns with Boeing’s 787 . That is why a investor goes with a proven winner Elon Musk , executive in charge of the successful PayPal , now tesla . James McNerney a oracle of failure, so far shown the door at GE, , and now Boeing not so good. Failure of the outsourcing MD production business model, continues with service issues . .. TSLA stock gain for three years 813% ,Airbus 155%. Boeing 78% Good stocks and good leaders make more money Boeing, pumped by con artists results in a huge opportunity cost loss.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380222628960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380222709113-87</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's the one I mean. And thanks.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380222709113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380222930198-88</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz is proof the GOP is the Party of Idiots !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380206182906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:36:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cruz may qualify as an unexpected ally</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380222930198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380223534962-89</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Ethiopian 787 that burned at Heathrow in July, LN 44 &amp;registration ET-AOP, is still there. The investigation is still underway, and repairs will not commence until that is complete.</Msg><Username>ba_hard_landing</Username><Timestamp>1380223534962</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380224136791-90</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes sense. Thanks to you, too.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380224136791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380224441794-91</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True, alb -- but I have to point out that the criteria for "gains" is the fuzziest of the conditions. One could plagiarize for all the "gains" you mentioned, but also for ESTEEM, real or imagined, within his circle. That's why communicators, for one, pay more attention to the exact form -- the words used in the order used. If you google "fair comment" you may come across the definition of the precise number of words copy-protected by someone else that a person can use without being accused of copyright violation. I know copyright and plagiarism are two different subjects, but copyright violation can carry monetary punishments, and plagiarism mainly costs one lower esteem.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380224441794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380224605094-92</Id><Topic><Title>elon one year ago and boeing today and facts</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380222628960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"TSLA stock gain for three years 813%" But you (your alter ego Fred) said you didn't buy TSLA 3 years ago. Ain't hindsight great. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380224605094</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380224805267-93</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I expect they will repair that 787, and I expect it will fly again. I do not expect that plane to ever re-enter commercial service. I believe the fate will be similar to that of ZA002. That plane was built for ANA and was on a test flight in November 2010 when a serious electrical fire broke out and the plane nearly crashed. That fire was not identified as battery-related, though it started in an electrical bay immediately adjacent the aft battery rack. Boeing repaired the plane and tried to get ANA to accept it. But ANA did not want a damaged aircraft, saying you could never be sure repairs are sufficient for a plane that has such delicate electrical systems and had suffered a serious fire. Boeing quietly put ZA001 in storage. The cost of the plane was absorbed into the program accounting, meaning that loss will not be appear on the income statement until some big program charge comes, maybe not until years from now.</Msg><Username>ba_hard_landing</Username><Timestamp>1380224805267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380224825995-94</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good explanation. May I add this: A person can even plagiarize himself. I have read books of the same genre and noticed identical descriptions for paragraphs or even pages only to learn they are just different noms des plumes for the same person. The problem arises when some of the copyrights have been sold, and some have not. Sometimes songwriters trip themselves up on that one.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380224825995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:47:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380225088495-95</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have heard that. I also seem to remember that Stephen Ambrose was accused of plagiarism (not copyright violation?), but I am not sure of the particulars (I don't trust the source I found in a quick Google search) and I don't know the outcome. Anyway, thanks again for injecting a bit of rational discussion into the various conversations here.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380225088495</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380225271100-96</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380225271100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380225405200-97</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I need to refresh on that but Ambrose used a GI's story from his letters or diary in one of his latest books without permission or payment to the family. I may have twisted it a little, but it was something to that affect.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380225405200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380225419703-98</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz is proof the GOP is the Party of Idiots !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380206182906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:36:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hpe, for the sake of the country, the Ted Cruzes run the country, and they had better here soon. Communism doesn't work for the folks.</Msg><Username>doublehaul32</Username><Timestamp>1380225419703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:56:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380226222967-99</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz is proof the GOP is the Party of Idiots !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380206182906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:36:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't beat around the "Bush," stick. DO YOU LIKE CRUZ, OR DON'T YOU ???</Msg><Username>capn_trade</Username><Timestamp>1380226222967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 16:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380226517626-100</Id><Topic><Title>seems to me you are in the wrong stock</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380211838037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't think Elon Musk was into drugs. Any proof? LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380226517626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 16:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380227195012-101</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ZA002 or ZA001? You list both in your post,</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380227195012</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 16:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380228189331-102</Id><Title>more contracts</Title><Msg>Boeing won four contracts from the U.S. Department of Defense (DoD) on Sep 25, 2013 with a total value of $118.6 million. Per the first contract, worth $57.4 million, Boeing achieved a delivery order under a previously awarded performance based logistics contract to supply various parts required for the repair of the AV-8 aircraft for the Navy. Work on this contract will be performed in St. Louis, Mo. with deliveries scheduled to be completed by Sep 30, 2014. The second contract calls for Boeing to perform non-recurring engineering, fabrication, inspection, and testing work on 10 pre-production Operational Test Program Sets to be used on the EA-18G Growler electronic warfare aircraft. With a value of $41.8 million, this contract is a cost-plus-fixed-fee delivery order that runs through Aug 2018. Work on this contract will be performed in St. Louis, Mo. The next contract, worth $9.7 million, is a cost-plus-fixed-fee delivery order to provide the necessary services to assess and dispose of non-avionics systems on the T-45 Subsystems Service Life Assessment Program. This would ensure that the T-45 Goshawk training jet planes remain operational through their expected life expectancy of 2035. This operation should be completed by July 2016. Lastly, Boeing achieved an approximately $9.7 million contract to supply 100 additional composite horizontal stabilators (CHS) and one tool string to the U.S. Army. This is a firm-fixed-price, non-option-eligible, non-multi-year modification contract.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380228189331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 16:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380230327165-103</Id><Topic><Title>charleston</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380125834366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They can either become test beds for future upgrades or become the first 787 cargo planes for lease. Even a loser can serve as an example. There are a million ways to account for it.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1380230327165</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 17:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380231770129-104</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Artist???? ROTFLMAO If Stick _putz is an artist, his artistry is limited to finger painting.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380231770129</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 17:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380232103181-105</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you plagiarizing my use of the word "putz" ???</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380232103181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 17:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380232719112-106</Id><Title>Does the BA board strap hanger......</Title><Msg>have a life? Or, is he just another REMF, horse holding, putz?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1380232719112</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 17:58:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380234388045-107</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz is proof the GOP is the Party of Idiots !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380206182906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:36:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just be thankful that Boeing isn't owned by a bunch of defense contractor hating liberals.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1380234388045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380235307109-108</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare Will Be Hugely Popular and There's Little the GOP Can Do to Stop It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380235247415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:40:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Most of that stuff is largely irrelevant or completely incidental to the core premises of the Affordable Care Act,” Redhead said, adding that many of those projects were added by individual members for their home districts. “The ACA is like the Bible. Calling it a law is like calling the Bible a book. You have lots of books in the Bible, including stuff on the Old Testament that no one ever looks at.” The heart of the ACA concerns a handful of core ideas about restructuring private health insurance markets, he said. There’s the creation and introduction of new government-run exchanges where individuals can buy insurance, where in the past they would be denied coverage or have had to pay higher rates. There is the coverage mandate, or requirement that every adult have health insurance. There also is the expansion of Medicaid to give lower-income people access to subsidized insurance. There also are new pathways to access care, such as community clinics and other patient-centered options. When Washington insiders look at the many ways the Obama administration has moved money around to implement the cornerstones of the ACA, they see an executive branch that has not been detered by GOP protests, Redhead said. Some of his colleagues say the administration has taken too many liberties, he said; however, those kinds of administrative acrobatics are nothing new in government. As has been the case in every budget fight since Obamacare passed, the Republican-led House hasn’t gotten anywhere with defunding or repealing it, as CRS reports note in detail. Moreover, the U.S. Supreme Court has upheld it, although they did say states not implementing the expansion of Medicaid would not be penalized. That means Americans will soon see what Obamacare is about and what impact it has in their lives, regardless of the GOP’s continuing noise about crippling or killing the law.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380235307109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:41:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380236192982-109</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare Will Be Hugely Popular and There's Little the GOP Can Do to Stop It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380235247415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:40:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doubt it ! Obama and minions have been shouting from the roof tops for years (to include campaign promises) that he will offer FREE health care when in office....well guess what ? it aint free and the twenty somethings dont want to sign up and pay $175 a month for the Bronze coverage. Already news reports of people showing up to get their free care as promised and getting violent when they are told to sign up for a plan. Looks like the Libs are going to burn it all down when they find out they were all PUNCKED voting for the liberal messia.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1380236192982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:56:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380236420591-110</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380234707285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:31:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And another: "I guarantee you that a couple of years down the road, when this thing works, they won't call it ObamaCare!" Barack Obama</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380236420591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 19:00:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380237355177-111</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare Will Be Hugely Popular and There's Little the GOP Can Do to Stop It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380235247415</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:40:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come Congress doenst have to have Obamacare ? Too Elite for you "Democrats" ? How come there are so many exemptions to Big Corporations...never mind..AS USUAL you wont offer a respon se to such questions...you WILL however either call me a loon or a racist ... You're so Anti American its sickening</Msg><Username>spartacus13579</Username><Timestamp>1380237355177</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 19:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380237564573-112</Id><Topic><Title>Wendy Davis to run for governor in Texas</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380233635292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:13:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And your point is ? Heck if Hugo Chaves was alive he would also be able to run for Gov of any of the 57 states according to Obama. Does not mean that he stands a chance.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1380237564573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 19:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380241205191-113</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently morons here still don't realize that this poem was posted in the comments section of the New York Times and it was not written by stick_putz</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380241205191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380241282972-114</Id><Title>westjet order</Title><Msg>SEATTLE, Sept. 26, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing (NYSE: BA) and WestJet announced today that they have completed an order for 65 737 MAX airplanes, fulfilling the carrier's letter of intent to purchase the airplanes announced on Aug 29. The order, valued at $6.3 billion at list prices, consists of 40 737 MAX 8s and 25 737 MAX 7s. The airplanes are a key component of the Calgary-based airline's fleet renewal initiative.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380241282972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380241792407-115</Id><Topic><Title>westjet order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380241282972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:21:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>orders for the year are at 834 as of Today. plane specific: "•771 "gross" orders for various flavors of its 737 regional airliner •132 orders for the 787 Dreamliner •44 for the 777 airliner •five 747 orders From this total, Boeing subtracted 104 737s, eight 777s, all five 747s, but just a single 787, for customer cancellations, resulting in a NET of 834 commercial airplanes ordered year to date.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380241792407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380242132210-116</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wrote the song "Yesterday" by myself, though it was credited to Lennon-McCartney. If people reprint the lyrics and do not benefit financially, I really don't care. You do realize this is a yahoo stock message board, don't you?</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1380242132210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380242224211-117</Id><Topic><Title>Wendy Davis to run for governor in Texas</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380233635292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:13:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So could Hitler if he were alive. Wendy Davis is far more attractive ( politically as well ) than both.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1380242224211</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380242965207-118</Id><Topic><Title>westjet order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380241282972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:21:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice....... Gotta Lov it! Bump it for the haters</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1380242965207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380243166649-119</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM!</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1380243166649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380243232317-120</Id><Topic><Title>elon one year ago and boeing today and facts</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380222628960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM!</Msg><Username>duffymagoo</Username><Timestamp>1380243232317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380243800976-121</Id><Title>whats better 63% gain in stock price in 60 days for tesla or in " a lttle more than a month 17% for boeing"</Title><Msg>another poster is stating that in" a little more than a month Boeing stock is up 17%" tht is an oppourtunity lost to a better stock---- July 3 tesla was $115.24 today $188.47 it is gaining more than 1 percent per day over time much better in a year than Boeing . Tesla year to date has gained 457% for 3 years airbus is up 155% and betters Boeing up only 78% for 3 years , try to read the stock chart and make some better gains with better stocks . remember Elon Musk is a serial success paypal and now Tesla, and James McNerney is a serial failure GE and now Boeing ------One year ago, Tesla (NASDAQ:TSLA) Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk told Fox News that there was a “tsunami of hurt coming for those holding a short position“ on the company’s stock. (up in the year 584% for 12 months) On September 13, 2012, the day his interview aired, shares of the electric vehicle maker’s stock closed at $28.28.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380243800976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380244364720-122</Id><Topic><Title>elon one year ago and boeing today and facts</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380222628960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you have a point ? the topic is tesla is up 584% and betters boeing all the way , spartacus99991 you said you did not hold Boeing Tesla or Airbus so that would make you a bigot, you have no reason to be here , you are a angry man , and your comment is more con artist stuff , separate the fact from the reply not going to work Tesla is a better stock remember , spartacus99991 you complimented me on my call on the shoart squeeze which made me 100% in May and now you continue to use a con job in your posts •spartacus99991, you have been a failure at your deceiver approach from day one . spartacus99991 • May 28, 2013 11:30 AM o Yes, TSLA and SCTY are better stocks than BA the last month for making money for traders. Happy now?</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380244364720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380244542193-123</Id><Topic><Title>elon one year ago and boeing today and facts</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380222628960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is the yahoo message board you have no problem with political posters you hate me because I point out that tesla is a better stock than Boeing as is ACAD , you are a bigot, filled with hate for me because I compare stocks that are much better than boeing and point out what you are doing duffymagoo,, if you really cared about making money in the stock market you would be glad to learn how much better tesla and Airbus is than Boeing</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380244542193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380244829328-124</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you know for sure that stick didn't post it there?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1380244829328</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380245030574-125</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the quality issues SC or Wash?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1380149823806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 18:57:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, do not agree. Boeings reputation on what was to be their future bread and butter plane is being affected. Q.C. is the answer. When I worked for various mfg co's when thing like this happened we would go from checking a few parts per hundred per spec. When trouble happened Q.C. had to inspect every piece--not lot(simple parts). At another mfg co that was into space flight EVERY part was 100% inspected by supplier--who provided a few destruct pieces to verify material and then we did 100% inspection. That process, while costly, keep our name and our business and we slowly decreased inspection percentage as the process improved. Its all 6 sigma process control. Never could happen once 6 sigma is Properly used. Once the process is controlled, you literally can't make a bad part easy. Upper and lower control factors have got so tight. Commerical requirements are so different then Defense work which is all I did. We taught over 500 suppliers 6 sigma after hiring about 40 experts to go to our top 500 suppliers--took a few years and now we are world class as far as quality</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380245030574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:23:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380245143064-126</Id><Topic><Title>Wendy Davis to run for governor in Texas</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380233635292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:13:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Point is, there are a lot of #$%$ off women in Texas......start from there</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380245143064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380245302847-127</Id><Topic><Title>whats better 63% gain in stock price in 60 days for tesla or in " a lttle more than a month 17% for boeing"</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380243800976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't give a damn how Boeing compares against other stocks......there are always gonna be some super stars compared to it's performance and also some duds........right now Boeing is doing more than just holding it's own.........go BA.......$135 by years end????</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380245302847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380245330825-128</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>duffymagoo, you are a bigot, if this were a political post you would not care, this is a yahoo message board not a duffymagoo message board----. If you were a neutral stock trader you would want to know that both tesla and airbus are better investments over time than Boeing and make adjustments , you may not own any Boeing Tesla and Airbus stocks stocks like spartacus99991 and cbx have said. duffymagoo, , why are you here and why are you so bigoted about me posting that for the last 3 years tesla and airbus are far better stocks to gain value than Boeing ? I don't care if you post about your stock and remember this is the yahoo message board not the duffymagoo message board.</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380245330825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380245511876-129</Id><Topic><Title>Cokie Roberts Nails It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380155686529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 20:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understood her and yes she's getting up there in years but she's speaking from wisdom as well as intellect ......I can't see or move like I used to but I've seen decades of this country's history.........she called it right</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380245511876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380245606528-130</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave it alone and don't humiliate yourself any further. There is a long history of satire with respect to this type of verse and you clearly do not grasp it. Maybe if it were in Farsi, but . . . you should stick to quoting climate "studies" and other fakery financed by the Koch brothers.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1380245606528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380245643850-131</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz is proof the GOP is the Party of Idiots !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380206182906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 10:36:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not as stupid as you think - they realize they have to distance themselves from the circus barker or suffer the consequences</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380245643850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380246399687-132</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vierzig_nachten you are the scam artist. once more for 3 years tesla stock has gained 815% Airbus stock has gained 155% Boeing only 78% the con man here is you, the source is CNN Money stock chart . most of yoru statement is crapola the type of stuff a person with issues has , just and angry reply in a bigoted manner tot he fact that both tesla and Airbus over three years is a much better investment than boeing, that is what you hate I pick better stock like ACAD and Tesla then compared them with boeing if you were a stock investor you would appreciated the informationa nd the continuing comparison over time and you would have loved my call in may, I made 1005 in tesla in 15 days here is your buddy spartacus9991 congratulating me , what could he do I called it and then pointed it out and I am now continuing with my 55-56-57=58=and now 60 day gains on tesla up 63% in just 60 trade days from july 3 check it out get back to me on this subject try not to stray into you issues personality as a bigot Vierzig_nachten, your message was from a person adept at lying, and consisted of glib self-serving talk</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380246399687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380246468254-133</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1005 should be 100%</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380246468254</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380246562713-134</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>• spartacus99991 • May 28, 2013 11:30 AM Flag o Yes, TSLA and SCTY are better stocks than BA the last month for making money for traders. Happy now</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380246562713</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380246640730-135</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well the third stooge has responded is there a fourth? lol P.S. I was right about the climate you moron and the models are diverging from reality as I explained to you 3 years ago. The exaggerations are extracting a heavy cost as liberals got kicked out of office in Australia and Germany. The German green party has fallen from their peak of 20% of the electorate to only 8% in the election last week. ;-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380246640730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380246771766-136</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you haven't owned TSLA for 3 years. P.S. I assume you know that cnn money is only approximate for the 3 year look-back.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380246771766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380246891944-137</Id><Topic><Title>Wendy Davis to run for governor in Texas</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380233635292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 18:13:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Sir Paul On this topic, the Republicans hate the black guy in the Oval Office so bad that it pollutes even their understanding and context of Dr. Seuss' writings. Perhaps some day you could speak with some of your mover/shaker friends and urge the Republicans to return to sanity.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1380246891944</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380247242125-138</Id><Topic><Title>Cokie Roberts Nails It</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_9115</Username><Timestamp>1380155686529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 20:34:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you still don't see the difference between what she said and what you said and why I agree with you but not her?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1380247242125</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380247257581-139</Id><Topic><Title>elon one year ago and boeing today and facts</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380222628960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 15:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just stated a fact back then (try it sometime without the biased opinions). I'm sorry if you took it as a compliment. It wasn't meant that way.LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380247257581</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380248645516-140</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus99991 reply here and explain yourself !</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380248645516</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380248789511-141</Id><Topic><Title>westjet order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380241282972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:21:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THe Westjet info release came after the order data. If accurate, it is possibe the order number is higher. ie 834 + 65 = 899</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380248789511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:26:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380248947622-142</Id><Topic><Title>whats better 63% gain in stock price in 60 days for tesla or in " a lttle more than a month 17% for boeing"</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380243800976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>docfunknstein,. Once you stubbornly hold onto a underperforming stock compared to better performing stocks---- Tesla Airbus and ACAD,---- you will only cause financial harm to the investor in this case you.-----. In economics, this situation is referred to as opportunity cost. Opportunity cost is defined as the cost of an alternative that must be forgone in order to pursue a certain action, or the benefits that could be received from taking an alternative action. Sounds like you feel awkward about selling Boeing . You feel attached to Boeing and don’t t think Boeing should be sold. then you said, in effect , that you realize that with being attached to Boeing stock while you are not obtaining now for three years as much beneficial gains comparing the Boeing investment with the better investments listed , ----tesla or Airbus or ACAD for the last year . you are in fact stating that the , chances are that if the stock in this case Boeing , trails both Tesla and Airbus and ACAD by 10, 15 or 30, or 800% or 750% percent, there could be problems with the Boeing company stock. , and it may potentially pay to sell and move to a better stock. . However, many of us find it psychologically difficult to admit that we have picked the wrong stock. It’s hard for us to say that we made a mistake. Very often, the longer you hold onto an under-performer, the more money it costs. The reason for this is that the investor could have put his funds into something that actually made money. Therefore, stubbornly holding onto a losing stock will only cause financial harm to the investor. In economics, this situation is referred to as opportunity cost. Opportunity cost is defined as the cost of an alternative that must be forgone in order to pursue a certain action, or the benefits that could be received from taking an alternative action</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380248947622</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380249059172-143</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the quality issues SC or Wash?</Title><Username>wutangbk2</Username><Timestamp>1380149823806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 18:57:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How would a worker check something on inspection equipment which is only in Q.C. ? They are not going to leave the line to check dimensions, plating thickness, electrical tests etc. It's Q.C. How would a worker tell if a starter on a car ,as you mention the auto industry, is per spec??-- check if the insides are assembled correctly and per spec---they can#$%$ done through a source inspection at the supplier. I agree with most of your thoughts falmouth, but on this IMHO you are way off. Workers leaving a line to check if a part is correct??? IF a part makes it to a line it better be per spec or the Q.C. is failing. No more on this issue</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1380249059172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380249174593-144</Id><Title>attention spartacus99991, VN duffy and other bigots Tesla is up in 3 years 815%,Aribus up 155% BA 78%</Title><Msg>stay on topic if you can otherwise you are running in circles and pounding the table and nothing you say will change the facts CNN money stock chart.</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380249174593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380249198062-145</Id><Topic><Title>attention spartacus99991, VN duffy and other bigots Tesla is up in 3 years 815%,Aribus up 155% BA 78%</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380249174593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>airbus should be airbus</Msg><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380249198062</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380251085163-146</Id><Topic><Title>I like green eggs and ham said Sam</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380135636684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-09-25 15:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea and what kinda perv stalks me to NYT and not retrieve the authors name</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1380251085163</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 23:04:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380251301824-147</Id><Topic><Title>whats better 63% gain in stock price in 60 days for tesla or in " a lttle more than a month 17% for boeing"</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380243800976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Therefore, stubbornly holding onto a losing stock will only cause financial harm to the investor. ......." I agree, but I increased my Boeing footprint at the beginning of 2013 and have scraped some gains to the sidelines......I still think BA has some more growth ahead and I am keeping my money where my thoughts are.....that Opportunity Cost you rail upon has been converted into some 2013 cash money profits.....not paper money profits....so I have benefited somewhat from Boeing's stellar performance this year.....I am not smart enough to catch most of the "obvious" rising stars out in the investment world....but I did catch me some</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1380251301824</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 23:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380252105791-148</Id><Topic><Title>whats better 63% gain in stock price in 60 days for tesla or in " a lttle more than a month 17% for boeing"</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380243800976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 21:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>docfunknstein, well a gain in boeing is better than a loss , I do claim being experienced enough to look at Elon Musk record with paypal and his comment about any shorts&amp;he decision to get it. ACAD was a simple study it was the number one rated stock in that sector over a year ago by a lot, maybe that is hard for some investors to figure out it seems not so hard to me. apple was pretty easy to catch too, for about 8 years straight until it went to the typical professional mangers like James mcnerney,they have such a good contract they have no incentive to do a good job. Steve jobs did,he took 1 dollar per year in pay the rest he made in stock gains So that is how I made those decisions the following posters have only bigot comments worthless spartacus99991, cbx mostly,veirig_nacjhien(spelling) duffymagoo,jjovaz a union hater and some time you get responsible posts from foulmouthharbor but his main deal is to promote boeing stock not look at stocks and made the best choice.</Msg><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380252105791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 23:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1380252344123-149</Id><Title>Boeing, stock market</Title><Msg>Any bets on whether there's a general sell off/profit taking tomorrow, ahead of the repubs unning an agreement down to the wire?</Msg><Username>sdietrich</Username><Timestamp>1380252344123</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 23:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380253147169-150</Id><Topic><Title>attention spartacus99991, VN duffy and other bigots Tesla is up in 3 years 815%,Aribus up 155% BA 78%</Title><Username>elonmusk909</Username><Timestamp>1380249174593</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You indicated you didn't own tsla 3 years ago. Might as well post the DOW was 22 in 1930. You probably did not buy it then either. Or maybe you did. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380253147169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 23:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380253530458-151</Id><Topic><Title>westjet order</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1380241282972</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 20:21:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Update on orders.......... The order, valued at $6.3 billion at list prices, consists of 40 737 MAX 8s and 25 737 MAX 7s. The WestJet order continues the momentum of the 737 MAX in the marketplace. The order brings the total number of 737 MAX orders to date to 1,567 airplanes. Bill</Msg><Username>retiredbill</Username><Timestamp>1380253530458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 23:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1380253556182-152</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing trails Airbus in airplane orders for 2013 FMH right !</Title><Username>fred.james48</Username><Timestamp>1380212352413</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 12:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the cnn expert. Try to look it up and see the problem. I'll check back later to see if you've been able to research it. LOL</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1380253556182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-09-26 23:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>