<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369974136670-1</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Majority says IRS attack on Conservitive Groups is breaking the law of the land, the Constitution. Gibson Guitar</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369966972758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:22:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was no attack on the idiot groups funded by the Kochs and other super rich - there was a special investigation which was triggered by the fact that a lot of these groups are income tax evaders and a lot of their members are eventually going to jail. I can just hear the weeping, wailing and gnashing of teeth from the extreme right of the GOP as the penitentiary doors slam shut</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1369974136670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:22:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369974434499-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just to be clear, I am a Democrat. However, It would be helpful to the country if the Republicans followed through with any such changes that returned them to coalition of the reasonable men and women that understood that legislation/politics is a matter of compromise and trade-offs. Previously , they were not a party of acrimony and insult, but rather embodied a somewhat more conservative platform that had its own unique personality/agenda, and a there was far more overlap between the two parties then currently exists. Thus we had a lot more positive legislation that fostered the public good. That to me is the point of politics. To benefit and protect the public. And that is also what is missing with the Tea Bagger mentality. Helping others is bad thing. Whether or not I agreed with the "previous" Republican party, at least I can say they had a lot more integrity and humanity. This vicious name-calling and insulting epithets hurled without discretion at the President and every one else that does not agree with their confused and warped irrational Fox-hole media spins. I hesitate to call what they say, "thought". No president has endured the level of insult that has been heaped upon Obama as well as anyone who supports him. It is as clear to anyone with half a brain what is behind the vast majority of Tea Bagger constituents motivation. They may as well pin Confederate flags on their heads. It's so obvious and it's pathetic that they don't realize that their racial bigotry is shining brightly. But it is not a hatred shared by the vast majority of Americans. They ought to wake up, stop being spoiled brats about losing the election and get it through their thick skulls that the majority of Americans have nothing against blacks and in fact elected a black President. They should hang their heads in shame. They're total misanthropes and they are passé and increasingly irrelevant in American politics. Intelligent Republicans should disassociate from these people ASAP.</Msg><Username>rumi1one</Username><Timestamp>1369974434499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369975346098-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hoozDIK is confident most Americans are as stupid and dependent on crooks within the collective as he is... given the results of the last election, who can argue</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369975346098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369975579685-4</Id><Title>airbus to take the Jet airways of india jet order due to better prices and planes</Title><Msg>rs2ms2ts2ks72 is in the dog house with his significant other, apparently he poured maple syrup all over his body and asked domer if he was ready for a short stack.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369975579685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369975758615-5</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Majority says IRS attack on Conservitive Groups is breaking the law of the land, the Constitution. Gibson Guitar</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369966972758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:22:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumbocrats gave the IRS expanded powers to discriminate and harass, commiecare bureaucrats will similarly discriminate</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369975758615</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369975845347-6</Id><Topic><Title>airbus to take the Jet airways of india jet order due to better prices and planes</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369975579685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:46:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still up spazticus, i mean wayne?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1369975845347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:50:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369975986951-7</Id><Topic><Title>airbus to take the Jet airways of india jet order due to better prices and planes</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369975579685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:46:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apparently the BHT is asleep they have formed a Boeing message board watch group the group called the c-men they monitor the board to advertise for Boeing on strictly BS information . This information like plane orders and potential new plane orders and deliveries that do not account for profit margin , late fees delayed deliveries and grounded 787 planes is important to these c-men. So sorry that is information that does not move the stock up. BTW in the real world, Airbus has made 146% return for owners of Airbus over 5 years while Boeing shareholders are up a pathetic 21%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369975986951</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369985647709-8</Id><Title>Wayne-I'n secure?</Title><Msg>I am not long or short on BA, just cannot figure why you put it down so much and anyone else that doubts your fame of picking winners every day.. Not a trol as you have accused me of when I post facts that are different than your opinions I do believe BA :"might" be a good long term investment for a person who is not going to take on alot of risk. •An insecure person becomes overly selfish. He tries to surround himself with possessions, accolades and attention. •An insecure person becomes overly accommodating and tries to gain other people's approval. •Insecure people tend to be very defensive and cannot handle criticism. They are not comfortable with their own-self. •Insecure people can't enjoy silence and they try to fill it with unnecessary chatter. •Excessive joking is also a mechanism for coping with insecurity. An insecure person craves for other people's attention, which is achieved when other people laugh at their jokes. However, this leads to insensitivity towards others. •Insecure people are self promoting and constantly talk about themselves. They need validation from other people for their actions and qualities. •Insecure people are even threatened by others and therefore by bullying they try to crush their opinion. •Insecure people tent to be overly authoritative as they tend to compensate for their lack of confidence by taking out their frustrations on their subordinates. •Over competitiveness is also a sign of insecurity. They are scared of losing and so they always keep themselves at the edge. •Being materialistic also shows that person is insecure because he feels that by acquiring material wealth and showing it off he will be able to gain people's attention and acknowledgement. •Over jealousy is yet another sign of insecure people as they lack trust in their partners. This is visible in constant questioning, mistrust and altercations with the members of the opposite sex. •Insecure people even become abusive if they fail</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1369985647709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 03:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369986641538-9</Id><Title>Amazing award pace--TUI travel place 6 Billion dollar order for Boeing 737 MAX</Title><Msg>British company TUI places order for 60 737 MAX with option for 90 more. Keep it up</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1369986641538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 03:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369993077631-10</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Majority Says Economy Should Trump Congressional Investigations</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369959531077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 20:18:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody believes your fake polls and BS propaganda posts. Everyone knows you are just a DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1369993077631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 05:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369993168592-11</Id><Topic><Title>Can Any Of You Liberals Tell Us What's Wrong with Communism?</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1369940216039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 14:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you another DFC alias of the BA Board DFC? I bet you are.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1369993168592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 05:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369993303332-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The DFC needs a dumbed down dependent population in order to survive.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1369993303332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 05:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370000196494-13</Id><Title>cbx6cylinder ,a BA troll ! Airbus up 146% over 5 years Boeing up 21% over five years which is better</Title><Msg>by any name if you do not understand that the number 1 maker of passenger planes for the last 11 years, Airbus makes shareholders a lot more money then you are a Boeing troll. Since you claim that I , after the fact took credit for a 100% gain on my March 3 post to buy TSLA , then cbx6cylinder your a Boeing pump and pimp for Boeing you can pretend to not understand as much as you like ! Go ahead pretend , you could have made 100% from May3 to the short squeeze end in 16 days this ended a few days ago . I haste pimps who push Boeing stock to newbys ,the fact is Boeing is a mismanaged company and Airbus is making shareholders a lot more stock value increase and much better dividends . That is what a stock market message board is for , its a blog pointing out the best deals not a advertisement vehicle for you to pump Boeing stock or criticize me for finding better deals. get it now , nope your a pimp or you would not be spewing your form of crapola der !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370000196494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 07:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370000542626-14</Id><Topic><Title>airbus to take the Jet airways of india jet order due to better prices and planes</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1369975579685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 00:46:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored a good name for you , sure I am up now at 440 am pacific time ,looking for the end of the month deals today on riding the big shots backs who need to make their books look good for this month, its easy if you know what to look for . are you asleep now ? I bet you are because your not a stock trader your a hack for Boeing a BHT, no response means I am right you sound asleep just like moe of the 3 stooges getting ready to be a kur all day long</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370000542626</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 07:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370001383671-15</Id><Title>Airbus hikes its order book expectations and dividend Airbus stock beats Boeing for the 5th year in a row</Title><Msg>I am comfortably forecasting that Airbus gross orders will be well above 800 units in 2013," CEO Tom Enders told a shareholders' meeting in Amsterdam.The comments point to potentially robust sales at the Paris Air Show next month, where Airbus will battle arch-rival Boeing . Enders and Denis Ranque, attending his first shareholder meeting as chairman, said EADS would maintain a dividend payout ratio in line with the sector after lifting it to 40 percent Airbus stock has increased 146% over 5 years compared with Boeing up a pathetic 21%. The move for 5 trade days is the same Airbus is up 5.28% for five days compared with Boeing up less than a percent at .79% for five days . "I . With the new Airbus plane on budget and on cost estimates , Airbus stock will make a much greater gain for Airbus shareholders going forward than the stock buyback fake rally for Boeing , it occurred during the 3 month grounding so you know Boeing was manipulating its stock price . Excluding the past 3 months Boeing stock for 5 years would be flat as a pancake . any more troubles with the 787, the 737 max or the 777x will spell even more pathetic stock performance for Boeing .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370001383671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 07:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370002231100-16</Id><Title>WAYNEDICK-FEB ON A RAMPAGE!</Title><Msg>....with nonsense of course...great day for boeing in the horizon...for sure!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1370002231100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370002855655-17</Id><Title>Boeing's fixed price tanker will loose money, read the contract</Title><Msg>Boeing won’t see a profit in the program to build aerial refueling tankers for the U.S. Air Force, Reuters said. And Boeing’s target cost to develop the tanker and deliver an initial 18 by the end of 2017 may run above its target of $3.9 billion. “For every dollar the program costs above target cost of $3.9B, the contractor pays $0.40, until the total amount paid to Boeing reaches $4.9 billion,” at which point Boeing assumes all further costs, the Air Force told Reuters. . Boeing predicted it would have cost overruns above the ceiling of $300 million for the development phase, so remember when a Boeing hack starts pumping the tanker then you need to understand the contract. Boeing was so worried that Airbus A330 would get the deal, remember they wont twice until Uncle Norm, the retired politician and now a Boeing aerospace paid consultant , got the rules changed ! , While Boeing got the contract is was a a give away price to keep Airbus from getting into the air refueling business with the USA military machine, To do that , Boeing gave away the farm and any air tanker profits including spares on the Boeing tanker deal . thanks Boeing the shareholders will fund this plane for free , no money for shareholders</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370002855655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370003206635-18</Id><Title>amazing problem Boeing may miss on the promiss to build the 737MAX deadline like they did on the 787</Title><Msg>just think with outsourcing the 737max the same conditions that caused the 787 miss are still on line to make sure the 737MAX is a failure too !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370003206635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370003673522-19</Id><Title>SBUX, I own that stock sure am glad r2d2 gets up and drinks my company stock</Title><Msg>too bad he does not really wake up Airbus stock value has increased 146% over 5 years and 5.28% over five day , Boeing not so good up a pathetic 21% for five years and only .79 of a percent for 5 days . a little lemon with your Starbux eh rs2ms2ts2ks72 it must be nice to get up in the morning and read that you buy my coffee company stock each time you drink my coffee. Keep supporting Boeing someone out there has too , it might as well be you</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370003673522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370004368789-20</Id><Title>Record unemployment, low inflation underline Europe's pain</Title><Msg>(Reuters) - Unemployment has reached a new high in the euro zone and inflation remains well below the European Central Bank's target, stepping up pressure on EU leaders and the ECB for action to revive the bloc's sickly economy. Joblessness in the 17-nation currency area rose to 12.2 percent in April, EU statistics office Eurostat said on Friday, marking a new record since the data series began in 1995. With the euro zone in its longest recession since its creation in 1999, consumer price inflation was far below the ECB's target of just below 2 percent, coming in at 1.4 percent in May, slightly above April's 1.2 percent rate. That rise may quieten concerns about deflation, but the deepening unemployment crisis is a threat to the social fabric of the euro zone. Almost two-thirds of young Greeks are unable to find work, exemplifying southern Europe's 'lost generation'. Economists and policymakers including Germany's finance minister, Wolfgang Schaeuble, have said the greatest menace to the unity of the euro zone is now social breakdown from the crisis, rather than market-driven factors.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370004368789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370005148671-21</Id><Title>TUI deal , hold on "class 1 transaction, meaning it would require shareholder approval the deal is speculation</Title><Msg>This airplane order is a no win for Boeing first , notice the airline got a huge discount if it is approved, and second they may be playing Boeing against Airbus to try to get a better deal from Airbus. In any event this deal first requires a shareholder approval, so it is nothing at this time . You need to understand the information r2d2!</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370005148671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370005187086-22</Id><Title>Majority of Women and feminine men Sill Supports Obama</Title><Msg>Proving that women and feminine men ______________. Fill in the blank.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370005187086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370005360083-23</Id><Title>Jet Airways of India is going to buy Airbus planes at the paris Airshow while considering Boeing</Title><Msg>r2d2 you say Jet Airways is considering Boeing that is like burping in public, it is rude and smells bad, you are a troll.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370005360083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370005430140-24</Id><Title>MAN I will NEVER sell one share of BOEING$$$</Title><Msg>I'm retiring with this Company's stock$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1370005430140</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370005569174-25</Id><Title>Is Valerie Jarrett Running the WH and the Country......</Title><Msg>......while Obama campaigns and raises money for corrupt politicians?</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370005569174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370005581304-26</Id><Topic><Title>Jet Airways of India is going to buy Airbus planes at the paris Airshow while considering Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370005360083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see your STILL trying to pump this euro trash POS company go Boeing and be set for LIFE wanyeDICK$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1370005581304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370006569661-27</Id><Topic><Title>Is Valerie Jarrett Running the WH and the Country......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370005569174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:06:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Valerie was one of BO's corrupt associates in Chicago when BO was a Community Organizer. Millions of tax payer funding was provided them to rebuild a large section of the slum area they dealt with in Chicago. No construction ever took place, and the money couldn't be found...just disappeared.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370006569661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370006624417-28</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK-FEB ON A RAMPAGE!</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1370002231100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add him to your ignore list, you'll be glad you did.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1370006624417</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370006837982-29</Id><Topic><Title>Majority of Women and feminine men Sill Supports Obama</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370005187086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:59:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same thing took place, and helped to put Clinton in the White House. Women are easily swayed by creating emotion rather than depending on facts to win issues. And the men? It has always been a theory of mine that there is a chemical imbalance in these liberal men that create the same thing as in women. They react to emotion rather than to the facts. Thus you see Obama winning the day with ads like "Granny over the cliff" rather than the facts on the healthcare issue.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370006837982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370006857435-30</Id><Topic><Title>BA deliveries as of Wednesday</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369932747196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like 52 or 53 planes delivered so far. NYC787 reports TUI took delivery of 2 787's, one on the 30th and one on the 31st but that has to be confirmed. Another 737 delivered on the 30th.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370006857435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370007262607-31</Id><Topic><Title>WAYNEDICK-FEB ON A RAMPAGE!</Title><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1370002231100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His stupidy, moronic attitude is a laughing stock for all of us...i need the laugh! Some day i will ignore him though!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1370007262607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370007633781-32</Id><Title>TSLA???</Title><Msg>Let me get this straight.Drive 2 hours then sit at a charging station for 1 hour,this car costs 90K?</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1370007633781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:40:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370007708350-33</Id><Topic><Title>Record unemployment, low inflation underline Europe's pain</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370004368789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please remember, for decades now under big govrt socialist governance countries in Europe have had unemployment in excess of 10% annually. Socialist governance creates a huge imbalance between the govt union employees, and the private sector that has to pay for the govt employees. Taxes get raised, the private sector continues to shrink, and the problem gets worse not better. That is the same model that Obama, and the left are using in this country.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370007708350</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:41:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370010058089-34</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA???</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1370007633781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:40:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The irony in this is they believe they are doing the "green" thing. What does it take to charge the car? Electric energy created in many states by burning coal and you guessed it petro!</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1370010058089</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370010484657-35</Id><Title>If you haven’t seen MISM you need to drop everything else</Title><Msg>MISM looks prime for a move higher. I have been researching it for a while.</Msg><Username>joseboyd990</Username><Timestamp>1370010484657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370010695669-36</Id><Title>Any Reported Problems With The New Battery And Enclosure ?</Title><Msg>I haven't heard anything. I guess no news is good news</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1370010695669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370010788696-37</Id><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Msg>1. al qaeda terrorists 2. I ran -nuclear threat 3. I ranian surrogate terrorists- Hizbollah and Assad of Syria. 4. North Korea 5. Russia -terrorist arms supplier 6. China -by their hacking American web sites, stealing of intellectual property and military technology and secrets. 20. Cuba</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370010999056-38</Id><Title>Boeing up 35% over past six months</Title><Msg>Wayneker's JRCC down 53% over past 6 months.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370010999056</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370011370155-39</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget the Tea Party.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1370011370155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370011724243-40</Id><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Msg>LOS ANGELES — The solar panels covering a vast warehouse roof in the sun-soaked Inland Empire region east of Los Angeles were only two years into their expected 25-year life span when they began to fail. Coatings that protect the panels disintegrated while other defects caused two fires that took the system offline for two years, costing hundreds of thousands of dollars in lost revenues. It was not an isolated incident. Worldwide, testing labs, developers, financiers and insurers are reporting similar problems and say the $77 billion solar industry is facing a quality crisis just as solar panels are on the verge of widespread adoption. No one is sure how pervasive the problem is. There are no industry-wide figures about defective solar panels. And when defects are discovered, confidentiality agreements often keep the manufacturer’s identity secret, making accountability in the industry all the more difficult. ____________________________________________________ Don't you just love green "secrecy" and green hypocrisy? Here we solar panels bursting into flames and burning down buildings and it doesn't see the light of day in news reports. God forbid that one bird is hurt by anything involving oil or coal and if so you can be sure that you will suffer the wrath of US Government fines whereas Wind Turbine farms are free to kill millions of birds, bats and other species, including endangered species, with the total support of the US Government and no fines. You can destroy the habitats and ecosystems of many creatures when you build a solar array in the desert, but the potential threat of harm to one critter by an oil pipeline is enough to turn greens into raging zombies seeking to eat the brains of oil executives. In China entire villages are dying from pollution caused by mining and processing of Rare Earth Elements needed in green energy products. Green are fine with the death and destruction of humans, animals and ecosystems as long as it is green energy doing it. Like Kermit said, “It isn't easy being green” except for those who are lying hypocrites.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370012065435-41</Id><Title>waynedickensen still extremely angry about being fired by Boeing</Title><Msg>Wayne if you and your boyfriend had just held your tryst somewhere else you might have gotten by with it but getting caught in the urinal at Renton wasnt very cool was it</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370012065435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370012267703-42</Id><Title>joedoakes and other dopey RWNJs still support Sen Joe McCarthy</Title><Msg>good thing Hittler is gone dopey joe would support him too</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370012267703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370012539997-43</Id><Topic><Title>joedoakes and other dopey RWNJs still support Sen Joe McCarthy</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370012267703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a clue. So is McCarthy.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370012539997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370012696102-44</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dont you just love green haters and bashers like the infested wretch who posts on this board-- I cant think of any other profuse liars who could make an argument if their lives depended on it. They are simply too stooooopid- infestid must think that any solar panel manufacturer whose solar panels could catch fire would not do the logical thing and fix the panels so they wouldnt catch fire. I guess we are to assume that fixing the panels to prevent fires is beyond human intelligence for all time. infestid like all human inventions- solar panels either work or will be made to work before this year is out--stake your life on it</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370012696102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370012874017-45</Id><Topic><Title>joedoakes and other dopey RWNJs still support Sen Joe McCarthy</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370012267703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:57:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really.....you wouldn't have to make up things if you weren't ashamed of the truth.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370012874017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:07:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370013106485-46</Id><Topic><Title>Majority of Women and feminine men Sill Supports Obama</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370005187086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 08:59:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With women and feminine men it's a fear of independence, personal responsibility and having to make your earn what you get.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370013106485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370013108629-47</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We used to get something for your infrastructure tax dollars like interstate highways, railroads, dams and electric grids. Now we spend hundreds of billions lining the pockets of failed green energy company executives and bailing out auto unions and giving fat cat paychecks and bonuses to bankers.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370013108629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370013698444-48</Id><Topic><Title>Why Democrats Will Win the House in 2014</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1369790457799</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Until the R party grows away from this, they lose another 5 of 6 national election vote counts.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1370013698444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370014094059-49</Id><Topic><Title>waynedickensen still extremely angry about being fired by Boeing</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370012065435</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:54:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome...he is a feb...waynedick-feb! Stupid moronic brain dead feb!</Msg><Username>domerrrrr45</Username><Timestamp>1370014094059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370014619536-50</Id><Title>OBAMACARE NIGHTMARE: 146% RATE HIKE IN CALIFORNIA</Title><Msg>But the data that Lee released tells a different story: Obamacare, in fact, will increase individual-market premiums in California by as much as 146 percent. Lee’s claims that there won’t be rate shock in California were repeated uncritically in some quarters. “Despite the political naysayers,” writes my Forbes colleague Rick Ungar, “the healthcare exchange concept appears to be working very well indeed in states like California.” A bit more analysis would have prevented Rick from falling for California’s sleight-of-hand. Here’s what happened. Last week, Covered California—the name for the state’s Obamacare-compatible insurance exchange—released the rates that Californians will have to pay to enroll in the exchange. “The rates submitted to Covered California for the 2014 individual market,” the state said in a press release, “ranged from two percent above to 29 percent below the 2013 average premium for small employer plans in California’s most populous regions.” That’s the sentence that led to all of the triumphant commentary from the left. “This is a home run for consumers in every region of California,” exulted Peter Lee. Except that Lee was making a misleading comparison. He was comparing apples—the plans that Californians buy today for themselves in a robust individual market—and oranges—the highly regulated plans that small employers purchase for their workers as a group. The difference is critical.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1370014619536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370014925998-51</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zo this is the only accurate part of your comment.........."I cant think....." There is no regulation of this industry Father Zo and the US government and EPA have given green energy carte blanche to lie, cheat and steal. Why aren't there any requirements for truth in labeling? What about consumer protection? Can you imagine car companies being able to hide their identity when their cars failed. Wouldn't it be nice if the government allowed the identity of car companies to remain secret and eliminate recalls on defective products. Where's the consumer protection concerns? As usual you skip the thinking and launch right into name calling. "There are no industry-wide figures about defective solar panels. And when defects are discovered, confidentiality agreements often keep the manufacturer’s identity secret, making accountability in the industry all the more difficult."</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370014925998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 11:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370016199709-52</Id><Title>Remember When Marion Barry was Caught Smoking Crack with a Prostitute</Title><Msg>He was still easily re-elected as mayor of D.C. Remember when Ray Negen failed to prepare New Orleans for hurricane Katrina and then prevented George Bush from responding with federal help. He was re-elected too - and has since been indicted on several charges of corruption. Who can forget "cold cash Jefferson" caught with $90,000 bribe money in his freezer. It's not so bad these guys were caught doing dirty......what's amazing is black people still overwhelmingly didn't care as long as they were black. Same thing is going on with Obama. 3 out of every 4 Americans think we need a special prosecutor. Even Democrats think so by a 63% to 37% margin. But 88% of black people don't want one and are still solidly approving of Obama and his administration. This is nothing but the worst kind of racism......but sadly it's nothing new.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370016199709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370016384765-53</Id><Topic><Title>Remember When Marion Barry was Caught Smoking Crack with a Prostitute</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370016199709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hows that poor me I`m a victim working out for yeah?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370016384765</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370016916987-54</Id><Topic><Title>Remember When Marion Barry was Caught Smoking Crack with a Prostitute</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370016199709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems you are connecting the dots...there is a definite pattern here. Liberalism can not even exist without corruption. It is corrupt by definition. Overwhelming evidence of both of those liberal crooks, and the left couldn't wait to re-elect them. Ray Negen came across the airwaves assuring the poor folks, most of his same race, Blacks, that to not worry about the Katrina flood that was sure to happen. Stay in your apartments, and we will be there with the buses to pick you up, and take you to safety. The buses stayed in the parking lot, and Negen, and his liberal cohorts fled to safety leaving those folks to die in their apartments.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370016916987</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370017254572-55</Id><Topic><Title>If you haven’t seen MISM you need to drop everything else</Title><Username>joseboyd990</Username><Timestamp>1370010484657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting</Msg><Username>julianstone157</Username><Timestamp>1370017254572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370017867787-56</Id><Topic><Title>If you haven’t seen MISM you need to drop everything else</Title><Username>joseboyd990</Username><Timestamp>1370010484657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:28:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MISM looks to be pre rally mode right now, thanks for the suggestion</Msg><Username>calebtanner106</Username><Timestamp>1370017867787</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:31:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370018170950-57</Id><Title>Whole system needs to collapse start all over</Title><Msg>All markets world wide are broken with these day trading games. All for quick buck mentallity. Need a 20% crash to wake these people up. All one massive scheme everybody buys stocks bonds etc world wide to inflate the world. Then you have governments/country promoting this with printing presses printing all this cheap money for banks etc. ONe MASSIVE PYRAMID scheme world wide to make it look like a global recovery and the world is just fine now. Wrong just a cover with all the massive world wide debt. They are trying to get markets to pay for a lot of it with this massive buying stocks world wide to get tax revenue. This is why i see A massive sell-off when people realize they have been had.</Msg><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1370018170950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370018235896-58</Id><Title>Bad Gas</Title><Msg>Russia has expressed concerns about yesterdays’ reports by Turkish media that the country’s security forces had found a 2kg cylinder with sarin gas after searching the homes of Syrian militants from the Al-Qaeda linked Al-Nusra Front. Prez O tells use gas is bad, a red line, Wonder were those rebel low life creeps got their gas. Nobody knows! Nobody will tell.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370018235896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370018370727-59</Id><Topic><Title>Whole system needs to collapse start all over</Title><Username>kopach</Username><Timestamp>1370018170950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:36:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That may just happen some day.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370018370727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370018482974-60</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tea Party is America.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370018482974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370018836377-61</Id><Topic><Title>Former IRS Chief had 159 meetings with Obonzo</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1369957714529</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 19:48:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would think they could just use E-mail rather than meeting in person. Then again maybe E-mail isn't a very good idea.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370018836377</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:47:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370019370467-62</Id><Topic><Title>Remember When Marion Barry was Caught Smoking Crack with a Prostitute</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370016199709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Black people will have to live with the embarrassment they bring upon themselves when it comes to supporting criminals like Jesse Jackson Jr. who won by a 90%+ voting margin even after he was indicted. It isn't racism though because the opponents of Jesse Jackson Jr. were also black and Black voters in Chicago still preferred a black criminal over a legitimate Black candidate. That speaks more to the corrupt nature of Chicago Blacks than to racism in that they prefer the corrupt candidate with the power to get them more government goodies than the honest politician who won't have such power. The underlying driver for such amoral behavior is that power corrupts and many people no longer have a moral foundation and are willing to support corruption when it benefits them. I don't judge this behavior as the science shows humans are programmed for survival/self-interest. If there is reward for supporting corruption, then corruption will flourish. Honest politicians trying to make morality an issue are vilified and ostracized so we are stuck with corruption = self-interest feedback loop we now have in politics. As long as corrupt politicians can keep the plebes at each others throats, reform will not happen. Most were fooled by the ultimate political manipulative insider Obonzo, who to my experience is the most divisive politician I've seen, in believing he would bring reform. If one looks objectively at Obonzo's track record, his entire history as an Illinois politician was all the proof needed to realize he was 180 degrees opposite of being a reformer to the point that it was a joke among Chicago political pundits who labeled Obonzo “the un-reformer”. We have a majority of voters that suffers from the “Prince Charming” fantasy syndrome and prefer pretty lies and make believe over the cold reality of facts. They also believe in the fantasy of something for nothing and want something for doing nothing now that our corrupt politicians have fed the fantasy. So unless those “Sleeping Beauties” waiting for “Prince Charming” wake up and unless those that prefer something for nothing, there will be no movement outside of DC to reform political corruption and corruption will prevail as the constant to be relied upon in politics.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370019370467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370020588687-63</Id><Title>More good news for the GOP !</Title><Msg>'..a growing majority of Americans think the sequester is bad policy and should be eliminated. In fact, along with Benghazirama, Republicans are claiming it as their biggest accomplishment...'</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370020588687</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370021225983-64</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Majority says IRS attack on Conservitive Groups is breaking the law of the land, the Constitution. Gibson Guitar</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369966972758</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 22:22:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>again stupid you know nothing. It had to do with exotic wood. here is the story. do you just dream up your #$%$? as you can see the Democrat was NOT attacked by the thugs at the IRS. Stupid idiots as your self, have been brainwashed to a point you dream it up Hot Air ^ | May 26 | Jazz Shaw Posted on Sunday, May 26, 2013 9:09:13 AM by Hojczyk An editorial at Investors Business Daily may wind up being filed under how did I miss this one? Following the recent revelations of cases where the administration appears to have used the muscle of the federal government to go after its political enemies, IBD takes a walk down memory lane to the strange case of Gibson Guitars and the federal raids on their facilities for alleged illegal importing of exotic woods used in their products. They reach one provocative conclusion. The inexplicable raid nearly two years ago on a guitar maker for using allegedly illegal wood that its competitors also used was another targeting by this administration of its political enemies… Interestingly, one of Gibson’s leading competitors is C.F. Martin &amp; Co. According to C.F. Martin’s catalog, several of their guitars contain “East Indian Rosewood,” which is the exact same wood in at least 10 of Gibson’s guitars. So why were they not also raided and their inventory of foreign wood seized? Well, let’s see… maybe C.F. Martin was getting their supplies from a properly regulated source? No. Did they fill out some forms that Gibson forgot to submit? No… so what could it be? Grossly underreported at the time was the fact that Gibson’s chief executive, Henry Juszkiewicz, contributed to Republican politicians. Recent donations have included $2,000 to Rep. Marsha Blackburn, R-Tenn., and $1,500 to Sen. Lamar Alexander, R-Tenn. By contrast, Chris Martin IV, the Martin &amp; Co. CEO, is a long-time Democratic supporter, with $35,400 in contributions to Democratic candidates and the Democratic National Committee over the past couple of election cycle</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370021225983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:27:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370021649538-65</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's gas $1.83 Obama gas $4.11 while the US is pumping more oil out of the ground then ever before. The media is protecting Obama</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369800262757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 00:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>via NAFTA and WTO now they play it back on the GOP for investing abroad, when the Dems changed the rules of the game. Libs prey on ignorant stupid people who do not have the brain power to Reason.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370021649538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370021722204-66</Id><Title>Stupid Things Republicans Say and Do !</Title><Msg>'... Fox News remains most animated about the controversy over the IRS's improper scrutiny of conservative groups that applied for tax-exempt status. With all the evidence indicating the White House was completely uninvolved in the review process, Fox has been happy to try to creatively connect non-existent points in order to expand the controversy so that it encompasses the umbrella claim of ruthless Obama "intimidation." Fox &amp; Friends this week brought back Fox's beloved right-wing saga involving Gibson Guitar in a failed attempt to claim the company's well-documented battle with the Department of Interior over rare imported wood was somehow tied into the IRS's targeting of conservative groups. ("Some people are trying to put together the dots," explained co-host Gretchen Carlson.) And then there's the ridiculous claim that Obama's IRS is going to take revenge on Tea Party members via Obamacare, by delaying their insurance requests for surgeries. (Not exactly.) Followed by claims the IRS tax-exemption review process was actually a sinister form of "voter suppression." (One so severe it swayed the entire 2012 election, according to Rush Limbaugh.)...'</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370021722204</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370021786372-67</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>less a couple of months the crash occurred under Obama's watch and don't blame Bush for Subprime Lending legislation that was Clinton and Rubin,</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370021786372</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370022005737-68</Id><Topic><Title>More good news for the GOP !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370020588687</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sequester was Obonzo's baby so that is really good news. Do you foresee Repubs launching an ad campaign showing Obonzo as the architect of the sequester?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370022005737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370022075694-69</Id><Title>Attacks in benghazi ?</Title><Msg>Naw- they didn't need extra security- as in 'what difference does/did it make " ? extra security ? NAW - ' go away Hicks, you bother us !! " The State Department released its annual Country Reports on Terrorism 2012 survey on Thursday. The section on the Middle East and North Africa includes a report on terror attacks in Libya. All told, there were eleven terrorism-related attacks last year in Libya prior to the 9/11 attack in Benghazi that took the life of Ambassador Christopher Stevens, Sean Smith, Glen Doherty, and Tyrone Woods. Six of those eleven attacks took place in Benghazi: • On May 22, assailants launched a rocket-propelled grenade at the International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC)’s building in Benghazi. The violent Islamist extremist group Brigades of Captive Omar Abdul Rahman claimed responsibility for the attack. The ICRC evacuated Benghazi in mid-July. • On June 6, violent extremists attacked the U.S. facilities in Benghazi with an improvised explosive device (IED). The group claimed that the attack was in retaliation for the assassination of Abu-Yahya al-Libi, the second highest ranking leader of al-Qa’ida. • On June 11, a convoy carrying the British Ambassador to Libya was attacked in Benghazi. • In August, there was a series of attacks against security personnel and facilities, including the bombing of the Benghazi military intelligence offices on August 1... • On August 10, Army General Hadiya al-Feitouri was assassinated in Benghazi. • On August 20, a car belonging to an Egyptian diplomat was blown up near his home in Benghazi. +++</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370022075694</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370022181345-70</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The other day a truck hit the rail of a bridge on I-5, north of seattle, causing an entire section of the bridge to collapse. That was part of the infrastructure taxpayers paid for 60 years ago. The country is peppered with the potential for bridge failures. Nothing is perfect, and nothing lasts forever, and it all requires maintenance and upgrades as more is learned.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370022181345</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370022433381-71</Id><Topic><Title>Stupid Things Republicans Say and Do !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370021722204</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:35:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm trying to reduce my news sources to only those reporters who get a thrill up their leg or skirt while fawning over Obanzo. Are their any left?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370022433381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370022985985-72</Id><Title>work changes locations</Title><Msg>Boeing will increase engineering jobs at existing facilities in South Carolina and Southern California. The company now has about 1,000 engineers in South Carolina, home of its second 787 assembly line, and 1,200 in Southern California. About 300 jobs will move from the Seattle area in about six to nine months. There's no firm timetable or headcount for growth at the other centers, Alder said.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370022985985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370023059867-73</Id><Title>NEXT 2 WEEKS THIS WILL BE 10 BAGGER (CPOW)</Title><Msg>watch!</Msg><Username>teddy55poo</Username><Timestamp>1370023059867</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370023391239-74</Id><Topic><Title>Remember When Marion Barry was Caught Smoking Crack with a Prostitute</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370016199709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes rockhead, you are a victim but just like those black Democrats who vote the color of skin rather than the content of character, you don't have enough brainpower to know it or you're so amoral you prefer evil over right. Either way you're a victim.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023391239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370023404147-75</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looking at the information you post on Gibson, IRS, Bengazzi and even an understanding of what happened in Greece, its obvious you are not a student of facts and truth but the deception that Obama is trying to help our society when even the top economic advisor for this country, that was chosen by the experts in this country does not matter to you. You are the expert making up your lies to deceive others. You attack others who are a threat to your way of not thinking. Satan a deceiver telling half truths that lead to a fallen man such as yourself.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370023404147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:03:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370023766975-76</Id><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Msg>......when they insist on voting for candidates because of the color of skin rather than the content of character. Then you have the Democrat Party who's foundation is based upon legalizing thievery or the taking of property from people who earn it and and giving it to people who didn't earn it.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370024086436-77</Id><Title>Who are the real Racists in the Country?</Title><Msg>An awful lot of evidence points to Blacks, Hispanics and white liberals. How do these people differ from Asians, Europeans, and other producers?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370024086436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370024157439-78</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to consider that a bridge built 60 years ago was not built to specifications that accommodate the much larger oversized semis that are commonly on the roads today and that may be responsible for the bridge failure. We have no idea if it was cumulative fatigue from continued oversized loads or a collision that caused the bridge to fail. If it was fatigue from oversized traffic of direct impact from an oversized truck (which it was), neither is the fault of the engineering design and who knows how long that bridge would have performed without fail. Whatever the case, taxpayers received far more value form that 60 year old bridge than the taxpayers who paid for solar panels that failed after 2 years or the taxpayers who subsidized battery and EV companies that went belly up while the Obonzo pals running those failed green companies walked away with golden parachutes. Making the comparison between taxes spent on infrastructure and taxes spent on bogus green programs is invalid.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370024157439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370024434842-79</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don`t you have anything better to do with life than worry about the color of someones skin? Jeezez age Christ man it is the year 2013 get over what ever it is that keeps you down.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370024434842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370024554413-80</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you the only one always bringing up racist remarks and racist observations? Are you some sort of liberal bigot?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370024554413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:22:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370024562075-81</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whats your feelings on subsidizing oil companies that export most of their oil out of the country?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370024562075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370024630045-82</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry David I don`t play that game , you may be stupid but I`m not.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370024630045</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:23:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370024846130-83</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rockhead....don't you have anything better to do than to avoid reality and resist discussing "sensitive issues." Are you going to spend your life in la la land where the most productive thing you ever do is to drudge up boring old names to call people whose comments illuminate the depth of your stupidity?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370024846130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370025476762-84</Id><Topic><Title>BA deliveries as of Wednesday</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369932747196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now 53 planes, A 787 for China southern was delivered. Still no confirmation on 2nd TUI 787 delivery.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370025476762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370025752750-85</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bridge had already been declared structurally insufficient but usable, like hundreds of other bridges in this country. The Federal government will pay $1 million to repair or replace it, but it will require about $50 million to do so. BTW, the Golden Gate and many other bridges were built 30 years or longer ago than the bridge near Mount Vernon, WA. Age is not the only mitigating factor. The Golden Gate has been upgraded many times. Just because we taxpayers have gotten our money's worth many times over from an asset doesn't mean we shouldn't still upgrade and maintain or replace altogether. The bridge system in this country should be one of the next big employment projects, like the freeway system was decades ago. Some bridges are already under work as part of a project for earthquake safety.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370025752750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370025779151-86</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoppiedoppy you`re a flipping fool stuck on stupid and one of the worse propaganda repeaters on the Boeing board. have a nice Friday loser.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370025779151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370025814845-87</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So on Planet Ali, a solar-electric plant is not infrastructure? And a few QA failures condemn an industry? OMG! A few Ford Pintos caught on fire! End the automotive industry! The truck at Skagitt was carrying an oversized load. Maybe the load should have been carried by train. Maybe the truck should have been required to cross the bridge at 3 a.m. at 10 mph.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370025814845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370025879606-88</Id><Topic><Title>Who are the real Racists in the Country?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370024086436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:14:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what do you produce other that stupidity ? you really make this easy man lol</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370025879606</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370025914032-89</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about the Blacks that were provided homes by the congressional democrats forcing banks to loan to them with nothing down, and no colatoral, even phonied up their loan forms. Then when they couldn't pay their mortgages liberals still considered the homes theirs, and supported them when they barackaded the doors, not allowing the banks to back the bank's home, and they even trashed the homes before leaving. Nice folks those liberal democrats.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370025914032</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370026060749-90</Id><Title>Top 1% Now Controls 39% of World's Wealth</Title><Msg>and mittens rawmoney mostly ill-gotten gains wanted to complain about the 47%...???!? The wealthiest 1 percent now control 39 percent of the world's wealth, and their share is likely to grow in the coming years, according to a new report. The world's total private wealth grew 7.8 percent last year to $135 trillion, according to the Boston Consulting Group's Global Wealth report. The top 1 percent control $52.8 trillion, and those worth $5 million or more control nearly a quarter of the world's wealth. That concentration is likely to increase in the coming years as the wealth of the wealthy grows faster than overall global wealth. The number of millionaires in the world surged by 10 percent year, reaching 13.8 million. The study predicts that global wealth will grow around 4.8 percent a year over the next five years-though millionaires will see their wealth grow nearly twice as fast. (Read More: Why Millionaire Investors Are Holding On to Cash ) Those worth $5 million or more will see their wealth grow 8 percent, while those worth more than $100 million will see their wealth grow 9.2 percent. The $100-million-plus group will see their share of global wealth grow to 6.8 percent in 2017 from the current 5.5 percent. What's driving the wealth of the wealthy? It depends on the country. In the developed world-the U.S. and Europe- it's mainly stocks. And stocks have been on a tear this year in the U.S., which has mainly benefited the top 5 percent, who own 60 percent of all individually held stocks. (Read More: Surging Stock Market Cheers Up the Rich) In developing markets, the main wealth creator is economic growth and savings. Yet the amount of wealth held in stocks and in offshore wealth (again mainly held by the wealthy) in developing countries is also growing. The amount of wealth held in equities in Asia (excluding Japan) surged by 21.9 percent in</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370026060749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370026271121-91</Id><Topic><Title>How Come Dims Don't Talk Much About Glow-Ball Warming Anymore ?</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1369881109294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 22:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is your chart "Global Sea Ice Area"? My chart is at the arctic.atmos.uiuc.edu/cryosphere web page, and it's called "Northern Hemisphere Sea Ice Area". The minimum of the curve is not "one data point". It is one of a set of data points.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370026271121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370026548057-92</Id><Topic><Title>How Come Dims Don't Talk Much About Glow-Ball Warming Anymore ?</Title><Username>jumbojetski</Username><Timestamp>1369881109294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 22:31:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are too busy trying to cover up all the scandals and corruption.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370026548057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370026622545-93</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was watching an old Clint Eastwood film last evening called White Hunter Balck Heart and it reminded me of you. In the film Clint was portraying the film director John Houston and during the scene he was dining with a biogted anti-semite woman and he was relating a story to her about him calling another anti-semite bigotted woman the ugliest beyathch he had ever met...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370026622545</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370026729783-94</Id><Topic><Title>Top 1% Now Controls 39% of World's Wealth</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370026060749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So.....what's your point. If someone has ill-gotten gains it's you obligation to report them to law enforcement people. On the other hand if you're making up stuff, slander could be expensive.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370026729783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370026829196-95</Id><Topic><Title>Barak Obama is a Felon</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1369543646313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 00:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush instituted the program. He wanted to try to make 5 million hispanic families homeowners, because he thought that could turn them into Republicans. A BBC doco told the story.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370026829196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370026871753-96</Id><Title>More Stupid Things Republicans Say and Do !</Title><Msg>Erik Rush: There Is a 50% Chance Obama Will Cancel the 2016 Elections and Become a Dictator Over the last several months, conservative commentator Erik Rush has been warning that President Obama is intent on becoming a dictator who will unleash a Gestapo-like force on the nation while sparking civil unrest so he can cancel future elections.</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1370026871753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:01:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370026939943-97</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't call people names. I might describe some like you as being very stupid but I wouldn't call you names.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370026939943</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370027178265-98</Id><Topic><Title>BA deliveries as of Wednesday</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369932747196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look forward to your reports every day. Now maybe you can be the one to put the positive spin in Boeing diversifying their engineering division that it deserves.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1370027178265</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370027766388-99</Id><Topic><Title>Think that the IRS and DOJ and the rest are just after tea partys, think again.</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369949595467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:33:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Word coming out now, more Fox News people were targeted by the DOJ and the rest of the gang AKA administration.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370027766388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:16:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370027847742-100</Id><Topic><Title>Think that the IRS and DOJ and the rest are just after tea partys, think again.</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1369949595467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 17:33:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just more of he poor me I`m a victim garbage lol</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370027847742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370027875983-101</Id><Topic><Title>Who are the real Racists in the Country?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370024086436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:14:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"what do you produce other that stupidity ?" Gotta love it when someone who can't write a simple sentence calls someone stupid. Good job rockhead!</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370027875983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370028482567-102</Id><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Msg>and RWNJ's say do nothing, keep the satus quo</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370028821228-103</Id><Topic><Title>Is it any wonder that most Blacks are Democrats when........</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370023766975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 14:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bigots is ugly AND stupid. or to paraphrase Forest Gump Bigotry is as bigotry does.. now explain how a 12 year vet of the NBA gets to be a spokesperson for GE Capital with his 150 Burger King's...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028821228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370029423759-104</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The state of Hawaii, birthplace of president Obama as decreed by Congress, is producing so much solar-generated power that it troubling their existing power grid ! Just the facts!</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370029423759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:43:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370029670568-105</Id><Title>Repubes are acting like it is 1999...</Title><Msg>ignoring real dangers and threats and focusing on a vendetta against Obama and democrats... and, yoiu know what happened after that RWNJ idiocy... 9/11 and the worst president in American history...G H W Bushco from which we as a antiuon are still trying to fill the RWNJ shithole made...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370029670568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:47:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370029733867-106</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . Email Share187 1 Print ... . . . More From . . .McCain Maneuvers to Lead Republicans on Response to Military Sexual Assaults Lincoln Chafee: A Party-Switcher Without Many Friends CBO Details Top 10 Most Expensive Tax Breaks Is the Housing News Really that Good? ... . . The number of gun deaths in the U.S. since the Newtown elementary school massacre has exceeded the total number of U.S. troops killed in the Iraq war. According to a tally of gun deaths from Slate, the number of people killed since the Dec. 14 shooting at Sandy Hook Elementary is now 4,499. The number of U.S. armed forces killed during the Iraq war was 4,409, according to the Defense Department. The Slate data comes from crowdsourcing and warns that it is “necessarily incomplete.” Authors of the tally call on readers to submit news stories to @GunDeaths. This comparison of the five months since the tragedy that redefined the debate for further gun control in this country and the nine-year conflict the U.S. has recently ended is now being used by Americans United for Change, a progressive political group. Already, the group has targeted several Republican lawmakers, including Sen. Rob Portman, R-Ohio, to support background checks, among other gun-control measures. Republicans successfully stalled gun-control legislation, arguing that further measures would not prevent gun violence but merely stifle the Second Amendment rights of lawful Americans. But Democratic lawmakers and progressive groups have signaled that they will continue this fight.</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1370029733867</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370029969127-107</Id><Title>Boeing stock price down on delivery and big order news down 1% today? Airbus up Boeing trolls and hacks ! what happened</Title><Msg>Boeing is not a trusted Company,.Airbus is up 45% year to date and 146% for 5 years and up 3.6% for the week. Boeing shareholders you have invested in stock that has lost money to airbus over time ! Boeing for 5 years up a pathetic 20% as of today down from 22% a few weeks ago! The Boeing stock value now that the fake Boeing stock buyback is over for now is going back to dead cat bounce territory at this time . I guess if another 787 is grounded then you might see some more Boeing stock buyback to keep the stock up. Clearly the Boeing Company and the hacks here had a negative result with listing airplane deliveries (foulmoutharbor), and the potential 6 billion dollar order. Meanwhile ?Airbus gained another .50 of a percent quietly staying on coarse to make the next plane that will take market share away from the 787 nod the 777X Notice how the Boeing hacks say that Wayne Dickenson is a fired Boeing employee that name never worked for Boeing they used to say Dell George was a fired Boeing employee! is that working to prop up the Boeing stock price or bother me in the slightest? that name never worked for Boeing. just like foulmoutharbor, joedokes,sparticus99991 and whstlefanms and censored50 the guy is the same person were all CEO's of Boeing The truth about Boeing hurst these fools they would rather pass on a 16day 100% gain on TSLA then accept the facts . Proof you can't teach stupid .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370029969127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370030248287-108</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price down on delivery and big order news down 1% today? Airbus up Boeing trolls and hacks ! what happened</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370029969127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, you are not a trusted stock reporter. No intelligent investor gives any credence to a one day stock move..means nothing.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370030248287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370030373979-109</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gun deaths in liberal big inner cities have always exceeded the war deaths. Has more to do with liberal governance, and policies than firearms.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370030373979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370030394225-110</Id><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Msg>....as long as it's committed by a Democrat?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370031110744-111</Id><Title>joedoke said , one day on Airbus beating Boeing is not a trend! and I am not a trusted reporter what do you say ?</Title><Msg>Joe dokes I know your a Boeing troll and Hack but do you read with blinders on too. Read the user comment Airbus is in a s trend that stretches from today up .5% to this week up 3.8% to the year to date up 45% to five years up 146% to being the number one plane builder in the world for 11 straight years that is not a one day report . And what do you say. Well you just did here is your comment . Joe Dokes said ,"No, you are not a trusted stock reporter. No intelligent investor gives any credence to a one day stock move..means nothing. Joe doke Boeing is down today 1% for 5 days down .86%, for the year lagging Airbus at up 31% down from 32% last week( airbus is now at 45% up from lower gains the week before) that is a trend Joe dokes your are living in denial or a very poor student of the stock market. Boeing is not competitive with Airbus as an investment. Boeing is now up a pathetic 20% for five years and it was up 22% a few weeks ago . Joe Dokes admit it the facts hurt and you are nothing but a boeing Hack</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370031110744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370031337439-112</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any data from a credible source to support your inane hypthesis,,, certai9nly not the re-emegence of Detroit</Msg><Username>prog101</Username><Timestamp>1370031337439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370031389332-113</Id><Topic><Title>joedoke said , one day on Airbus beating Boeing is not a trend! and I am not a trusted reporter what do you say ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370031110744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>21 Tuesdays in a row...</Msg><Username>iaminwiththeincrowd</Username><Timestamp>1370031389332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370031543307-114</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price down on delivery and big order news down 1% today? Airbus up Boeing trolls and hacks ! what happened</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370029969127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read the user comment Airbus is in a trend that stretches from today up .5% to this week up 3.8% to the year to date up 45% to five years up 146% to being the number one plane builder in the world for 11 straight years. Joe dokes25, that is not a one day report . And what do you say. Well you just did here is your comment . Next Boeing is down for the day 1% down for the week minus .86% made less over time and going down now at 31% ytd for 5 years at 20% gain down from 22% gain last week for five years . In fact Boeing is sinking fast now that the shareholder buyback to cover the 787 grounding is over So Joe Dokes your not a trusted troll you can't even make a good argument to cover for the Boeing company stock price decline .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370031543307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370031625641-115</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I found a 5/30/2013 MSNBC article titled "U.S. gun deaths since Newtown exceed Iraq war deaths" and I assume that is where you got your info. The interesting thing for those of you on this board with a brain and math skills slightly better than Obonzo's 7th grade math skills is the following: The article states that, "In 2010, there were 31,672 firearm deaths" and it also states, "According to Slate’s gun deaths project, which has been tallying the total number killed from gun violence less than six months ago, there have been 4,499 gun deaths in the U.S. The Defense Department has counted 4,409 U.S. armed forces killed in the Iraq war". So lets do some math. In 2013 we have 4,499 firearm deaths since Newtown whereas in 2010 we can calculate an equivalent 6 months worth of deaths by dividing the yearly total in half or 1/2 x 31,672 firearm deaths or 15,836 firearm deaths in 2010. So which number is BIGGER, 6 months of 2013 deaths = 4,499 or 6 months of 2010 deaths = 15,836? Now let's calculate deaths/100,000 the common statistic used around the world and by the FBI. 4499/320,000,000 x 100,000 = 1.4 firearm deaths per 100,000 and if this trend continues for the next 6 months we will have 2.8/100,000 firearm deaths in the US in 2013. In 2010 we get 31,672/320000000 x 100,000 = 9.9/100,000 firearm deaths. I checked 2011 and the rate was 10.3/100,000 firearm deaths. So based on statistics given by MSNBC, we have seen a 73% decline in firearm deaths since Newtown compared to 2011. See what is possible when a person has a brain, uses that brain to learn advanced math and science and is trained to question and think rather than blindly accept a misleading MSNBC story that actually provides statistics that indicate gun violence has gone down since Newtown. My hat is off to MSNBC's Clare Kim for understanding how stupid her readers are and for spinning the story so that her readers would think gun deaths are up instead of drastically down.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370031625641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032016422-116</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently you DID NOT read or f\ully comprhend the article posted on Yahooty and claim to be smarter than FBI when IAM fBI worker bee lol...</Msg><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1370032016422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:26:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032065900-117</Id><Topic><Title>work changes locations</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370022985985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:56:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>according to some reports, the changes are to insure uninterupted work progress in the event of a problem at any one facility, (storm daamage, labor relations, etc.) Since these issues have occurred in the past, it is a wise move. (altho I dont see a big difference between Seattle and California in terms of labor)</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370032065900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032148716-118</Id><Topic><Title>BA deliveries as of Wednesday</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369932747196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>see work changes locations topic(: )</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370032148716</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032283293-119</Id><Topic><Title>BA deliveries as of Wednesday</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369932747196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>day tripper</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370032283293</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032469157-120</Id><Topic><Title>joedoke said , one day on Airbus beating Boeing is not a trend! and I am not a trusted reporter what do you say ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370031110744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>attention Joedokes attention Joedokes explain yourself , joe dokes ? anybody there ? nope I guess joe dokes has nothing to come back with on the trend of Airbus compared to Boeing and the result of foulmoutharbor delivery orders which are known through the world and the pump it , pump it good group that monitor and harass anyone with the real facts about Boeing stock ownership compared to airbus this group is called by they given name they are the C-MEN group and are closed tied to the BHT the Boeing Hack Team and have representation by the law firm of Kikem,Harder, Ingroin. their principal financial and stock advisor is the world renowned Mr. I. Fleecem. their advisors on the boeing message board crapola order and delivery instead of 30 billion and 4 year late real important 787 date is put in a sales package for the BHT by the world renowned team of advertisement executive Dewey,Cheatem and Howe . bottom one don't listen to these crapola peddlers stay out of Boeing stock</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370032469157</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032571907-121</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dimwit who wrote the post didn't cite any source and you apparently are too stupid to comprehend where the information I got came from even though I clearly cited the MSNBC story. Sobased on the data provided in the MSNBC story, tell me what I got wrong you moron.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370032571907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032813981-122</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price down on delivery and big order news down 1% today? Airbus up Boeing trolls and hacks ! what happened</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370029969127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol joedokes25 domer, Spartacus,wstelfanms father z all the same fool , all you know is how to troll , so that is what you do your not holding any stock including Boeing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370032813981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032860016-123</Id><Topic><Title>joedoke said , one day on Airbus beating Boeing is not a trend! and I am not a trusted reporter what do you say ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370031110744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joedokes has left the building ha ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370032860016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:41:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370032983615-124</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Slate data comes from crowdsourcing and warns that it is “necessarily incomplete.” Authors of the tally call on readers to submit news stories to @GunDeaths. Read and Understand! In the meantime...</Msg><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1370032983615</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370033174727-125</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I looked up and read the Yahooty story and it had less information than the Clare Kim story posted at MSNBC. Again I fully cited my source as Clare Kim at MSNBC and my analysis is accurate while you flail frantically like a swordfishiii on dry land.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370033174727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370033456808-126</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>azpparently ali_infesto has some serious sheriff joe ffrom AZ issues... all lies</Msg><Username>swrordfishiii</Username><Timestamp>1370033456808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370033609948-127</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Further proof of why chemical ali infested is regarded universally with scorn and derision.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1370033609948</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370034454758-128</Id><Topic><Title>Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasy</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370011724243</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:48:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor - I appreciate your sincerity and your independent thinking which is rare here. The Pinto was not funded by tax dollars to my knowledge. Ford never accepted Obonzo bailout money either and somehow they are doing fine without taxpayer dollars. I am not against infrastructure improvements and where I live there has been an expansion of toll roads to deal with infrastructure improvement expansion including toll bridges. However I don't see giving money to Obonzo's crony friends at green companies that contribute to his campaign as a wise investment of taxpayer dollars when the private sector won't fund those companies. Al Gore gets $1,000,000/day from Apple so let him and his multi-billion dollar investment firm fund Obama's buddies green fantasy instead of taxpayers who actually work for a living rather than give speeches. I want solar but where are the consumer protections for this industry? The industry is more secretive than the skull and bones society. Thanks.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370034454758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370034603783-129</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe write a letter to Jane McCain Fonda and ask why he is in Syria trying to run guns to terrorist.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1370034603783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370034844896-130</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, and then look for a way to profit from it themselves.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370034844896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:14:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370034859285-131</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks rockhead.........your answer brings up my next question. Is there any question that a Democrats has mental and moral capacity to answer directly and honestly?</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370034859285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370035287859-132</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>teabaggers applying for 501 status</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370035287859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370035388530-133</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No wait, that cannot be true, that brainwashed McSame is on their team...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370035388530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370035645977-134</Id><Title>Democrat Gets 2 Years for illegally funneling $200,000 to Hillary Clinton's campaign</Title><Msg>ALEXANDRIA, Va. A northern Virginia businessman was sentenced Friday to more than two years in prison for illegally funneling nearly $200,000 to Hillary Clinton's political campaigns in 2006 and 2008. William Danielczyk, 51, of Oakton pleaded guilty in February to violating campaign-finance laws by reimbursing employees of his company, Galen Capital, and others who were recruited to attend fundraisers and make contributions Clinton's Senate and presidential campaigns. There are no allegations Clinton or her campaign acted improperly. The sentence of 28 months was roughly half of the five-year maximum sought by prosecutors in U.S. District Court. Danielczyk's lawyers, meanwhile, argued that many similar violations of the campaign-finance laws had resulted only in probation. In imposing his sentence, U.S. District Judge James Cacheris compared Danielczyk's case to defense lobbyist Paul Magliocchetti, who received 27 months for illegally funneling more than $380,000 to House members controlling the Pentagon's budget. Arguing for a lighter sentence, defense lawyer Abbe Lowell said Danielczyk's case differed from more serious violations in part because Danielczyk did not seek any special favors in exchange for his fundraising efforts. But prosecutor Eric Gibson disputed that, citing grand jury testimony that Danielczyk had told others he hoped to land an ambassadorship and saw fundraising as a means to achieve it.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370035645977</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370035771359-135</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every teabager in the country wants to do direct mail solicitation and apply for tax-exempt status under the rules yet do not want to live by the rules of law</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370035771359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370035777861-136</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't read the Slate story and you never cited the Slate story you ignoramus. You pointed to the Yahooty story moron. Did you expect me to read the thoughts emanating from your pea sized fish brain? How many times are you going to pull another source out of your #$%$? The Clare Kim MSNBC story which any moron but you can clearly see that I cited, has no caveat about crowd sourcing. Explain why dimwit fourmoreprog didn't cite his source and why you originally cited Yahooty. Again I can't read your fishiii mind. Explain why you are excited by a bogus story based on bad data that is being posted by the dimwitted fourmoreprog. We know with certainty that many previous years saw more firearm deaths than Iraq US casualties so this is not news of any sort and is useless and misleading in 2013. What we do know from FBI statistics is that firearm deaths have fallen 15% from 2007 to 2011 according to "FBI Homicide data table 8".</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370035777861</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370035914069-137</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I made sushi out of you lying moron. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370035914069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370035992255-138</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corrupt Democrats applying for 501 status are teabaggers? Strange.....really strange.</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370035992255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370036123485-139</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh, really Billo on Faux news has a story 4 u</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370036123485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370036310477-140</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fourmoronprog why did you post a LWNJ article that has no reliable data? Did you intend to show how stupid and uncritical progs are and how emotional they get over useless data that doesn't support anything. Were you unaware that we have always seen more firearm deaths in the first 5 months of the year because we have been averaging 2,500/month firearm deaths for years long before Newtown? Thanks for illustrating what a turd polisher you are.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370036310477</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370036559113-141</Id><Topic><Title>Repubes are acting like it is 1999...</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370029670568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your mother must have let you play in your own #$%$ when you were a baby and and a kid and it looks like you never broke the habit. ROTFLMAO</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370036559113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:42:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370036572652-142</Id><Title>'Liberal Activist' Admits to Bugging Mitch McConnell's Office</Title><Msg>Writing for Salon, Curtis Morrison, a self-titled "liberal activist," admits to bugging Mitch McConnell's office. He claims to have been inspired by Julian Assange and claims, "If given another chance to record him, I’d do it again." "Earlier this year, I secretly made an audio recording of Sen. Mitch McConnell, the most powerful Republican on the planet, at his campaign headquarters in Kentucky. The released portion of the recording clocks in at less than 12 minutes, but those few minutes changed my life," writes Morrison. I leaked the recording to Mother Jones, which published it with a transcript and analysis in April, and over the days that followed, blogs and cable news shows lit up with the revelations from that one meeting. At the time, McConnell was prepping for a race against the actress Ashley Judd — it was “the Whac-a-Mole stage of the campaign,” McConnell said smugly — and the recording captures his team in some Grade-A jackassery, including plans to use Judd’s history of depression against her. But also up for debate was the the ethics of the audio recording itself. Here’s the latest: An assistant U.S. attorney, Brian Calhoun, telephoned my attorney yesterday, asking to meet with him next Friday as charges against me are being presented to a grand jury. In a technology age marked by vigilante heroes like Julian Assange and Anonymous, the line between journalism and espionage has grown thin. Here's how describes himself: "I’m a liberal activist in Kentucky. I’m also a citizen journalist — at least I used to be — because I don’t subscribe to the lie that activism and journalism can be separated. Howard Zinn wrote,“You can’t be neutral on a moving train.” That’s how I see it: Journalism is a moving train, and we all choose which perspectives to bring along on the ride. Needless to say, journalists tend not to like me." And here's where he claims Julian Assange as inspiration: "It was a frustrating moment, but in truth, I’ve never doubted that making the recording was ethical. I believe in the philosophy of Julian Assange: When we open up governments, we bring in freedom. Helping the voting population better understand a political leader’s true priorities is a good thing. And hell yes, it’s ethical."</Msg><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370036572652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370036704355-143</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so, now ali_infesto is now an expert on gun data and the 2nd ammendment better fire up the faux news ho-ho's in order to get facts "right"</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370036704355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370036985646-144</Id><Topic><Title>joedoke said , one day on Airbus beating Boeing is not a trend! and I am not a trusted reporter what do you say ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370031110744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 16:11:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joedokes, recess is over! I have your dunce cap , come on back to the reporter room ha ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370036985646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:49:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370037127235-145</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still didn't answer why you were excited about a LWNJ story containing unofficial statistics as if it was something meaningful and important. What were you thinking? What was your purpose?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370037127235</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370037256127-146</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure that the only scorn and derision directed at me is coming from Obonzo turd polishers like you. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1370037256127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370037580141-147</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price down on delivery and big order news down 1% today? Airbus up Boeing trolls and hacks ! what happened</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370029969127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joe dokes , there is more trend for you that means , yep you guessed it, more reporter news! Attention JoeDokes, in the after market trading Boeing has now gone even lower than in the 1% loss in regular stock trade today. It is now not just 1% lower it is 1.51% lower , attention, JoeDokes we have established who is the reporter and who is the Boeing hack and troll, you are part of the multiple user group of" BHT" yep, that's you Joe Dokes , your a Boeing hack Troll, your in a select group , your a full member of the special C-men attachment, part of the of the Boeing investors advertisement agency . Congratulations you lost money today way to go. And you missed my May 3 call to buy TSLA in 16 days you missed a 100% gain going from 55 on May 3 to a nice short squeeze get out 16 days later at $110 so sad to be a C-man group leader . I guess you should stop putting maple syrup all over your body and asking domer if he wants a short stack, that guy does not have a sense of humor for a little short one like you . .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370037580141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370037668343-148</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five thumbs down to my post - is that all Ahkmed's doing.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370037668343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370037732523-149</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just b-jabbering and b-jawing while cleaning my musket and smelting bullets from red-coat buttons as far south as the Carolinas, them georgia boys will succumb to their own petards if left up to me...</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370037732523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370038197634-150</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>conter - that by 10 fold according to the old book and bulky-blob rules LIVING IS EASY WITH EYES CLOSED IT'S UNDERSTANG ALL THAT YOU SEE</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370038197634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370038313842-151</Id><Title>i WAS WRONG ABOUT sILICONE vALLEY</Title><Msg>Concerning boise or duluth it should have been in the south</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370038313842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370038427917-152</Id><Title>HPOE 4-WHITE PEOPLE</Title><Msg>1. Magical Mystery Tour - 0:00 2. The Fool on the Hill - 2:50 3. Flying - 5:49 4. Blue Jay Way - 8:04 5. Your Mother Should Know - 11:59 6. I Am the Walrus - 14:28 7. Hello Goodbye - 19:04 8. Strawberry Fields Forever - 22:32 9. Penny Lane - 26:40 10. Baby You're a Rich Man - 29:40 i SAY HELLO</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370038427917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370039206100-153</Id><Title>Wall Street Drops 1% on the Day, but Still Up for May</Title><Msg>Canada, aka uber-USA say it's great day</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1370039206100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370039601039-154</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tea Party?! HAHAHA That is what Obama told the IRS at the Mar. 31st meeting, and the very next day the IRS UNION members targeted the Tea Party Organizations. There is no doubt the Radical Left is far and away the biggest danger to USA's health and welfare, and to our national security.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370039601039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370039629753-155</Id><Title>There's never been a dance that's so easy to do.</Title><Msg>Ev'rybody's doin' a brand new dance now. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) I know you'll get to like it if you give it a chance now. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) My little baby sister can do it with ease, It's easier than learnin' your ABC's, So come on, come on, do the loco-motion with me. You gotta swing your hips now. Come on baby, jump up, jump back. Oh, well, I think you got the knack. Now that you can do it, let's make a chain now. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) A chuga chuga motion like a railroad train now. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) Do it nice and easy now, don't lose control, A little bit of rhythm and a lot of soul. Come on, come on, do the loco-motion with me. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) Move around the floor in a loco-motion. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) Do it holdin' hands if you get the notion. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) There's never been a dance that's so easy to do. It even makes you happy when you're feelin' blue. So come on, come on, do the loco-motion with me. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) So come on, come on, do the loco-motion with me. (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.) (C'mon, baby, do the loco-motion.)</Msg><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1370039629753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370040296678-156</Id><Topic><Title>work changes locations</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370022985985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:56:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Investigators say Boeing's loss of key engineering talent in recent years played a role in the company's flawed analysis during the Columbia mission that the crew would return safely. At issue is whether Boeing Co.'s relocation of its space shuttle engineering staff from Southern California to Texas in 2001 resulted in a brain drain. Boeing officials said they are not aware investigators have reached a judgment and disputed the contention that the move weakened the company's engineering staff. During the Columbia mission, Boeing engineers provided three critical reports that concluded foam debris that struck the shuttle shortly after launch had not catastrophically damaged its thermal protection system and that the seven-member crew would return safely. In fact, the investigation has found that foam debris almost certainly did breach the leading edge of the left wing, which led to the orbiter's breakup over Texas on Feb. 1, killing the crew. The reports influenced all the key decisions by NASA managers, who then downplayed the entire foam event, investigation board chairman Harold Gehman Jr. said in the spring. As a result, the board became keenly interested in how and why Boeing erred. Boeing's technical assessments for NASA were performed by its engineering staff in Houston, which until 2001 had been located in Huntington Beach. About 80% of the 500 engineers in California refused to move, forcing Boeing to hire and train new workers in Texas. The Columbia flight was the first time Boeing's staff in Texas had primary responsibility for providing NASA with engineering support, according to accident board investigators. Engineers in Huntington Beach have told Columbia investigators that they would have reached different conclusions during the mission than their counterparts in Houston. Boeing space shuttle program manager Steve Oswald acknowledged in an interview that he had heard those allegations.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1370040296678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370040519147-157</Id><Topic><Title>There's never been a dance that's so easy to do.</Title><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1370039629753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It even makes you happy when you're feelin' blue. now</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370040519147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370040692262-158</Id><Topic><Title>work changes locations</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370022985985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 13:56:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now, the company expects you to move</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370040692262</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370042145939-159</Id><Topic><Title>There's never been a dance that's so easy to do.</Title><Username>green.onions23</Username><Timestamp>1370039629753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 18:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like Smokey Robinson, and green onions better.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370042145939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370042222067-160</Id><Title>Just like hittin' taters back home</Title><Msg>what is?</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370042222067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370043049443-161</Id><Title>IAM pretty sure the 15 year old black cat is a communist</Title><Msg>as the sole slave to the last of the family pets even outlasting the Saint Bernard fresh cold water, good clean air, and proper exercise does that cat good</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370043049443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370043126305-162</Id><Title>NO MORE JAPAN STOCK! WHY JAPAN STOCK SHOULD COLLAPSE SO FAST?</Title><Msg>Why japan stock will collapse so fast. 1. Japan old age group is over 30% population. 2. Japan no natural resource. 3. Japan debt over 250% vs japan gdp. 4. Japan have bad relationship with south korea, north korea, russia, china, thailand, singapore, hong kong, taiwan, myanmar. 5. Japan no innovation ability like before even south korea better than japan. 6. Japan did low japan yen and qe (george solo warning - japan qe is risky). 7. Huge drop over 10% one day and drop over 5.5% one day. All happen in one week. 8. It's beginning collapse signal.</Msg><Username>kaoginger</Username><Timestamp>1370043126305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370043154697-163</Id><Title>President Barack Obama to sign an international arms trade treaty previously rejected by US Senate.</Title><Msg>President Barack Obama will soon sign an international arms trade treaty previously rejected by the United States Senate. One New World Order / Anti Democracy Globalist Outrage after another ...perpetrated by the Elites favorite teleprompter reading puppet.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370043154697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370043964613-164</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama should be in there somewhere, top 10 for sure</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1370043964613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370044295168-165</Id><Topic><Title>BA deliveries as of Wednesday</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1369932747196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 12:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Final count 54 planes. 2nd TUI 787 delivery confirmed. Final 787 count is 6 delivered.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370044295168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 19:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370044920530-166</Id><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Msg>Too bad SPEEA members couldn't see that until it was too late.</Msg><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370045184467-167</Id><Title>God punishing Oklahomans</Title><Msg>God is punishing the Coburns, Inhofs, anti Obama people, anti Obama Care people for the evil they have foisted on America by accepting the pay of the Kochs and the ultra rich while ignoring the needs of the people</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370045184467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370045271066-168</Id><Title>Boeing new design centers should improve product and help innovations</Title><Msg>The new design centers are Engineering design, Propulsion, and Out-of-Production Support. Centers to be located in Southern California, Washington , and South Carolina. Centers like this, will probably be think tanks and addressing current designs. DARPA think tank does extremely well. Expect same from Boeing. Heard something about them making some sort of center in Russia.</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370045271066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370045697397-169</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gloating because it's YOUR war criminal in the WH instead of THEIR war criminal. Disgusting.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370045697397</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370045722673-170</Id><Title>Whoa-ah whoa-ah whoa-ah</Title><Msg>Grand Funk Railroad/an average white band don' the locomotion and, you know what... it worked when you're feeling blue you can pick ypiurself and chooga chooga like a railroad chain, now</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370045722673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370046822739-171</Id><Topic><Title>God punishing Oklahomans</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370045184467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:06:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>plesase god-almioghty to forvige father_zostima he knows not of which he speaks oakies include a far and wide swayth of peop;le throuygh the time hardirer than thou seatlle sold the sonics to the thuindfer beep</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370046822739</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370047030956-172</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if there is even a glimmer of understanding in the object of your scorn. They hypocrisy that feeds his engine is glutted on the only thing he has left. THAT he called who would win the White House ...the rightness or wrongness of the actions of the teleprompter reader apparently mean nothing to this one.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370047030956</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370047478687-173</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like a little pansy and a DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370047478687</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370047574517-174</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Gloating" ? I recall a day painting myself with black mud to float in the Dead Sea thinking it might be therapeutic... there was no gloating mentioned although the semites seemed ahead of the game</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370047574517</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370047597601-175</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hypocrisy is all the Kent Raven has left.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370047597601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370048426060-176</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>alla approved an egyptian visa a couple of US military and 33000 tons of payload the black elder pricipal said "nothing" almost 33000 tons of payload except, hey you do i bwnna get a cup of joe spot off</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370048426060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370049057642-177</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Barack Obama will be your president for about 1,300 more days... unless the 22nd Amendment is repealed. As for me, I am sitting with my: Toes in the water #$%$ in the sand Not a worry in the world A cold beer in my hand Life is good today Life is good today Obama's in charge And Bachmann is gone" The #$%$ just can't seen to "shake" his Bromance with his A-n-o-I-n-t-e-d W-o_n even with his said W-o-n's repeated lies! Pitiful little Dim #$%$!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1370049057642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370049199979-178</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I wonder if there is even a glimmer of understanding in the object of your scorn..." Dim #$%$ and his ilk? "glimmer"? Never in a million years!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1370049199979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370049223251-179</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, and Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045102609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>google "Minstrel Boy Black Hawk down" and listen to the song.... to get an idea of what real commitment and sacrifice and loyalty mean......The leadership at the top are bought and paid for and the betrayal of trust at every level has never been more pronounced ...I spit on all of them</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370049223251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370050305652-180</Id><Title>A little bit of rythym and a lot of soul</Title><Msg>warm up was swimming more than 1000 yards (GASPING FOR AIR) 1 POINT FOR THIRD PLACE OOOH LA LA RONNIE WOODLAND</Msg><Username>bapsycho</Username><Timestamp>1370050305652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370050585295-181</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like much you are "sure" of, written in goonese. The world moves on and you clearly enjoy being stuck in this weird, perverse little universe of ignorance.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1370050585295</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:36:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370050953536-182</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>US Murder Rate Down Since The Assault Weapons Ban Was Lifted Posted on December 27, 2012 by stevengoddard The Assault Weapons Ban was lifted in 2004, and the murder rate in the US has declined 14% since then.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370050953536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370051150333-183</Id><Topic><Title>'Liberal Activist' Admits to Bugging Mitch McConnell's Office</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370036572652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Proof that the Klan lives. A truly sad era for republicans and by extension, the U.S.</Msg><Username>jumboyjetski</Username><Timestamp>1370051150333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370051536209-184</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No correlation.... is that what they are implying???</Msg><Username>dellag1</Username><Timestamp>1370051536209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370051760525-185</Id><Topic><Title>Va. school board member asked to resign over racist Michelle Obama emails</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045437149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tough t I t t I e s.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370051760525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 21:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370053346375-186</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Deaths Since Newtown Now Surpass Number of Americans Killed in Iraq</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370028482567</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:28:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The FBI's own WEB site and statistics show categorically and conclusively and irrefutably that violent crime is way down since the Clinton Gun ban was lifted.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370053346375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 22:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370053445839-187</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is Obama arming AlQaeda Rebels in both Lybia and Syria ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370053445839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 22:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370053897723-188</Id><Title>upside-down and backwards at 5000 mph</Title><Msg>2 + 2 = 4</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370053897723</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 22:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370055980454-189</Id><Topic><Title>upside-down and backwards at 5000 mph</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370053897723</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 22:31:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1 G</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370055980454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370056454437-190</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rayn is only part of the problem Try the 2008 EBoard, the 2009 eboard, the 2010 e board and two or three of the longest serving members starting back in 2000- 2001. Add to that member apathy - who gleefully turned out a higher percentage to recall the few members who tried to correct things by firing the Boff. The remainder of the board then hired a marxist- and later ms pres admitted under oath she had staff help on the recall.- and the council and the members paid no attention. As it was withn the boff - so it is with the goforth . More staff than eboard members attend board meetings. And the president lives in his own reality..</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370056454437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:14:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370056614539-191</Id><Title>Ode to Joy</Title><Msg>the folder slide into my slot and she's a hot one fryday afternoon or about 1600 hrs one of three cases</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370056614539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370056698597-192</Id><Topic><Title>Ode to Joy</Title><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370056614539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:16:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your a paid CHAOS agent</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370056698597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 23:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>