<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357707939573-1</Id><Topic><Title>Miss the political #$%$</Title><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357672082243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:08:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I found and posted the $400M number right after you posted $250K ($250,000). You made the silly mistake of using K for millions and I questioned you on it. Now, you can't admit the mistake and are trying to say you were making a joke. LOL. About everyone on this board knows you don't make jokes.</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357707939573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 00:05:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357708617875-2</Id><Topic><Title>2nd amendment was for muskets and militias against the Brits....... irony</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357697675342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:14:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They were the assault rifles of the time</Msg><Username>team_hozomeen</Username><Timestamp>1357708617875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 00:16:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357709095923-3</Id><Topic><Title>Strike is tomorrow word is...............</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357703835647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH BULLPUCKY CUBED ! While it is theoretically possible to strike on feb 1, practically it will be mid feb at the earliest. Poster csaintswin is missing more than a few sandwiches for a picnic</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357709095923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 00:24:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357709249069-4</Id><Topic><Title>AIRBUS RULES THE SKY!</Title><Username>soldier_boy63h</Username><Timestamp>1357691313184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:28:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots ... He scores!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357709249069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 00:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357709907325-5</Id><Topic><Title>How is that outsourcing working for you now Chicago Managment ?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357587073340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 14:31:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump it for Dell (oops, Wayne) not knowing that K stands for thousands (not millions) and not remembering (I'll be kind and assume he forgot) my post referencing Reuters that said the SPEEA strike losses would be about $400M per day (not $250K). (check Jan 7, 3:13 PM in this thread) P.S. Never worked on a 727 (maybe the first 726 IDs were already taken) Sort of like what happened to WD1 thru WD39. HaHa</Msg><Username>ronanderson727</Username><Timestamp>1357709907325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 00:38:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357710991891-6</Id><Topic><Title>Alot of wannabe engineers out there on this board but failing</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357692929253</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:55:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There seem to be a lot of wannabe engineers at Boeing also!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357710991891</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 00:56:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357711259587-7</Id><Topic><Title>Strike is tomorrow word is...............</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357703835647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes timing is brutal. How long has the contract been up? Oh lets wait till after we get paid for the Christmas break....oh just a few more weeks to pay down the mastercard......nuw lets only stay out 4-6 weeks or I will miss my house payment.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1357711259587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 01:00:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357712968185-8</Id><Topic><Title>Strike is tomorrow word is...............</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357703835647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still waiting for csaintswin to post the press release that he got his "mis" information from?</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357712968185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 01:29:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357713541494-9</Id><Topic><Title>Today's fuel leak was a non issue</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357694017165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:13:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do not know who Don is, he seems to have alot of knowledge about airplane safety/ systems and I agree totally with his response when it comes to airplane features built in for that purpose.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357713541494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 01:39:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357714536439-10</Id><Topic><Title>Today's fuel leak was a non issue</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357694017165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:13:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analysis: Boeing 787 program won't break even until 2034 Puget Sound Business Journal by Steve Wilhelm, Staff Writer</Msg><Username>fmlana</Username><Timestamp>1357714536439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 01:55:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357719019339-11</Id><Topic><Title>Strike is tomorrow word is...............</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357703835647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$. A strike authorization vote hasn't even been conducted yet so SPEEA's negotiating teams don't even have the authority to call for a strike. Wanna try again?</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1357719019339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 03:10:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357720074715-12</Id><Topic><Title>Blue States just Can't play football.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357680089908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:21:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still smarting over the presidential election I see. Pity. About football ... Ever hear of USC (multiple NCs)? How 'bout Washington (shared the NC with Miami in the early 90's) or Colorado (also an NC in the early 90's)? Last but not least, Notre Dame is located in Indiana, a traditionally "red" state. Good one there professor.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1357720074715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 03:27:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357728289548-13</Id><Title>"Not Even Close: 2012 Was Hottest Ever in U.S."</Title><Msg>And of course not: t has nothing to do with human activity: ==== The numbers are in: 2012, the year of a surreal March heat wave, a severe drought in the Corn Belt and a huge storm that caused broad devastation in the Middle Atlantic States, turns out to have been the hottest year ever recorded in the contiguous United States. How hot was it? The temperature differences between years are usually measured in fractions of a degree, but last year’s 55.3 degree average demolished the previous record, set in 1998, by a full degree Fahrenheit. If that does not sound sufficiently impressive, consider that 34,008 daily high records were set at weather stations across the country, compared with only 6,664 record lows, according to a count maintained by the Weather Channel meteorologist Guy Walton, using federal temperature records. That ratio, which was roughly in balance as recently as the 1970s, has been out of whack for decades as the country has warmed, but never by as much as it was last year. “The heat was remarkable,” said Jake Crouch, a scientist with the National Climatic Data Center in Asheville, N.C., which released the official climate compilation on Tuesday. “It was prolonged. That we beat the record by one degree is quite a big deal.” Scientists said that natural variability almost certainly played a role in last year’s extreme heat and drought. But many of them expressed doubt that such a striking new record would have been set without the backdrop of global warming caused by the human release of greenhouse gases. And they warned that 2012 was probably a foretaste of things to come, as continuing warming makes heat extremes more likely. Even so, the last year’s record for the United States is not expected to translate into a global temperature record when figures are released in the coming weeks. The year featured a La Niña weather pattern, which tends to cool the global climate over all, and scientists expect it to be the world’s eighth- or ninth-warmest year on record. Assuming that prediction holds up, it will mean that the 10 warmest years on record all fell within the past 15 years, a measure of how much the planet has warmed. Nobody who is under 28 has lived through a month of global temperatures that fell below the 20th-century average, because the last such month was February 1985. Last year’s weather in the United States began with an unusually warm winter, with relatively little snow across much of the country, followed by a March that was so hot that trees burst into bloom and swimming pools opened early. The soil dried out in the March heat, helping to set the stage for a drought that peaked during the warmest July on record. The drought engulfed 61 percent of the nation, killed corn and soybean crops and sent prices spiraling. It was comparable to a severe drought in the 1950s, Mr. Crouch said, but not quite as severe as the legendary Dust Bowl drought of the 1930s, which was exacerbated by poor farming practices that allowed topsoil to blow away. Extensive records covering the lower 48 states go back to 1895; Alaska and Hawaii have shorter records and are generally not included in long-term climate comparisons for that reason. Mr. Crouch pointed out that until last year, the coldest year in the historical record for the lower 48 states, 1917, was separated from the warmest year, 1998, by only 4.2 degrees Fahrenheit. That is why the 2012 record, and its one degree increase over 1998, strikes climatologists as so unusual. “We’re taking quite a large step above what the period of record has shown for the contiguous United States,” Mr. Crouch said. In addition to being the nation’s warmest year, 2012 turned out to be the second-worst on a measure called the Climate Extremes Index, surpassed only by 1998. Experts are still counting, but so far 11 disasters in 2012 have exceeded a threshold of $1 billion in damages, including several tornado outbreaks; Hurricane Isaac, which hit the Gulf Coast in August, and, late in the year, Hurricane Sandy, which caused damage likely to exceed $60 billion in nearly half the states, primarily in the mid-Atlantic region. Among those big disasters was one bearing a label many people had never heard before: the derecho, a line of severe, fast-moving thunderstorms that struck central and eastern parts of the country starting on June 29, killing more than 20 people, toppling trees and knocking out power for millions of households. For people who escaped both the derecho and Hurricane Sandy relatively unscathed, the year may be remembered most for the sheer breadth and oppressiveness of the summer heat wave. By the calculations of the climatic data center, a third of the nation’s population experienced 10 or more days of summer temperatures exceeding 100 degrees Fahrenheit. Among the cities that set temperature records in 2012 were Nashville; Athens, Ga.; and Cairo, Ill., all of which hit 109 degrees on June 29; Greenville, S.C., which hit 107 degrees on July 1; and Lamar, Colo., which hit 112 degrees on June 27. With the end of the growing season, coverage of the drought has waned, but the drought itself has not. Mr. Crouch pointed out that at the beginning of January, 61 percent of the country was still in moderate to severe drought conditions. “I foresee that it’s going to be a big story moving forward in 2013,” he said.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357728289548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 05:44:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357728974185-14</Id><Topic><Title>Strike is tomorrow word is...............</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357703835647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPEEA doesn't have the sack to strike. They have been mooching off the IAM contract talks for so long they do not know how to negoiate. Why don't you clowns wait until the EIP payout before leaving your 90plus K job forever. Engineers from Russia and China are standing by to deliver all dispositions, quicker than the in-house engineers can. Good riddance.</Msg><Username>trujrnyfan</Username><Timestamp>1357728974185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 05:56:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357729380447-15</Id><Topic><Title>Strike is tomorrow word is...............</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357703835647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talks begin TODAY................... press still is all over this story and the DREAMLINER is in question with the public, not the Airlines by they want $$$$$$ PERIOD. The government will look into it........ Being way too too big.</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357729380447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 06:03:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357734031203-16</Id><Topic><Title>2nd amendment was for muskets and militias against the Brits....... irony</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357697675342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:14:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Winchester came out with their lever action repeating rifle it was considered to be a weapon of mass destruction at the time and it was predicted that a weapon so lethal would wipe out the human race.</Msg><Username>blackshango</Username><Timestamp>1357734031203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 07:20:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357734432573-17</Id><Topic><Title>2nd amendment was for muskets and militias against the Brits....... irony</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357697675342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:14:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>laws restricting Guns from School areas. Since that law was passed, several nuts have used scghool facilities as their personally safe "hunting area"</Msg><Username>usenatgas</Username><Timestamp>1357734432573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 07:27:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357735820340-18</Id><Topic><Title>2nd amendment was for muskets and militias against the Brits....... irony</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357697675342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 21:14:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regardless... the time has come to reevaluate the Amendment and to AMEND it.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1357735820340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 07:50:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357737157618-19</Id><Topic><Title>Today's fuel leak was a non issue</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1357694017165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:13:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about a fuel leak at ETP ?? Not good I think.</Msg><Username>pdoty728</Username><Timestamp>1357737157618</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:12:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357737262150-20</Id><Title>Why is this stock up? Is it now good to have fire and leaks on planes?</Title><Msg>and labor strikes. This thing should be $55.</Msg><Username>brattle_smattle</Username><Timestamp>1357737262150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:14:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357737864447-21</Id><Title>Teething? Get real, there are lives at stake.</Title><Msg>This product is a disaster in the making. Live by the headlines, die by the headlines. I wish BA luck but this machine they built is too risky to business.</Msg><Username>brattle_smattle</Username><Timestamp>1357737864447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:24:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357738297605-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why is this stock up? Is it now good to have fire and leaks on planes?</Title><Username>brattle_smattle</Username><Timestamp>1357737262150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont forget brake problems !</Msg><Username>elronns</Username><Timestamp>1357738297605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:31:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357738527459-23</Id><Topic><Title>Why is this stock up? Is it now good to have fire and leaks on planes?</Title><Username>brattle_smattle</Username><Timestamp>1357737262150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its up over 1% because everything you mentioned are NON issues. let me guess --- you are short?</Msg><Username>rwh4fshg</Username><Timestamp>1357738527459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:35:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357738582212-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why is this stock up? Is it now good to have fire and leaks on planes?</Title><Username>brattle_smattle</Username><Timestamp>1357737262150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Put your momo where your mouth is and SHORT IT like I have.</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1357738582212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:36:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357739180471-25</Id><Topic><Title>BA would certainly come to be the ticker to pay attention to this month.</Title><Username>gary_isakson</Username><Timestamp>1357732711384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 06:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is you are right man</Msg><Username>fitchettgregory</Username><Timestamp>1357739180471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:46:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357739688864-26</Id><Title>I did not know about the brakes problem? So, leaking fuel, fire and may not be able to stop on landing.</Title><Msg>Ok. I am alright with that if the paying passengers are.</Msg><Username>ram9751</Username><Timestamp>1357739688864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:54:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357739736767-27</Id><Title>when were the brake problems? Was that today?</Title><Msg>Jesus Christ!!!!</Msg><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1357739736767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:55:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357739890786-28</Id><Title>Is the flight crew ok with all this? I mean their odds are higher.</Title><Msg>What do they say?</Msg><Username>tommy_loops</Username><Timestamp>1357739890786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:58:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357741118409-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a prepper.....I have the 5 Gs. I have 3200 acres of fine bottom land with a half mile of it fronting on the Atchafalaya. That's enough land for a small survival garden and the river is full of Catfish Bass, Catfish, Sakalay and Alligators. I have gas, and Oil wells on the property - Every one down here does. I have a 3000 gal propane tank I use to run the tractors and trucks. I have a generator that automatically supplies electricity to the house in case of power disruption - common equipment here in hurricane alley. I have a smoke house (not the kind you pot-heads use) for the wild hogs, deer and turkeys I shoot. Got a small armory including archery equipment, dogs and all the gadgets necessary for security on the place. We have auxiliary communications set up and operational. Lots more.....to but they're secret. If things every really got bad I have horses for transportation and about 80 head of cattle I can eat with them homegrown maters and taters. The one thing I don't have is air transportation. I've been thinking about buying a helicopter but I don't know how to fly one. I was hoping I could find a chopper pilot who is Vietnam veteran preferably one who earned a DFC that would fly me out to the Miracle (my boat) if I have to evacuate - not likely but possible. Of course that most likely would be a one way trip so he would have to have some stay of the Miracle until we reached my place on Grand Cayman. We could tell old Vietnam war stories and he would be free to tell me of his heroism and I would listen attentively as he he elaborated on his bravery and super human feats. One qualification of the utmost importance would be that he have a pair not and be a flaming sissy liberal. A guy like that will just won't pay attention and will likely get REAL AMERICANS killed. Beside, folks on Grand Cayman are pretty independent and don't cotton to sissies who are collectivists. Those guys belong on a neighboring island. I think Hugo Chavez is there right now getting some socialized government medical care.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357741118409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:18:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357741179803-30</Id><Title>The brake problem was today in Japan. That is 3 days of problems. It is only Wednesday can they go 5 for 5</Title><Msg>this week?</Msg><Username>tommy_loops</Username><Timestamp>1357741179803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:19:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357741196542-31</Id><Title>Was BA Management Asleep?</Title><Msg>The 787 program has apparently been bungled from start to today. It is almost as if there was little oversight/management or those responsible incompetent. The risks were not adequately analysed and backup plans fell short. This project should be a case study at Wharton on How Not To Manage Billion Dollar Programs.</Msg><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357741196542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:19:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357741515038-32</Id><Topic><Title>UAL limits 787 action</Title><Username>u8everything</Username><Timestamp>1357671568858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:59:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder how long this will be in effect for....</Msg><Username>elronns</Username><Timestamp>1357741515038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357742055944-33</Id><Title>A New Term In Prog-Talk!</Title><Msg>What is “prog-talk”? That is the language that progressives and liberals like to use in order to say bad things but in a way that doesn’t sound as bad to the dumbmasses … actually that should be dumb masses … or the ignoranuses. Let’s review our list real fast before we get to our latest entry, shall we? “Undocumented workers” became the politically acceptable term so as to not offend “illegal immigrants” or “illegal aliens” “Revenues” are a fancy way of saying “taxes” in prog-talk “Revenue positive” is how liberals like to say “tax increases” without using the forbidden “t-word” (taxes) “Letting the Bush tax cuts expire” was, for a long while, the way to say “increase taxes on the rich!” “Investing” is the word that proggies use to describe “government spending” “Earmarks” and “pork-barrel spending” were replaced by the politically correct “congressionally directed spending” “Stimulus” became a dirty word after the $800 billion flop of 2009, so proggies managed to use the word “job creation” instead .. still puzzled as to how the two are related. The latest proggie term has been coined by proggie princess herself Nancy Pelosi, the hallow-eye hippie from Haight-Ashbury. In the discussion over gun control, apparently Princess Pelosi would prefer to do away with the term “gun control” and replace it with “gun violence prevention.” This is how the proggies will get what they want out of this fight .. they will change the language so as to make anyone challenging them out to be for gun violence and against preventing gun violence. Isn’t that clever? Nuze</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357742055944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:34:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357742243550-34</Id><Topic><Title>UAL limits 787 action</Title><Username>u8everything</Username><Timestamp>1357671568858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:59:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have no problems though with A330? Curious.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1357742243550</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:37:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357742319507-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why is this stock up? Is it now good to have fire and leaks on planes?</Title><Username>brattle_smattle</Username><Timestamp>1357737262150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bratt this will be green all week long so you better Cover you a sses$$$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1357742319507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:38:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357742500487-36</Id><Title>Obama and Gun Control</Title><Msg>Obama says he wants to “close the gun show loophole.” My challenge has been out there for over a week … a challenge for anyone to tell me just how the laws pertaining to the sale of a gun at a gun show differ from laws elsewhere. No responses. That’s because there IS NO GUN SHOW LOOPHOLE. Obama’s goal here is to forbid the transfer of guns between private individuals. If he can’t accomplish that, he wants a federal record of all private party transfer. The goal here is for the government to know just who owns the guns. Registration. Make no mistake … Obama’s goal is the same goal that has been the leftist Democrat dream for ages … gun confiscation … especially handguns. Why aren’t we remembering what Rahm Emanuel said when he was Obama’s Chief of Staff? “Never let a good crisis go to waste.” The Sandy Hook shootings certainly qualified as a crisis … and in the eyes of the White House it was a “good” crisis; a good crisis because it caused an overwhelming wave of emotion across the country. Emotion blocks rational thought. What a perfect time to advance the gun control and eventual gun confiscation cause. Oh .. and this thing about banning high capacity magazines? Earlier this week there was a story in Atlanta about four thugs with guns carjacking library patrons in a high-income neighborhood. Four urban thugs .. four guns .. four magazines … a minimum of 28 rounds. So let’s be sure to make sure the victim of these carjackings only has seven rounds to protect himself. NBN</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357742500487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357742511297-37</Id><Title>goodnight shorts</Title><Msg>told you to buy at 74.50</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357742511297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357742732048-38</Id><Title>SELL NOW, MORE PROBLEMS COMING!!!! 65</Title><Msg>COMING SOON</Msg><Username>patrickstock</Username><Timestamp>1357742732048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:45:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357742907754-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Democrats so Fearful of Freedom?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357168835381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 18:20:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Astonishingly dumb post. Please explain how those two words are synonomous. I don't believe you can do it.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1357742907754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:48:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357742965231-40</Id><Topic><Title>SELL NOW, MORE PROBLEMS COMING!!!! 65</Title><Username>patrickstock</Username><Timestamp>1357742732048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:45:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more like $85</Msg><Username>rwh4fshg</Username><Timestamp>1357742965231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:49:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357743055651-41</Id><Topic><Title>Why is this stock up? Is it now good to have fire and leaks on planes?</Title><Username>brattle_smattle</Username><Timestamp>1357737262150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 08:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is up because the big institutions are not ready to unload it yet. The CEO promised he would cut costs to the bone so he and his execs could get big bonuses this year for jacking up the price and the wall street institutions are waiting patiently.</Msg><Username>zevach</Username><Timestamp>1357743055651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:50:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357743126799-42</Id><Topic><Title>SELL NOW, MORE PROBLEMS COMING!!!! 65</Title><Username>patrickstock</Username><Timestamp>1357742732048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:45:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For sure! Where is the idiot that shorted at 74.18 late yesterday claiming millions would be made? LOL</Msg><Username>yourgonnalosebigbucks</Username><Timestamp>1357743126799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:52:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357743405394-43</Id><Topic><Title>A New Term In Prog-Talk!</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357742055944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:34:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you talk about something you understand, like temperature conversions.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1357743405394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:56:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357743551892-44</Id><Title>New York ferry accident injures 17</Title><Msg>Now ferries are not safe. AT least 17 people have been injured in a commuter ferry accident in New York City. The Seastreak ferry had a hard landing at a lower Manhattan pier around 9am local time (1am AEDT), WABC-TV reported. Live TV footage showed firefighters and ambulances swarming the scene, administering medical aid. One person is believed to have a head injury. FDNY said 50 people were being evaluated but that all injuries were minor, NBC4 New York reports. A large gash of approximately 2 metres was also visible on the ferry's bow.</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1357743551892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:59:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357743574542-45</Id><Title>Is this a buying opportunity ??</Title><Msg>any comments ?</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357743574542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:59:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357743620683-46</Id><Title>ALL BA CONTRACTS WILL BE DEALYED AND HOLD!!!!</Title><Msg>DON'T HOLD</Msg><Username>patrickstock</Username><Timestamp>1357743620683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:00:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357743902164-47</Id><Title>BRAKEING NEWS ! (No pun Intended) Another 787 flight canceled this time due to BRAKE WARNING LIGHT !</Title><Msg>YOWSA !!!!!!!! A brake problem has forced an All Nippon Airways flight to be cancelled in Japan - the third glitch in as many days involving a Boeing 787 Dreamliner. It was scheduled to fly from the Yamaguchi prefecture in western Japan to Tokyo's Haneda Airport. But the domestic flight was grounded by Japan's ANA because brake parts to the rear left undercarriage needed replacing, a spokesman at Yamaguchi Ube Airport said. An ANA spokeswoman said: "In the cockpit, an error message related to its brake system was displayed. "The exact nature and the cause of the error message is not clear yet." All 98 passengers on board were switched to another flight for Tokyo. On Tuesday, a Japan Airlines jet was grounded at Boston Logan International Airport in the US following a fuel leak, a day after another plane of the same type suffered a fire. About 40 gallons (150 litres) of fuel spilled from the jet that was supposed to be bound for Tokyo from Boston last night.</Msg><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1357743902164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:05:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357744238422-48</Id><Topic><Title>BRAKEING NEWS ! (No pun Intended) Another 787 flight canceled this time due to BRAKE WARNING LIGHT !</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1357743902164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:05:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow amazing a plane could have a break problem. Check you car brakes Kored then check your short account. The brokerage has a call out for you!!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1357744238422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:10:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357744673821-49</Id><Title>MCD one of the most abused stocks</Title><Msg>check it out</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357744673821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:17:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357744754547-50</Id><Topic><Title>goodnight shorts</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357742511297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>up 2.50 batterys were made in japan,,,,short the battery companys HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357744754547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:19:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357745052683-51</Id><Topic><Title>ALL BA CONTRACTS WILL BE DEALYED AND HOLD!!!!</Title><Username>patrickstock</Username><Timestamp>1357743620683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't delay your trip to your psychiatrist please!</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1357745052683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:24:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357745313145-52</Id><Topic><Title>ALL BA CONTRACTS WILL BE DEALYED AND HOLD!!!!</Title><Username>patrickstock</Username><Timestamp>1357743620683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:00:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is short and caught,,,,lmao</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357745313145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:28:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357745389525-53</Id><Topic><Title>MCD one of the most abused stocks</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357744673821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:17:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does BA Message Board have to do with MCD?</Msg><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357745389525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:29:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357745722311-54</Id><Title>BA gets an outperform reiterate from Oppenheimer.</Title><Msg>According to TipRanks the Analyst is Yair Reiner. and as a matter of fact he is a pretty good one as well (surprised? so am i :) ) I ran into his upgrade at MarketWatch and TipRanks displayed his statistics.. so here they are: 1) he is ranked (today but it might change) #227 out of 1600 analysts. 2) since 2009 following his recommendations on average outperformed the S&amp;P500 by 13.5% 3) out of the last 14 buy/sell ratings his success rate was 64% (9 that where better than the market). 4) he is ranked the best performing analyst covering BA and the 2 after him (Howard Rubel and Richard Tortoriello) also have Buy ratings.</Msg><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357745722311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357745755372-55</Id><Title>Copper Wire was replaced by Aluminum on 787 ! Isn't Aluminum wire dangerous because it expands</Title><Msg>and shrinks more than copper ? Didn't they make a lot of homes wired with aluminum then they had fires due to the aluminum wireing espcially prevalant in trailers houses I beleive ? Boeing says 60 miles of copper wire was eliminated in 787 on their web site does that mean 60 miles of aluminum wire in 787 ?</Msg><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1357745755372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:35:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357745808452-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Gun Control</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357742500487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>idiot !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357745808452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:36:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357745849754-57</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones: Best Night of Television Ever</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357690656502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have that quite right. Alex Jones is the number 1 TWIT trend.</Msg><Username>gerbilfood4me</Username><Timestamp>1357745849754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:37:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357746046374-58</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones: Best Night of Television Ever</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357690656502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who the heck is twitter? Alex Jones is a good example of the lunatic fringe that need to be mentally evaluated before denying them weapons. dudes like the #1 Wack Job! right ahead of his followers</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1357746046374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:40:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357746441579-59</Id><Topic><Title>MCD one of the most abused stocks</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357744673821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:17:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think stocks like CAT CMI TOL MCD HD BA are quality stocks that fall under one group</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357746441579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:47:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357746672061-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Gun Control</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357742500487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It all started with the fake tears.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1357746672061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:51:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357746920600-61</Id><Topic><Title>MCD one of the most abused stocks</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357744673821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:17:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i cant see anything in common. They are all totally different industries that are exposed to different global trends. Have you ever tried to compare the graphs of CAT, BA and MCD? it looks like spaghetti.</Msg><Username>donnapinkwater</Username><Timestamp>1357746920600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:55:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357747115184-62</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones: Best Night of Television Ever</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357690656502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Piers Morgan just last night had guests on who said Alex Jones should be killed...and had his family threatened. Think thats normal and acceptable behavior from the "anti-gun" crowd do you ? Dangerous hypocrites all of them</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357747115184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:58:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357747155871-63</Id><Topic><Title>goodnight shorts</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357742511297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure the real issue is your need to buy some new shorts. Get them quick before all you have are soiled.</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1357747155871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:59:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357747274143-64</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones: Best Night of Television Ever</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357690656502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“I don’t care what the justification is that you’re allowed in this country to own a semi-automatic weapon – much less a handgun. But what do you need a semi-automatic weapon for? The only reason I think you’d need it is, Piers, challenge Alex Jones to a boxing match, show up with a semi-automatic that you got legally and pop him,” said Daily Beast sports columnist Buzz Bissinger. Abby Huntsman (Huffington Post) : “I’d love to see that… [laughter] in uniform.” Piers Morgan: “I’ll borrow my brothers uniform.” So what’s the takeaway from this “undignified” and “unedifying” exchange? Turn in your guns or we will shoot you? When conservatives merely hint at violence even in the context of satire, the liberal blogosphere and the corporate networks explode with feigned outrage, yet when a prime time CNN host and his guests make light of murder, it’s no big deal. Piers Morgan has spent weeks rhetorically assaulting the constitutional rights of Americans in the name of preventing mass murders in America, yet then proceeds to make fun of murdering people on his prime time CNN show. Imagine if Alex Jones had joked about assassinating Piers Morgan. What do you think the reaction would have been then? Is CNN comfortable with one of its main hosts making veiled murder threats live on air?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357747274143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:01:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357747823891-65</Id><Title>Fire aboard an aircraft is very very bad within such a confined space and time to emergency land. Some say</Title><Msg>that it the worse possible scenario with burning alive and choking, etc. So why is the pps up?</Msg><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1357747823891</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:10:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357748165032-66</Id><Title>Panic is over</Title><Msg>shake out done</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357748165032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:16:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357748307106-67</Id><Topic><Title>Panic is over</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357748165032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:16:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shorts are still skaking.....</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357748307106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:18:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357748562530-68</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know of one pilot that comes close but sadly, he doesn't have a pair.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357748562530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357748753478-69</Id><Topic><Title>Panic is over</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357748165032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:16:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, shorts don't have to shake at all. They know there is little upside in this Obama created, terrible economy with 3 more economic cliffs to take on in the near future. Lots of downside potential, and no upside.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357748753478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:25:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357749014954-70</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Gun Control</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357742500487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty obvious what Obama has wanted. He's weighed the political price he would pay for turning against the gun lobby, and the NRA, and gun owners, and his desire to do just what you said. He gave speeches at the UN as to his desire for gun control. Hillary did as well. When you are a slimy liberal, you have to read between the lines as to what they want, not what they often say.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357749014954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:30:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357749352816-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Gun Control</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357742500487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It all started with the fake tears. Obummer is real good at that. When he came to NJ after Sandy and said we will get all the help we need.......69 days later they gave up 9 bil......</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1357749352816</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:35:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357749854037-72</Id><Topic><Title>Copper Wire was replaced by Aluminum on 787 ! Isn't Aluminum wire dangerous because it expands</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1357745755372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:35:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem in homes is not homes being built with aluminum wiring, but homeowners doing repairs by replacing some copper wiring with aluminum, creating a mix of the two.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357749854037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:44:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357750264117-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obama and Gun Control</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357742500487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:41:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 thugs, 7 rounds. That's 3 more than needed.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357750264117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:51:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357750375165-74</Id><Topic><Title>Panic is over</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357748165032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:16:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Air lines across the world need upgrades in planes and equipment also 3 world countries are growing</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357750375165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357750407486-75</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones: Best Night of Television Ever</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357690656502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Insiders claim" is code for "I just made this up".</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1357750407486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:53:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357750627134-76</Id><Topic><Title>Copper Wire was replaced by Aluminum on 787 ! Isn't Aluminum wire dangerous because it expands</Title><Username>kored35</Username><Timestamp>1357745755372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 10:35:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said albucucu.</Msg><Username>artsbest</Username><Timestamp>1357750627134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357751151703-77</Id><Topic><Title>Panic is over</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357748165032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 11:16:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is upside potential because of market manipulation obviously.</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1357751151703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:05:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357751310946-78</Id><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Msg>In my opinion, It is important to see how a long term stock market works vs short term stock With the Quality issues, 1. Boeing needs to improve quality - better assurance and better testing needed. 2. Not a fuel leak - but think of a major event like an accident that can happen with a simple issue. All the airlines that support will back off supporting as once they know lifes can be in a danger. It is nice for someone time to come forward and support it. 3. They shoul plan to update all Dreamers with some bandaid to makesure it is safe to fly. I am sure FAA takes care of this 4. In case of any major issue - does anyone know the insurance companies protect Boeing from any corporate cases against Boeing? I would be careful at this time buying Boeing as we all know it is close to 52 week high. The potential for downside can be significant in case of any unfortunate event.</Msg><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357751408667-79</Id><Topic><Title>BA would certainly come to be the ticker to pay attention to this month.</Title><Username>gary_isakson</Username><Timestamp>1357732711384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 06:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checking it out right now.</Msg><Username>rodrick.gamby</Username><Timestamp>1357751408667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:10:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357752517797-80</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones: Best Night of Television Ever</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357690656502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is fairly common to find this form of hypocrisy from anti-gunners. One al.gore22 made this statement on the MO message board recently, Re: btdt100 by al.gore22 . Dec 19, 2012 5:01 PM, "the best possible thing that could happen is for people s(t)o start shooting up NRA headquarters nationwide, and start murdering every judge, politician and business leader who opposes sensible gun reform." After he was made aware he had been reported to proper authorities, he shortly thereafter quit using is al.gore22 alias and began using al.gore23. He has refused to fully recant or retract his statement. As concerned citizens, we should confront each and every incident of this type head-on. These people need to be put on notice their language provoking physical harm toward others will not be tolerated.</Msg><Username>greedyoilbastards</Username><Timestamp>1357752517797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:28:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357753377856-81</Id><Title>Why the Dreamliner is turning into the NIGHTMAREliner!</Title><Msg>Boeing aircraft used to have an unparelled reputation for safety and reliability. They were simply the best planes in the sky. Why? Because they were built using a vertically integrated system of few, local, high quality suppliers that they could manage and had tight relationships with. These were mainly in the good ole USA! Then they decided to adopt that crazy European system of farming work and components out all over the place. The Europeans did this because of politics. Everyone wanted a piece of the pie. It was a disaster and documentaries made of the problems in language, span of control, work ethic, costs, etc. And then than opera loving CEO, Connors, moved their hq to Chicago to be next to their Civic Opera House. Another crazy move. The corporate headquarters belong next to key manufacturing and testing operations. So the bottom line is that Boeing tried to penny-pitch and it is now landing up costs them gazillions. The y alone had to scrap the first TWO DOZEN PLANES off the production line as beyond repair. And folks it is not going to get any better with these already problem plagued composite wings. With aluminum is is simple cut and patch replace. With these it is a long drawn out process to repair damaged composite which is brittle and does not handle temperature change well. In short I fear, the Dreamliner is well on the way to being Boeing's NIGHTMARE liner!</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753377856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:42:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357753449795-82</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unforetunate event, ...you got that right! See my post on Boeing.</Msg><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753449795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:44:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357753590623-83</Id><Topic><Title>The brake problem was today in Japan. That is 3 days of problems. It is only Wednesday can they go 5 for 5</Title><Username>tommy_loops</Username><Timestamp>1357741179803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 09:19:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should sell, sell, sell. Sell till you don't own any Boeing stock. Then you will have no reason to be concerned and can #$%$.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357753590623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:46:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357753592739-84</Id><Title>Going to tank, nothing resolved. Sell now before it retraces!</Title><Msg>That is how I see it.</Msg><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357753592739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:46:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357753627498-85</Id><Topic><Title>Alex Jones: Best Night of Television Ever</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357690656502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting a lot of web hits or tweets doesn't necessarily mean positive or negative. Just shows interest. A lot of the time that suggests absurdity, and people want to investigate it.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357753627498</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:47:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357754287931-86</Id><Topic><Title>Going to tank, nothing resolved. Sell now before it retraces!</Title><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357753592739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:46:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not whining, just look at the daily chart, it will pull back. Just trying to be helpful :)</Msg><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357754287931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:58:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357754505602-87</Id><Topic><Title>Strike is tomorrow word is...............</Title><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1357703835647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 22:57:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still angry and bitter that we make more than you I see. Pity. You have a very selective memory. We struck for 40 days in 2000 and we'll do so again IF and ONLY IF there's good reason to. Unlike you grease monkeys, we don't cut off our nose to spite our face. That's one of the things that differentiates us from you. You guys often act like petulant little children who throw a temper tantrum if you don't get your way. We're the rational, responsible adults in the room. About all those engineers from Russia and China ... Yes, I'm quite sure you're right. I mean, look at all the highy successful commercial A/Ps that have been designed in those two countries. The world is just beating down the door to buy them. BWAA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA!</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1357754505602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:01:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357754615760-88</Id><Topic><Title>Going to tank, nothing resolved. Sell now before it retraces!</Title><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357753592739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:46:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You see nothing. Boeing still makes the safest planes in the world. The other choice is to go with airbus or Brazilian made airplanes. Take your pick!</Msg><Username>madmonsoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1357754615760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:03:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357754682995-89</Id><Title>Third Boeing Dreamliner problem reported in Japan Link in message section</Title><Msg>http://www.usatoday.com/story/todayinthesky/2013/01/09/boeing-dreamliner-problems-fire/1819873/</Msg><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357754682995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:04:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357754749357-90</Id><Topic><Title>Going to tank, nothing resolved. Sell now before it retraces!</Title><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357753592739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:46:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you sold all your BA stock? If not, why can'y you practice what you preach?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1357754749357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:05:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357754809635-91</Id><Topic><Title>Going to tank, nothing resolved. Sell now before it retraces!</Title><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357753592739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:46:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Third Boeing Dreamliner problem reported in Japan</Msg><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357754809635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:06:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357755221547-92</Id><Title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS 'EXECUTIVE ORDERS' ON GUNS</Title><Msg>Vice President Joe Biden revealed that President Barack Obama might use an executive order to deal with guns. "The president is going to act," said Biden, giving some comments to the press before a meeting with victims of gun violence. "There are executives orders, there's executive action that can be taken. We haven't decided what that is yet. But we're compiling it all with the help of the attorney general and the rest of the cabinet members as well as legislative action that we believe is required." Biden said that this is a moral issue and that "it's critically important that we act." Biden talked also about taking responsible action. "As the president said, if you're actions result in only saving one life, they're worth taking. But I'm convinced we can affect the well-being of millions of americans and take thousands of people out of harm's way if we act responsibly." Biden, as he himself noted, helped write the Brady bill. Eric Holder was scheduled to be at the meeting that's currently take place at the White House.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:13:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357755289456-93</Id><Topic><Title>Going to tank, nothing resolved. Sell now before it retraces!</Title><Username>ambermignone</Username><Timestamp>1357753592739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:46:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody has accused you of having an IQ, so your ignorance is well understood.</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1357755289456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:14:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357755337122-94</Id><Title>This is NOT the Airplanes R us Board.</Title><Msg>This is a Finance Board</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755337122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:15:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357755909757-95</Id><Title>Do airlines charge a bag fee for parachutes?</Title><Msg>I want to wear a parachute when i fly Boeing products. Better safe than sorry. And don't rip me just because you are long the Boeing stock, either. Safety before profits!</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1357755909757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:25:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357756009904-96</Id><Topic><Title>Do airlines charge a bag fee for parachutes?</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1357755909757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:25:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You would have no need for a parachute. The crew would just throw your $#@ out the door!</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1357756009904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:26:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357756188019-97</Id><Topic><Title>Do airlines charge a bag fee for parachutes?</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1357755909757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:25:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they trow you out pull a liberal out with you. If you tell the liberal there's something free at the the bottom he'll jump out and try to get there first.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357756188019</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:29:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357756625136-98</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm an airline pilot that has flown both Boeing and other airliners. Nothing has come close to the Boeing in terms of build quality, reliability, and performance. The "brake problem" was simply a faulty warning, and even if it was a brake issue, these things happen. Fuel leak was 40 gallons, or the equivalent of about .1% of the fuel onboard. The fact it was even discovered leads me to believe it was probably an engine fuel leak that was visually identified. The engines are not made by Boeing. The press is all over this, and I'm sure every single flight that is delayed due to mechanical will be sensationalized by the media. The only REAL issue I have seen is the battery that caught fire. That is definitely one to keep an eye on, but the odds of it being a design problem are almost nil.</Msg><Username>fndmntlinvstr</Username><Timestamp>1357756625136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:37:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357757210566-99</Id><Topic><Title>BA would certainly come to be the ticker to pay attention to this month.</Title><Username>gary_isakson</Username><Timestamp>1357732711384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 06:58:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dont drink it</Msg><Username>adamgutierrez93</Username><Timestamp>1357757210566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:46:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357757309686-100</Id><Title>AAPL QCOM FB all lifting at the same time</Title><Msg>........................and rimm is drooping ? Hmm ?? think think think I hate buying stocks after the news is out</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357757309686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357757564548-101</Id><Topic><Title>This is NOT the Airplanes R us Board.</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755337122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:15:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My point is you should get off this board. Go play with your blow up doll.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357757564548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:52:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357757699589-102</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS 'EXECUTIVE ORDERS' ON GUNS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:13:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what if he did? Do you have a point......besides the one on your head?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357757699589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:54:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357757724506-103</Id><Title>'Teething Problems'</Title><Msg>This is totally mind blowing that the stock is back up and all the analists or referring to these incidents as teething problems...wonder what they would have called it if the electrical fire had occured 1500 miles over the pacific ocean... BOEING WHALE WATCHING TOURS!</Msg><Username>oil042004</Username><Timestamp>1357757724506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:55:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357758166738-104</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS 'EXECUTIVE ORDERS' ON GUNS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:13:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do YOU have a point when you say Chavez supports Obama? You've said it often enough, so your question is moot. And if you had more than half a brain you'd know what I mean.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357758166738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:02:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357758194689-105</Id><Title>Al Gore, Super-Rich Sellout</Title><Msg>The liberal media have spent 12 years feeling sorry for Al Gore. The Man Who Should Have Won in 2000 has had megatons of positive publicity dumped on him, hailing him as the "Goracle." They cheered as leftists honored him with the Nobel Peace Prize and gave an Oscar to his filmed eco-sermon, "An Inconvenient Truth." So when Gore sold his left-wing cable channel Current TV to Al-Jazeera for $500 million, where were they? Despite the fact that conservatives thought the deal sounded like a ridiculous April Fools' joke, the networks had nearly nothing to say. ABC skipped it entirely. CBS and NBC offered a perfunctory sentence on a couple of newscasts. These networks might argue this was not an Earth-shattering business event given the puny size of Current's audience, which is true. At about 42,000 viewers during primetime, the nationwide audience could fit inside the Washington Redskins' Fedex Field and still leave the stadium half-empty. It's about one-fiftieth of the audience TLC gets with "Honey Boo Boo." Of about 96 cable channels that are publicly rated by Nielsen, 93 of them have higher ratings than Current. It is a Nothing Network. But the controversy is not about ratings. It's about one network selling itself to another best known for vicious anti-American propaganda. Al-Jazeera is not buying Current for the potential profits. Surely, they'll shut the old channel down. They want the cable slots to push their poison in American homes. In 2006, CNN's Frank Sesno interviewed Al-Jazeera talk show host Riz Khan and asked if the terrorist group Hamas should be designated as a terrorist organization. "I'm not one to judge," Khan replied. What about Hezbollah? Khan answered: "Same thing, you know, I'm not going to judge." There are other signs of disturbing pro-Islamist bias. In the midst of the "Arab Spring" celebrations in Cairo's Tahrir Square on Feb. 11, 2011, some 200 men sexually assaulted CBS correspondent Lara Logan. Al-Jazeera English, which was credited by Hillary Clinton and other liberals for its ubiquitous coverage of the uprising, deliberately ignored the assault on Logan. When they were called out by Washington Post columnist Jonathan Capehart, Al-Jazeera English publicist responded that the network "believes as a general rule" that journalists "are not the story." Capehart then noted that just days before, Al-Jazeera touted a story on how "Domestic and foreign journalists have come under siege amid the turmoil in Egypt." Brent</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357758194689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:03:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357758718369-106</Id><Title>Lithium Ion battery fire</Title><Msg>I wonder if Fox News will start a Chevy Volt - car fire type charade to scare everyone from 787. I hope Boeing is using some stable chemistry for their batteries (like LiFePo) and didn't just go with the cheapest/lightest supplier. I think its GS Yuasa is their battery supplier.</Msg><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357758718369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:11:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357759159902-107</Id><Topic><Title>Do airlines charge a bag fee for parachutes?</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1357755909757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:25:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!!!LOL!!!!!!that is funny</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357759159902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:19:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357759317699-108</Id><Title>Boeing can't never beat AIrbus A380</Title><Msg>The A380 is the King of the sky!</Msg><Username>soldier_boy63h</Username><Timestamp>1357759317699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:21:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357759326082-109</Id><Title>Obama Protecting America from Gun Fanatics !</Title><Msg>"The president is going to act," Biden said. "There are executives orders, there's executive action that can be taken. We haven't decided what that is yet. But we're compiling it all with the help of the attorney general and the rest of the cabinet members as well as legislative action that we believe is required." Biden suggested that, as he develops a set of proposals for Congress, Obama could use his executive authority now to address gun violence. "We're not going to get caught up in the notion that unless we can do everything, we're going to do nothing," Biden said. " It's critically important that we act."</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357759326082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:22:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357759551909-110</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS 'EXECUTIVE ORDERS' ON GUNS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:13:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357759551909</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:25:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357759961300-111</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing can't never beat AIrbus A380</Title><Username>soldier_boy63h</Username><Timestamp>1357759317699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:21:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yea, cracked wings and all</Msg><Username>suppleej01</Username><Timestamp>1357759961300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:32:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357760388934-112</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS 'EXECUTIVE ORDERS' ON GUNS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:13:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when do game makers become the real solution to the problem? That wacko was a Call of Duty fan and played that awful game in his basement for hours and hours. He was hooked on it. In Connecticut several towns are implementing buy back programs to get these games off the street. When is the president going to address the REAL problem here?</Msg><Username>vernnimble</Username><Timestamp>1357760388934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:39:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357761294474-113</Id><Title>Im not being a #$%$, I do love Boeing, however......</Title><Msg>It is just a question of time before the stock gets hit. Just MHO.</Msg><Username>stockwizard10</Username><Timestamp>1357761294474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:54:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357761359961-114</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing can't never beat AIrbus A380</Title><Username>soldier_boy63h</Username><Timestamp>1357759317699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:21:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and your grammer is so good also.</Msg><Username>stockwizard10</Username><Timestamp>1357761359961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:55:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357761407211-115</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing can't never beat AIrbus A380</Title><Username>soldier_boy63h</Username><Timestamp>1357759317699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:21:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can never vs Can't never......either way......................you're WRONG</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357761407211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:56:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357761450242-116</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore, Super-Rich Sellout</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357758194689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:03:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>E O M E O M</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1357761450242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:57:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357761619521-117</Id><Topic><Title>Blue States just Can't play football.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357680089908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:21:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I much preferred Alabama winning vs Romney and his army of wackos</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357761619521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:00:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357761661649-118</Id><Topic><Title>Shell Game</Title><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1357687596664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:26:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We don't need no stinkin' regulations. Trust us, we know what we're doing.</Msg><Username>randroids</Username><Timestamp>1357761661649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:01:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357761768557-119</Id><Topic><Title>Answer for your question .</Title><Username>travis.ostlund</Username><Timestamp>1357759000496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:16:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing</Msg><Username>lisadavis788</Username><Timestamp>1357761768557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:02:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357761797051-120</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore, Super-Rich Sellout</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357758194689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:03:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish one of the Koch brothers had bought Current......after securing it they could have installed Richard Morris with an hour long show (plus other kooks)........that would have raised the viewship but not the intelligence level</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357761797051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:03:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357762072999-121</Id><Topic><Title>Lithium Ion battery fire</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357758718369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:11:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox is prone to try to torpedo anything that is close to "green" technology.......just want to drill till all the coastline on the east coast is coated with oil slicks, etc</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357762072999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:07:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357762484497-122</Id><Topic><Title>Lithium Ion battery fire</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1357758718369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:11:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean like the millenia old oil slicks around santa barbara in California- no doubt due to G Bush and evil oil ?? drilling there would reduce those...</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357762484497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:14:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357762915715-123</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore, Super-Rich Sellout</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357758194689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:03:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lying liberal mental dwarf who hares freedom. Geeezzzzz this is easy!</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357762915715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:21:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357762935851-124</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Protecting America from Gun Fanatics !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357759326082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:22:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@ "The president is going to act," Well sure he is. He's been good enough at acting and reading his lines to fool most Americans most of the time so why wouldn't he continue to act for four more years? I don't know any gun fanatics personally but I know many anti-gun fanatics. These are the types of idiots that suspend a six year old from school for using his hand to pretend it's a gun during school recess.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357762935851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:22:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357763172115-125</Id><Title>More info on fire from NYC787 blog</Title><Msg>The aircraft from yesterday's incident (ZA183) is still in Boston as the NTSB assigned two more investigators to team looking into the event from yesterday. The team said that the lithium ion battery fire did cause extensive damage in the battery pack area and the damage was confined to no more than 20 inches away from the source. These batteries are used to start the APU. Boeing in a separate statement that this incident is not related to the other electrical issues that the 787 has faced. However, Jon Ostrower reported that United Airlines, while inspecting the lithium ion batteries in one of their 787s, found that the wiring to the batteries were incorrectly connected. This does not mean that the same condition existed in ZA183 or caused the fire but it may it disturbing nonetheless and would be looked into as a possible cause of the fire by the NTSB. The battery fire may be a design issue with the battery, a one off manufacturing flaw, or incorrect installation or maintenance of the battery among the many root causes that the investigators have to examine.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1357763172115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:26:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357763301391-126</Id><Topic><Title>Do airlines charge a bag fee for parachutes?</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1357755909757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:25:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe there should be signs when boarding that warn of the dangers of the possible ignition of petroleum based clothing on Boeing flights? I only wear wool or denim. :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357763301391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:28:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357763472143-127</Id><Title>Talks With Union Resume Today</Title><Msg>"To date, there's been little movement on either side, with Boeing last reported to be demanding union members swallow a reduction in the rate of salary increases, pay more toward the cost of employee health insurance, and begin transitioning from a system of defined pension benefits to one emphasizing individual 401(k) plans. SPEEA is insisting Boeing share more of the wealth from a year in which the company has reported its biggest profits ever."</Msg><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357763472143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:31:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357763589401-128</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing came out and gave the expected statement about reliability. My opinion is that to they have to give the statement and have no choice otherwise people would be scared flying which will impact the company bigtime. If there is a real issue under the hood, I am sure we are going to find out soon.</Msg><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357763589401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:33:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357763672596-129</Id><Topic><Title>Talks With Union Resume Today</Title><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357763472143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:31:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regardless of the issues, this is good news.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357763672596</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:34:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357763815170-130</Id><Title>No selling just slow buying</Title><Msg>BA - 77-78 tomorrow</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357763815170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:36:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357763913932-131</Id><Topic><Title>Talks With Union Resume Today</Title><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357763472143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:31:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why is it good...?</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357763913932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:38:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764040928-132</Id><Topic><Title>Talks With Union Resume Today</Title><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357763472143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:31:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just find it interesting that about the same time union talks resume Boeing should have a fire on a 787. What if anything does it mean?</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357764040928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:40:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764260400-133</Id><Topic><Title>Talks With Union Resume Today</Title><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357763472143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:31:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's good news because it's an issue that has to be dealt with. SPEEA has been working without a contract since sometime in November, which is basically an extension of the old contract, until a new contract is ratified.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357764260400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:44:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764267210-134</Id><Topic><Title>Blue States just Can't play football.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357680089908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:21:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Red State Champions - 18 Blue State Champions - 5 I would have to say Mir is Correct Red State Champions 1990 -2012 2012 *Alabama: BCS 2011 *Alabama: BCS 2010 *Auburn: BCS 2009 *Alabama: BCS 2008 *Florida: BCS 2007 *LSU: BCS 2006 *Florida: BCS 2005 *Texas 2003 *LSU: BCS, 2001 *Miami 2000 *Oklahoma 1999 *Florida State 1996 *Florida 1995 *Nebraska 1994 Florida State 1993 Auburn 1992 *Alabama 1991 *Miami Blue State Champions 1990 - 2012 2004 *Southern California 2002 *Ohio State 1998 Ohio State 1997 *Michigan 1990 *Colorado</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357764267210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:44:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764326340-135</Id><Topic><Title>Talks With Union Resume Today</Title><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357763472143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:31:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It means you're mentally unstable. Please, get some help.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1357764326340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:45:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764766264-136</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot of pilots have that sentiment about the Boeing planes.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357764766264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:52:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764836414-137</Id><Topic><Title>Blue States just Can't play football.</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357680089908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:21:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And as we all know, universities located in "red" states only have players from "red" states on their roster ... Right? Note also that Washington and Miami shared the NC in 1991.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1357764836414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:53:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764882098-138</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know a guy like that but based on his latest Facebook photo looks like he is well over 300 pounds. Probably need a forklift and a K-loader and a Loadmaster to lift him in the chopper and strap him down...he's also a flaming communist who thinks the world owes him a living.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357764882098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:54:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764932076-139</Id><Topic><Title>No selling just slow buying</Title><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1357763815170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:36:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slow buying? You are nots 11M shares is over twice daily volume. Heavy buying would be appropriate</Msg><Username>thisgameistooeasy</Username><Timestamp>1357764932076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:55:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357764961208-140</Id><Topic><Title>Talks With Union Resume Today</Title><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357763472143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:31:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now thats one opinion.. I think we need more clues!!!!!!</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1357764961208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:56:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357765011044-141</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing can't never beat AIrbus A380</Title><Username>soldier_boy63h</Username><Timestamp>1357759317699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:21:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A huge money loser!! 737/767/777/787 will all outsell the A-380 by far</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1357765011044</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:56:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357765499911-142</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the sentence not in quotes that is disturbing.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1357765499911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 16:04:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357765981790-143</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>premul, good post , your right, the way I can tell is the self appointed Boeing mangement enablers for forgiving Boeing Management failure have given you thumbs down. In fact the number one rated stock trader in the USA today just gave a report on Boeing. Phil Grande said BA today is now in the kill zone and institutions are selling out now. 2. Boeing PR is doing 787 damge control, the 777 is being used to compare with the 787, only the comparison is faulty. the 787 had 3 years of late delivery to find and to test and fix the 787, the 777 came out on schedule and while there was a real bad fire on 1 of the 777's it was after several years of service not on a new airplane. The Boeing story is just that, the 787 is a troubled airplane. the major differences , the Union -SPEEA had control of the design on the 777 and does not on the 787, the 777 was built and delivered on time and on budget , the 787 was delived 3.5 years late and 30 billion over budget. Boeing does not have engineering control of their product on the 787. So the problem comes first then the fix, unfortuately a much higher chance to crash and kill passengers. The electric and carbon situation is new. the 777 in my opinion was one of the best planes that Boeing has built, while the 787 was not designed or built by Boeing. if its a outsourced 787 I am not going is what the public thinks now. any more failures reinforces that feeling, the BOAC comet was fixed , after it crashed and killed passengers , but it failed because the comet was not accepted by the public . If the 787 does crash and kill passengers with all the BA hyle and the 4 incidents in 34 days in the publics minds, then most likely the public and therfore the customers will not accept the 787. Time will tell.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357765981790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 16:13:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357766270354-144</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait till five more years you'll be eating these words boy!! BOEING LONG AND STRONG BABY 787!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1357766270354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 16:17:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357767658134-145</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And incredible the Democrats in congress, and the White House are willing to take us down that path. Thinking must be that the liberal, mainstream media will support their BS that is was GW Bush's fault, and the Republicans that caused it.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357767658134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 16:40:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357768614380-146</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Protecting America from Gun Fanatics !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357759326082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:22:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in denial and clueless as usual...!!!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357768614380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 16:56:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357769087199-147</Id><Title>Executive Action imminent to curtail the second amendment.</Title><Msg>I TOLD you Executive action would be taken....there is an Agenda that this administration has been following ever since Obama and Holder performed the False Flag Operation of Fast and Furious to Demonize the second amendment. “The president is going to act,” said Biden. “There are executives orders, there’s executive action that can be taken. We haven’t decided what that is yet. But we’re compiling it all with the help of the attorney general and the rest of the cabinet members as well as legislative action that we believe is required.” “As the president said, if you’re actions result in only saving one life, they’re worth taking. But I’m convinced we can affect the well-being of millions of Americans and take thousands of people out of harm’s way if we act responsibly.” In other words, according to the Obama administration and the Justice Department, if trashing the Constitution saves one life, it is worth it. Issuing an executive action, unlike an executive order, does not modify a law. Executive actions, a Obama administration office told NBC News in October, concern “regulation, enforcement, statements of policy… and numerous other things.” Obama, unlike his predecessors, “is not expanding executive power to meet the demands of an external crisis. Instead, he is counteracting a new pattern of partisan behavior – nonstop congressional obstruction – with a new, partisan pattern of his own,” Andrew Romano and Daniel Klaidman wrote for Newsweek prior to the election. White House communications director Dan Pfeiffer told Newsweek Obama will “work with Congress where we can – and then be willing to act where they won’t.” Obama has already used executive action to instruct the ATF to conficate guns. In September, Obama’s Justice Department gave the ARF authority to “seize and administratively forfeit property involved in controlled-substance abuses.” In other words, the agency now has the power to seize firearms from people not convicted of a crime or even charged with a crime. In July, as the Fast and Furious scandal unfolded, Obama’s Justice Department devised new rules requiring border-state gun dealers to report large purchases of firearms made by individual buyers over short periods of time.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357769087199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:04:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357769650153-148</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would anybody care what a worthless Communist thinks? Perhaps you should be deported?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357769650153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357769675171-149</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS 'EXECUTIVE ORDERS' ON GUNS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:13:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it IS awesome. I can't think of a better use of 'executive order' than this.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1357769675171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:14:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357769748569-150</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think I know which worthless Communist you are referring to. DFC (Dumb #$%$ Communist).</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357769748569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:15:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357769972403-151</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS 'EXECUTIVE ORDERS' ON GUNS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:13:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>totally illegal to circumvent the second amendment.....if it IS legal for an executive order at the Federal level ...then it is legal for a local city manager or a State Governor to use and executive order to NULLIFY the order using the 10th amendment as the legal basis. btw...government CANNOT keep you safe from every contingency.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357769972403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:19:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357770375889-152</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE HOUSE THREATENS 'EXECUTIVE ORDERS' ON GUNS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357755221547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 13:13:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357770375889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:26:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357770477055-153</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"coming from a complete loon......" well God Forbid you would never lauch an off topic adhominem...hit the bricks...You Neo-Maxie-Zendweebie Dork</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357770477055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:27:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357770492366-154</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Protecting America from Gun Fanatics !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357759326082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:22:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is nothing specific in the info you posted of any value. It is Joe Biden, an idiot, saying nothing, which deserves to be made fun of. It's Biden coming to the podium and saying, "We have no idea what we're gonna do but by golly we're gonna do sumpin." That may be Earth shattering news for you to slobber over, but everyone else can see it for the nonsensical twittery that it is. So I mock you.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357770492366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:28:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357770712516-155</Id><Title>Do Democrats think You can Have $trillion deficits forever?</Title><Msg>Are all of them economic illiterates? Do the think there's no consequence to this insane spending? Did they really believe their own lies about Obamacare lowering insurance premiums?</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357770712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:31:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357770803081-156</Id><Topic><Title>Bug-out Bags, Gold, Food and Weapons</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357668501812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:08:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz is the Kent Raven.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357770803081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:33:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357770980863-157</Id><Topic><Title>Far More Children are killed by Scalpel and Suction Devices Than Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357653501840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 08:58:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or Children killed by Drones in the Middle East by the Nobel Peace bombs or ......</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357770980863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:36:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357771219892-158</Id><Topic><Title>Far More Children are killed by Scalpel and Suction Devices Than Guns</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1357653501840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 08:58:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many are MURDERED by scalpel and suction devices? THAT is the more relevant question.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1357771219892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:40:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357771234675-159</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Protecting America from Gun Fanatics !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357759326082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:22:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you gorilla face chimp... everyday Joe is in office is Great news to me !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357771234675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:40:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357771309036-160</Id><Title>The Only Way To Keep Congress From Wasting Your Money......</Title><Msg>.......is not to give it to them in the first place. Get a legal tax avoidance plan. Minimize your taxes with off-shore trusts and corporations.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357771309036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:41:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357771436717-161</Id><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Msg>....to demonize the second amendment...coupled with full spectrum Government run CNN and MSNBC Media coverage on the "Evil of guns" ... Any Vegas odds on the Time Frame ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357771497135-162</Id><Topic><Title>Talks With Union Resume Today</Title><Username>wallstsharks</Username><Timestamp>1357763472143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 15:31:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it means you are a flake- the fire was in an area of section 48 assembled in SC btw</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357771497135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:44:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357771725382-163</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Protecting America from Gun Fanatics !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357759326082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:22:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@ you gorilla face chimp Racist! @ ... everyday Joe is in office is Great news to me !! It's nice to see that Joe Biden sends a thrill up your leg</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1357771725382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:48:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357771774775-164</Id><Title>Romney's Inauguration !</Title><Msg>dear Republicons... Mr Romney's Inaugural speech has been postponed... indefinitely !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357771774775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:49:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357772007762-165</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you suppose you make the same typos as the Kent Raven?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357772007762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:53:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357772157080-166</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for proving my point, you DFC (Dumb Fg Communist)</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357772157080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:55:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357772257565-167</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not at all...I feel my COUNTRY is in Danger....A Country for which I took an oath and was prepared to write a check for ..a Check that was cashable up to an INCLUDING my life....for an amount of time that included 3 wars and encompassed 26 years. Dweebs who never served a day in uniform who think they can intimidate me on a message board are delusional.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357772257565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:57:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357772321931-168</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you waiting your time here, Sparty? Please research the END of the World that happened 12/12/12. The government and trilateral commission are conspiring to keep this quiet. Please get right on it.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1357772321931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:58:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357772355687-169</Id><Title>How to Pay Zero Income Taxes</Title><Msg>Here's some goo advice from a CPA - just Type the above title in a search engine then go down to Vernon Jacob's website,.</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357772355687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:59:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357772396415-170</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This anti-gun cropola is all part of the liberal progressive agenda! It's a GD conspiracy! The Silent Majority is on to your game!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1357772396415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:59:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357773062228-171</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Protecting America from Gun Fanatics !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357759326082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:22:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somehow dieing from a gunshot wound seems more compassionate than dieing from multiple stab wounds. Don't you think? I'm more afraid of a serrated knife then I am a handgun.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1357773062228</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 18:11:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357773155996-172</Id><Title>Hi. I'm Paul McCartney...</Title><Msg>Most of you probably know me as the writer of such songs as "Yesterday", "Penny Lane", "Let It Be", and "Live and Let Die". But today, I am here to teach you how to pay zero in taxes. Oh, wait... I'm rich. What the hell do I care about taxes? Only a loser would worry about a measly $5 million.</Msg><Username>sir_paul_mccartney777</Username><Timestamp>1357773155996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 18:12:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357773434734-173</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Dreamliner is turning into the NIGHTMAREliner!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753377856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I too have read about how difficult it is to work with fiber composities and their unreliability in heavy use. Years ago the Austrailians were showcasing their latest prized state-of-art fiber composite racing yacht. As it left the warm waters of Syndey harbour and went into the colder ocean waters cracks appeared and the yacht soon broke up and sank to become "the fastest yacht on the bottom of the ocean". Luckily for the crew there were many media boats around tp pick them up. Unlucky though for the Austrailian's ship building reputation, the whole world got to see their latest and greatest high tech effort break up!</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1357773434734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 18:17:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357774085707-174</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats think You can Have $trillion deficits forever?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357770712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:31:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats don't think - they react to their emotions. If any thing goes wrong, it triggers an auto response from their left side brains that causes them to automatically utter "it's George Bushe's fault.' They are perfect and never have to be responsible for anything. That's why Obama can say straight faced, "we don't have a spending problem."</Msg><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357774085707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 18:28:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357775360917-175</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Dreamliner is turning into the NIGHTMAREliner!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753377856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Connors was NOT CEO when move to chicago - try stonedcipher</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357775360917</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 18:49:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357775991717-176</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOSTON — Japan Airlines is giving more details about a fuel leak on one of its Boeing 787s that delayed a nonstop flight from Boston to Tokyo. A spokeswoman said Wednesday that one of four valves connecting the center and left main fuel tanks was open. That led to fuel flowing between those tanks to a surge tank near the wing tip and then out a vent, spilling about 40 gallons. She says that valve was deactivated and the flight was cleared to depart later Tuesday. A more detailed inspection was scheduled in Tokyo.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357775991717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 18:59:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357776709964-177</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats think You can Have $trillion deficits forever?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357770712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:31:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is the deal. Socialism depends on massive spending of tax payer money. You lie about the need for a windfall tax on those evil Big Oil Co's. No congressional lib would ever tell the folks how much tax revenue the govt receives every quarter from the Big Oil Co.'s. It is huge. They lie about man induced global warming, and the need to heavily tax Corporate America in order to save the planet. Called the carbon tax, and the ignorant buy into it. It would kill what economy we have if ennacted. They go after the successful that create jobs trying to milk more out of them. The need to drum up every source of revenue they can to pay for socialism, and now they are scrapping the bottom of the barrel...WE are BROKE!</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1357776709964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:11:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357777389075-178</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Dreamliner is turning into the NIGHTMAREliner!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753377856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the wires 010913: There was no immediate suggestion that the 787 Dreamliner, the world's first passenger jet built mainly from carbon-plastic lightweight materials to save fuel, was likely to be grounded as investigators looked into the fire incident.</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1357777389075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:23:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357778825003-179</Id><Topic><Title>Here's the Best Argument Ever for Gun Control</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357776639185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:10:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the best argument you've got is the ad hominem, maybe you'd better find another issue.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1357778825003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:47:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357779119228-180</Id><Topic><Title>The Only Way To Keep Congress From Wasting Your Money......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357771309036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:41:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Until you starve-the-beast types support military budget cuts of 80% you're only showing your hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1357779119228</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:51:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357781461154-181</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bongo 52, I rog. Sabre 6, out.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357781461154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 20:31:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357782046000-182</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe in 5 years... but real questions now at Boeing... 787 issues, strike, defense spending cuts. Justin Beiber says buy at 52 week high.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1357782046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 20:40:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357782205962-183</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats think You can Have $trillion deficits forever?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357770712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:31:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The need to drum up every source of revenue they can to pay for socialism, and now they are scrapping the bottom of the barrel...WE are BROKE! *** Obama has instituted the European model economy in America. You can see our future across the pond. You vill all be equal.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1357782205962</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 20:43:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357782297381-184</Id><Topic><Title>Here's the Best Argument Ever for Gun Control</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357776639185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:10:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saudi bin Laden Construction is building the tallest building in the world -- a 1 kilometer tall skyscraper that drafts the Burj Khalifa. Now, that's a stimulus package!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1357782297381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 20:44:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357782465059-185</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bongo 52</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357782465059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 20:47:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357782714645-186</Id><Topic><Title>Here's the Best Argument Ever for Gun Control</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357776639185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:10:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're attacking an argument not on its merits or lack of same but by illegitimately and irrationally associating it with one man you dislike.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1357782714645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 20:51:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357783331449-187</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Inauguration !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357771774775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:49:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>47%</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357783331449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:02:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357784528636-188</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Inauguration !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357771774775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:49:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...idiot</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1357784528636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:22:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357785108316-189</Id><Topic><Title>Here's the Best Argument Ever for Gun Control</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357776639185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:10:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it as unstable as when Piers Morgan had guests on the next NIGHT and laugh while they were threatening Alex Jones family with being shot ? YES THATS RIGHT ! You're a flaming hypocrite</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357785108316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357785826270-190</Id><Title>*****Gun Control Advocates are Racists*****</Title><Msg>The first gun control advocates were the Ku Klux Klan.... Arican Americans couldnt defend themselves...its true</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357785826270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:43:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357786037501-191</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder when the next Staged shooting will take place</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357771436717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:43:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes...folks are waking up to the fact that there IS an agenda to disarm law abiding Americans</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357786037501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:47:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357786985186-192</Id><Topic><Title>*****Gun Control Advocates are Racists*****</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357785826270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:43:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your brains are scrambled, your idiocy is monumental, and your mental health issues are probably beyond help. I am glad the Air Force booted you out before your screwed up head could cause any real problems.</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1357786985186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 22:03:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357787366809-193</Id><Topic><Title>*****Gun Control Advocates are Racists*****</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357785826270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:43:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're just another DFC.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1357787366809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 22:09:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357787406464-194</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats think You can Have $trillion deficits forever?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357770712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:31:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of your problem, how's that conversion from C to F going? Care to lecture again?</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1357787406464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 22:10:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357787594804-195</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats think You can Have $trillion deficits forever?</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1357770712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:31:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In short, yes, According to the W_O_N, the US doesn't have a spending problem!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1357787594804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 22:13:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357787597804-196</Id><Topic><Title>*****Gun Control Advocates are Racists*****</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357785826270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:43:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A sure sign you are a fool, any one you disagree with is called a #$%$". You would have to get a lot smarter to reach "pathetic".</Msg><Username>freedumber</Username><Timestamp>1357787597804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 22:13:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357787828569-197</Id><Topic><Title>*****Gun Control Advocates are Racists*****</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357785826270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:43:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And yet another throw down my gun @ Charlie and run Dim! Pitiful...just pitiful!!!</Msg><Username>badolt</Username><Timestamp>1357787828569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 22:17:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357787836070-198</Id><Title>Sixty thousand flights take off daily around the world....</Title><Msg>is the Boeing 787 the only plane having incidents? I smell a rat. Boeing stock up today at $76 and change. Go Boeing!</Msg><Username>maramwp</Username><Timestamp>1357787836070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 22:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357787992248-199</Id><Topic><Title>Quality Issues with Boeing Airlines - My opinion</Title><Username>pvemul</Username><Timestamp>1357751310946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:08:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in 5 years ? you could use your investment money for better stock now and return to Boeing stock for example look at BAC on the yahoo stock chart for the year ,compare BAC to BA . BAC was a buy based on charting at the w formations aound March 12, Jul12 and November 12, a new investor could have got in, and you missed 90% investor gain on BAC. now BAC is a short term top and sell on the M formation,Another stock comparison , you can compare BA to LMT(Lockheed ) and you missed 16%. If you like BA then first make 90% on BAC and then invest in BA when ready. Today you can go to the Phil Grande show online and listen to todays radio show , Grande singled out BA for a "kill zone" stock and stay away. He shows you the chart on the show go online to the archieved free shows . Grande is the number 1 rated stock chart trader in the USA, he does not use fire, plane order, stock buyback , only charts and now according to Grande , BA. is not a buy. Or you can trade your opinion and ignor the charts , the fundamentals that Boeing and another user here sure have not worked. Plane orders and EPS and sizzle talk , do not beat a good chart and then you know when the big investor institutions are selling out of BA . According to Grande .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357787992248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 22:19:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357791369388-200</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's Inauguration !</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1357771774775</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:49:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Romney in a Landslide"......#$%$ Morris (Fox News)</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357791369388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:16:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357791436185-201</Id><Topic><Title>332, 3, 8, 88, and 44 are all Good Numbers.</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1357773286373</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 18:14:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Add 47 to the group</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357791436185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:17:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357791506209-202</Id><Topic><Title>How to Pay Zero Income Taxes</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357772355687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:59:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try jobless if you're that determined to pay nothing</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357791506209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:18:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357791640353-203</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing can't never beat AIrbus A380</Title><Username>soldier_boy63h</Username><Timestamp>1357759317699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 14:21:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You want to fly DIRECT or do you prefer the hub &amp; spoke wheel........sorry A380....you can only fit into so many airports and it's not that MANY!!!</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357791640353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:20:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357791961499-204</Id><Topic><Title>The Only Way To Keep Congress From Wasting Your Money......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357771309036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:41:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When was the last time somebody really showed interest in us being in Afghanistan</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357791961499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:26:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357792058002-205</Id><Topic><Title>Here's the Best Argument Ever for Gun Control</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1357776639185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 19:10:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the most paranoid man in America" Even more than Spartaloon?</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1357792058002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:27:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357792216013-206</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Dreamliner is turning into the NIGHTMAREliner!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753377856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing did a little more homework than you give them credit on composite technology....their problem was outsourcing too much of the aircraft structure (thanks McD &amp; H. Stonecipher....good biz model)</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1357792216013</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:30:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357792558496-207</Id><Topic><Title>*****Gun Control Advocates are Racists*****</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357785826270</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 21:43:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Damn....that had to leave a welt. Good one</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357792558496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:35:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357793328503-208</Id><Title>Boeing sure bought a lot today</Title><Msg>Thank god they reinstituted that 3.5B buy back program last month. I wonder if they had an idea they would need it so soon?</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1357793328503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:48:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357793487007-209</Id><Topic><Title>The Only Way To Keep Congress From Wasting Your Money......</Title><Username>mir_roguns</Username><Timestamp>1357771309036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 17:41:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Military Industrial Complex Security State is not compatiable with a Democratic Republic...so Libertarians usually ARE and SHOULD be at the forefront of peacefully brining the troops home...on both Constitutional Grounds and on Fiscal monetary grounds....we simply CANNOT AFFORD TO BE THE POLICEMAN OF THE WORLD....Even Though Republican and Neocons are fiscally conservative...they always get the Welfare debate correct but never the warfare debate right......The Liberals on the other hand......they are simply cult members that well obey ANYTHING their leaders tell them ..because its...you know ..... hip and trendy and liberal.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1357793487007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:51:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357793686920-210</Id><Topic><Title>Why the Dreamliner is turning into the NIGHTMAREliner!</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1357753377856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 12:42:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Composit structure is not the problem. Outsourcing is the problem and we all know it. We have worked with composits on aircraft for years on the military side of the house in all kinds of weather and under stress. We have our chit together. This will be a revolution in aerospace.</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1357793686920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 23:54:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>