<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370059489104-1</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh you poor poor feeble fool. Worry not, as worry does you nothing and owes you nothing. your ranking system is ill informed. 6. China -by their hacking American web sites, stealing of intellectual property and military technology and secrets. Is far more sinister than your ignorant knewledge betrays even you. These threats are mostly to the middle east and maybe, by a slim amount, parts of Europe. al qaeda terrorists 2. I ran -nuclear threat 3. I ranian surrogate terrorists- Hizbollah and Assad of Syria I don't live over there so I don't care. 4. North Korea is only a threat to the south. I don't live over there so I don't care. 5. Russia -terrorist arms supplier Again, I don't care unless it is something aimed at me. I just attached a 6 part story about China and thats only the unclass stuff. China has huge coffers of US dollars and Euro's. In a very short time they've gone from wooden dummy rifles for their army to space stations. Their grad students learn well while they are in the US or Tel Aviv University. Next time you sit down for your bowl of matzah ball, er ah, wonton soup, ask yourself how much of this bill is going outside the country to people that don't like me. Reading ahead I see that your blaming the ficticious Ahkmed for a problem. Typical. Some men just want to see the world burn, and some men want to commodify it. When the Boston Marathon Bombings happened, loads of images were flooding the internet. Photo based sharing network Instagram started the #PrayForBoston hashtag and many images from the event were made public. One man, Steve Goldstein, tried to make some extra dough from all these photos–so he put together a small photo book and charged money for it. Its the Goldsteins of the world I worry more about than I worry about al qaeda</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370059489104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370059609444-2</Id><Topic><Title>America's Main Adversaries</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370010788696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 10:33:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tea Party are a bunch of tea bagging, tax dodging, PHONIES.</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370059609444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 00:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370062831694-3</Id><Title>As you know from my early morning Saturday posting</Title><Msg>u a b\unch ot tweeters we/us only feathers in our mouths and claws loiol;l Treat was a song in the high school gymnasium featuring Carlos Santana and Greg Rolle near Veterans Day 1968 and a bunch of otters Good Morning Sunshine</Msg><Username>fourmoreprog</Username><Timestamp>1370062831694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 01:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370062947031-4</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>August 28, 1996 Social Justice Friends: I guess I should open up this letter by thanking you all for helping to make Social Justice such a success. Right now about 4,000 people receive the e-mail version while another 500 visit our web version every month. Quite good when you conider that the whole operation is managed by Kim and I out of our home computer. I'm writing today to ask a personal favor. As you probably know, I am a law student interested in issues of human rights and sustainable development. I am currently looking for a job for the summer of 1997. My hope is that some of you can give me some good leads and/or pass on my resume to someone who might. I am geographically flexible and thus available for work anywhere. Brief Bio: In 1988, I was a twenty year old staff member on a state assembly campaign in California. The federal amnesty law granting citizenship to illegal residents had just been passed and there were high hopes in the immigrant communities of Southern California. Our campaign had spent months registering these new citizens to vote and more importantly, convincing them that it was safe to vote. Not only had the majority of these people fled nations where political activity often brought death, but they had survived as illegal immigrants in the United States by consciously avoiding any contact with the authorities. Registering to vote for them was a courageous act. On election day our opponent hired uniformed security guards to intimidate the non-white voters at the polls. Our campaign office was flooded with calls from people accusing us of betraying them. The word went out that the entire amnesty program was a scam and that the authorities were waiting for people. Tragically, I'm afraid that this incident made many of these new american citizens lose their faith in democracy.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370062947031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 01:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370062998408-5</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On election day our opponent hired uniformed security guards to intimidate the non-white voters at the polls. Our campaign office was flooded with calls from people accusing us of betraying them. The word went out that the entire amnesty program was a scam and that the authorities were waiting for people. Tragically, I'm afraid that this incident made many of these new american citizens lose their faith in democracy. I emerged from this experience with an understanding that being "right" is not a talisman against misfortune. One must be able to articulate and defend one's rights. I found myself strongly drawn towards positions that allowed me to help the powerless articulate their rights and navigate their way through our society. I went on to work for a well known environmental group and then to a position working with gang members and homeless teenagers in Seattle, Washington, USA. In 1991, I began my undergraduate studies, graduating with a B.A. in Political- Economy in 1995. That fall I began my first year of law school and have just completed a summer position working for a non- profit agency that defends whistleblowers who have been punished for raising safety and environmental concerns on government projects. I now hope to find a position that will allow me act within the same theme of social justice work. An e-mail version of my resume will follow this letter. I appreciate any help that you may be able to give me. Sincere Thanks, Ray Goforth</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370062998408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 01:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370072682632-6</Id><Title>Boeing talks with future 777x customers British Airways, Emirates,Qatar and Air Lease Corp</Title><Msg>Discussions to refine aspects of the 777x design and performance. Like that approach a whole lot as this could be their bread and butter system for years to come. Make the Customer happy. Already I hear freighter discussions are happening</Msg><Username>rs2ms2ts2ks72</Username><Timestamp>1370072682632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 03:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370085408429-7</Id><Title>Tornado Alley</Title><Msg>And Boeing wants to move more business to St Louis, that's a bad business plan.</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1370085408429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 07:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370092137503-8</Id><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Msg>Might have a shot...since both parties are now depised by the American people. Ventura would be the first to win as a President without a Party since George Washinton</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370093181803-9</Id><Topic><Title>'Liberal Activist' Admits to Bugging Mitch McConnell's Office</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370036572652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>holy cow, looks like ahkmed, err sparty, has another clone for jumbo..jumboYjetski seems he's also confused bout the origins of the klan “the Democrat Party is as it always has been, the party of the four S's: slavery, secession, segregation and now socialism. It was the Democrats who fought to keep blacks in slavery and passed the discriminatory Black Codes and Jim Crow laws. The Democrats started the Ku Klux Klan to lynch and terrorize blacks. The Democrats fought to prevent the passage of every civil rights law beginning with the civil rights laws of the 1860s, and continuing with the civil rights laws of the 1950s and 1960s.”</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370093181803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370093338880-10</Id><Title>787 fundamental cost saving</Title><Msg>At the start of the 787 program, Boeing’s leadership in Chicago insisted on the need to reduce the development cost by bringing in “risk-sharing partners” who would take on — and help pay for — more of the development work. Hans Weber, a leading aviation-engineering consultant, calls this the “fundamental weakness in the 787 program from the start.” This was “ultimately a financial invention. It’s not done for technical reasons,” Weber said. Internal documents showed Boeing planned to spend just $5 billion to develop the 787, a figure that later ballooned to at least 30 billion dollars . So now you know why the 787 will never make a dime for the Boeing shareholders its a dead cat bounce plane .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370093338880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370093506759-11</Id><Topic><Title>787 fundamental cost saving</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370093338880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How to take a formerly high-quality, high-profession, ethical company and let the bean counters run it into the ground. Through short-sighted, selfish greed.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370093506759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370093566981-12</Id><Topic><Title>Va. school board member asked to resign over racist Michelle Obama emails</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045437149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumbocrats are politically sensitive, free speech and equal rights take a back seat anyone lost their job at the IRS yet? commie/terrorist friendly state dept? injustice? homeland insecurity? moochelle's hand maidens?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370093566981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370093928576-13</Id><Topic><Title>787 fundamental cost saving</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370093338880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you get laid on wayne, or do you prefer to live on the dole, like sparty?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370093928576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370094216892-14</Id><Topic><Title>Va. school board member asked to resign over racist Michelle Obama emails</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045437149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no such thing as being a racist to a liberal if you are a Black. That is acceptable. It is only racism is a Caucasian makes a fried chicken joke. Obama tends to try to avoid his racist feelings after the gaff he made calling Hillary a racist. He acts like he is above it all, but is very happy to send out his thugs, and make the racist statements in his behalf, and then never criticize them for making the racist remarks.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370094216892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:43:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370094382477-15</Id><Topic><Title>'Liberal Activist' Admits to Bugging Mitch McConnell's Office</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370036572652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This "bugging" of the other parties offices was a standard activity, until Nixon was caught doing it, and then it was a terrible offense....far worse than BO allowing the 4 American's to be murdered, or calling in the IRS, and having them target Tea Party Organizations, or providing weapons to Mexican Drug lords that got our border agent murdered.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370094382477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370094483577-16</Id><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Msg>Airbus is in a s trend that stretches from Friday up .5% to this week up 3.8% to the year to date up 45% to five years up 146% to being the number one plane builder in the world for 11 straight years Boeing stock price trend is very clear too, the wrong way!, down Friday 1.5%, for 5 days down .86%, for the year both lagging Airbus at up 31%, but going down from its high point at 32% last week( airbus is now at 45% up from lower gains the week before) that is a trend and for 5 years Boeing is now slipped to only 20%, down from 22% earlier this year. What is driving this negative stock price trend the fake rally is over, the Boeing company was buying their own shares back to cover the 787 grounding for 3 months. Boeing executives are too greedy to keep that up now .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370094498232-17</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are making a bold assumtion there...that Jesse Ventura "thinks" The guy's a space case. He's even talked about seeing space ships landing on earth with little green people getting out of them.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370094498232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370094834565-18</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty luvs space cases, the whackier the better, negative value added and enemy friendly a bonus</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370094834565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370095428798-19</Id><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Msg>$120,000 not counting dividend. Airbus , that same amount of $100,000 is now worth $246,000 not counting a better dividend than Boeing pays. why ? Boeing executives are too greedy paying themselves for failure to produce .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370096691943-20</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA???</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1370007633781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:40:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A good question that wayne skips.I also noticed TSLA is losing 2.70 a share?</Msg><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1370096691943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370097278944-21</Id><Title>Final May delivery count</Title><Msg>55 planes 36 737's. 3 747's. 5 767's. 5 777's. 6 787's.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370097278944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:34:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370097596321-22</Id><Topic><Title>Final May delivery count</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370097278944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got one more 777 delivered yesterday to make the final count 55 planes.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370097596321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370098271030-23</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA???</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1370007633781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:40:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right. Wayneker doesn't say anything about his TSLA when it drops like it did yesterday down 6.81% or his JRCC which went down 5.47%.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370098271030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370098701622-24</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sparty luvs space cases, the whackier the better" censored... actually, that's true.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370098701622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370098754640-25</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still he's much better than Prez O or Romney, but then most people would be.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370098754640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370098805705-26</Id><Topic><Title>Va. school board member asked to resign over racist Michelle Obama emails</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370045437149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:10:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Tough t I t t I e s." Wow... very profound thought, freeveritas. And so eloquently expressed.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370098805705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:00:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370098821499-27</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have a link for stating that he has SEEN little green people ... Personally I think Ventura represents mainstream American values and the Constitutional view of the Republic far more then any candidate from last election cycle (other then Ron Paul) ... You should back up your claims if you're going to make them</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370098821499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370098961813-28</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly...Ventrua is the type of antidote America needs..the definition of insanity is doing the same tired thing over and over....picking the same tired candidates from either party has FAILED AMERICA..and this is no longer even debatable. Ventrua ...or someone like him</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370098961813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370099066955-29</Id><Title>unposter uniposter same old BHT your right but you missed a 16 day 100% stock price gain your 100% right</Title><Msg>unposter who cares! from May 3 at 55 dollars per share to 16 days later at $110 per share. BTW, I posted on May 3 to buy it and made 100%. You have a point / But This is a financial message board , are you making a stock market statement? I guess not. Every good investor knows that there is nothing new or special about tesla. If this lithium battery thing was a go ,the big 3 would be all over it. They have all the technology that Elon has. This is a rich persons, look at me, car. What he did right , Elon is combining his companies on the battery supercharge idea.Secondly the secondary offering was going to be supported by the government so it was a easy choice. If you learn to be a stock trader and look at this as a fake game which the stock market is now, it is easy to become a very rich person. Next, take a look, the tesla is good looking toy for a rich person . I make money in the stock market, so it was a slam dunk to follow the modern version of Steve Jobs a money making maverick, on the tesla . He decides what the public wants and gives it to them . Fisker on the other hand had a, what was he thinking , idea for the recharge problem; a storage warehouse of batteries to stop in and get a replacement what was Fisker thinking ? Fisker , no car owner wants to go to a repair shop every few hundred miles and wait for a new battery. Finally besides under engineered and breaking down the car was just not as nice looking. for a toy, you have to be good looking. same thing with the Boeing 787, under engineered and they break down. Same problem with the 787, Boeing's greedy bean counter style management , who take customer surveys and gives airlines want what is technologally not ready for prime time aka 787 all composite passenger plane . You need to go with leaders like Elon not failures like Jim Mcturdy kicked out by Jack Welch for being sub par.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370099066955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370099099647-30</Id><Topic><Title>God punishing Oklahomans</Title><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1370045184467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:06:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really need to stay on your medication. I know it's hard for you to remember to take it, but it's important!</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370099099647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:04:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370099217562-31</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty likes the fringe kooks, incompetents, and others who have the potential of being destructive</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370099217562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370099307289-32</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What make you think that?</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1370099307289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370099614066-33</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA???</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1370007633781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:40:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unposter your slow and late as usual, I gave you a complete answer that will burn your ears off now be a good student and go read it under my unposter uniposter headline , and learn something , you should pay me for this education Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370099614066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370099618598-34</Id><Topic><Title>Is there any Corrupt Activity a Democrat won't Excuse......</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1370030394225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbocrats bottom up and top down, Party first, before God before Country</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370099618598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:13:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370099724222-35</Id><Topic><Title>unposter uniposter same old BHT your right but you missed a 16 day 100% stock price gain your 100% right</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370099066955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unposter your late and as usual make a statement about me and forget I have already answered and gave you a lesson in stock buying so be a good student wake up and go read about you thesis and why I made 100% and you made another worthless hack statement !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370099724222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370099898253-36</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ventura's TV show "Conspiracy Theory" featured some of the nuttiest 9/11 conspiracy theorists he could find. In one episode he was downright dishonest. You can see about that in the five-minute Youtube "Incendiary Experimnents".</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370099898253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370099912677-37</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA???</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1370007633781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:40:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sure did I said on the day it opens up 22% that is was nice to make 22% and out. I tell you thins now the stock market had a near term peak the day I cleared my TSLA and I have already said the rest of that week the stock market would trade sideways and perhaps a little down , You really need to start learning how to stop being a troll if your going to ever make any money Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370099912677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370101036551-38</Id><Topic><Title>TSLA???</Title><Username>unposter76</Username><Timestamp>1370007633781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 09:40:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's wholly owned by institutions/funds it's a game they play once they've jacked the price beyond reason, their sole focus becomes periodically squeezing wealth from the short interest lured by the excessive valuation. the only difference between the purse snatcher and institution/fund crooks is the magnitude of the TAKE.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370101036551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370101120497-39</Id><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Msg>• waynedickenson961 waynedickenson961 • May 28, 2013 4:16 PM Flag CEO of BA and the CEO of TSLA which is better ? • FACT check, Here is the founder of Tesla accomplishments, Elon is the Chairman of SolarCity, the leading residential solar provider in the U.S. In addition to his role at SolarCity, Elon is also the co-founder, chairman and CEO of Tesla Motors, an all-electric American car company. As Chairman at Tesla Motors, Elon helped design the ground-breaking Tesla Roadster, for which he won an Index and a Global Green award, the latter presented by Mikhail Gorbachev. Elon is also the founder and CEO of SpaceX - a space launch vehicle company. Prior to SpaceX, he co-founded PayPal, the world's leading electronic payment system, and served as the company's chairman and CEO. PayPal went public in early 2002 and was sold to eBay later that year for $1.5 billion., so like Steve jobs of Apple then a money maker for his shareholders . SCTY ,, one month stock price gain SCTY 86%, 3 month stock price gain SCTY 168% year to date stock price gain SCTY 296%. I would stick with TSLA but he is the man making a lot of money for his shareholders Today TSLA is up 12%, short squeeze, and if you were in when I pointed it out as a buy on May 3 at $55.45 today at $110, you would have made 97% what has the CEO of Boeing Jim McNerdey done other than take excessive pay from Boeing shareholders for failure on the 787 and be booted from GE by Jack Welch So after the profit out today look for a pullback as all short squeeze stock will go into a range after the shorts buy back their shares. Next look fo Elon to start news reports of some sort of new add on and he will try to excite the stock buying public. Just look at support and trade the stock chart now . Wayne</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370101304941-40</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you here, diane feinstein's hubby has sole contract to dispose of excess usps properties dumbos use gov't to get rich, huh wayne</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370101304941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370101418296-41</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unposter76 • 1 hour 16 minutes ago Flag1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 1 Reply A good question that wayne skips.I also noticed as usual unposter aka uniposter as a Boeing hack and not a stock trader you missed once more already explained that any short squeeze stock will go sideways and down for a while because of all the shorts having to buy back their shares you really don't kknow how to trade a stock do you unposter</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101418296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370101427367-42</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i meant HEAR, do a search on USPS and diane feinstein</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370101427367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370101562630-43</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>attention freeveritas as a BHT you need to explain yourself your hiding again make a BS statement and then run away your a troll nothing more " freeveritas • 53 minutes ago Flag1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 1 Reply Right. Wayneker doesn't say anything about his TSLA when it drops like it did yesterday down 6.81% or his JRCC</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101562630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370101690976-44</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets bump this for unposter and freveritass</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101690976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370101745950-45</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>many thanks to the c-men group especially unposter and freveritass</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101745950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370102016513-46</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ is a BHT, less your intent is to keep us guessing, maybe you spell it out your obscure acronyms</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370102016513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370102546176-47</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spaz is for anybody who'll weaken America</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370102546176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370102564539-48</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't you used to have some controversial theories. Since AlQaeda works for US interests in Syria and Libya ...is it a stretch to consider that they worked for some shadowy elites on 9-11 ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370102564539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370102808554-49</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets look at the posters comment s clear case of hack and troll nothing of any substance but gibberish ,unposter76 58 posts | Last Activity: 1 hour 38 minutes ago Member since: Mar 23, 2010 1 2 3 3 months 3 months 6 months 1 year AllSort: Newest | Oldest | Highest Rated Expand all messages Reply to TSLA???by unposter76 •May 31, 2013 9:40 AM unposter76 unposter76 • 1 hour 38 minutes ago Flag2 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 1 Reply A good question that wayne skips.I also noticed TSLA is losing 2.70 a share? 4 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 4 Reply TSLA???unposter76 by unposter76 • May 31, 2013 9:40 AM Flag Let me get this straight.Drive 2 hours then sit at a charging station for 1 hour,this car costs 90K? Sentiment: Strong Sell Reply to So how to trade a stock EGLE and,another 787 electrical problem on the 787 on a test flightby waynedickenson961 •May 16, 2013 12:00 PM unposter76 unposter76 • May 17, 2013 6:34 AM Flag3 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 5 Reply Once again,imaginary trades really don't count.Get a life. Sentiment: Strong Buy Reply to Boeing gets 6.9 Billion dollar Turkish orderby rs2ms2ts2ks72 •May 15, 2013 3:42 AM unposter76 unposter76 • May 15, 2013 7:34 AM Flag3 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 4 Reply Going over 100 quickly!!! Dell the resident short can eat my shorts. Sentiment: Strong Buy Reply to 60 by juneby unposter76 •Apr 30, 2013 7:20 AM unposter76 unposter76 • May 15, 2013 7:31 AM Flag4 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 1 Reply Another up day on its way!!!!! Reply to Nice ride today......by retired_geezer •May 14, 2013 4:25 PM unposter76 unposter76 • May 14, 2013 4:33 PM Flag0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply Delayed reaction to jim cramers article yesterday about WY ??????? The shorts are getting crucified!!!! lol Sentiment: Strong Buy Reply to at the closeby lbi1000 •May 9, 2013 4:03 PM unposter76 unposter76 • May 13</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370102808554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:06:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370102882683-50</Id><Title>Spazticus's Community/Message Board Outreach</Title><Msg>bought to you by Barack and the Dumb Party part n parcel of the fleecing, i mean looting, of America</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370102882683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370102955479-51</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lets look at more BHT gibberish shall we censored you up next hold on to yourself , "freeveritas 147 posts | Last Activity: 1 hour 16 minutes ago Member since: Feb 21, 2013 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 3 months 3 months 6 months 1 year AllSort: Newest | Oldest | Highest Rated Expand all messages Reply to TSLA???by unposter76 •May 31, 2013 9:40 AM freeveritas freeveritas • 1 hour 16 minutes ago Flag2 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 1 Reply Right. Wayneker doesn't say anything about his TSLA when it drops like it did yesterday down 6.81% or his JRCC which went down 5.47%. Reply to Va. school board member asked to resign over racist Michelle Obama emailsby hoozdik_hertz_557 •15 hours ago freeveritas freeveritas • 14 hours ago Flag1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 2 Reply Tough t I t t I e s. Reply to Solar panels failing prematurely and starting fires....more tax dollars wasted on green fantasyby ali_infesto •May 31, 2013 10:48 AM freeveritas freeveritas • May 31, 2013 11:11 AM Flag2 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 7 Reply We used to get something for your infrastructure tax dollars like interstate highways, railroads, dams and electric grids. Now we spend hundreds of billions lining the pockets of failed green energy company executives and bailing out auto unions and giving fat cat paychecks and bonuses to bankers. Reply to joedoakes and other dopey RWNJs still support Sen Joe McCarthyby father_zosima •May 31, 2013 10:57 AM freeveritas freeveritas • May 31, 2013 11:02 AM Flag1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 5 Reply Just a clue. So is McCarthy. 3 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 5 Reply Boeing up 35% over past six monthsfreeveritas by freeveritas • May 31, 2013 10:36 AM Flag Wayneker's JRCC down 53% over past 6 months. Reply to When will the GOP come up with a job bill?by wutangbk2 •May 30, 2013 2:07 PM freeveritas freeveritas • May 30, 2013 2:30 PM Flag0 users liked this posts u</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370102955479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370103097875-52</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you tell us what BHT means moore-on</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370103097875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370103144843-53</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored50 aka joedokes 25 aka starticus 99991 aks just another troll , lets review your gibberish are you making any money doing this nope that is all you know so you do this instead of making money here you go again "0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply Spazticus's Community/Message Board Outreachcensored50 by censored50 • 1 minute 20 seconds ago Flag bought to you by Barack and the Dumb Party part n parcel of the fleecing, i mean looting, of America Reply to Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For Presidentby spartacus67517 •3 hours ago censored50 censored50 • 6 minutes ago Flag0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply spaz is for anybody who'll weaken America Reply to Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truthby waynedickenson961 •30 minutes ago censored50 censored50 • 15 minutes ago Flag0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply #$%$ is a BHT, less your intent is to keep us guessing, maybe you spell it out your obscure acronyms Reply to Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truthby waynedickenson961 •30 minutes ago censored50 censored50 • 25 minutes ago Flag0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply i meant HEAR, do a search on USPS and diane feinstein Reply to Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truthby waynedickenson961 •30 minutes ago censored50 censored50 • 27 minutes ago Flag0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply did you here, diane feinstein's hubby has sole contract to dispose of excess usps properties dumbos use gov't to get rich, huh wayne Reply to TSLA???by unposter76 •May 31, 2013 9:40 AM censored50 censored50 • 32 minutes ago Flag1 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply it's wholly owned by institutions/funds it's a game they play once they've jacked the price beyond reason</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370103144843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370103194083-54</Id><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Msg>Why do they continue to drag their feet in releasing a final report on the investigation into the devastating Dec. 14 shootings at Sandy Hook Elementary School? Who gave that agency the authority to decide what the public should know and when they should know it?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370103258109-55</Id><Topic><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what are your questions sparty?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370103258109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370103286834-56</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to Censored .... Ignorance is Strength slavery is freedom War is Peace</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103286834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370103420501-57</Id><Topic><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i know what happened at sandy hook, i still don't know what barack was doing while his ambassador was being sodomized, or why the IRS clown visited the whitehouse some 140 plus times, but only mentioned the easter egg hunt</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370103420501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370103509316-58</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayneker, please excuse me for not waiting with bated breath for your posts. I beg your leave and will be gone now for the rest of the day.</Msg><Username>freeveritas</Username><Timestamp>1370103509316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370104290929-59</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Controversial is one thing, and any alternative theory about 9/11 will arouse controversy because it will immediately be dismissed by people who are too lazy to examine the facts. Nutty (as in evidence-free) is another thing entirely. Ventura did two 9/11 programs. One of them was a whole hour devoted to the Pentagon Flyover theory. Best soundbite was where Ventura's researcher asked the conspiracy theorist "Where did the plane go?" and he answered "It went . . . somewhere." On the other program he interviewed the 9/11 scamster Willie Rodriguez, hired Dr. Van Romero to paint some thermite on a steel column, and then misrepresented Dr. Romero's findings, as the "Incendiary Experiments" video shows.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370104290929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370104534060-60</Id><Topic><Title>Notice two of the BHT C-men are attempting to remake history on my TSLA call so here is the truth</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370101120497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 11:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freveritass yes, I know, your too ashamed to be humiliated any more today, by you very poor arguments and basic crapola and have to go hide in your mothers room for a while on quiet time . Well hurry back, I enjoy your BS crapola ,your a real joke and your just as important to me as you are to yourself. Lets hear it for you latest argument on TSLA down 55 this week , so that would be like, if your up100% in TSLA since May 3, and if you lost 5% on Friday then that would make you up 95% on Friday . Or if your in Boeing stock then your down 1.5% on Boeing from a loss of ..98% for the whole week frevertiass, your arguments are just so much crapola the May 3 buy in was very clear , any reader can go and look it up. And if you are still holding tesla and purchased the day I called it and then held until today after a short squeeze as I am guessing you did , well blame yourself then . If you holding Boeing well your only up 20% compared to Airbus up 146% blame yourself. I told you five years ago to be in airbus and I am telling you today to be in Airbus not Boeing in five years given the Boeing management strategy , it will be the same Airbus is number 1. Freeveritass I know you hate me because your jealous of me but please go now go have fun I hate to see a loser punish himself all the time</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370104534060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:35:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370104951379-61</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freeveritass , started crying again and has to go to the psychologist today , he said he will not be able to post useless garbage until he gets back with his stronger blood pressure RS due to the hypertension caused by losing all that investment money on Boeing what was he thinking? freeveritass , he could have been up 146% on Airbus right now ? well have fun. frevertiass, and remember if your complaining about TSLA pulling back this seek 5 or 10 percent than if you got in on May 3 like I posted! your still up 95% or 90% and you can still get out Monday . Your argument sucks as usual and ditto for unposter and censored all part of the BHT and on the BOD of a c-men foundation</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370104951379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370106690471-62</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney was beyond a shadow of a doubt ane xpert at how to create jobs reducing the debt. Jesse Ventura is a kook. Appears to be a drug induced kook. And for spartacus' information, I listened to the horses mouth talk about seeing aliens from outer space. And the guy is no conservative.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370106690471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370106874464-63</Id><Topic><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The incredible reality is over 6 mo. later folks still without a home, their home exactly like it was after the storm....crumbled to the ground. And here comes BO, and fat boy Gov. Cristy taking credit again for the Board Walk opening up...some of it. But BO says, "we still have work to do." Really?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370106874464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370106949221-64</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wayne you related to sparty? you remind me of sparty, one things pretty certain you're paid outta the same community agitator slush fund.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370106949221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370107425184-65</Id><Topic><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we still don't know why the obama admin was arming mexican drug cartels if not to use resultant crime and deaths to disarm law abiding Americans</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370107425184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370108045982-66</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>convenient time slice you picked ahkmed, i mean wayne</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370108045982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370108298345-67</Id><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Msg>Really Patty, nice to see you jolted awake, where have all the great minds been?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370109462033-68</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well yes of course, cg gives a thumbs down on that.</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370109462033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370109685307-69</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>part n parcel of the rainbow dumbocrat/obama admin assault on the arms services</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370109685307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370110266986-70</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how come YAHOOs won't let me correct typos...i meant armED services, the rainbow dumbocrat / obama admin assault on the armed services</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370110266986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370110606702-71</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you think our brave fighting men and women should be able to rape anybody they please?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370110606702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370110739881-72</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh wow, joedokes! An anonymous internet poster's hearsay account! And you're dumb enough to think people might be dumb enough to believe you?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1370110739881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370110822219-73</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope, i'm saying many of the suits turn out to be frivolous, no doubt obots are recruiting gays and women and encouraging them to complain...surprisingly when gays make unwanted advances, their targets are singled out for sensitive training and or discipline...understand now moore-on, i mean ahkmed</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370110822219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370111174327-74</Id><Title>Spacecraft milestone</Title><Msg>HOUSTON, May 31, 2013 – By successfully completing two significant tests of the integrated Commercial Crew Transportation System, Boeing [NYSE: BA] and United Launch Alliance (ULA) have moved the United States closer to regaining its capability to return humans to space. The team recently completed the first wind tunnel test for connected scale models of the Crew Space Transportation-100 (CST-100) capsule, launch vehicle adaptor and Atlas V rocket, as well as a thrust test of the Centaur rocket stage. The wind tunnel test, at NASA’s Ames Research Center in California, allowed for evaluation of the proposed launch configuration. “The CST-100 and Atlas V, connected with the launch vehicle adaptor, performed exactly as expected and confirmed our expectations of how they will perform together in flight,” said John Muholland, Boeing vice president and program manager for Commercial Programs. The CST-100 will be able to transport up to seven people, or a mix of people and cargo, to low Earth orbit destinations such as the International Space Station and Bigelow Aerospace’s planned space station.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370111174327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370111186621-75</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oops, another typo... nope, i'm saying many of the suits turn out to be frivolous, no doubt obots are recruiting gays and women and encouraging them to complain...surprisingly when gays make unwanted advances, their targets are singled out for sensitivITY training and or discipline. he's implementing the same non competitive, EEOP/affirmative, action initiatives that characterize many DMV offices, and lessen competitive advantage in the private sector.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370111186621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370111623980-76</Id><Topic><Title>Spazticus's Community/Message Board Outreach</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370102882683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>continues, he's newest luv interest, jesse ventura</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370111623980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370111653525-77</Id><Topic><Title>Spazticus's Community/Message Board Outreach</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370102882683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oops...ontinues, hIS newest luv interest, jesse ventura</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370111653525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370112642113-78</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This off another board regarding Jesse Ventura....."Ex Gov., #$%$ bag Jesse Ventura(which has been proven was never on a SEAL team), former pro wrestler and perpetual raving nut job filed a defamation suit last year against Chris Kyle , ex-Navy SEAL, and author of "American Sniper". In his book he had written about a fight between him and Ventura. Kyle said Ventura was bad-mouthing the war, bad-mouthing former President Bush, and bad-mouthing America. He told us we were killing innocent men, women, and children and that we were murders. Kyle said he told Ventura to tone down his retoric. Ventura then said that we deserved to lose a few guys. After Kyle was tragically murdered last Feb. Ventura asked that Kyle's widow, Taya be substituted as the defendant in the lawsuit. What a low life American" All submitted comments are subject to the rules set forth in our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. ADVERTISEMENT Message Boards HOT BOARDS Announcements Backlash and Blowback Survival School The Tip Board All Message Boards RECENT THREADS The Truth Has Finally been Revealed to the American People (62) Most</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1370112642113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370114100067-79</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think Ventura cab become president, but that criticism is gratuitous. He was awarded the Vietnam Service Medal, which was given to military personnel who took part in the contributions to the war effort in Vietnam, and the point about the Seals is hair-splitting. Here are the facts: "Minnesota Governor Jesse Ventura was NOT, nor was he ever, a Navy SEAL; though part of Underwater Demolition Team 12, he left the Navy 8 years before they were combined with the SEAL Teams, and SEAL status was not retroactive."</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370114100067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 15:15:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370114267395-80</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's unanimous then, sparty agrees with sparty</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370114267395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 15:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370114739433-81</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's different then the people like Bush and Clinton and Obama HOW exactly ? Ill say it again since you are slow ... Doing the same thing over and over with disastrous results and expecting a different result is the definition of insanity ...time for a change...time to vote indepenendent...Independent of Fascist Corporate?Government nepotism leading America down the path of destruction.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370114739433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 15:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370115025991-82</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I'm not spartacus. But he would be a Seal today and earned a medal for his service, and you have to respect that.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370115025991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 15:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370117558778-83</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Ventura thinking of Running For President</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370092137503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what’s true? You decide. Is Kyle’s death just a random coincidence that coincides with a certain lawsuit that would have seen Kyle pay a large sum of money for lying about Jesse Ventura? Was Kyle ever going to reveal the reason why he lied about the incident? What we know right now is two men are dead, Kyle being one of them, and one lawsuit is still pending. Kyle profited by telling a lie and Ventura wants to clear his name. “The event this man spoke of never happened. I have been to Mc P’s many times since leaving the Navy. I was never there alone. I was always accompanied by other people. If this happened 6 years ago, someone would have known of it before now. Certainly in the UDT/SEAL community it would have been known. This has to be news to all of us. I have always opposed the war in Iraq but I have never spoken or wished any ill will towards the soldiers. My heart aches that soldiers have died or been wounded because this war should never have taken place. I am perplexed over the agenda this man has and why a fellow Navy Seal would tell a lie about an event that never happened. Clearly between this story and the previous week’s story about supposedly getting pulled over for tailgating in CA that was also a lie, someone is out to destroy my credibility</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370117558778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 16:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370117743289-84</Id><Topic><Title>Spazticus's Community/Message Board Outreach</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370102882683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>reread your last post.....confirmed...you're a babbling idiot</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370117743289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 16:15:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370119886174-85</Id><Topic><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever notice how the people running the planet never want you to know the truth...whether it is 9-11, JFK, Obamas Birth Certificate or Sandy Hook...All of which justified much larger agendas (in the case of Sandy Hook it was gun control)....What is my question you ask...What is the Truth ..is the answer.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370119886174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 16:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370124640078-86</Id><Topic><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please please please please get a life. For God's sake, man. A LIFE. Now.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1370124640078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 18:10:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370125422344-87</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blame for what?</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1370125422344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 18:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370127056614-88</Id><Topic><Title>Six Months on and STILL no Sandy Hook report</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1370103194083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:13:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and your aliases seem very obsessed with him.......talk about needing to get a life....</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1370127056614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 18:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370127238025-89</Id><Title>HOLDER downgraded to MOSES !!</Title><Msg>Now we have MSNBC contributor Michael Eric Dyson. In a discussion on MSNBC about the mounting pressure for Eric Holder to resign, Dyson went as far as to compare Holder … to Moses? "I think the attorney general should step down, too … off of that plateau where he resides in high principle and whip some heads But he shouldn't give up his office. What he should understand is that he is the chief law-giver of the United States of America, so to speak - he's the Moses of our time - and at least for this administration."</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370127238025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 18:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370128802649-90</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for making a total mess of the negotiations by pushing his ALL corporations are evil, and marxist philosophy in addition to pushing his Staff dummy to fear monger on pension issues. OTOH shooting of his mouth without authorization, and generally being a near perfect jerk didn't help much either. Thats in addition to his being a bully, and hiring a bunch of his non competent friends to do ' organizing " . The e-board is afraid to challange him - since the last time the board did fire the ED, they were recalled due to admitted help from the STAFF.</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370128802649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370129648368-91</Id><Title>Testimony of Chairman Alan Greenspan And LEONHARDT on Greenspan &amp; Unemployment</Title><Msg>The Federal Reserve's semiannual monetary policy report Before the Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, U.S. Senate July 22, 1997 This strong expansion has produced a remarkable increase in work opportunities for Americans. A net of more than thirteen million jobs has been created since the current period of growth began in the spring of 1991. As a consequence, the unemployment rate has fallen to 5 percent--its lowest level in almost a quarter century. The expansion has enabled many in the working-age population, a large number of whom would have otherwise remained out of the labor force or among the longer-term unemployed, to acquire work experience and improved skills. Our whole economy will benefit from their greater productivity. To be sure, not all segments of our population are fully sharing in the economic improvement. Some Americans still have trouble finding jobs, and for our work force real wage stagnation persists. In the late 1990's "The jobless rate, at its nadir, was below 4 percent." Greenspan and Unemployment By DAVID LEONHARDT In the process, Mr. Greenspan helped demonstrate that unemployment could fall lower than many economists had believed without setting off inflation. The late 1990s remain the only sustained period over the past 35 years when incomes rose at a healthy rate all across the income spectrum. The jobless rate, at its nadir, was below 4 percent. The contrast with the today’s situation — when unemployment is near a 27-year high, median household income is lower than a decade ago, core inflation is far below its long-term average and yet some Fed officials are more worried about the economy being too strong than it being too weak — is telling. Alan Greenspan’s reputation obviously isn’t what it used to be, and for good reason. His re-entry into partisan politics — arguing that Wall Street is over-regulated — that he believes we need more Madoff types to stimulate wall street. "Banksters always go unpunished"</Msg><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370129648368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:34:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370130222046-92</Id><Title>Fewer Americans Call Themselves Economic Conservatives</Title><Msg>A new Gallup survey shows only 41 percent of Americans call themselves economic conservatives—the lowest since President Obama took office in 2009 and roughly the same percentage as in 2008. Additionally, 30 percent of Americans identify with social liberalism—the highest percentage reported in 13 consecutive years. Why the change? “Today, there’s a widespread feeling of skepticism about the form of capitalism we’re saddled with, which works well for a few and causes the rest of us various kinds of misery,” Lynn Stuart Parramore writes at AlterNet. “Many Americans are beyond sick and tired of bankers, financiers and political hucksters. We see that crony capitalism is destroying our communities, our democracy, our economic well-being, and the natural world.” It didn’t look this way a couple of years ago. Republicans won big in the 2010 congressional midterm elections. During that year, 51 percent of Americans were calling themselves economic conservatives. The arrival of Ronald Reagan, who convinced many Americans that government was the problem, ended America’s liberalizing postwar era. “America became more ‘economically conservative,’ ” Parramore writes. “The idea that economic conservatism equals prudence is an old association, dating all the way back to 18th-century thinker Edmund Burke, and it’s one that proponents of reckless free-market fundamentalism took full advantage of. They vigorously repeated the lie that markets can regulate themselves, that they are resistant to fraud, and that things would be fine if the government would just let the capitalists alone. They claimed, ad nauseum, that liberals were financially naive and irresponsible spendthrifts. They more or less got away with this package of deceit until the financial crash, which happened on the watch of a free-marketeer, and one who, by the way, had the worst record on job creation in modern history. That was a serious blow to their mythology. “Gradually it become harder to argue that government should be shrunk to the size where it could be drowned in a bathtub because it grew obvious that government intervention and things like unemployment benefits (what economists call ‘automatic stabilizers’) kept us from plunging into a Great Depression,” Parramore continues. “Slowly, painfully, Americans have begun to see that focusing on austerity and debt reduction is a road to nowhere, and that the economists whose work is frequently cited by proponents of this view doesn’t hold up to scrutiny. We’re gradually getting the message that economic prudence means government making long-term commitments to investing in the kind of robust education, research and infrastructure that our future well-being depends on.”</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130222046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370130556852-93</Id><Title>Watergate Amnesia, the Nixonian Slur and Other Big Lies</Title><Msg>By Joe Conason Let’s state this very simply, so everybody will understand. The notion that Barack Obama is “Nixonian”—or that his administration’s recent troubles bear any resemblance to “Watergate”—is the biggest media lie since the phony “Whitewater scandal” crested during the Clinton presidency. Fraudulent as it is, we have listened repeatedly to versions of this bogus comparison uttered by figures as diverse as former Fox News commentator #$%$ Morris and Bob Woodward of the Washington Post, alongside a phalanx of Republican politicians, including Senator Lindsey Graham and Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell—whose latest attack ad directly links Obama with Nixon. Only in a country afflicted with chronic historical amnesia could they issue such accusations without shame or embarrassment. Only under those circumstances could the Republicans continue their fitful fabrication of a “Democratic Watergate” without fear of being laughed off the stage. It is a project that they will never grow tired of pursuing. Coming from figures such as former White House political boss Karl Rove and Fox News chief Roger Ailes—both of whom worked for Nixon and defended him with vigor—- the hypocrisy is stunning. They can only say words like “Watergate” or “Nixonian” because most Americans have forgotten who they really are behind the respectable masks—or never knew. The last time we heard Obama mentioned in the same breath as Watergate was in 2009, when Rep. Darrell Issa—the same Issa who has labored for months to pump air into the Benghazi “scandal”—decided that a job offered to a potential political candidate had erupted into a Constitutional crisis. Is it necessary to note that nothing of consequence ever emerged from Issa’s investigation back then? Yet somehow, he maintains credibility with the Washington media. So does Graham, who slandered Susan Rice over the Benghazi talking points, which he deemed “worse than Watergate”—an assertion since proved entirely wrong, irresponsible and vicious. Nevertheless Graham is treated as someone worthy of airtime and quotation, rather than a discredited blowhard. But certain liberals in the media have fretted loudly over Obama’s “scandals,” too. Is it reasonable to compare the Benghazi incident, the vetting of abused tax exemptions by the IRS, or the Justice Department’s leak investigations with the Watergate crisis? Or is it all just trumped-up hysteria? To answer those questions, it helps to remember what Nixon and his gang actually did to America—and why they were driven out of Washington and, in many cases, sent to prison. In these circumstances, a quick history lesson seems vital. For those who have forgotten or don’t know, Watergate is the name of an apartment complex near the Potomac River in northwest Washington, D.C., where then-President Nixon’s henchmen staged a “third-rate burglary” of the Democratic National Committee headquarters on a June night in 1972. But Watergate came to stand for a vast agglomeration of gangster conspiracies based in the Nixon White House but spanning the nation. Watergate was a series of burglaries, warrantless domestic wiretaps, illegal spying, campaign dirty tricks, election tampering, money laundering and assorted thuggish schemes conceived by a large and lawless gang whose leaders included G. Gordon Liddy and the late E. Howard Hunt. And Watergate grew into a cover-up of those initial felonies with still more felonies, committed by lawyers and bureaucrats who collected cash payoffs from major corporations and then handed out hush money and secret campaign slush funds. Eventually, Watergate implicated scores of perpetrators, from the right-wing Cuban foot soldiers all the way up to the president, his closest advisors, and his crooked stooges at the highest levels of the Justice Department, the FBI and the CIA. Again then, in what sense is the Benghazi tragedy—thoroughly investigated by an independent board, as provided by law—akin to Watergate? How is the IRS effort to vet the tax exemptions of tea party groups, which were violating their status brazenly, similar to Nixon’s criminal abuse of the agency to punish his enemies with audits? What makes the Justice Department probe of national security leaks, conducted with valid subpoenas, resemble the secret Nixon White House war against “enemies” in the press, which went so far as trumped-up FCC license challenges and even threats of violence against the Washington Post? The answers are fairly obvious: None. Not at all. Nothing whatsoever. And so far as we know, Attorney General Eric Holder hasn’t rung up any Fox News reporter drunkenly at midnight to warn that Roger Ailes is “going to get his tit caught in a big, fat wringer.” But if and when that ever happens, the chance to roll out the Watergate clichÇs will arrive at last—starting with “Nixonian.”</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130556852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370130696345-94</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For more details- search on SPEEA 2012 NEGOTIATIONS - MSDSite Forums</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370130696345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:51:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370131300222-95</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know, Don, I find it amusing that you badmouth the union that made it possible for you to have a good retirement. What you should be doing is to post on the poor management that the company has. Most who work there would be able to identify with that.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1370131300222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370132048440-96</Id><Topic><Title>Fewer Americans Call Themselves Economic Conservatives</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130222046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:43:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more'n more government dependent slugs, just like you....by design, huh sparty, i mean hoozDIK</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370132048440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370132262374-97</Id><Topic><Title>Watergate Amnesia, the Nixonian Slur and Other Big Lies</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1370130556852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:49:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nixon was a boy scout relative to barack and slick willy anytime you'd like to review the past you just let me know, K ahkmed, i mean spart, i mean hoozDIK</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370132262374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370133103427-98</Id><Topic><Title>Testimony of Chairman Alan Greenspan And LEONHARDT on Greenspan &amp; Unemployment</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1370129648368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 19:34:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's by design, huh spazticus, err pretend patriot rainbow dumbocrats are trying to transform the military into another non-competitive EEOP/affirmative action slumber party...not so surprisingly when gays make unwanted advances, their targets are singled out for sensitivITY training and or disciplinary action.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370133103427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:31:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370133905349-99</Id><Topic><Title>Final May delivery count</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370097278944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:34:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They snuck in another 787 delivery on the 31st. 787 count now 7. Total now 56 planes.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1370133905349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 20:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370134939205-100</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA - only one person to blame and that's Ray Goforth</Title><Username>ba_nonsense</Username><Timestamp>1370044920530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 20:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You simply do not pay attention. I do hammer the company. And as far as SPEEA, my issue is not with the union and the members with integrity, but with the corrupt staff and several union officials who collectively for the past decade have ripped off the members of several tens of thousands of $$, paid 3 to 5 times the going rate for janitorial services provided by a staff member, and totally screwed up future members retrirement, plus slipping in a hidden fee for those who have funds still in Boeing. And then there are little gotchas like an Officer threatening a e-board member ( police report in Tukwilla ) a few years ago, and also a few years ago the ED grabbing a member ( as in assault ) - and being covered up cuz majority of E-board officers were afraid to stand up. Of course little things like staff members without authorization signing federal forms, and via deception having SPEEA pay into Teamsters Pension for speea 'management" for a decade ( without authorization ) , and then when found out, manage to cover up and not demand any refunds also play into my dislike for Staff and wimpy or apathetic E-board. As to my pension - it was the IAM who did the heavy lifting, and SPEEA who to this day gave Boeing a license to screw over many retirees who use the alternate formula. Its not that I'm against unions or SPEEA as a union- but that I'm against the unethical officers and Staff who have but one purpose which is NOT serving the members, but their own pockets and egos, either thru apathy, incompetence, or just plain shady methods that seem to scoot under the radar. For those who wonder about my comments- they are mostly ALL backed up by documents which can be accessed thru FOIA or simple requests. search on Q4SPEEA for just part of the data and documents</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1370134939205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 21:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370135567151-101</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"many of the suits turn out to be frivolous...." And you acquired your vast knowledge via what manner here? From your vaunted position as 2nd shift assistant salad bar manager at the Burger Barn? Or from the bathroom wall at the truck stop? Or maybe at a _______ ________ meeting?</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1370135567151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 21:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370135933523-102</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spaz err censored err assault on typos err better tunnel in through Somalia or North Korea, spaz bumper fascist err islamospazmo</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1370135933523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 21:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370136091203-103</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spaz is having another one of his sissy fits</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370136091203</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 21:21:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370136420554-104</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here you go spazticus, from the washington times, a real news source.... False complaints of sexual abuse in the military are rising at a faster rate than overall reports of sexual assault, a trend that could harm combat readiness, analysts say. Virtually all media attention on a Pentagon report last week focused on an increase in service members’ claims of sexual abuse in an anonymous survey, but unmentioned were statistics showing that a significant percentage of such actually investigated cases were baseless. From 2009 to 2012, the number of sexual abuse reports rose from 3,244 to 3,374 — a 4 percent increase.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1370136420554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 21:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370136929254-105</Id><Topic><Title>787 fundamental cost saving</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370093338880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't the Seattl;e Times article from about 5 years ago state the $30 B was half development cost and half build up of inventory?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370136929254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 21:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370137587510-106</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$100,000 invested in BA in March 2009 (less than 5 years ago) would be worth $337,000 now, not counting dividends. As someone on this board recently posted: "no response means I am right" .</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1370137587510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 21:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370139149409-107</Id><Title>The Latest Fatwa</Title><Msg>The latest Fatwa calls on all Sunnis to fight H izbollah and the I ranian backed Syrian regime. The Fatwa issued by a known Sunni Cleric brands all Shiites as worse infidels than J ews and Christians. It will be hot town in Syria tonight.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1370139149409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 22:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370139978371-108</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Washington Times. Moonie paper. Pffffbttthhhhhh.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1370139978371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 22:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370140425109-109</Id><Topic><Title>Murray: Number of military sexual assaults is 'unconscionable'</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1370108298345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 13:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Censored quoting the Washington Times as an authority is like Sparty quoting Orly Taitz also as an authority.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1370140425109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 22:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370142309219-110</Id><Topic><Title>What is a $100,000 retirement investment made 5 years ago in Boeing stock worth today?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370095428798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 10:03:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spartacus 99991 is playing Texas holdem with a short stack again, , you can use your secret probation animal house chart spartacus9991 happy now ! or the world in reality can use CNN Money stock chart and live in reality , spartacus99991, your special friend I cheatem , stock charter bogus is always a pleasure to point out a BHT. you must have found a perfect bottom to chart from and I know you actually did that , but you were lucky right ha ha</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370142309219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 23:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370142748402-111</Id><Topic><Title>787 fundamental cost saving</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370093338880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored50 have you been playing Texas holdem with a short stack ? there are you nappy now I spoke troll for you ! , now are we having fun ? but getting back to the Boeing financial message board Boeing as an investment for 5 years is up to 21% while Airbus has made 146% censored 50 aka joedokes 25, sparticaus 99991 you sure like yoru numbers BHT, a 100k invested in Boeing for 5 years is now $121000 However that same 100k invested in airbus is now have $ 246000 and your still holding a short stack 5years later censored 50 , and you really missed my 15 year call on Apple and the 100% 16 day gain on TSLA It just proves you can't teach stupid !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370142748402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 23:12:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370142820632-112</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock price trend</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370094483577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the trend is your friend remember that BHT</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1370142820632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 23:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>