<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372824661658-1</Id><Title>787 Dispatch Reliability</Title><Msg>Boeing (NYSE: BA ) also fell, dropping 1.7% and marking a much bigger drag on the Dow because of its relatively high share price. A report from Bloomberg noted that United Continental, the only U.S. airline that's currently flying the new 787 Dreamliner aircraft, has cancelled Dreamliner flights at roughly quadruple the rate of its other airplane models. Undoubtedly, awareness of potential problems for the Dreamliner is at a heightened level in light of the battery problems that grounded the new model for months earlier this year. But at some point, Boeing needs to get past these problems in order to assure investors that it can move forward to focusing on actually delivering on the vast backlog of existing orders for the 787 and other aircraft.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1372824661658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 00:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372824694810-2</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, And Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797102806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your sentiment is not unlike the Muslim Brotherhood of Egypt and their admiration of President Morsi.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1372824694810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 00:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372826929979-3</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, And Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797102806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except that hooz is expressing for support for a U.S. President legally elected by constitutional processes -- twice.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372826929979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 00:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372827174996-4</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, And Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797102806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Legally elected because the other party saw that it was in their interests to let him win, so they sabotaged themselves, twice.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1372827174996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 00:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372831871095-5</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, And Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797102806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Morsi was also elected by about the same slim margin. Kind of funny how Obama called on Monday and "encouraged President Morsi to take steps to show that he is responsive to their (the people's) concerns". In the meantime, the crowds and the Egyptian military have demanded that Morsi step down. Kind of a "deja vu all over again" - only this time Obama is soft-pedaling because Morsi is Muslim Brotherhood and a hater of Israel and no friend of the United States. The previous time Obama stuck his nose in their affairs, Mubarak, a friend of the United States and Israel, "had to go", according to Obama's hourly and frenetic press conferences of two and a half years ago.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1372831871095</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 02:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372849885651-6</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing that is not a theory is that the attacker is dead and that's a good thing ! It's nice to see the good guy win... One shot in the 10 ring and Trayvon's off to thug heaven.....</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1372849885651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372850703969-7</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With some luck, the real murderer in this case -- Zimmerman -- will see justice served. Capital punishment would be about right.</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1372850703969</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372851003060-8</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still fallin' for that sweet 12 year old angelic picture of the thug are ya ....Try something other than "The View " for info / news...........</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1372851003060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372851774787-9</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Try something other than "The View " for info / news..........." You mean like Fox News?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1372851774787</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372851953516-10</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, And Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797102806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Mubarak was ousted after 18 days of demonstrations during the 2011 Egyptian revolution[5] when, on 11 February 2011, Vice President Omar Suleiman announced that Mubarak had resigned as president and transferred authority to the Supreme Council of the Armed Forces.[6][7] On 13 April, a prosecutor ordered Mubarak and both his sons to be detained for 15 days of questioning about allegations of corruption and abuse of power.[8] He was then ordered to stand trial on charges of negligence for not giving orders to stop the killing of peaceful protestors during the revolution.[9] These trials officially began on 3 August 2011.[10] Egypt’s military prosecutors then also proclaimed that they were investigating Mubarak's role in the assassination of his predecessor Anwar Sadat.[11][12] On 2 June 2012, Mubarak was sentenced to life imprisonment by an Egyptian court. After sentencing, he was reported to have suffered a series of health crises. As of 20 June 2012, multiple sources reported that he was very ill, with some reporting that he was in a coma, others stating that he had had a stroke or had been on life support.[13]"</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1372851953516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372851962237-11</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, not Fox alone, CNN, MSNBC, Brietbart, HLN, WSJ, and others, print and electronic. And , no, I don't follow Limbaugh......</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1372851962237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372854081148-12</Id><Title>Barack Hussein Delays Start of Employer Mandate</Title><Msg>he thinks he's king, and without dumbos to hold him to account he is in effect king obama, imperial #$%$...delaying the brunt on the backlash / job losses until AFTER the election young folks can expect triple the rates</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372854081148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372855535759-13</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better Boeing Barkers, or TSLA and SCTY?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372744070569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 01:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Son. I wish you would stop crossdressing, start taking your medication, and get over the fact that Boeing terminated you for unusual acts in the mens room. Live up to the fact that you are a pretty sick man, and the delusions of you being some sort of stock market expert are so far from the truth. Why don't you use your real name of Dell George? Oh, thats right, Yahoo deleted that ID because you were harrassing too many on this message board. Be careful that doesn't happen to your fales name of Wayne.</Msg><Username>dellgeorgesr</Username><Timestamp>1372855535759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:45:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372857246699-14</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At what point in the trial do you think the prosecution will produce a witness that helps their case? lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1372857246699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372857775952-15</Id><Topic><Title>Damage Control</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1372709043077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 16:04:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Clapper, Director of Intelligence admitted in a formal letter of apology to the Chairwomen of the Senate Intelligence Committee Dianne Feinstein that he made an erroneous NSA statement in telling Congress that the NSA does not gather data on millions of Americans. Edward Snowden could not live with that lie on the American people and any implications that had on American constitutional civil liberties. Mr. Snowden is a US patriot and should be pardoned by the President for the crimes committed in whistleblowing to the American people the truth. of possihe is a true patriot and should be pardoned by the President</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1372857775952</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372858198865-16</Id><Topic><Title>There's Hope for Hoozdik: Scientist Says Close to Human Head Transplant...</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372800302716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 17:25:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz is such a true blue Dem he would choose the party mascot and go with the head of a jackass. LOL</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1372858198865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372858539478-17</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, And Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797102806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>infesto, why do keep on bumping long dead hooz/sparty threads?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372858539478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372859551806-18</Id><Topic><Title>Investigation Update: July 2nd... FBI Still Hasn't Contacted IRS-Targeted Tea Party Groups</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372857451840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Right Wing nut jobs have been tossing poo at the wall for what about 5 going on 6 years and nothing has stuck yet they just move on to another pile of different poop and start all over again leaving a big mess behind them.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372859551806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:52:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372859838006-19</Id><Title>Putin speaks</Title><Msg>Hooz's, and Chrisy's buddy Puttin speaks out. They should listen up. "In Russia live Russians. Any minority, from anywhere, if it wants to live in Russia, to work and eat in Russia, should speak Russian, and should respect the Russian laws. If they prefer Sharia Law, then we advise them to go to those places where that's the state law. Russia does not need minorities. Minorities need Russia, and we will not grant them special privileges, or try to change our laws to fit their desires, no matter how loud they yell 'discrimination'. We better learn from the suicides of America, England, Holland and France, if we are to survive as a nation. The Russian customs and traditions are not compatible with the lack of culture or the primitive ways of most minorities. When this honorable legislative body thinks of creating new laws, it should have in mind the national interest first, observing that the minorities are not Russians.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372859838006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372860006790-20</Id><Topic><Title>Putin speaks</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372859838006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Radical Muslims around the world are severely punishing WOMEN, and NO libs, not the liberal Media, are speaking out against it! Instead, the libs attack the GOP for not being sympathetic to Muslim . Sheria Law is brutal towards women!</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372860006790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372860257743-21</Id><Title>The Mindset of the Left and their role of protector of "the poor."</Title><Msg>The political left has long claimed the role of protector of "the poor." It is one of their central moral claims to political power. But how valid is this claim? Leaders of the left in many countries have promoted policies that enable the poor to be more comfortable in their poverty. But that raises a fundamental question: Just who are "the poor"? If you use a bureaucratic definition of poverty as including all individuals or families below some arbitrary income level set by the government, then it is easy to get the kinds of statistics about "the poor" that are thrown around in the media and in politics. But do those statistics have much relationship to reality? "Poverty" once had some concrete meaning -- not enough food to eat or not enough clothing or shelter to protect you from the elements, for example. Today it means whatever the government bureaucrats, who set up the statistical criteria, choose to make it mean. And they have every incentive to define poverty in a way that includes enough people to justify welfare state spending. Most Americans with incomes below the official poverty level have air-conditioning, television, own a motor vehicle and, far from being hungry, are more likely than other Americans to be overweight. But an arbitrary definition of words and numbers gives them access to the taxpayers' money. This kind of "poverty" can easily become a way of life, not only for today's "poor," but for their children and grandchildren. Even when they have the potential to become productive members of society, the loss of welfare state benefits if they try to do so is an implicit "tax" on what they would earn that often exceeds the explicit tax on a millionaire. If increasing your income by $10,000 would cause you to lose $15,000 in government benefits, would you do it? In short, the political left's welfare state makes poverty more comfortable, while penalizing attempts to rise out of poverty. Unless we believe that some people are predestined to be poor, the left's agenda is a disservice to them, as well as to society. The vast amounts of money wasted are by no means the worst of it. If our goal is for people to get out of poverty, there are plenty of heartening examples of individuals and groups who have done that, in countries around the world. Millions of "overseas Chinese" emigrated from China destitute and often illiterate in centuries past. Whether they settled in Southeast Asian countries or in the United States, they began at the bottom, taking hard, dirty and sometimes dangerous jobs. Even though the overseas Chinese were usually paid little, they saved out of that little, and many eventually opened tiny businesses. By working long hours and living frugally, they were able to turn tiny businesses into larger and more prosperous businesses. Then they saw to it that their children got the education that they themselves often lacked. By 1994, the 57 million overseas Chinese created as much wealth as the one billion people living in China. Variations on this social pattern can be found in the histories of Jewish, Armenian, Lebanese and other emigrants who settled in many countries around the world -- initially poor, but rising over the generations to prosperity. Seldom did they rely on government, and they usually avoided politics on their way up. Such groups concentrated on developing what economists call "human capital" -- their skills, talents, knowledge and self discipline. Their success has usually been based on that one four-letter word that the left seldom uses in polite society: "work." There are individuals in virtually every group who follow similar patterns to rise from poverty to prosperity. But how many such individuals there are in different groups makes a big difference for the prosperity or poverty of the groups as a whole. The agenda of the left -- promoting envy and a sense of grievance, while making loud demands for "rights" to what other people have produced -- is a pattern that has been widespread in countries around the world. This agenda has seldom lifted the poor out of poverty. But it has lifted the left to positions of power and self-aggrandizement, while they promote policies with socially counterproductive results.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372860257743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372860506846-22</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better Boeing Barkers, or TSLA and SCTY?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372744070569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 01:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another easy day trade for TSLA at open just follow my one sentence trade rule, it opined at 118 and in a few minutes your out at 119,25 on 100k easy over $1000 day and now an update to the Boeing Barkers , ,remember these Boeing barkers and add dellgeorgius, an old barker is now being reactivated and recruited from the 6 people who attempt to control the Boeing message board to sell you Boeing stock they have no interest in you other than selling you Boeing stocks so. Remember Airbus betters Boeing by over 90% in the last 3 years , remember dellgeorgius, spartacus99991 and his other name neospart99, domerrrrr, the worker hater - jojvaz,custerious, foulmoutharbor( how many BA deliveries today BS-, joedokes45 and barbing these users are only boeing advertisement barkers ,they sit at the Boeing message board most every day only rotating their names and attempt to sell you boeing stock .Sirbus is better than Boeing by over 90% in stock price gain over 3 years and will continue that lead as the newer better and on time on buget A350 comes on board for deliveries .and</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372860506846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372860684655-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Mindset of the Left and their role of protector of "the poor."</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372860257743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:04:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have to read anything more to know that the left crushes the poor, and greatly adds to their numbers. When you bankrupt the country with big govt, crony capitalism policies, and corruption, run unemployment very high, and your t ax base is destroyed, the poor get clobbered. Capitalism pays for the health and welfare of all Americans. The left, and BO are anti-capitalists.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372860684655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372861196437-24</Id><Topic><Title>Paris Air Show- Vote on Boeing vs Airbus Stock Price</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371247771854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and a update tally to see that I won and all the Boeing barkers did not . Airbus won the Paris airshow and I said , Airbus had already won at Paris , but it was better than I said . spartacus99991 had a fit ha ha The Paris Air Show was a success for major airplane makers Airbus and Boeing. At the show, the two companies reported more than $160 billion in orders. Airbus and Boeing are always battling for orders at the high profile Paris and Farnborough Air shows, held in alternating years in France and the United Kingdom. This year was no different. Airbus came out on top, notching deals for 466 planes worth more than $70 billion. In dollar terms, that just about matched the $72 billion sold at the 2011 Paris show. At the 2013 show, Airbus orders were strongest from Asian operators, including Singapore Airlines, and U.S. operators, including United Airlines, who ordered 35 A350-1000s. Airbus took its A350XWB into the air for the first time above the show. Boeing made a debut of the 787-10 that can hold more passengers and inked agreements for 442 planes worth $66 billion. The new Airbus orders add to a backlog of 4,928 planes at the end of May. Boeing's backlog exited this Spring north of 4,400. Airbus stock price increase over 3 years has bettered Boeing by over 90% and once the A350 comes on line expect Airbus to better Boeing stock price by another 100% over time</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372861196437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:19:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372861701045-25</Id><Topic><Title>Are you Democrats and RINOs Opposed to lower Taxes?</Title><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1372772838792</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 09:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welcome to the TEA Party all you Democrats and RINOs. Nice to to know we all agree on a a few principles the government should live by..</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372861701045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372862108961-26</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats have always had a problem with that question and refuse to answer it. ..Hmmmmmmm wonder why?</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372862108961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372862284210-27</Id><Topic><Title>How much of a Slave do you have to be to be a Slave?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372713556109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:19:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats think you can change what you call something and it won't be the same.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372862284210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372862320184-28</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My taxes are less now than they have been for 40 years and that`s all though Republicans and Democratic controlled governments. neither one is better when it comes to taxes , it`s just who they tax and how they line up the numbers on a chart .that is different. The same propaganda repeaters never change though .</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372862320184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372863618983-29</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BS..A friggin democrat never saw a tax they didn't like, and they are willing to act stupid to the fact that taxes are regressive...the higher you raise them the less you take in. Any party that thinks the way to serve the public is to INCREASE the size of govt is the best path to prosperity is as stupid as you appear to be.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372863618983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372864225416-30</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even thugs aren't generally punished by the death penalty -- administered by a vigilante, without an indictment, arrest, trial and verdict. That seems a little unAmercan to me.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372864225416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372864484134-31</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, And Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797102806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The U.S. Constitutions doesn't say a d am thing about the REASON for your vote. It only says you get to vote. Again, you seem to apply the H word to every one else, but you pay lip service to the Constitution until it doesn't suit you to do so.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372864484134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372864558438-32</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why are you always ranting about Democrats all the time taxing you? when the Republicans have done the same thing to you. Historically if you look at it Republican have raised taxes more than the Dem`s have.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372864558438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372864801038-33</Id><Title>Quote of the day</Title><Msg>"Life, faculties, production—in other words, individuality, liberty, property—this is man. And in spite of the cunning of artful political leaders, these three gifts from God precede all human legislation, and are superior to it. Life, liberty, and property do not exist because men have made laws. On the contrary, it was the fact that life, liberty, and property existed beforehand that caused men to make laws in the first place." Claude Frédéric Bastiat (1801-1850) Obama should have read that before he blurted out, "If you have a business, you didn't build that....."</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372864801038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372864878915-34</Id><Topic><Title>Investigation Update: July 2nd... FBI Still Hasn't Contacted IRS-Targeted Tea Party Groups</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372857451840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>censored err bumper err fascist err Benghazi err fraudulent existence brain damage delusions of persecution err spaz</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1372864878915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372865310391-35</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats and RINOs are rowing the same boat. The TEA Party targets the RINOs and does its best to replace them. Democrats have no such movement to rid it's self of the bureaucratic thieves in its party. The very foundation of the Democrat Party is to confiscate wealth from those who earn it and let their elected bureaucrats redistribute it to those who will help them the maintain power to confiscate the wealth of those who earn it.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372865310391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372865328269-36</Id><Title>Trayvon is Not on Trial</Title><Msg>he's already been tried, judged and executed by Zimmerman !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1372865328269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372865351834-37</Id><Topic><Title>Investigation Update: July 2nd... FBI Still Hasn't Contacted IRS-Targeted Tea Party Groups</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372857451840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spatipuss hates the tea party, like barack hussein and his ever faithful dumb party</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372865351834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372865581502-38</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon is Not on Trial</Title><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1372865328269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:28:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stikdik, err sparty, stands steadfast behind @no_limit#$%$ and mobros dem parasite marxists n mobros gotta divide to conquer</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372865581502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372865674983-39</Id><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Msg>"There is no end to what we can do together. There is no end, there is no end. The willow turns his back on inclement weather; And if he can do it We can do it, just me and you." Sir Paul McCartney, 1978</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372865674983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372865816496-40</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, Chris.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372865816496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372865873611-41</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tea Party people are fools being used by Corporate America to regain their foot hold in power, basically they have been led by talking heads to repeat propaganda endlessly. And as usual what they will end up doing Republicans and all of us more harm than good.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372865873611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372865879680-42</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372865674983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:34:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>barack's still got many supporters, just like morsi, huh sir paul</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372865879680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866059061-43</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372865674983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:34:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. To quote Carl Sagan, "billions and billions".</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372866059061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:40:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866063365-44</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>spazticus hates corporations, err employers, sparty's been gnawing on the hands that feed him for more'n a decade, a full time msg board garbage peddler....stuck on public, err taxpayer, funding</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372866063365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866274213-45</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372865674983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:34:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we are duh world, we are duh dumbos....if only we could just hold hands, surrender, err be at one with dem parasitic marxists n mobros, huh chrissie./spart?</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372866274213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866332001-46</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reality here is the fact there is a major portion of the GOP that luvs big govt, and taxes. WA DC, as inner city poor, and high incidence of crime that there is, has a very wealthy section of lobbiests and bureacrats that have thrived at the expense of the working public. It is the TEA Party that supports less govt. and giving the country back to the citizens...and they get attacked by the democrat left, and not supported by the RINOS in the GOP.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372866332001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866445888-47</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when is your morning feeding time little one? you should run along before mommy gets mad.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372866445888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866547696-48</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no need to change costumes just for me spazticus, i mean roksta</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372866547696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372866982929-49</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the day</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372864801038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bastiat? LOL. You might as well quote the Bahbull.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1372866982929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372867128256-50</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ah the easy way out huh?</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372867128256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372867199099-51</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chrissie/spart throws his whole hearted support behind @no_limit#$%$, marxists, n mobros, and himself of course, just like barack hussein comes down on the side or mobros with resources, revenue, arms, and coverups, excuses, and alibis</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372867199099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372867370479-52</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tea Party people are just average everyday Americans fed up with politicians of all stripes who want to take the wealth people earn and use it for unconstitutional and wasteful purposes, They are people who believe people who earn their wealth can spend it better than bureaucrats who didn't earn it. It's Democrats and RINOs that are beholden to corporate fat cats and bankers. You should educate yourself and read "Throw Them All Out" by Peter Schweizer for proof. It's People like rockstar that have drunk the kool-aid and swallowed the propaganda who can't handle the truth and examine the thieving principles of the Democrat party that are its enablers.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372867370479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372867448504-53</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>roksta, i mean sparty, has been a parasite since i've known him, a full time #$%$ peddler USING our money to disseminate the worst in yellow journalism and disinformation, one of the dumb party's ACORNs/community agitators</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372867448504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372867639329-54</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the day</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372864801038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Clorox.......just because you're a victim of socialized government education doesn't mean you can't learn from great minds of the past. Have you rediscovered gravity yet?</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372867639329</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372867763762-55</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the day</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372864801038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:20:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sparty tries on his leotards, i mean chaps...rhinestone</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372867763762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372868124158-56</Id><Title>Poll: Liberals favor the Communist Manifesto over the U.S. Constitution</Title><Msg>According to a UTI poll, by a marging of 67 % to 33% left leaning voter think the Communist Manifesto is a more relavant guide for governing than is the U.S. Constitution.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1372868124158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372868146731-57</Id><Topic><Title>How much does a thief have to steal to be a thief?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeoples</Username><Timestamp>1372715271431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 laptops of classified data.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1372868146731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:15:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372868327565-58</Id><Topic><Title>Investigation Update: July 2nd... FBI Still Hasn't Contacted IRS-Targeted Tea Party Groups</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372857451840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poo? You mean bringing up things like the 17 Trillion dollar debt, the EPA gone wild, no social security reform, IRS, businesses don't want to hire people because of Obama Care, those things? You mean facts..</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1372868327565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372868434098-59</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Liberals favor the Communist Manifesto over the U.S. Constitution</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1372868124158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:15:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Self-polling your family Urinary Tract Infection is evidently your source of "news." What's a "marging?" Marge Simpson doing something for Homer?</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1372868434098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372868515636-60</Id><Topic><Title>Public Spending</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1372868266147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Upon what basis do you conclude that they are poorer?</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1372868515636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372868673139-61</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Liberals favor the Communist Manifesto over the U.S. Constitution</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1372868124158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:15:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical of the left, don't talk about the facts, make fun of the person. People like you are slowly killing the country.</Msg><Username>binder_jim</Username><Timestamp>1372868673139</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372868770153-62</Id><Title>The Boeing Company is flailing around trying to work out what to do," said Airbus as they better Boeing</Title><Msg>Airbus is scoring key wins and building up a serious threat to Boeing's mini-jumbo franchise with a 350-seat version of its new carbon-fibre jet, the A350-1000. Boeing conceded Airbus had outsold it in the past five years after delays on its 787 model! Airbus says its A350-1000 will burn 25 percent less fuel per seat than the 777-300ER when it enters service .Boeing has now walked into a trap, the 777 next big thing can't work, here is why ".of the 22 current Boeing 777-300ER operators for which data is available, 27 percent are already at 10 abreast. Ironically, that may make the 777X's improved efficiencies harder not easier to prove. Airlines already operating this way would not get the full boost advertised for the 777X since the efficiency goal depends partly on going from nine to 10 abreast. You cant sell a 777 with addition rows as the airlines are already doing this . The larger wing is more drag boxed by their own out sourced engineering model . Boeing lost the 747 with the new wing to the A380 and to its own 777. Now Boeing will lose the 777, with the new wing to the better A350. It's a done deal, just start crying now Boeing Barkers Airbus has bettered Boeing for the past 3 years in stock price gain by over 90% and once the A350 is delivered expect Airbus to better Boeing stock price by another 100% gain.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372868770153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372868784865-63</Id><Topic><Title>No Matter How Much You Shake, Kick, And Dance!!!</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797102806</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:31:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republicans behind the scenes were real geniuses. They ensured that Obama would win, and thus take the blame for everything. Only Obama could make Bush's crimes go away. President McCain couldn't. And if McCain had to take the blame for the Great Recession following the crash of 2008, then surely a Democrat would have been elected in 2012, and there was no way of knowing it would be one as wimpy and servile as Obama.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1372868784865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372868853395-64</Id><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Msg>.......the people to whom Jessie redistributed other people's money had no need to lie about him being a thief.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372869009305-65</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why not just say whats the difference between what Democrats and Republicans do ? they both tax you they both raise and lower taxes depending on the season. there really is not much difference other than the charts they hold up.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372869009305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372869322026-66</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The big difference is the people who received money from Jessie James were not ignorant enough to be under the illusion that the money was not stolen.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372869322026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870118984-67</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most likely they were just happy to have booze money and had not a care in the world where it came from. what difference does it make if it`s a Democrat or Republicans doing the stealing/taxing they both do it. pretty equally</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372870118984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870466164-68</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now we're getting somewhere.....at least we agree they are both engaged in thievery. Now the question is how to stop it. The less we let them steal, the better off we'll be. So work with any politician who wants to reduce the amount they steal and spend.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372870466164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871171506-69</Id><Topic><Title>Public Spending</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1372868266147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Understanding social spending compared to a nations GDP. The why Europe is buried in debt and deep recession.</Msg><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1372871171506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:06:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871241102-70</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously we do it better.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372871241102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871360594-71</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Liberals favor the Communist Manifesto over the U.S. Constitution</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1372868124158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:15:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our poll says you are.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372871360594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871450003-72</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If that post means I'm on the other side, then yes.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372871450003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372871710911-73</Id><Topic><Title>Paris Air Show- Vote on Boeing vs Airbus Stock Price</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1371247771854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:09:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I predicted Airbus stock (EAD.PA) would outperform BA (percentagewise) during the 5 days of the Paris Airshow, which was the OPs question. It didn't. Big deal.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372871710911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872020876-74</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why not just hold the politicians in office on both sides accountable ? just electing new people giving you lip service to get elected to do the same thing over and over does not get us anywhere. pointing fingers and blaming each other does nothing either.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372872020876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872068723-75</Id><Topic><Title>Which is better Boeing Barkers, or TSLA and SCTY?</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372744070569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 01:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" these Boeing barkers and add dellgeorgius" Wayne's trying to be cute now, when everyone knows he was the original dell.george (who made $28M on APPL before Jobs died as did fred.james48 who also claimed the $28M gain)</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372872068723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872392752-76</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The best of the thieves was Robin Hood. He stole from the hooz's crooked magistrate tax collectors, and gave the money back to the people. Not much difference between Jesse, and Hooz, and his leftist bureaucrats. They both are corrupt, and have no moral compass.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372872392752</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872579040-77</Id><Topic><Title>The Mindset of the Left and their role of protector of "the poor."</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372860257743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:04:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha - you two ladies are all about saving the poor !!</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1372872579040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872587588-78</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimmerman should have never even gone to trial. The spineless Florida State Gov. caved in to the loud mouthed leftist thugs, and put him in jail. Florida could find no evidence at all for three weeks, and saw no reason to jail Zimmerman. Then the lyin left came up with some phony, 3rd party witness that lied. No way will Zimmerman ever be found guilty given what has transpired thus far.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372872587588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872660588-79</Id><Topic><Title>Still waiting for Wayne's invention to change airplane technology</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372807174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of all the postings of Wayne, this has got to rank as one of his most outrageous. Either that or we have one of the great aeronautical minds of the past 130 years gracing us with his presence. I wonder which it is. Let's just wait for his patent and disclosure. Collier trophy will take a little longer.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372872660588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872779419-80</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The prosecution's latest witness testified that Zimmerman received an A in a law course he taught and said of Zimmerman, ""He was probably one of the better students in the class". The prosecution also pointed out to the jury that Zimmerman had ambition too, unlike Martin. This is brilliant work by the prosecution to paint Zimmerman as an individual that does well in class and aspires to have a career in law enforcement because we know those are traits of lying evil doers. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1372872779419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872956569-81</Id><Topic><Title>Public Spending</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1372868266147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>List of countries by GDP (PPP) per capita Switzerland # 6 USA # 7 Austria # 10 Netherlands # 11 Ireland # 13 Sweden # 15 Denmark # 16 Germany # 17 Belgium #18 France # 21 United Kingdom # 22 Italy # 24 Spain # 25</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372872956569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872998254-82</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no idea why you continue this think I`m the loon sparty , my guess it`s like everything else you post SO WRONG and misinformed, or just bat sht crazy .now run along your mom is probably wondering where you are</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372872998254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873115240-83</Id><Topic><Title>Still waiting for Wayne's invention to change airplane technology</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372807174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can't you work it out amongst yourself, err selves, i figure he shares the ba cube at your msg board jihad, err disinformation, center.</Msg><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1372873115240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873512022-84</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because they have the monopoly on power, its pretty hard to hold them accountable. They have made themselves immune from insider trading laws among other schemes.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372873512022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873633028-85</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A; simple fact that a simple person like yourself should be able to understand. The Tea Party folks want less big govt that steals. You libs want more big govt that steals. GET IT? If not you are far more stupid than a simpleton.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372873633028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874428312-86</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The best of the thieves was Robin Hood." He always wore tights. You neocons really like men in tights, don't you?</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372874428312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372874444623-87</Id><Title>BA</Title><Msg>airbus down on both Paris and OTC markets. Boeing up 1.42 Good end of quarter and half year delivery numbers. 3rd quarter production numbers higher. Defense sales/contracts looking good.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1372874444623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372874681436-88</Id><Title>first half deliveries</Title><Msg>From the AP: Boeing delivered more planes than Airbus during the first half of this year. Boeing has delivered 306 jetliners so far, including 17 787s. Boeing is playing catch-up with those deliveries because of the problems with the 787's battery earlier this year. Boeing is aiming to deliver 60 of those planes this year. Airbus has delivered 295 civilian planes this year. It delivered more of its smaller A320 family of planes than the comparable Boeing jets. Airbus handed over 233 of its A320 family of planes, compared to Boeing's deliveries of 218 of its 737s.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1372874681436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874871714-89</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kent Raven trying to inject some Kent Bath House humor on the BA board........................</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1372874871714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874913984-90</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Liberals favor the Communist Manifesto over the U.S. Constitution</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1372868124158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:15:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are DFC's.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1372874913984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874979206-91</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Levon your hero?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1372874979206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372876409737-92</Id><Title>Wayne - NYSE actually closed early today</Title><Msg>Wayne, now today the market actually did close early, not like the disinformation you posted on Mar 28. LOL " the stock market closes early thrusday and is not open friday-osulinn get a clue waynedickenson961 by waynedickenson961 • Mar 28, 2013 5:10 AM Flag osulinn get a clue."</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372876409737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372876470708-93</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Company is flailing around trying to work out what to do," said Airbus as they better Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372868770153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:26:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice to know how to trade stock with a stock chart and ot Barking that is like hope its not a good way to make money in the stock market. The worst is to listen to a Boeing barker, they don't care about you all they want to do is sell you Boeing stock all day long every day and you need to protect your investment not go with a stock like Boeing bettered by Airbus by 90% over 3 years. attention Boeing Barkers Airbus is up over 90% better than Boeing over 3 years in stock price gain, Airbus beat Boeing at Paris and Boeing admitted Airbus is better over 5 years , Boeing has gone from competition for number 1 to now; Boeing is saying , don't count us out yet, we are number 2, what a loser bunch of barkers and trolls , dellgoeroious,spartacus9991 and his second name neospart99,jojvaz,domerrrr, custerious, joedokes 45, foulmoutharbor, barbing you should have been in Apple until Jobs died, then ACAD then TSLA , 100% gain in 15 days like Jobs Elon is a proven money maker, he was the owner of PayPal in case you Boeing barkers missed that one too. Tesla gained 100% in May over 15 days, and now you could be following my one sentence day trade rule and making day trades on it</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372876470708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372876633029-94</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Company is flailing around trying to work out what to do," said Airbus as they better Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372868770153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:26:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the symbol for Airbus(EADS)?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372876633029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372876697064-95</Id><Topic><Title>Still waiting for Wayne's invention to change airplane technology</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372807174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Made any appointments to see Burt about your invention?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372876697064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372876865683-96</Id><Topic><Title>first half deliveries</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1372874681436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:04:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Wall Streel Journal: Boeing Co.'s BA +1.40%second-quarter jetliner deliveries rose to a 15-year high as it continues to increase production to keep pace with demand for new aircraft. The Chicago-based plane maker said Wednesday it has delivered 306 commercial aircraft in 2013, including 169 from April through June, the most it has delivered in a single quarter since 1998 and a 13% increase over the same period a year earlier. The record output was driven by production increases for its single-aisle 737 and the May resumption of shipments of its 787 Dreamliner</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1372876865683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372876987942-97</Id><Title>What Metric is used to determine who is the #1 aircraft manufacturer?</Title><Msg>Is it deliveries, sales, stock price, profits, customer satisfaction? If deliveries, Boeing is ahead so far this year</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1372876987942</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:43:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372877512881-98</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Difference between What Jessie James did and what Democrats do?</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372868853395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think electing tea party people into office will change the cycle? might as well just put in more far leftest.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372877512881</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:51:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372877929324-99</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. But Willie O'keefe is your hero.</Msg><Username>fats_marty</Username><Timestamp>1372877929324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372878190191-100</Id><Topic><Title>The smearing of Rachel Jeantel</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797853297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:44:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe if she could read her own letters, then she would be a more effective witness. It's kind of hard to believe a person can write but not be able to read. Maybe not to you rac5ist true believers though. You guys are a joke LMAO.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1372878190191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372878231416-101</Id><Topic><Title>What Metric is used to determine who is the #1 aircraft manufacturer?</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1372876987942</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:43:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AvWeek often ranks by annual revenue, including both commercial and military/space divisions (and any other misc divisions). Other rankings can use different metrics depending on what they're trying to high-light (or prove to make a point).</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372878231416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372878342711-102</Id><Topic><Title>Travyon Martin conspiracy theorists get desperate</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372797737127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 16:42:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The law says if you shoot someone, there ought to be an investigation, and that investigation can lead to charges, on which there should be a trial. Why do you fear justice?</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372878342711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372879254291-103</Id><Topic><Title>Public Spending</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1372868266147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greece is # 40 In many ways we are worse off than Greece</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879254291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372879909699-104</Id><Topic><Title>The Mindset of the Left and their role of protector of "the poor."</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372860257743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:04:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They frame it in terms of the middle class helping the lowest class, but it's really about the clowns helping the 1% at the expense of the rest of us.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1372879909699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372879911348-105</Id><Topic><Title>What Metric is used to determine who is the #1 aircraft manufacturer?</Title><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1372876987942</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:43:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Revenues seems like a bad metric. as in the case of the current situation on the 787. They currently loose money on each one of these early planes they deliver until they come down the learning curve/productivity curve. I think earnings would be a better way to measure sucess/ being #1. Selling at a loss as compared to a profit would certainly make airplane purchases more attractive to the lower cost planes provided both planes being considered have the same benefits to an airline. Like you said, I guess it all depends on what point someone is trying to prove</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1372879911348</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372880023834-106</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: IT CAN WAIT UNTIL AFTER THE ELECTION...</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372870159898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So let's see--small businesses and individuals still have to comply with the law, but businesses employing more than 50 don't? The odor of rodent abounds.</Msg><Username>poordumbbastard</Username><Timestamp>1372880023834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372880120392-107</Id><Title>Crumble: The Disastrous Obamacare Delay</Title><Msg>A classic bad news dump on the front end of a long holiday weekend. The administration is out of luck if it hopes their major announcement will disappear amidst hot dogs and parades; we'll be talking about this move for the next year-and-a-half: The Obama administration will delay a crucial provision of its signature health-care law, giving businesses an extra year to comply with a requirement that they provide their workers with insurance. The government will postpone enforcement of the so-called employer mandate until 2015, after the congressional elections, the administration said yesterday. Under the provision, companies with 50 or more workers face a fine of as much as $3,000 per employee if they don’t offer affordable insurance. It’s the latest setback for a health-care law that has met resistance from Republicans, who have sought to make the plan a symbol of government overreach. Republican-controlled legislatures and governors in several states have refused funding to expand Medicaid coverage for the poor and declined to set up exchanges where individuals can buy insurance, leaving the job to the federal government. The delay in the employer mandate addresses complaints from business groups to President Barack Obama’s administration about the burden of the law’s reporting requirements. If the White House had listened to business owners before passing this law, they wouldn't be mopping up their own mess today because Obamacare wouldn't exist. This development also marks the death of Democrats' bogus "Republican obstructionism" excuse-making. (It was always bogus because (a) the exclusively Democrat-written and -passed law allowed states to opt out of setting up exchanges, and (b) the mandatory Medicaid expansion element was struck down by seven Supreme Court justices). Now we have the Obama administration delaying a (second) major component of its own law due to a combination of incompetence, admitted economic harm and political considerations.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372880120392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372881081844-108</Id><Title>Obama Exploits a Compliant America</Title><Msg>“You can’t have 100 percent security and also then have 100 percent privacy and zero inconvenience. We’re going to have to make some choices as a society.” So says Barack Obama, in defense of his administration’s policy of monitoring the phone records of private citizens, just because he can. This is like saying: “You can only have so much liberty.” How is this any different from a dictatorship, in principle? A dictator allows lots of “freedom.” Soviet Russia, #$%$ Germany and other dictatorships throughout history allowed plenty of freedom—to those who supported the regime. Some of them even allow elections—so long as the outcome is not in question. Plenty of “rights” exist in dictatorships—to those who comply with the ruling authorities. U.S. Senator Rand Paul, one of the few Americans who appears to be awake on this issue, puts it well. He’s stating what should be the obvious. Paul says the government should be using a specific warrant, not a general warrant, to get the data required to prevent terrorist attacks, arguing the Fourth Amendment prevents unreasonable search and seizure. “The Founding Fathers didn’t want that,” said Senator Paul. “I think the American people are with me.” This last remains to be seen. The question is: How much are Americans willing to take before they rise up and say, “No more”? In family therapy for alcoholics, we’re trained to confront people in denial about the alcohol or substance abuse taking place in their families. One of the things we say to clients is, “How long are you willing to take this? How long before you stop tolerating this? Do you think the problem will go away if you say (or think) nothing about it?” The sickness in dysfunctional families—or societies—isn’t a failure to do the impossible. It’s a failure to call things what they are. It’s a refusal to name aloud what is plainly true…because of fear, and sometimes self-loathing.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372881081844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372881138128-109</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: IT CAN WAIT UNTIL AFTER THE ELECTION...</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372870159898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama, and the left know ObamaCare is a huuuuuge tax on businesses that will skyrocket unemployment much higher than the already high unemployment Obama, and the left have created. Do you really have to be smarter than a 5th grader to understand liberalism is a total failure?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372881138128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372881268711-110</Id><Topic><Title>The Mindset of the Left and their role of protector of "the poor."</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1372860257743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:04:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Called a safety net that the corrupt left can not provide for long. Liberalism/socialism always goes bankrupt.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372881268711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:54:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372881455442-111</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: IT CAN WAIT UNTIL AFTER THE ELECTION...</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372870159898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and the Democrats have never been about helping the poor or middle class. Who's out of work - the poor. Who's businesses got bailed out - not the small and middle class businesses unless you were a big donor with a phoney green energy company. He did bail out the fat cat bankers and huge corporations like GE, BAC and Citi.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372881455442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372881956663-112</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets give a big shout out to all the Republicans that have done their part to contribute to the nations debt. I guess in your world we can call them the forgotten ones.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372881956663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372882029803-113</Id><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Msg>Rock-and-Roller Ted Nugent Mulls Presidential Bid Rock-and-roll star and staunch conservative Ted Nugent is contemplating running for president. "Things are just so wrong in the country now," he told The Washington Post Magazine. "And I know that my answers would make things wonderful, unless you just refuse to produce. And then I’d recommend that you move to Canada — or Illinois." Nugent already has an idea for a campaign slogan. "Hi, I’m Ted Nugent. I have nine children from seven women, and I’m running for president." The avid gun advocate has contemplated running for political office before, considering campaigns for governor of Michigan in 2006 and 2010. Nugent was a guest of Rep. Steve Stockman, R-Tex., at President Barack Obama's State of the Union address in February. Less than a year earlier, Nugent received a call from the Secret Service after proclaiming he would "be dead or in jail" if Obama won re-election. Nugent is a columnist for Newsmax. In his latest piece, published June 6, the rocker said that is a date "that all Americans should study, know and remember. It is as important as July 4th." That's because U.S. and allied forces invaded Normandy that day in 1944, during World War II.</Msg><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372882089778-114</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OH God help us if that ever happens, and I`m atheist!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372882089778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372882267854-115</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Exploits a Compliant America</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372881081844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul can say whatever he wants but if he ever becomes President ( Which will never happen) and the day he takes office and his job is to protect the nation he will do whatever needs to be done including everything being done today.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372882267854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372882299165-116</Id><Title>Myths, Fallacies, and the History of Capitalism</Title><Msg>I know that I should not be surprised that most people have little knowledge regarding the history of capitalism. Our schools certainly don’t teach it, and everybody “knows” that capitalism leads to all sorts of evils, such as abuse of employees by employers, “predatory” lending, and “dog-eat-dog” competition. These myths and fallacies are repeated by the media and most Americans with alarming frequency. As an example, I recently received an email that contained the following statement: A study of history makes it clear that corporations are not interested in protecting their employees unless forced to by law. Actually, history shows the opposite. For example, in 1869 George Westinghouse implemented a nine-hour work day (ten hours was common) and also instituted “welfare” programs for his employees. In 1914 Henry Ford doubled the daily wage of his workers and reduced the hours worked per day. Ford, who called his policy “enlightened self-interest,” later described the results: In 1914, when the first plan went into effect, we had 14,000 employees and it had been necessary to hire at the rate of about 53,000 a year in order to keep a constant force of 14,000. In 1915 we had to hire only 6,000 men and the majority of these new men were taken on because of the growth of the business. [Henry Ford, My Life and Work, (Garden City, NY: Garden City Publishing Co.) p. 119.] When Ford’s profits soared, other companies began emulating his policies. Ford, Westinghouse, and others, did not have to be forced to “protect” their employees. They simply needed to be free to act as they judged best. Another statement from the email: The housing crisis is another example of an unregulated market… Banks are only interested in getting the deal done. Shareholders are only interested in profit, and the CEO knows that he will be replaced if the bank isn’t profitable. Regulation provide a mediator between the company and the consumer. Many others have pointed out the myth that the mortgage market is unregulated, so I will not repeat those points here. I will point out that John Allison at BB&amp;T was interested in more than getting the deal done, and his company has been very successful. Nor was he replaced by stockholders. Further, regulators are not “mediators.” They are dictators who impose their will on businessmen. Regulators force businessmen to act contrary to their own judgment. When a businessman is free and makes a poor decision, he (and those who voluntarily associate with him) suffers the consequences. When a regulator makes a poor decision, everyone suffers. Finally, one last statement from the email: The trick is finding a balance between competition and cooperation. While I favor individual freedom, we can’t go to the extreme of Social Darwinism. We need some regulations to protect the masses. This claim is loaded with too many myths and fallacies to address in a single post. Those myths and fallacies are founded on a false alternative: We must choose between “competition and cooperation.” Freedom is viewed as “survival of the fittest.” According to this view, success can only be gained at the expense of others. Again, history (and the contemporary world) provides a different picture. Prior to the advent of the “entitlement” state, mutual aid societies were common throughout the United States. These societies were voluntary, cooperative organizations that provided health care, burial insurance, and other benefits to members. As one example, in Tampa, workers in the cigar industry formed five different mutual aid societies. Contrast these voluntary, cooperative endeavors with the competition for “entitlement” benefits. Seniors demand that Social Security be protected from budget cuts. Advocates for the poor lobby for more programs to help the needy. The unemployed call for an expansion of unemployment benefits. Supporters of these programs, and others like them, compete for the “privilege” of plundering their neighbors. In a sense, we must choose between competition and cooperation. But cooperation is only possible when individuals are free to act on their own judgment, when they are free to associate as they choose. “Cooperation” at the point of a government gun is worse than a contradiction. It sets up a competition of warring interest groups, each seeking to extract money from taxpayers. As these few examples show, the myths and fallacies regarding the history of capitalism are not only untrue, they are the exact opposite of what actually occurred.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372882299165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372882584685-117</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Are You a Democrat?</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372882584685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372882756594-118</Id><Title>AIRBUS Record Backlog and going a Lot HIGHER! Opening Factories in the U.S.</Title><Msg>Mobil gets the first one and others and engineering Centers are planned. Airbus is going for the 3 count.</Msg><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1372882756594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372883099866-119</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you a parasite?</Msg><Username>cliberg</Username><Timestamp>1372883099866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372883380155-120</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I`m an American first and I find Democrats more tolerable and less of liars than Republicans are . the lesser of two evils you could say .</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1372883380155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:29:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372883421289-121</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's easy.....Democrat insist that I be one.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372883421289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372883879707-122</Id><Title>The Age of Envy and Entitlements: A New Kind of Civil War</Title><Msg>Now that all the excuses, rationalizations, analyses, number-countings, hand-wringings, finger-pointings, and tear-sheddings have largely passed, I feel that I can say something about why, on November 6th, Mitt Romney lost his bid for the presidency and Obama retained it. It seems that all that is left to do, for someone who realizes that a second Obama term will be more destructive, vindictive, and malicious than the first, is fulminate anew at a succession of fresh assaults on liberty, freedom of speech, property, wealth, standards of living, national security, the military, and on America from without and from within. I’m guessing that about half the people who voted for Romney voted for him because he wasn’t Obama. The choice can be likened to voting for Barney Fife because he isn’t Hannibal Lecter. That was why I voted for Romney. Other than recommend that everyone who opposed Obama just stay home and let the Obamatons monopolize the polling places, there wasn’t much choice in the way of action. Fife in the White House could have at least stalled the movement to full statism and allowed some serious steam to build up against big government – or of Hannibal Lecter not making a meal of everyone. But Hannibal Lecter had the Chicago machine working for him and a brainwashed, idolizing fan club that could be counted on to vote for him. They turned out to vote early and often. Romney’s campaign, on the other hand, was reminiscent of a large-scale drive to get people to buy Girl Scout cookies. Many who opposed Obama stayed home because Romney waffled on what he really believed and charged Obama with being an “extremist.” Which is exactly why many disliked Obama, because he was an “extreme” advocate of policies and programs that were eating them alive or had targeted them for the cannibal’s cooking pot. They already knew he was a Marxist extremist. What they wanted from Romney was a counter-extremism, one that was point for point the exact opposite of Obama’s ideology. What they heard instead were approximations and equivocations and denials of being an “extremist.” What many who stayed home observed was that Romney’s touting of financial independence and freedom of choice contradicted his enactment of RomneyCare in Massachusetts, which the administration has confessed served as the boilerplate for Obamacare. What, in these voters’ minds, could be the difference between a state-enforced socialist program and a federally-enforced socialist program? There was no difference, except in scale. Obama garnered the states with the most Electoral College numbers. Those are what count. And over the years Democrats were “hollering” for the abolition of the Electoral College because they said it was an anachronism and unfair, just as they hollered for and got the popular election of Senators (formerly appointed by the states), which, from a political mechanism perspective, undid the work of the Founders. The Senate was created as a bulwark against populist movements originating in the House. The Senate, as a result of this election, has become an unofficial departmental adjunct of the White House. I’m betting the Democrats are grateful they didn’t succeed. Now it’s the House that will need to act as a bulwark against the Senate and the White House. But House Speaker JohnBoehner has telegraphed that the House will not stand against Obama and the Senate. “Mr. President, this is your moment. We’re ready to be led,” said Boehner. “Not as Democrats or Republicans but as Americans. We want you to lead not as a liberal or a conservative but as president of the United States of America. “We want you to succeed,” said Boehner. “Let’s challenge ourselves to find the common ground that has eluded us. Let’s rise above the dysfunction and do the right thing together for our country.” When I read that, I kept hearing Hitler saying the same thing to masses of uniformly clad zombies held rapt by his oratory. Or Evita Peron addressing her adoring Argentines. Or Mussolini daring anyone to smack his jutting jaw. The people who voted for Obama are morally corrupt. You would have thought that the Benghazi debacle alone would have convinced voters that he was no good, that he was indeed a nihilist prepared to sacrifice American lives to protect a failed policy. You have to then examine what that means, which is that they don’t mind seeing him destroy things, things on which their lives depend. You must grasp that they don’t know what their lives depend on. Or don’t care to know. They just want it their way. They see no relationship between Obama being willing to see American lives sacrificed in a pesthole and sacrificing American lives at home. Or, if they do see the relationship, they don’t care to dwell on it, because that would lead them to conclusions about Obama’s character and intentions which are not pretty and which they don’t care to dwell on. One of those conclusions would be that Obama is a moral monster, a Moloch to whom everything must be sacrificed, even their children. And that would imply that they, too, are moral monsters. They didn’t want to go there. They wanted to believe that Obama and his policies are a causeless cornucopia of free things and social justice and multicultural enrichment and diversification. And if some Americans have to be sacrificed to make their fantasies come true – tough.</Msg><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372883879707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372885536541-123</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic! The burned out former rock star can siphon off all the gun nut votes from the Repugnantcon candidate and that will help ensure Hillary's -- or Wendy Davis' -- win.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372885536541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372885695913-124</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unprovoked wars against middle east nations like Iraq, while giving huge tax breaks to the "debt producers" can sure be costly.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1372885695913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372885969590-125</Id><Topic><Title>AIRBUS Record Backlog and going a Lot HIGHER! Opening Factories in the U.S.</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1372882756594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:19:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Shell and Chevron also get some?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372885969590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:12:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372887766404-126</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Misery loves company, and liberals sure have made a lot of misery in the USA, and more than happy to be like other economically miserable countries.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372887766404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372889860730-127</Id><Topic><Title>The Age of Envy and Entitlements: A New Kind of Civil War</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372883879707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:37:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quite likely the most flaccid, vapid, brainless, pointless, worthless, and stupidest cut &amp; paste post from pretend wannabecapitalist all day.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1372889860730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372890497577-128</Id><Title>BA to get a new A380 , has 12-A380 now and retiring the Boeing 747-400's going with A350 planes</Title><Msg>British Airways has 19 new A350 on order and may shift from the 787 to include more A350's going forward , if the lemon 787 continues to have problems. BA has 6 new 777X on order but can cancel if like the 787 the plane is late, over cost and not working as promised. Remember the Boeing barkers they will constantly give you a story and bark you into Boeing a stock Bettered by Airbus over 3 years by 90%. the barker are spartacus99991, and his second name neospart99, jojvaz the Boeing worker hater, foulmoutharbor who seems to think a plane delivered late by 4 years , over cost by 30 billion and not working as planned is a good thing, 787, domerrr a troll,custerious atroll, Jokedokes45 and Barbing who has been waiting for Boeing to hit 150 for several years now while ACAD went yo 12005, then TSLA went up 2465 and SCTY went up 2355 over that past 12 months Boeing went up 38% while Airbus went up 47% so Airbus for one year bettered Boeing by 9% and for 3 years Airbus stock price bettered Boeing by over 90% CNN money stock chart . all the barking by spartacus9991 ans his other fradulant name neospart99 and his coaching by Chris genna is worthless int eh face of the facts he might as wel go back to talking about his wife and stocks he picked like IGZ that do not exsist . Barking does not work stock charting does work !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372890497577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372890582632-129</Id><Topic><Title>BA to get a new A380 , has 12-A380 now and retiring the Boeing 747-400's going with A350 planes</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372890497577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:28:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12000 should be 1200%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372890582632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372891177861-130</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Company is flailing around trying to work out what to do," said Airbus as they better Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372868770153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:26:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so remember for one year ,Airbus stock bettered Boeing by 9%- 38% gain for Boeing , 47% for Airbus cnn money stock chart, and for 3 years Airbus stock price has gained more than 90% better than Boeing.;Remember this, all the Boeing barkers can do is spin stories, that is spartacus99991, and his second name neospart99,domerrrr,jojvaz, the Boeing hourly worker hater, next is custerious a troll, joe dokes45, dell georgious a troll, ,and foulmoutharbor, a daily poster for boeing, who is a serial barker, who thinks giving you daily delivery on Boeing planes that are 4 years late, 30 billion over cost and grounded , not to mention are still having to divert to make unscheduled landings is a selling point , and lets not forget the safety of the flying public, never put a dangerous lithium battery in a box, instead of fixing the root cause . Remember you can not carry lithium batteries in a cargo area it is too dangerous due to fire and actual more than one airplane crash and total burned up and killing all people aboard, this is what flying a 787 is. Flying on a 787 is a very dangerous thing to do.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372891177861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372892695787-131</Id><Topic><Title>AIRBUS Record Backlog and going a Lot HIGHER! Opening Factories in the U.S.</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1372882756594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:19:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>futurperson , good user comment , notice and remember there are 6 Boeing barkers that monitor this Boeing message board and will do everything they can, propaganda, or make lair statements to try to stop your freedom to make you user comment . spartacus9991 and he has another name uniposter99 and his handler Chris Genna have been working the Boeing barker plan for years they stand at the Boeing message door and try to get people to buy Boeing stock any day and time. spartacus99991 claims to be a MD retiree who owns no Boeing, stock but for years ,6 by his own account on this name he dogs anyone with a factual view on Boeing especially any truthful comparison to the number one maker of planes , Airbus. In fact, just go to cnn money then enter BA for 1 year it is 38%then do the same for Airbus stock symbol is eadsy, it is 47% so in addition to besting Boeing in both billions of dollars sold 70.5 to 66, at Paris and total orders at Paris, Airbus has a larger backlog of planes to build than Boeing. So as you said, airbus rules over Boeing other Boeing barkers to not listen to are spartacus9991 other name neospart99,domerrrr,custerious, jjovaz a Boeing worker hater, Joe dokes45, delgeorgius, foulmooutharbor, who seems to think posting airplane orders is a good selling point or deliveries, both are less than Airbus all the time every day joedokes45 and barbing who works at Boeing but trust her Boeing will be a 150 dollar stock while apple went up thousands of percent for years , ACAD went up 1200 in the lst year, TSLA went up 100% in May and over 240% in a year and same for SCTY , play with Airbus if you want but never Boeing too risky lithium batteries have caused more than one crash and kill</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372892695787</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:04:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372893033721-132</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, Here Is Your What The #$%$!!! Moment of the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372882029803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:07:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what it has come to with the new right wing. A guy who #$%$ his pants to get out of fighting for his country, has a campaign slogan. "Hi, I’m Ted Nugent. I have nine children from seven women, and I’m running for president.", and is an inarticulate fool is a Tea Party favorite. Crazy, but not unlike Sarah Palin.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1372893033721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372893134933-133</Id><Topic><Title>Expert: No Martin DNA On Gun Grip</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372892219553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:56:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound way to emotionally involved with Levon...........</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1372893134933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372894339283-134</Id><Topic><Title>Expert: No Martin DNA On Gun Grip</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372892219553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:56:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why should Martin's DNA be on Zimmerman's gun grip? Zimmerman testified that during the time Martin was on top of him beating in his head as the evidence hasshown Martin reached his hand down for Zimmerman's gun, and Zimmerman drew the gun, and shot Martin fearing that he would be the guy killed if he didn't. Zimmerman's voice has been identified as the one screaming for help, and no one came. That forced Zimmerman to draw, and shoot Martin given what happened.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1372894339283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372894800468-135</Id><Topic><Title>AIRBUS Record Backlog and going a Lot HIGHER! Opening Factories in the U.S.</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1372882756594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:19:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just about everything Wayne or almost everyone else has ever posted to this board pales in comparison to Wayne's bombshell disclosure that he has an invention "that will be a giant step forward in aerospace technology". Wayne, where's the patent so airlines can start benefiting from your invention and making lots of money. We're waiting.</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372894800468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372894974876-136</Id><Topic><Title>BA to get a new A380 , has 12-A380 now and retiring the Boeing 747-400's going with A350 planes</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372890497577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:28:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"while ACAD went yo 12005, then TSLA went up 2465 and SCTY went up 2355 over that past 12 months" What kind of gibberish is this?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372894974876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372895027615-137</Id><Topic><Title>Still waiting for Wayne's invention to change airplane technology</Title><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372807174784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 19:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any word from Burt yet?</Msg><Username>spartacus99991</Username><Timestamp>1372895027615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 19:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372896102180-138</Id><Title>★★★★INDEPENDENCE DAY=Democrats/LIBs OUT asap !!★★★★</Title><Msg>wooohooooooo !!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1372896102180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372901704846-139</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Company is flailing around trying to work out what to do," said Airbus as they better Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372868770153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:26:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>eadsy for over the counter market ead.pa for the paris market</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1372901704846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 21:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372903920969-140</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Trayvons were very significant! Good guy 1 , Thug 0........ BTW, how many times are you to suffer a thug beating your head on a sidewalk before it's significant? Wonder if the white community will riot if a guilty verdict ? Doubt it, but guaranteed the black community will riot and burn and loot if not guilty...</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1372903920969</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372905463718-141</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Company is flailing around trying to work out what to do," said Airbus as they better Boeing</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372868770153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:26:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and remember spartacus9991 and the crew of barkers, hey have nothing to offer but buy Boeing all the time, every day no matter Airbus is a better stock than Boeing what is the symbol for boeng is it the fakes stock that spartaucus99991tried to tell me was better than ACAD -IGZ wow and bark for Spartacus 99991 been a dog for Boeing ever since he retired from MD but has no stock in Boeing apparently he did not understand Smith Hart or was it hart Smith at least he should get the name right whatever,this spartcus99991 is nothing but a Boeing barker if you remember that,you have everything you need to know about spartacus99991 or neospart99 when he needs to help the alternative name , who knows, e missed the run up in apple for years , he missed ACAD for a 1200% gain he missed TSLA ,t least he is not in Boeing but sure seems to like Boeing, what a deal missed 9% better gain in Airbus for the last year compared to Boeing and missed over 90% gain over BAin 3 years so do not listen to spartacus99991 all he wants to do is put you into Boeing, while he sits on the sideline with no Boeing stock somehow that seems off maybe he like two names not a guy to trust,.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372905463718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372905500086-142</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A medical examiner who reviewed video and photographs of George Zimmerman's injuries...." Apparently, no one that actually saw or treated Zimmerman's injuries in person were willing to testify on the behalf of the prosecution. Says a lot.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1372905500086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372906602368-143</Id><Topic><Title>George Zimmerman Jury Told His Injuries Were 'Insignificant'</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_557</Username><Timestamp>1372897132116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 20:18:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She will be discredited in cross examination. She's a nut job and the defense has a long list of former associates that filed complaints against her that can testify that she's a nut. Watch and learn.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1372906602368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372907886920-144</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Liberals favor the Communist Manifesto over the U.S. Constitution</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1372868124158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:15:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is probably written in goonese, or maybe tehadese, or teabaggerese.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1372907886920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 23:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372909887872-145</Id><Topic><Title>BA to get a new A380 , has 12-A380 now and retiring the Boeing 747-400's going with A350 planes</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372890497577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:28:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spartacus99991 to wayne , “IGZ made 144% gain today (3-21-2013) so what’s your point! Well spartacus99991, , oh really, what is my point spartacus9991 you do a tirade against me, but you do not trade stocks, because you’re a Boeing hack that is it. , spartacus99991, well then IGZ is a test stock symbol and you are a very ignorant Boeing hack spartacus99991 , as usual you fooled yourself , you yanked your own chain attempting to find a gainer today , you cannot find a real stock to put up against me in your tirade against me , how sad for you spartacus9991! Spartacus99991, and now go ahead , please put your next spin on your lifetime of mistakes spartacus99991! While ACAD is a real stock that traded today for me and the volume is in the millions of shares ,and did make me 26% Because this ACAD is a rocket I trade stocks you’re a Boeing hack that is the major difference between me and spartacus9991. unlike IGZ which is not a real trade stock, but your too ignorant to know that !, , spartacus99991 you also have claimed to make perfect low to high Boeing trade. then later you claimed to not own Boeing stock but be a retired MD engineer , so what are you really a fake and a fraud is most likely what you are . Spartacus99991 you claimed you were just lucky then har</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1372909887872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 23:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372910154333-146</Id><Topic><Title>So, You Democrats and other Socialists Want the U.S. to be More LIke Other Socialist Countries</Title><Username>capitalists4freedom</Username><Timestamp>1372879704477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:28:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's apparent to me that democrats do poorly in history. People who do poorly in history tend to make the same mistakes over and over. People in the know know that Capitalism has been more successful over time than any other form of government. Even America's poor are better off than the poor in other countries. That's something for the Progressive Socialists to consider the next time they go to Starbucks!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1372910154333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 23:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>