<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359697487234-1</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing...is the Fix-In yet?</Title><Username>rogerjames55346</Username><Timestamp>1359658960999</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 14:02:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, they'll replace the Li-Ions with some Kirkland-Brand AA batteries tied together with duct tape.</Msg><Username>rogerjames55346</Username><Timestamp>1359697487234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 00:44:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359702401871-2</Id><Title>OXF - Ready to Rally 100%</Title><Msg>Oversold, Enjoy!</Msg><Username>davidgoldberg652</Username><Timestamp>1359702401871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 02:06:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359713726221-3</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA to ratify the strike over pensions and a comparison with Boeing Executive pension costs</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359687964804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 22:06:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, in your opinion Boeing management might provoke a strike to gain some time to put the original battery design back to operation? That would make some sense, if they finally cope with the battery issue. IMHO, after all the critics about the inherently unsafe and unreliable design of Boeing's lithium-ion battery, they rather change the direction and announce Plan B, the use of state of the art and safe Ni-Cd batteries. Or give a chance to the Tesla design. Better than having their heads buried deep in the sand and delivering Blowing Screamliners with batteries catching fire.</Msg><Username>divesius</Username><Timestamp>1359713726221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 05:15:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359714855218-4</Id><Topic><Title>6 year old girl expelled for bringing Toy Gun to school</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359690832845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 22:53:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thing she didn't bring a pair of semi auto scissors...... Why do you suppose Liberals are so afraid of toy guns?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1359714855218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 05:34:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359715990052-5</Id><Title>The 787 is a lost cause..... dazed and confused</Title><Msg>The engineers are lost. The problems is will NEVER be fixed.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359715990052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 05:53:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359716090019-6</Id><Topic><Title>6 year old girl expelled for bringing Toy Gun to school</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359690832845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 22:53:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>False message board. Please go and find the "Guns For Kids" discussion group".</Msg><Username>divesius</Username><Timestamp>1359716090019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 05:54:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359716388365-7</Id><Topic><Title>The 787 is a lost cause..... dazed and confused</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359715990052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 05:53:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They need a bold approach, one that makes clear: "We have solved the problem. Our new batteries are safe and reliable. They won't catch fire as the old ones did." Problem is, Boeing shows no sign of insight. Instead they have their heads burried deep in the sand. It is going to take some time to change their minds.</Msg><Username>divesius</Username><Timestamp>1359716388365</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 05:59:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359718073138-8</Id><Title>RIP Ed Koch</Title><Msg>He died this morning at the age of 88.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1359718073138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:27:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359718134970-9</Id><Topic><Title>The 787 is a lost cause..... dazed and confused</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359715990052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 05:53:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a retired electricial engineer and I can tell you if the masses of engineers have zero to show for two weeks or 5 years (depending on how long this has been an issue) things are real bad. THE ENGINEEERS HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IS GOING ON. THEY NEED TO RE-ENGINEER THE GENERATOR FROM SCRATCH. The box must be a cluster of issues.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359718134970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 06:28:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359720090547-10</Id><Title>US satellite lost in failed launch from Pacific</Title><Msg>The Boeing. Co-built spacecraft was launched Thursday from the Odyssey ocean platform. http://finance.yahoo.com/news/us-satellite-lost-failed-launch-094434221.html</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1359720090547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:01:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359720234970-11</Id><Topic><Title>The 787 is a lost cause..... dazed and confused</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359715990052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 05:53:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, do you recommend a Plan B? Ni-Cd batteries or the inherently safe approach of Tesla/SpaceX? Boeing still denies anything is wrong with their battery system although experts have warned them of using LI batteries with inherently unsafe cells too big to be safely controlled and contained in case of malfunction or thermal runaway. OK, that's one mistake. But Boeing uses these fire prone batteries even without a cooling system and with obviously inadequate balancing and monitoring. And that crippled piece of battery sits in some sort of a shoe box. Unbelievable!</Msg><Username>divesius</Username><Timestamp>1359720234970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:03:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359720379759-12</Id><Topic><Title>6 year old girl expelled for bringing Toy Gun to school</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359690832845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 22:53:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Active demonization of Guns. Guns represent Freedom and personal responsibility and Liberals hate freedom....The average Control Freak Authoritarian like Forbes or Coumo or Feinstein wants Humanity to be like the Eloi in HG Wells "Time Machine".....childlike and innocent and prayed upon by the Morloch.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359720379759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:06:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359720588722-13</Id><Title>Feinstein and Flunkies be exempt from Gun Control laws</Title><Msg>Not everyone will have to abide by Senator Dianne Feinstein’s gun control bill. If the proposed legislation becomes law, government officials and others will be exempt. “Mrs. Feinstein’s measure would exempt more than 2,200 types of hunting and sporting rifles; guns manually operated by bolt, pump, lever or slide action; and weapons used by government officials, law enforcement and retired law enforcement personnel,” the Washington Times reports.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359720588722</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:09:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359720700900-14</Id><Topic><Title>County Sheriffs ALL over America are saying NO to gun confiscation</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1359668128481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:35:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't Job lose everything but in the end...because Job trusted in the Lord ... and when all seemed blackest, Job did not abandon God and God retored Job to happiness.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359720700900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:11:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359721144997-15</Id><Title>I see the greedy union engineers are going to strike</Title><Msg>At a time when BA is struggling to find the problem with batteries, the engineers are going to strike. I hope they all choke on their steak tonight and some new ones get hired. There are lots of people in this country who need jobs, and I am sure those BA engineers make great salaries, and the union as true to its colors always wants to strike at a time when it will hurt the most. Well, I hope the #$%$ rot.</Msg><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721144997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:19:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359721476479-16</Id><Title>Did the engineers cause the problem so they could call a strike soon and be the ones to solve it</Title><Msg>and look like the great savior because they would get called back and find the problem. To strike when BA needs them is next to criminal. It is no wonder America is fed up with unions.</Msg><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721476479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:24:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359721546643-17</Id><Title>Wouldn't that be a heck of a note to see the engineers caused the problem so they could call a strike</Title><Msg>at a very appropriate time? Nothing is impossible with unions---NOTHING.</Msg><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721546643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:25:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359721558675-18</Id><Topic><Title>I see the greedy union engineers are going to strike</Title><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721144997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't understand your point. Great salaries for engineers? Do you confuse that with management's excessive payment, bonuses, luxury etc.?</Msg><Username>divesius</Username><Timestamp>1359721558675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:25:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359721598168-19</Id><Title>Obamacare to soon cost the average American family $20,000 a year, announces IRS</Title><Msg>TOLD YA SO Obamacare to soon cost the average American family $20,000 a year, announces IRS Mike Adams Natural News Feb 1, 2013 Under Obamacare, American families are forced to buy conventional health insurance that primarily benefits the pharmaceutical industry. By 2016 — just three years from now — the cheapest health insurance plan available will cost a typical American family $20,000 a year, the IRS has now announced. Here’s the news: The IRS just published descriptions of the financial penalties American taxpayers will pay if they fail to purchase the rip-off health insurance mandated under Obamacare. “The examples point to families of four and families of five, both of which the IRS expects in its assumptions to pay a minimum of $20,000 per year for a bronze plan,” reports CNS News. It goes on to report, “The IRS’s assumption that the cheapest plan for family will cost $20,000 per year is found in examples the IRS gives to help people understand how to calculate the penalty they will need to pay the government if they do not buy a mandated health plan.” We warned ya: Obamacare has always been a financial scam For the record, we here at Natural News repeatedly warned people about the Obamacare scam, describing how it was a forced taxpayer handout to Big Pharma and the dangerous sick-care industry which kills 783,000 Americans a year. Over the last few years, critics of my reporting on this subject insisted we were “conspiracy theorists” and that Obamacare would offer free health care to nearly everyone! Those who still had to buy health insurance would see rates go down, we were told by hypnotized, Kool-Aid-drinking Obama supporters. That’s why Obamacare is called the “Affordable Care Act,” after all. How could it be called the “Affordable Care Act” if it wasn’t going to be affordable, they insisted. So now the truth comes out. Obamacare is a total scam, a complete rip-off, a massive handout to Big Pharma and a disaster to the U.S. wage earner. Obamacare is going to bankrupt America. Every family, small business owner and corporations is going to be financially suffocated under this burden, to the point where tens of millions simply surrender to the system, get on welfare, and become lifelong Democrats voting for larger and larger handouts. I hate to say it, but once again I told ya so. Did you really think Obama was going to save money for the voters and make Big Pharma’s profits go down? Seriously? (Don’t be so gullible…) Obamacare was always designed, from the very start, to loot the American taxpayer and put government in a position of monopolistic power over your health care decisions. This is the move toward fascism that’s going to absolutely gut America and put millions of people on the street, homeless, jobless and diseased. Who can afford $20,000 a year in health insurance? Like everything else Obama has tried to shoved down America’s throat, the Affordable Care Act is an outright catastrophe. It funnels hundreds of billions of dollars into the coffers of health insurance companies, vaccine manufacturers and drug companies, but it does absolutely NOTHING to help the American people.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359721598168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:26:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359721699712-20</Id><Topic><Title>6 year old girl expelled for bringing Toy Gun to school</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359690832845</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 22:53:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So then, today's Liberals aren't really very liberal?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1359721699712</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:28:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359721764884-21</Id><Topic><Title>County Sheriffs ALL over America are saying NO to gun confiscation</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1359668128481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:35:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you approaching climax ?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359721764884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:29:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359722520117-22</Id><Title>Decorated Combat Veteran Arrested Charged With 5 Felonies For Possession of AR Magazines</Title><Msg>Decorated Combat Veteran Arrested In New York: Charged With 5 Felonies For Possession of AR Magazines Robert Richardson Off Grid Survival Feb 1, 2013 In the latest attack on the American people, a decorated War Hero has been arrested and charged with five counts of third degree criminal possession of a weapon, for having empty 30 round AR-15 Magazines in his vehicle. On Sunday January 6th Staff Sgt. Nathan Haddad, a decorated combat veteran, was driving through Jefferson County New York when he was randomly pulled over for a vehicle check. Haddad, who had five 30 round empty magazines in his possession, was arrested by the Jefferson County Sheriff’s Department and charged with five felony counts. According to Haddad’s brother, Michael Haddad, Nathan thought these magazines were legally made before the New York Assault Weapons Ban. When Nathan Haddad was arrested the new ban had not even been fully enacted yet. This is not a criminal, this is not some thug looking to hurt people; this is a decorated combat veteran who was recently honored by the Philadelphia chapter of Blue Star Mothers and the Union League’s Armed Services Council for helping disabled vets get back on their feet. What’s happening to Army veteran Nate Haddad is an absolute attack on liberty. Here we have a man who honorably served his country, who was trusted with weaponry that far exceeded anything he was carrying, that now finds himself facing the possibility of spending years in prison. Still think these gun control laws are meant to stop criminals?</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359722520117</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:42:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359722885092-23</Id><Title>BOEING ROCKET CRASHES INTO THE PACIFIC</Title><Msg>Must have been the batteries</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1359722885092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:48:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359723047259-24</Id><Title>Almost 8 o'clock and no pre-market trades yet...something is up...</Title><Msg>Or down !!!!!</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1359723047259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:50:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359723707366-25</Id><Title>Blast at US Embassy in Turkey Kills at Least One</Title><Msg>An explosion at a side entrance to the U.S. embassy in the Turkish capital Ankara killed at least one person and wounded several others on Friday and Turkish state media cited witnesses as saying was the attack was carried out by a suicide bomber http://www.cnbc.com/id/100426458</Msg><Username>low_mac</Username><Timestamp>1359723707366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:01:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359725197980-26</Id><Title>Japan sending Boeing 787 Dreamliner investigators to United States</Title><Msg>and next week Boeing calls in the Boy Scouts to help determine what is the cause of 787 battery problems, multiple fuel leak problems, electrical overload problems, cracked windshield problems, and plane durability problems. If the Japanese and the Boy Scouts can't figure out the problem our only hope in then the Girl Scouts.</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1359725197980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:26:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359725485690-27</Id><Topic><Title>Decorated Combat Veteran Arrested Charged With 5 Felonies For Possession of AR Magazines</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359722520117</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:42:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks .... we all have to hang together or hang seperatly. Ya know, ironicly there are Anti Americans like Piers Morgan that are swelling the ranks of Gun Owners of America and the NRA. After his supercilious comments with his British accent lecturing Americans on how we should fear guns have fed up Americans to the Gag point.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359725485690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:31:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359725494496-28</Id><Title>BA CEO - I have no problem with 5 Billion Dollar write off</Title><Msg>and BA says going forward its business as usual (HA). Wall Street analysts and others have floated many numbers, from an estimated $350 million in direct expenses to a possible $5 billion write-off as a result of the Dreamliner grounding. Boeing has declined to release any numbers of its own or comment on those being suggested, because it always prudent to stall, lie and cover things up when you have a major FAA investigation going on.</Msg><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1359725494496</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:31:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359725512174-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to soon cost the average American family $20,000 a year, announces IRS</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359721598168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:26:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!!!</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359725512174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:31:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359726386561-30</Id><Title>MIDDLE SCHOOL SHOOTING NO HELP TO DEMOCRATS</Title><Msg>here was a school shooting in Atlanta yesterday. Oh! You didn’t hear about it? Actually, that’s understandable. First, the young man who was shot was released last evening from the hospital. That’s good news. But there are other elements to this story that disqualified it for frenzied media coverage, especially by the elements of the media dedicated to supporting our skeet-shooting president’s attack on the Second Amendment. Let’s make a list. First – the shooter at the Price Middle School was apprehended by an armed school resource officer. Did you get that word “armed?” That’s right! There was an official in that school with a gun. That leaves you to wonder just who is making more sense here: Homeland Secretary Janet Napolitano and her promotion of scissors as a defense against workplace (and presumably school) shooters? Or NRA CEO Wayne LaPierre who has suggested armed law enforcement in our government schools? While we’re at it here … has anyone ever heard of a school or workplace shooting being stopped by someone with scissors? The Democrats antipathy toward guns and people being armed for self-defense is so intense that our esteemed Homeland Security Agency will not even acknowledge that firearms can be a useful tool for protecting yourself from an armed attacker. And while we’re on the subject … there have been at least three incidents where an armed civilian has stopped a school shooting. The Price Middle School shooting would have made it four, but we can’t count a school resource officer as a civilian. Background check? The shooter here underwent no background check. It would seem that he got that gun on the streets just as most gang-banging thugs do. Any new Democrat proposals for background checks would have had no affect on this incident. Large capacity magazine? Forget it. The gun used was a small caliber pistol without a large capacity magazine. Again, the new proposed laws would have made no difference. Assault weapon? I guess we’ll have to ask Senator Diane Feinstein here. She seems to be the official go-to Democrat in defining assault weapons. Somehow, though, I don’t think a small-caliber rather ordinary looking pistol would qualify. I’m certain that as soon as the news broke yesterday that there had been a school shooting in Atlanta the left went into overdrive preparing to exploit the situation for their own anti-Second Amendment goals. Imagine the disappointment when they learned that an adult with a gun in that school might – there’s no certainty – but might have saved some lives. Know this though … the left is waiting anxiously for the next multiple shooting, While they wait there will be innumerable episodes where armed private citizens protect themselves and others from predators. Those stories hurt the liberal agenda, so they will be largely ignored. Nuze</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359726386561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:46:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359726579958-31</Id><Title>Forward: Unemployment Jumps Up to 7.9 Percent</Title><Msg>The Bureau of Labor Statistics has released the latest unemployment numbers for January. The unemployment rate has jumped back up to 7.9 percent with just 157,000 jobs being added to the economy. The number of unemployed and under-employed persons still sits at an alarming number. The number of unemployed persons, at 12.3 million, was little changed in January. The unemployment rate was 7.9 percent and has been at or near that level since September 2012. In January, the number of long-term unemployed (those jobless for 27 weeks or more) was about unchanged at 4.7 million and accounted for 38.1 percent of the unemployed. These numbers are hardly enough to keep up with population growth.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359726579958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:49:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359727243636-32</Id><Title>Schumer: We Won't Let Border Security Block the Path to Citizenship</Title><Msg>Schumer is a total typical Democrat dimwit. We already have a path to citizenship and have had one for decades. We don't have border security and we don't have a president who will enforce the laws we already have.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359727243636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:00:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359727251130-33</Id><Topic><Title>MIDDLE SCHOOL SHOOTING NO HELP TO DEMOCRATS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359726386561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:46:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason US schools don't have on site armed police protection is because Republicans wont allow raising taxes for schools to be able to afford this kind of security</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359727251130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:00:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359727497679-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare to soon cost the average American family $20,000 a year, announces IRS</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359721598168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:26:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason for the high cost is because ignorant redneck state legislatures and governors wont set up their own states insurance exchange to assist in acquiring insurance. The federal government will have to set up individual exchanges for virtually all the red states which will presumably drive the price up to 20,000$ for a family of 5</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359727497679</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:04:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359727670153-35</Id><Topic><Title>MIDDLE SCHOOL SHOOTING NO HELP TO DEMOCRATS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359726386561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:46:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father_zosima you're obviously brainless imbecile. Look at all the spending on worthless school programs and tell us they're a higher priority than the safety and security of our children. Dimocrats first solutions to any problem is raise taxes, spend more, write more rules and regulations.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359727670153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:07:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359727917815-36</Id><Title>I watched the CNBC 2011 Dreamliner special last night</Title><Msg>Scared the heck out of me. When test proved that plastic wings began separating when bent, they applied a bandaid fix by reinforcing them with titanium rods. However, common sense now tells you that they won't bend! Wings are designed to bend so they wont snap off the fuselage. Well, now they just might!</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1359727917815</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:11:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359727921227-37</Id><Title>8,500,000 Americans Left Labor Force In Obama's First Term...</Title><Msg>The Bureau of Labor Statistics released jobs numbers for January Friday showing that nonfarm payroll employment increased by 157,000 and the unemployment rate rose to 7.9 percent. Lost in these headline numbers was another rise in the number of people not in the labor force. This number now stands at a staggering 89 million, up from 80.5 million when President Obama took office. This means that there are currently 8.5 million more Americans not in the labor force than just four years ago. Forget all the other numbers. This continued explosion of people not in the labor force should be tremendously concerning as it represents an obstacle for the government to ever balance the budget without drastically raising taxes on those still working. Noel</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359727921227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:12:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359728070110-38</Id><Title>Existing 787 Dreamliners will be turned into attack drones</Title><Msg>Boing is going to wire off the entire Dreamliner program as nobbody will ever fly one. Boeing will sell the 70 manufacured already to the Air Force to be converted to unnanned drones. If they crash it will be over the enemy and will be bured to nothing so non of the plane can be salvaged.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359728070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:14:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728088238-39</Id><Topic><Title>BA CEO - I have no problem with 5 Billion Dollar write off</Title><Username>wise4us</Username><Timestamp>1359725494496</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:31:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the probes were simple then they would of been corrected weeks ago. BA is hiding the real truth that that truth is the the 787 was rushed to completion without proper testing. Now the FAA and BA have a serious problem that they can no long hide. A defective airplane that will be grounded for months, if not longer.</Msg><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1359728088238</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:14:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728216644-40</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Reinitiated It's Stock Buy Back in 2013 After 3 Year Lapse</Title><Username>instantkarma22</Username><Timestamp>1359669102955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:51:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thtas right</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359728216644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:16:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728366711-41</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA to ratify the strike over pensions and a comparison with Boeing Executive pension costs</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359687964804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 22:06:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so far Boeing has only said they are looking to solve and fix the exsisting battery and the operating system, not change to another tyle of batter,, remember that would increase the weight by .000000001%</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359728366711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:19:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728390776-42</Id><Topic><Title>I watched the CNBC 2011 Dreamliner special last night</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1359727917815</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:11:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This plane has too many issues to count of track. The plane will be scrapped.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359728390776</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:19:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359728424826-43</Id><Title>Koch dead at 88...</Title><Msg>Was one of the last few Democrats that are REAL AMERICANS.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359728424826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:20:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359728511861-44</Id><Title>Engineers have gone from scatching their heads to their balls.</Title><Msg>I guess they all smoke weed now that it is legal.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359728511861</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:21:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728552778-45</Id><Topic><Title>Legalize Any Type of Fire Arm</Title><Username>paul_revere_patriotsssssssss</Username><Timestamp>1359688865959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 22:21:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about we take a major U.S. city and make all firearms illegal.. I'll bet that city would be a shining example to the gun grabbers, a true beacon of peace. Oh wait, Chicago already did that.. How's that working out ???!!! Chicago beginning to look like a penitentiary without walls !!!! My home town...</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1359728552778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:22:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359728578673-46</Id><Topic><Title>I watched the CNBC 2011 Dreamliner special last night</Title><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1359727917815</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:11:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, they said that they had to get the blessing form ANA (All Nippon Air) because they were they most thorough of all global companies. Well they did and made their first major sale to them. However, CNBC said that it was at a MAJOR discount (read bribe of sorts). Possibly at 50% disocunt !!!!</Msg><Username>foxgang7878</Username><Timestamp>1359728578673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:22:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359728766374-47</Id><Title>POOF: Another 170,000 disappeared in January...</Title><Msg>(CNSNews) - The number of Americans not in the labor force grew by 169,000 in January, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics’ latest jobs report. BLS labels people who are unemployed and no longer looking for work as “not in the labor force,” including people who have retired on schedule, taken early retirement, or simply given up looking for work. There were 89 million of them last month.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359728766374</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:26:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359729418502-48</Id><Title>IRS: Cheapest Obamacare Plan Will Be $20,000 Per Family...</Title><Msg>(CNSNews) – In a final regulation issued Wednesday, the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) assumed that under Obamacare the cheapest health insurance plan available in 2016 for a family will cost $20,000 for the year. Under Obamacare, Americans will be required to buy health insurance or pay a penalty to the IRS. The IRS's assumption that the cheapest plan for a family will cost $20,000 per year is found in examples the IRS gives to help people understand how to calculate the penalty they will need to pay the government if they do not buy a mandated health plan. The examples point to families of four and families of five, both of which the IRS expects in its assumptions to pay a minimum of $20,000 per year for a bronze plan. “The annual national average bronze plan premium for a family of 5 (2 adults, 3 children) is $20,000,” the regulation says. Bronze will be the lowest tier health-insurance plan available under Obamacare--after Silver, Gold, and Platinum. Under the law, the penalty for not buying health insurance is supposed to be capped at either the annual average Bronze premium, 2.5 percent of taxable income, or $2,085.00 per family in 2016.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359729418502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:36:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359729770638-49</Id><Topic><Title>Did the engineers cause the problem so they could call a strike soon and be the ones to solve it</Title><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721476479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:24:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get real you #$%$". Engineers don't think that way. The fact that you do however says a lot about you ... and it isn't good.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1359729770638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:42:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359729935637-50</Id><Title>FOUR DOMINICAN #$%$ Confirm They Attended Sex Parties With Sen. Bob Menendez</Title><Msg>The main source in the Bob Menendez underage #$%$ scandal sent the FBI the names of four #$%$ who confirmed they had attended sex parties with Salmon Melgen and Sen. Bob Menendez (D-NJ) in the Dominican Republic. On Tuesday, FBI agents raided the West Palm Beach business of Dr. Melgen who is suspected of providing free trips and even underage Dominican Republic prostitutes to U.S. Sen. Bob Menendez, D-N.J.</Msg><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359729935637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:45:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359730204697-51</Id><Topic><Title>FOUR DOMINICAN #$%$ Confirm They Attended Sex Parties With Sen. Bob Menendez</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359729935637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:45:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why didn't I get the memo? Off to sex parties beats a bunch of socialist democraps sitting around spending tax payer money buying votes.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359730204697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:50:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359730394366-52</Id><Topic><Title>Did the engineers cause the problem so they could call a strike soon and be the ones to solve it</Title><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721476479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:24:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO, absolutely not! The engineers aren't smart enough to think of that. Maybe one of those cigar smoking union heads could have put them up to it, but the thought would have never occurred at the ground level.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359730394366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:53:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359730461620-53</Id><Topic><Title>Koch dead at 88...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359728424826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:20:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Koch BROS???</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359730461620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:54:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359730583836-54</Id><Topic><Title>On the Negotiation front re SPEEA</Title><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1357869000025</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 20:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats right</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359730583836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:56:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359730611381-55</Id><Topic><Title>8,500,000 Americans Left Labor Force In Obama's First Term...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359727921227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:12:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That never gets reported by the leftist media...and a positive indication that the economy is shrinking and why we are deep in debt. Many of those jobs were replaced by Obama via govt bureacracy, and many more govt workers tax payers can't pay for....even when taxes are raised much higher.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359730611381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:56:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359731460092-56</Id><Topic><Title>TOTAL BLACNESS is ENGULFING USA.</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1359730369044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:52:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Co-Intelpro alert....CHAOS AGENT trying to stir up racial hatred in lame attempt to get us fighting with each other...while Offshore bankers...the real enemy of America laugh and rip off your retirement and life savings at Historic levels.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1359731460092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:11:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359731564958-57</Id><Topic><Title>TOTAL BLACNESS is ENGULFING USA.</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1359730369044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:52:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is not hope. Threre is no place on the panet that is all black that is not 3rd world. Black people do not want to be educated. They just want food stamps and seex.</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359731564958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:12:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359731706493-58</Id><Title>McNerney Still Makin' $30,000 a Day, 7 Days a Week... What a Pig</Title><Msg>If this 787 fiasco goes on for 6 months and at the end they discover incompetent management and then fire McNinny, he will earn another $5.4 million.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1359731706493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:15:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359731715284-59</Id><Topic><Title>I see the greedy union engineers are going to strike</Title><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721144997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really are a clueless dolt. If you're looking for greed, you're looking in the wrong place. You might want to take a look at Boeing Corporate in Chicago, specifically at its executives with their bloated compensation packages. THAT'S where the greed's at. It certainly isn't with Boeing's engineers or techs. About us going on strike ... And you've reached that conclusion how? Ballots haven't even been mailed yet. Good one there professor. "I hope ... some new ones get hired. There are lots of people in this country who need jobs ..." And how many of those people are degreed engineers? Answer: Not many Engineering is a very academically demanding field of study and the washout rate is typically in the 75% to 80% range. There aren't nearly enough engineers in the world presently available to replace us (you're going to need about 15,500) and many of those who are available don't have the necessary experience or expertise. Also, if SPEEA strikes it'll be a federally protected strike which means that we can't be permanently replaced.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1359731715284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:15:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359731762912-60</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever notice how they never refer to those dead white men who died freeing slaves from Democrat run states as heroes . . Ever notice how they never refer to those dead white men who died freeing slaves from Democrat (who all became republicans to benefit from Nixons Southern strategy) run states as heroes? The stench of the proslavery hope4whitepeople is overpowering this morning- also he is an unmitigated liar or stooopid beyond belief trying to blame Democrats for something that republicans do.</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359731762912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:16:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359731885929-61</Id><Title>The Dreamliner is "all jacked up" and nobody can fix it.</Title><Msg>I am lauging at all the engineers on this program. This bird is a turd and will not fly. Dreamliner = pinto = vega = yuo = poop Got it !</Msg><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359731885929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:18:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359731995476-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of the reasons are rather depressing. One is they feel "holyer than thou" by appearing to be for minority interests, and compassionate individuals. It's a phony fascade because when it counts, they wouldn't pay for it, and would let minorites die rather than save them. Example. The Blacks they let drown waiting in their slum apts. in N. O. waiting for liberals to show up with the buses to take them out of harms way. They cared not that Saddam was slaughtering thousands upon thousands of his people. Even Sandy victims that are now facing extreme cold weather still living in tents, and homes without electricity or heat. They bought into Obama's photo op after the storm hit, and now "see ya, glad I don't have to be ya."</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359731995476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:19:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359732096487-63</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you got it upside down there ignorant redneck- True history is taught by liberals but is rewritten by you anti intellectual yahooos and luddites who live in the 16th century</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359732096487</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:21:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359732243310-64</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>public school bashing is the product of anti intellectual ignorant racist rednecks who want to rewrite history to suit their agenda- private schools will allow them to defacto resegregate schools since they are unaffordable by most of the poor and minoritys</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359732243310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:24:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359732350325-65</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner is "all jacked up" and nobody can fix it.</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359731885929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:18:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dreamliner will be back in the air soon.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1359732350325</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:25:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359732411511-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hawfaeces as the boards pre-eminent ignorant anti intellectual racist redneck I wouldn't have expected less from you</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359732411511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:26:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359732419289-67</Id><Title>Why engineers have come up with zero problems with the 787 !</Title><Msg>There is nothing wrong with it. Lets go flying !</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1359732419289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:26:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359732525348-68</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner is "all jacked up" and nobody can fix it.</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359731885929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:18:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, I'd rather put it that way: outsourcing of critical components and systems did not help in reducing the complexity of a very ambitious project. But that's not the fault of Boeing's engineers, it's the sad result of management failure.</Msg><Username>divesius</Username><Timestamp>1359732525348</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:28:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359732679384-69</Id><Topic><Title>Why engineers have come up with zero problems with the 787 !</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1359732419289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:26:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. Btw let's rename your fireworks bird to Blowing Screamliner.</Msg><Username>divesius</Username><Timestamp>1359732679384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:31:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359733487026-70</Id><Topic><Title>Why engineers have come up with zero problems with the 787 !</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1359732419289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:26:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats what I said when Only Japan had problems!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1359733487026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:44:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359733776476-71</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner is "all jacked up" and nobody can fix it.</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359731885929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:18:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your right</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359733776476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:49:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359733874609-72</Id><Topic><Title>McNerney Still Makin' $30,000 a Day, 7 Days a Week... What a Pig</Title><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1359731706493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:15:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he got a bonus f the 787( flying), hows that bonus looking now to the shreholders</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359733874609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:51:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359733968451-73</Id><Topic><Title>Japan sending Boeing 787 Dreamliner investigators to United States</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1359725197980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:26:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are they in a union ?</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359733968451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:52:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359734223497-74</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats Really Believe in Racial Equality?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359733844493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:50:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not by their record they do not. My old fishin buddy use to say, "Talks cheap, whiskey costs money."</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359734223497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:57:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359735018981-75</Id><Topic><Title>MIDDLE SCHOOL SHOOTING NO HELP TO DEMOCRATS</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359726386561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:46:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's give some credit where it's due; lots of bad situations, many involving guns, are diffused by mediators and negotiators without the use of guns. Certainly, many of the negotiators are if possible, backed by people with guns. But more guns and more people bearing arms is not always the answer, as Chicago will attest.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1359735018981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:10:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359735391291-76</Id><Topic><Title>Decorated Combat Veteran Arrested Charged With 5 Felonies For Possession of AR Magazines</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359722520117</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:42:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He won't be doing that again too soon, eh? ;))</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1359735391291</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:16:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359735490103-77</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359733352549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:42:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent post my man! Democrats have never lost their love er lust for slavery. They're all for forcing people to do what they aren't willing to do themselves. Just beware the more you point it out the angrier they become. Notice how they resort to name calling because they can't stand the light of truth.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359735490103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:18:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359735548834-78</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Common myths about school vouchers. Myths and facts include: (1) African Americans support private school vouchers (in actuality, most opt for smaller classes and other commonsense reforms, but not vouchers); (2) students who participate in voucher programs do better than public school students (in actuality, more than a decade after the first publicly funded voucher program began, there is no good evidence that vouchers do a better job of educating students than public schools); (3) without vouchers public schools would lack incentives to adopt reforms and improve performance (in reality, many public schools are improving, and voucher programs undercut this improvement); (4) voucher plans for urban school systems were adopted only after all other approaches failed to improve public school quality (in the three states with publicly funded voucher programs, state officials embraced vouchers long before they pursued other approaches); (5) vouchers are needed in Cleveland because the city's public schools are hopeless (while Cleveland's schools are not optimal, positive changes are occurring); and (6) Cleveland vouchers are a bargain for taxpayers since they cost less per student than traditional per-pupil expenditures (the truth is, voucher programs drain critical funds from public schools, and the Cleveland program is far more costly that it appears). (Contains 40 endnotes.) (SM)</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359735548834</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:19:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359735699016-79</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359733352549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:42:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey yeah!!! hope4 is the same ignorant anti intellectual redneck racist as pay4 and he has to answer himself to get anybody to agree with himself HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HARH AR HAR HAR HARH AR AR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359735699016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:21:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736061598-80</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359733352549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:42:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not hope4whitepeople but father_zosima is chris_genna AKA the Kent Raven. It would be hard to believe there are two people on the planet that ignorant.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359736061598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:27:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736081709-81</Id><Topic><Title>County Sheriffs ALL over America are saying NO to gun confiscation</Title><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1359668128481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:35:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah. God allowed Job to forget all about his dead wife and dead kids and find happiness with another set. The were on sale that week at Wal-Mart</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1359736081709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:28:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736412813-82</Id><Topic><Title>OXF - Ready to Rally 100%</Title><Username>davidgoldberg652</Username><Timestamp>1359702401871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 02:06:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts are only nervous at 7%, they will start covering at 20%!</Msg><Username>davidgoldberg652</Username><Timestamp>1359736412813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:33:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736668361-83</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They cared not that Saddam was slaughtering thousands upon thousands of his people" yet most Republicans will say "NUKE THE PLACE AND KILL all the mu slims!!!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359736668361</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:37:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736676229-84</Id><Topic><Title>Did the engineers cause the problem so they could call a strike soon and be the ones to solve it</Title><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721476479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:24:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would they think about striking at a time when BA needs them most? Explain that one smart one. I just know how unions think.</Msg><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359736676229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:37:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359736720805-85</Id><Topic><Title>Did the engineers cause the problem so they could call a strike soon and be the ones to solve it</Title><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721476479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:24:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goforth does not smoke cigars- and is NOT a union head- just an overpaid Office manager President Mccarty gtries to play the mandolin, used to smoke cigarettes Not only he or any other engineer- tech would think of such a thing- neither one is capable - and if either one suggested such a thing, they would land in club fed within a few hours if not sooner. I suggest the rest of the few sane posters put you on ignore you stupid SOB !!!</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1359736720805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:38:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359736861381-86</Id><Title>From each accroding to his ability to each according to his needs.</Title><Msg>Isn't that the philosophical underlying foundation of the Democrat Party? For you victims of socialized government education, Karl Marx also justified communism as the "struggle of the classes." You know.....we must punish the upper class with higher taxes in order to protect the mediocre class. But there's no relation between the Democrat's philosophy and that of Karl Marx is there?..........naaw couldn't be.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359736861381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:41:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359737330308-87</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those are all the same argument the Soviet Politburo used to justify only State run grocery stores.....how'd that work out. Eve socialized countries in Europe are using school vouchers .....probably why the U.S. students rank much lower in science and math than most in 3rd world countries.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359737330308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359737398837-88</Id><Title>Biden Flip Flops On Gun Control</Title><Msg>It looks like Joe has partially accepted the truth about gun control. This from AP/Huffington Post today. ________________________________________________ 'Joe Biden: Gun Laws Won't 'Guarantee' End To Mass Shootings' WASHINGTON — Curbing guns can't ensure an end to mass slayings like December's killings of 20 first-graders in Newtown, Conn., but it will reduce firearm deaths, Vice President Joe Biden said Thursday. "Nothing we're going to do is going to fundamentally alter or eliminate the possibility of another mass shooting or guarantee that we will bring gun deaths down to 1,000 a year from what it is now," Biden told reporters. _______________________________________________________ I'm sure why he thinks that curbing guns to those that follow the law will reduce firearm deaths (notice Joe didn't say murder). Is he including suicides and accidental gun deaths in that view? It won't do anything to curb criminal and gang related murder. Chicago's January 2013 murders by gun body count was 42 on pace for another 500+ year. Tough gun laws have done nothing to curb murders. Mayor "Dead Fish" is so upset that he mobilizing 200 of Chicago's finest desk jockey/pencil pusher cops to go back on the street. Since guns are already banned in Chicago that's all they can do.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359737398837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:49:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359738134224-89</Id><Topic><Title>SOLUTION TO BOEING BATTERY PROBLEM</Title><Username>oneinrev333</Username><Timestamp>1359738044052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:00:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Explain!</Msg><Username>ewblanchard</Username><Timestamp>1359738134224</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:02:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359738306950-90</Id><Topic><Title>Koch dead at 88...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359728424826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:20:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, former mayor of NYC. ED KOCH</Msg><Username>ewblanchard</Username><Timestamp>1359738306950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:05:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359738528839-91</Id><Title>Worst Socialist President Ever</Title><Msg>Obama is the worst Socialist President: 1. Public sector jobs down 600,000 since inauguration. 2. Private sector jobs up 1.6 million since inauguration. Up 6.1 M since bottom. 3. Dow up 75% since inauguration. I may have to re-consult my "Sheriff Joe Arpaio's Answers for Everything in Creation Handbook" again.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1359738528839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:08:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359738611002-92</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats Really Believe in Racial Equality?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359733844493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:50:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because the old white guys that do the admitting would favor white people regardless of the scores.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359738611002</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:10:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359739626734-93</Id><Topic><Title>BA may well prove to be the ticker to look at this week.</Title><Username>ericmccain68</Username><Timestamp>1359726203635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looking good</Msg><Username>bergersid682</Username><Timestamp>1359739626734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:27:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359740271437-94</Id><Topic><Title>Japan sending Boeing 787 Dreamliner investigators to United States</Title><Username>truthbtoldhonest</Username><Timestamp>1359725197980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:26:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They need to get some engineers from China. Two weeks and zero to show.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1359740271437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:37:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359740594340-95</Id><Topic><Title>Decorated Combat Veteran Arrested Charged With 5 Felonies For Possession of AR Magazines</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359722520117</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:42:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being a decorated war hero has nothing to do with it. The only question is, was having the magazines in his possession legal or ilegal. Don't flower up your answer with "honorably sered his country", "attack oon liberty" or other BS. That has nothing to do with the question.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1359740594340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:43:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359740790114-96</Id><Topic><Title>Why engineers have come up with zero problems with the 787 !</Title><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1359732419289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:26:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100 to 150 batteries replaced, I doubt they were all Japan airline planes.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1359740790114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:46:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359741283857-97</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats Really Believe in Racial Equality?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359733844493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:50:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Because the old white guys that do the admitting would favor white people regardless of the scores." Thank rocks4brains for proving you're a liberal bigot. Of course people should be admitted on their merits and not skin color. But the Democrats want affirmative action to make sure that doesn't happen.</Msg><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359741283857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:54:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359741453215-98</Id><Topic><Title>From each accroding to his ability to each according to his needs.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359736861381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:41:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bingo!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1359741453215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:57:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359741654989-99</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats Really Believe in Racial Equality?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359733844493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:50:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welcome to the 21st century!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359741654989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:00:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359741963022-100</Id><Topic><Title>From each accroding to his ability to each according to his needs.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359736861381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:41:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have we always been communist or only recently?</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1359741963022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:06:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742104616-101</Id><Topic><Title>6 months to recertify Dreamliner</Title><Username>lah2day</Username><Timestamp>1359649772432</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 11:29:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fairly obvious that you're right, but most people are in denial for some reason. They just want 14000 at any cost. LOL</Msg><Username>one_smooth_stone</Username><Timestamp>1359742104616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:08:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742145749-102</Id><Topic><Title>Decorated Combat Veteran Arrested Charged With 5 Felonies For Possession of AR Magazines</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359722520117</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:42:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hear hear! Sparty only cares about decorated vets if they agree with him or if their case can be made to suit his political agenda.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1359742145749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:09:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742267191-103</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Flip Flops On Gun Control</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359737398837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:49:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe is a smart guy. No one has been saying gun laws would "eliminate" gun deaths. All anyone has said is that such laws will make them a little less common. You go Joe!!!!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1359742267191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:11:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742294044-104</Id><Topic><Title>From each accroding to his ability to each according to his needs.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359736861381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:41:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Have we always been communist or only recently?" Legalized Thieves is synonymous for Democrats. Yes, Democrats have always stood for legalized thievery.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1359742294044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:11:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742334098-105</Id><Topic><Title>BA may well prove to be the ticker to look at this week.</Title><Username>ericmccain68</Username><Timestamp>1359726203635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>listen to the masters</Msg><Username>henrydonald303</Username><Timestamp>1359742334098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:12:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742535595-106</Id><Topic><Title>Decorated Combat Veteran Arrested Charged With 5 Felonies For Possession of AR Magazines</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359722520117</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:42:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He should of known what the law was if he was breaking a law which is sounds like he did than he will have to do the time , don`t do the crime if you can`t do the time . I could care less of his military background most people using that as some excuse for somebody's innocent have never served a day in the military. and when its convenient for you you would just pee on a veteran if he has a different opinion than you, you folks do it everyday!</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359742535595</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:15:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359742998084-107</Id><Topic><Title>Do Democrats Really Believe in Racial Equality?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359733844493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:50:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like I said you you fail to comprehend with your closed mind the scores would not matter when all the people doing the admitting are white 99.9 % of the time they would toss the scores out and admit the white guy even if the black guy scored better . You should be happy it`s less people your taxes have to support on welfare and food stamps! right? but I doubt it would matter your stuck on constant whine mode so not much would change just he subject.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359742998084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:23:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359743031992-108</Id><Topic><Title>Why Are White Liberals Such Bigots?</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359731183099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:06:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably guilt for wanting to keep blacks on the government dependency plantation instead of treating them as equals.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1359743031992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:23:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359743127561-109</Id><Topic><Title>From each accroding to his ability to each according to his needs.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359736861381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:41:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans do just as much legalized thievery they just point fingers and whine better</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359743127561</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359743428284-110</Id><Topic><Title>BA may well prove to be the ticker to look at this week.</Title><Username>ericmccain68</Username><Timestamp>1359726203635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>listen to people who got it right befote</Msg><Username>thomasmilton84</Username><Timestamp>1359743428284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:30:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359743718383-111</Id><Title>Why Not have a Law that automatically repeals Laws Passed based on Lies.</Title><Msg>For example when they pass a law like Obamacare based on lies that it would lower healthcare costs and then we find out the truth that it increases the cost of healthcare is should automatically be repealed. Bad laws never seem to get repealed.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1359743718383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:35:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744010092-112</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner is "all jacked up" and nobody can fix it.</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359731885929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:18:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the A 350</Msg><Username>jackrip_eu</Username><Timestamp>1359744010092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:40:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744135270-113</Id><Topic><Title>Why Not have a Law that automatically repeals Laws Passed based on Lies.</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1359743718383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:35:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While your at it lets make a law to not get involved in wars half a world away based on lies. with the money saved health care would not even be an issue.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359744135270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:42:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744306535-114</Id><Topic><Title>The entire middle east is about to UNRAVEL and COLLAPSE</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1359743764156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:36:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good !</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1359744306535</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:45:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744351448-115</Id><Topic><Title>BA may well prove to be the ticker to look at this week.</Title><Username>ericmccain68</Username><Timestamp>1359726203635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 08:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checking it out right now.</Msg><Username>robertclay116</Username><Timestamp>1359744351448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:45:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744389682-116</Id><Topic><Title>Why Not have a Law that automatically repeals Laws Passed based on Lies.</Title><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1359743718383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:35:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After a conservative SCOTUS upheld it as constitutional, what's the point?</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1359744389682</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:46:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359744605945-117</Id><Title>Thanks, Mr. Obama!</Title><Msg>The DOW hit 14,000 today, the first time in 5 yrs!</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1359744605945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:50:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744609255-118</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congressional Black Caucus Praises Communist Cuban Dictator a group of Congress critters to go to Cuba and come out with praises for Fidel Castro. Don’t get me wrong. I know they love the guy. But rarely do they so blatantly display it: “The fifty-year embargo just hasn’t worked,” CBC Chairwoman Barbara Lee (D-Ca.) told reporters this evening at a Capitol press conference after returning from a congressional delegation visit to Cuba. “The bottom line is that we believe its time to open dialogue with Cuba.” Lee and others heaped praise on Castro, calling him warm and receptive during their discussion. But the lawmakers disputed Castro’s later statement that members of the congressional delegation said American society is still racist. “It was quite a moment to behold,” Lee said, recalling her moments with Castro. “It was almost like listening to an old friend,” said Rep. Bobby Rush (D-Il.), adding that he found Castro’s home to be modest and Castro’s wife to be particularly hospitable. “In my household I told Castro he is known as the ultimate survivor,” Rush said." Unreal. For those who don’t know, Fidel Castro is a brutal communist dictator. He’s not a rockstar or a righteous dude. He’s a killer. Here’s a little bit of Cuban history under Castro: "Castro tried to get Nikita Khrushchev to nuke several southern cities in the US in the early 1960′s, including New Orleans and probably Baton Rouge. He incarcerates more people as a percentage of population than Hitler or Stalin did. He murdered 17,000 Cubans and (several dozen U.S. citizens) with firing squads and dumped their bullet-riddled bodies in mass graves. He has impoverished and brutalized Cuba to the point where 20 percent of its population risked their lives to flee. And prior to his glorious reign, Cuba took in more immigrants per capita than any country in the Western Hemisphere . More Americans lived in Cuba than Cubans in the U.S. , and Cuba even had to turn away European immigrants. Castro sent his agents to torture to death American POWs in North Vietnam ‘s Cu Loc POW camp outside Hanoi in 1967." And since this was the Congressional Black caucus that is praising Castro, let’s have a look at the racism issue as it relates to the communist paradise: According to anthropologists dispatched by the European Union, racism is systemic and institutional.[2] Blacks are systematically excluded from positions that tourism related jobs, where they could earn tips in hard currencies.[2] According to the EU study, blacks are relegated to poor housing, complained of the longest waits for healthcare, were excluded from managerial positions, received the lowest remittances from relatives abroad, and were five times more likely to be imprisoned.”[2] Enrique Patterson describes race as “social bomb” and says that “If the Cuban government were to permit black Cubans to organize and raise their problems before [authorities] . . . totalitarianism would fall”.[5] Esteban Morales Domínguez, a professor in the University of Havana, says that “The absence of the debate on the racial problem already threatens . . . the revolution’s social project”.[5] Carlos Moore, who has authored extensive on the issue, says that “There is an unstated threat, blacks in Cuba know that whenever you raise race in Cuba, you go to jail. Therefore the struggle in Cuba is different. There cannot be a civil rights movement. You will have instantly 10,000 black people dead”.[5] He says that a new generation of black Cubans are looking at politics in another way.[5] Barack Obama’s victory has raised disturbing questions about the institutional racism in Cuba.[2] The Economist noted “The danger starts with his example: after all, a young, black, progressive politician has no chance of reaching the highest office in Cuba, although a majority of the island’s people are black.”[6] Jorge Luis García Pérez, who was imprisoned and tortured for 17 years, states “The authorities in my country have never tolerated that a black person oppose the regime. During the trial, the color of my skin aggravated the situation. Later when I was mistreated in prison by guards, they always referred to me as being black”.[7] These free, liberal African Americans are praising a man who also presided over the rounding up of homosexuals into concentration camps. Not my characterization, but the New York Times’s: In Cuba, thousands of homosexuals were sent to concentration camps in the late 1960′s, together with others deemed deviant by the Castro regime. Echoing the slogan on the gates of Auschwitz, the camps were emblazoned with the words “Work will make you men.” Though the camps were shut after a few years, the subsequent purges of homosexuals from the ruling Communist Party were condemned by intellectuals like Jean-Paul Sartre and Susan Sontag. In 1980, when angry mobs at officially organized rallies denounced gay men and women as #$%$,” many homosexuals were among the 125,000 Cubans who fled in the Mariel boatlift. Cuba is the only country in the world to have quarantined homosexuals and others who test positive for H.I.V., the virus that causes AIDS. It is impossible for me to see these Congressmen and women who praise Castro as anything other than morons. These are the same people who vilified Bush for waterboarding, but they praise Castro. Behold the modern Democrat.</Msg><Username>rover472u</Username><Timestamp>1359744609255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:50:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744667892-119</Id><Topic><Title>TOTAL BLACNESS is ENGULFING USA.</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1359730369044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:52:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your son has just fallen in love with a black woman.......don't worry your grandchildren will still be beautiful and love you despite your bigotry</Msg><Username>docfunknstein</Username><Timestamp>1359744667892</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:51:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744690026-120</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it's because for reasons like the 75% appreciation in the DOW under President Obama.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1359744690026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:51:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359744734486-121</Id><Topic><Title>TOTAL BLACNESS is ENGULFING USA.</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1359730369044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:52:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He shoots... he scores!</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1359744734486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:52:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359745551921-122</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Flip Flops On Gun Control</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359737398837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:49:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many gun deaths are by the police ? I have proposed ammo for the police handguns that makes a hammer wound but that maintains trajectory. And I have a design and patent claim. Of course a hammer wound could break a collar bone or break a rib. If the ammo makers are not interested in making ammo like this, then anyone else could. Boeing could do it.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1359745551921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:05:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359745862963-123</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner is "all jacked up" and nobody can fix it.</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359731885929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:18:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dreamliner? Sorry, wrong name! It's officially renamed to Screamliner, Burning Screamliner to be correct.</Msg><Username>divesius</Username><Timestamp>1359745862963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:11:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359746238248-124</Id><Topic><Title>The Dreamliner is "all jacked up" and nobody can fix it.</Title><Username>snaps4u2</Username><Timestamp>1359731885929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 10:18:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am now starting to think the engineers know plane is a lost cause so they are just buying time. I bet pressure will get them to start smoking crack if not already.</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1359746238248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:17:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359746800750-125</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>welfare, food stamps , heating and cooling, obmama phones, WIC, free heath care da ?</Msg><Username>art.constantine</Username><Timestamp>1359746800750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:26:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359747229940-126</Id><Topic><Title>Americans to Washington: Don’t tread on me</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359746787556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If its not the government you fear it`s people with dark skin if not them it`s the freaking Irish whats next martians? B holes from Uranus ? these same words have been repeated for hundreds of years and nothing changes the clowns just keep exiting out of the VW in Circus ring 2</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359747229940</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:33:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359747916279-127</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because democrats can't run on policies like those that produce over 14% unemployemnt in the black community so they wage campaigns based on race baiting and lies</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1359747916279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:45:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359748150962-128</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks, Mr. Obama!</Title><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1359744605945</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:50:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hip hip !</Msg><Username>stick.man007</Username><Timestamp>1359748150962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:49:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359748825395-129</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Flip Flops On Gun Control</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359737398837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:49:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A round that makes a "hammer wound". Just what you want when the bad guy has a 30 round clip of jacketed hollow points . You break his collar bone and he blows your head clean off your liberal body. Are you that Kimmel comedian guy doing a prank ???</Msg><Username>president_peace_prize</Username><Timestamp>1359748825395</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359749252659-130</Id><Topic><Title>Americans to Washington: Don’t tread on me</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359746787556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh please mr. white hopedopy , Racist are real good at pointing fingers and accusing somebody else of doing what they are the best at doing BEING A PIG RACIST like you. you don`t fool anybody but fools! you play the race card everyday you loser</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359749252659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:07:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359749694939-131</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's for the same reason that 72% of African American women have children out of wedlock. They are dysfunctional and lack discipline like the Dems so it's a match made in heaven. Did I win a prize for the best answer? :-)</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359749694939</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:14:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359750118000-132</Id><Topic><Title>Did the engineers cause the problem so they could call a strike soon and be the ones to solve it</Title><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721476479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:24:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, you don't know jack. It's a fluke of timing, nothing more. SPEEA and Boeing have been in contract talks since LAST APRIL. Had Boeing not insisted on robbing from its engineers and techs to give to its execs (who already receive bloated compensation packages), a new contract would've been in place LAST OCTOBER when the prior contract expired and there would be no possibility of a strike. Boeing insisted however so contract talks have dragged on far longer than they ever should have. There's also this little nugget. Mike Delaney, Vice President of Engineering for BCA, also stated that if SPEEA is on strike Boeing can use engineers working at other locations around the company (e.g. Huntsville, Philadelphia, Mesa, southern California, St. Louis, etc) to work the 787 battery issue. Yeah, good luck with that.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1359750118000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:21:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359750215470-133</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's funny, you respond to a charge of race baiting by race baiting -- unfortunately lots of people of all races succumb to the constant drone of lib lies. For example, did ya know that a higher percentage of Republicans voted for the 1964 Civil Rights act than democrats? Of course you didn't know that because it doesn't fit the left wing race bait propaganda campaign</Msg><Username>jetstream_2010</Username><Timestamp>1359750215470</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:23:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359750299453-134</Id><Topic><Title>I see the greedy union engineers are going to strike</Title><Username>shep21998</Username><Timestamp>1359721144997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 07:19:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpity bump ...</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1359750299453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:24:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359750683672-135</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Flip Flops On Gun Control</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359737398837</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:49:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The subject is ammo that makes a hammer wound while maintaining trajectory. A hammer wound to the head is a skull fracture. Also, the police usually respond with multiple backup. But the average person would also be willing to use ammo that has a lower lethal percentage. It's a technological solution rather than the one-million-commandments.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1359750683672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:31:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359752200708-136</Id><Title>Watch for the beginning of a downplay on the financial impact of 787</Title><Msg>To be honest, I'm mystified by the strength of the stock today. I still firmly believe that the 787 Li-Ion issue is months away from an acceptable solution, and that the cost of this problem will run Boeing $1B - $2B, this year. As this investigation drags out, I'm going to listen very carefully to what Boeing management says about the financial impact for this failure. If they start to say "Even if we have a slow down in 787 deliveries for a few weeks, we can overcome this delay in revenue by offsetting revenue in our business units." to me that's a sure sign that they are lying the ground work to announce a longer delay in 787 production and lost revenue in the future. I'd be surprised if we see a 787 flying before March.</Msg><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1359752200708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359752205104-137</Id><Title>BA will have a big jump any time soon</Title><Msg>NTSB just annouces good progress has been made in the battery investigation. Expect the resolution any time soon. BA will shoot to $80, IMO.</Msg><Username>redmonkey56</Username><Timestamp>1359752205104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359752341914-138</Id><Topic><Title>BA will have a big jump any time soon</Title><Username>redmonkey56</Username><Timestamp>1359752205104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they announced that progess is being made into the cause of the fire, not the solution ! And to the NTSB, progress simply means that they can rule out possibilities. they may be closer to finding the cause, but then Boeing has to develop a solution.</Msg><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1359752341914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:59:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359752370064-139</Id><Title>NTSB</Title><Msg>Feb 1 (Reuters) - The U.S. National Transportation Safety Board on Friday said it was looking closely at flight data recorded by a Boeing Co 787 Dreamliner for any information about the performance of a battery that caught fire at Boston airport on Jan. 7, and its charging system. The safety board said an expert from the Department of Energy had joined the investigation, as all 50 Boeing 787s remained grounded. An NTSB investigator would also travel to France with a "battery contactor" from the battery fire for an examination at the company's office, the safety board said in its seventh update on the battery fire</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1359752370064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:59:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359752837760-140</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep pushing the racial division. The folks running the planet really love pushing the Race card. After all....If the White Middle America and Blacks are killing each other ..then golly gee...they are not thinking about how the Central Bankers are stealing their pension funds and committing False Flag attacks and taking away their guns or why their President is a fraud or why endless Wars are bankrupting America.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1359752837760</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:07:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359753029439-141</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it`s is a direct correlation to the whine coming from Republicans and the amount of okra and catfish consumed.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359753029439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:10:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359754163289-142</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO shows how stupid you are I`m not white fool</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1359754163289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:29:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359754631341-143</Id><Topic><Title>BA will have a big jump any time soon</Title><Username>redmonkey56</Username><Timestamp>1359752205104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does seem that someting positive is in the air. The stock performance (price and volume) today seems to indicate that some news is out there that we have not heard yet. The trip to France by one of the "experts" with one of the battery components may be a clue.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1359754631341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:37:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359754687285-144</Id><Topic><Title>BA will have a big jump any time soon</Title><Username>redmonkey56</Username><Timestamp>1359752205104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Believe me, it won't take much time for Boeing to develop a new battery system, considering Boeing's experience of having designed so many airplanes. And I believe Boeing has many backup systems ready during this suspension period. The current complexity is due to the uncertainty resulted from unidentified cause of battery burndown. Regulator and general public won't trust any new battery system if the uncertainty is not removed. The key issue is the cause identification, IMHO.</Msg><Username>redmonkey56</Username><Timestamp>1359754687285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:38:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359754743573-145</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for the beginning of a downplay on the financial impact of 787</Title><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1359752200708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe your firm belief is incorrect. Time will tell.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1359754743573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:39:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359754935991-146</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for the beginning of a downplay on the financial impact of 787</Title><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1359752200708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I agree. Time will tell. If I'm wrong, I'll lose some money. If I'm right, I'll make some money. That's what I love about America.</Msg><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1359754935991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:42:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359754949779-147</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for the beginning of a downplay on the financial impact of 787</Title><Username>madrusky</Username><Timestamp>1359752200708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:56:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget about insurance.</Msg><Username>redmonkey56</Username><Timestamp>1359754949779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:42:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359755404496-148</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"why their President is a fraud" Why is their president a 'fraud'?</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1359755404496</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:50:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359755841723-149</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Company CEO on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>arnoldblacksmith</Username><Timestamp>1359747522328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:38:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful info, thanks</Msg><Username>lawrenceronald13</Username><Timestamp>1359755841723</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 16:57:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359756085361-150</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does not matter, If they keep printing money we will all be green trash! buy aud dxy</Msg><Username>thaddeus9992001</Username><Timestamp>1359756085361</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:01:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359756199842-151</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so why don't you tell us why Jetstream- don't know? Im not surprised- I will give you a hint- in 1964 the solid south was still 100% Southern Democrat and of course they would rather have died than vote for Civil Rights. The pre Civil War North remained intact and republican and the number of pro votes put the legislation over the top- of course after 1958 the Nixon Southern strategy kicked in and all those southern Democrats converted to republicanism and your ratios of pros and cons would be replaced so that a re vote on Civil Rights would yield different republican democrat ratios supporting the legislation and the most pro votes would be Democrats</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1359756199842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:03:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359756297860-152</Id><Topic><Title>-+$+- The Boeing Company to be featured on MAD MONEY tonight! -+$+-</Title><Username>lucianoanderson120</Username><Timestamp>1359569677040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 13:14:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful info, thanks</Msg><Username>lawrenceronald13</Username><Timestamp>1359756297860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:04:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359757645331-153</Id><Topic><Title>From each accroding to his ability to each according to his needs.</Title><Username>pay4ityourself</Username><Timestamp>1359736861381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 11:41:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you another one of those morons who equate taxes with thievery? Now that takes some really bottomless stupidity.</Msg><Username>bebop_arugula</Username><Timestamp>1359757645331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:27:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359757646442-154</Id><Topic><Title>Thought for the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359756862276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, what's really hilarious is your story about why you are such a DFC.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1359757646442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:27:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359757716871-155</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretending not to be white makes you a funny poster fool.....or should I say "word".</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1359757716871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:28:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359757723722-156</Id><Title>I said it the first day when the 787 had a fire in Boston.</Title><Msg>First thing to consider is a bad battery batch. Second is the charging system. In every case the aircraft had a thermal runaway during APU and or start operations. In all cases there was no warning until there was smoke on the ground or warnings after takeoff. The monorting systems of the battery were not working properly. The charging system voltage indication may also be at fault, causing an overvoltage to the Hybrid battery system which was undetected by the electrical sytem. Just a guess from a former and retired 40 year commercial pilot.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1359757723722</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:28:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359757873231-157</Id><Topic><Title>Why do Democrats Normally Receive 90%+ of the African-American Vote?</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359743120175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:25:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps he thinks he passed the beta test?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1359757873231</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:31:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359758043385-158</Id><Topic><Title>Thought for the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359756862276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its also hiarious that Hooz actually HAD a thought today</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1359758043385</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:34:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359758348127-159</Id><Topic><Title>More Stimulus is Necessary</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359742521207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:15:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where does that stimulous come from ? Is this organization EVER audited to discover where MOST of this stimulous money actually goes ? Is this Cartel actually Federal or are they REALLY private...and run by PRIVATE citizens with no access to private discussions about how they MAKE money ? When you answer that question you will come one step closer to understanding the NATURE of evil...and the nature or REAL POWER...and WHO rules the world.</Msg><Username>generaljackripper</Username><Timestamp>1359758348127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:39:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359759044413-160</Id><Topic><Title>More Stimulus is Necessary</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359742521207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 13:15:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@ "I venture to say that the long-range budget of the present Administration of our government has been in the black and not in the red." Red Ink is the new Black Ink just as failing is the new succeeding for Dems.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359759044413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:50:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359759109842-161</Id><Title>With Scott Brown Out of the Running is Willard Gonna Try?</Title><Msg>Former Senator Scott Brown bowed out of the upcoming special election in Massachusetts for John Kerry's Senate seat, Repubs want to run Willard in Brown's place. The thing is,he says he doesn't want to run, meaning the only way to get him to run would be to draft him. Unfortunately Willard heard the word draft and he ran off to France again!!! Au Revoir!!!</Msg><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1359759109842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:51:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359759830276-162</Id><Topic><Title>Thought for the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359756862276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What does it matter?"</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359759830276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:03:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359760380489-163</Id><Topic><Title>With Scott Brown Out of the Running is Willard Gonna Try?</Title><Username>imshockedshocked</Username><Timestamp>1359759109842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:51:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROTFLMAO!</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1359760380489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:13:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359760410428-164</Id><Topic><Title>Worst Socialist President Ever</Title><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1359738528839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 12:08:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suicide rates climbing in the Confederacy. AGAIN.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1359760410428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:13:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359761120831-165</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's the million dollar question! We can all speculate on the answer. I have a lengthy answer to the question but don't feel comfortable stating it for fear of being called a racist! If you can connect the dots with a logical conclusion, why would the obvious truth be anything other than the truth? The Left would prefer to censor the truth rather than have to hear the truth. If they can't censor you they'll try to discredit or destroy you.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1359761120831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:25:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359761664075-166</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"for fear of being called a racist! " Why fear it? This is because you are a racist. 20-Aug-2012 What will it take to get blacks not to vote for Obama? ...Is there anything that blacks cherish more than money, drugs, and white women? Maybe tickets to next year's Superbowl! sdmiller474...</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1359761664075</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:34:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359761929331-167</Id><Title>Want a laugh? check out the Airbus plan "B"</Title><Msg>Airbus is gonna eject the flaming battery from the plane like a flare! "Airbus has declined to say whether the A350 would include battery fire extinguishers, but industry sources say burning materials would instead be expelled outside the plane and that the fire hazard is reduced by electronics also provided by Saft." http://www.reuters.com/article/2013/02/01/us-airbus-a350-batteries-idUSBRE91006F20130201</Msg><Username>indejavulandyoueatleftovers</Username><Timestamp>1359761929331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:38:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359762010541-168</Id><Topic><Title>gas went up .14 overnight, Has Obama cut drilling on gov. land again?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1359760518357</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:15:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Governor of Nebraska signs on to the Keystone Pipeline. It's in Obama's hands now. I give this illegal immigrant radical leftist president about a 20% chance at signing on to Keystone. He would rather punish us! Drilling on Private Property is way up while drilling on Government Property is way down under Obama's reign of power.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1359762010541</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:40:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359762165763-169</Id><Title>Why did 90% of African Americans vote for Democrat Jesse Jackson Jr.?</Title><Msg>A. They like corrupt Democrats B. They were confused and thought it was JJ senior</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359762165763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:42:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359762994968-170</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.Thank you for taking notice of the communication skills that I possess. It's the highest form of flattery when you recognize and repeat other people's quotes. I never realized that you are that impressionable. I promise I will never let you down!</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1359762994968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:56:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359763130745-171</Id><Topic><Title>Why did 90% of African Americans vote for Democrat Jesse Jackson Jr.?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1359762165763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:42:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do liberals/Blacks re-elect politicians that were corrupt, and then locked up?...Like the DC Mayor Berry? Caught taking bribe money, and doing cocaine, but libs were happy to re-elect him. Why does NO LIBERAL ever object to anything one of their leftist politicians supports? Lots of conservatives question/object to policies their govt party members want. Bush often got criticized by conservatives. Looks to me like conservatives want what's best for the overall population, and selfish libs could care less if their politicians are corrupt.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359763130745</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:58:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359763457818-172</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1359752370064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The expert here at my house says that carbon fiber reflects electromagnetic fields rather than absorb them.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1359763457818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:04:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359763492106-173</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1359752370064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's hope the flight data recorder is programmed to collect the information about the batteries. If not, there could be a redesign of the recorder software and possibly hardware before any future flights.. I'm sure the FAA will want this information recorded after this investigation.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1359763492106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:04:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359763607198-174</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too late. Can't hide behind fantasy "communication skills." It's your simple public diplay of hateful, ugly, filthy, rotten, nasty aspects that mark you.</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1359763607198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:06:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359764170255-175</Id><Topic><Title>8,500,000 Americans Left Labor Force In Obama's First Term...</Title><Username>x6xxx234</Username><Timestamp>1359727921227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 09:12:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, all those people no longer working since Obama took office would fill over 130 super bowl stadiums.</Msg><Username>bogeywonder2</Username><Timestamp>1359764170255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359764332004-176</Id><Topic><Title>gas went up .14 overnight, Has Obama cut drilling on gov. land again?</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1359760518357</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 18:15:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And libs are rejoicing that unemployment is now 7.9% GW Bush lowered taxes, and unemployment dropped to 4.5% for 52 straight months. And it happened immediately after taxes were lowered. Going on the 5th year of Obama wasting over $800,000,000,000 dollars on a phony stimulus, and raising taxes 5 yrs later we are still at 7.9%, and libs think we are going in the right direction?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1359764332004</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:18:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359764819855-177</Id><Topic><Title>SPEEA to ratify the strike over pensions and a comparison with Boeing Executive pension costs</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359687964804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 22:06:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember BA is a dead cat bounce stock , compare BA ytd down .65%, for one year down ..66% for five dayd\s down .22% too much risk and no reward. the dow up over 10% and Sand P up over 15% so for a long time BA has been a poor risk. better stocs with better dividends next strike, then max and 777x guess if they will be done on time and on budget with outsourcing business model or weakend SPEEA workers</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359764819855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:26:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359765042027-178</Id><Topic><Title>The Boeing Company CEO on MAD MONEY!</Title><Username>arnoldblacksmith</Username><Timestamp>1359747522328</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 14:38:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if itws Crammer do exactly the oppposite , his show is pure entertainment bull yah and honk the horn, read his book he had a fund and his wife was the trade godest and she called all the shots , so when she decided to get out he went to talk show ie stocks but he can not trade or figure out much he is consistently wrong and a mouthpiece for larger institutions tha want to sell into rokkie traders or get rookies to sell so institutions can buy</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359765042027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:30:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359765549052-179</Id><Title>mad money cramer can you say bull yah , he is a pumper for institutions</Title><Msg>Jim cramer is a retirred hedge fund manager that had to quit because his wife was the tradiing goddess and she retired. read his book he decided to get a talk show., because his wife was the skill behind the hedge fund, not Jim. Read his book. Here is how Jim Cramer does it now, it goes like this if the institutions want out of a stock cramer builds it up for rookies to buy into weakness, and the big houses are selling. And also Jim Cramer does the oppostite, if the stock will be going up , Jim cramer talkes rookie investorsinto selling. Think about it, how many other investment advisors are free and say bullya and honk a clarabell horn he got from his childhood show, he watched Ucle Bob and the puppett , howdie doodie . can you say bull to yah, and honk the clarabell horn , anyone who believes in those antics is not going to make any money</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359765549052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:39:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359765632173-180</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1359752370064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:59:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would suppose that the battery is not the problem but that the battery is being burned up by the problem. The battery might survive with additional cooling but the actual problem not found. Then I would say that dozens of electrical meters need to be added to the electrical system of a test aircraft and that aircraft flown until the problem re-occurs.</Msg><Username>hia_intell</Username><Timestamp>1359765632173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:40:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359766568188-181</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't even bother with sdmiller4747. He has made multiple statements on this subject. Imagine being trapped inside that sdmiller brain with no way out.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1359766568188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:56:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359769189215-182</Id><Topic><Title>Thought for the Day</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1359756862276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:14:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not if its true</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1359769189215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 20:39:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359770876428-183</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Welfare, Foodstamps, Unemployment and illegitimate birth rates go up for blacks.....</Title><Username>hope4whitepeople</Username><Timestamp>1359751376835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 15:42:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you spewing nonsense like this on a BA board?</Msg><Username>dellag1</Username><Timestamp>1359770876428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:07:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359772908159-184</Id><Title>Obama's Department of Homeland Security</Title><Msg>DHS advice for confronting mass shooters: Scissors If your workplace getting shot up by a crazed gunman? No problem - just grab a pair of scissors.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1359772908159</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 21:41:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359775180532-185</Id><Title>Comparisons</Title><Msg>Romney, post election: “Mitt Romney's campaign donated nearly $90,000 to the Red Cross in the weeks after the Republican presidential nominee's electoral defeat, filings with the Federal Election Commission showed Sunday. The donation was made on Nov. 30, weeks after Election Day, and not publicized by the campaign.” Obama, post election: “Four years after President Barack Obama promised to change the culture of Washington, it’s hard to imagine how his ethics, transparency and campaign finance pledges could have backfired more thoroughly. Even before the president solicited unlimited corporate donations for his inauguration and announced he will reinvent his campaign operation as an unrestricted lobbying group, government watchdog groups were already fed up with Obama’s many reversals.”</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1359775180532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:19:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359775758770-186</Id><Title>Boeing Stock is ready to go to 80? not going to happen not since 2008</Title><Msg>there are some boeing mismanagement enablers here with an opinion that Boeing stock will be 80 soon due to the investigation is continuing on the grounded 787, that is called a spin. Factually Boeing has very seldom been at 80 and never at 150 a user claimed last year it would be 150 this year Barbing who said to trust her. The facts when Boeing was doing better apparetly , but not really for a short time Boeing was a 80 dollar stock. Today a strike is possible, grounding of the 787 is a reality and no the stock would not appear to be heading up Since 1-9-2013 it has been selling off on lower highs and lower lows on larger than normal average volume, classic selling by institutions. Today was the first of the month large firms sell and adjust Boeing has 2 billion in stock buy back to protect the share price for some time. In any event BA is down for the year to date and the entire 52 weeks by about 1% while the dow is up 10% and the S and P is up 15% so nope Boeing is not about to jump up on a failed 787 fix that is 3.5 year laate and 32 billion dollars over budget</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359775758770</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:29:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359775862867-187</Id><Topic><Title>mad money cramer can you say bull yah , he is a pumper for institutions</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359765549052</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 19:39:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>give me a bull yah and honk the horn for Jim Carmer ! mouthpice of the company not the investor</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359775862867</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:31:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359777421257-188</Id><Title>From the 8th to today Ba is still a 74 dollar stock dead cat bounce</Title><Msg>Carter Leake, an analyst at BB&amp;T Capital Markets in Virginia. "Said onboard fires on airplanes are as bad as it gets. Even though it happened on the ground, rest assured the FAA is asking 'What if it happened in the air?'"Leake, the analyst at BB&amp;T Capital Markets, who is also a former commercial and military pilot, said” Any electrical problem in the next 30 days, for whatever reason, , is going to be a big deal," he added.( sell your Boeing stock ) The Chicago-based jet maker's shares closed down 2 percent at $76.13 after the news. The electrical fire is troubling in part because the 787 relies heavily on electrical power to drive onboard systems that in other jet models are run by air pressure generated by the engines. The new jet also suffered an electrical fire during a test flight, prompting a redesign of electrical systems. since entering service in October 2011, the plane has repeatedly made headlines for mechanical problems. The FAA and the NTSB are looking into what caused the problem, which came just weeks after Boeing endured a string of other electrical problems that briefly grounded three of the planes. The new jet also has suffered an engine failure and fuel leaks in the 14 months it has been in service. Last July, the FAA investigated an incident in which a 787 engine made by General Electric Co blew apart on the ground in South Carolina, prompting changes in how the engines are made, maintained and inspected. A similar engine failed on a Boeing 747 in Shanghai in September. In late December, , calling the problems "normal squawks." Monday's electrical fire raised questions about the view of Boeing Chief Executive Jim McNerney who said the 787 has not experienced an unusual number of problems for a new aircraft. The number of incidents and especially an onboard fire is likely to make Boeing highly susceptible to the public, shareholders and customers, if any other issues arise on the 787 aircraft.( sell Boeing stock ) Wing de-icing and cabin air conditioning systems on the 787 are electrical. If ventilation failed on a flight or the cockpit filled with smoke, the pilots would have to descend to 10,000 feet to survive, is just an example . . Boeing Chicago is pressing their bad management into the danger zone, so many incidents that could bring this outsourced plane down with all aboard dead. Hopefully the FAA, NTSB will ground this outsourced 30 billion dollar mistake before a 787 crashes killing all passengers onboard. If it's a outsourced Boeing I am not going. Boeing shareholders each 787 deliverd cost you 300 million loss and the SPEEA strike will cost you 400 million per day. Boeing stock is held for dividends and increased value, for one year your stock valuation has increased BA 1.02%, DOW JONES average is up 8.29%,NASDAQ average is up 15.8%, other aerospace companies are way up Northrup (NOC) is up 18.6%, Lockheed (LMT) is up 17.8%, another DOW stock Bank of America (BAC) is up more in the last five days (6.41%) and 96% for the year. Going forward with a potential strike and this huge 787 failure look around for much better stocks sell and move on, your holdings will grow at least 7% faster if you just go with a ETF for the DOW or 16.8% more growth if you go with a ETF for the NASDAQ will far less risk than Boeing a mismanaged and dangerous stock to hold . Until Chicago managment is terminated and replaced any investor should stay clear of Boeing stock . This was my opinion on 1-8-2013 and twice this week in my user comments I pointed out KERX was a short term buy and sell it is up 106% for the week, I am out now but for all the Boeing mismangment enablers you need to make you money in the stock market not being paid or wasting your time making worthess opinions about Boeing going to 80 or 15o or airplane orders making any difference to investors</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359777421257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:57:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359779343746-189</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Stock is ready to go to 80? not going to happen not since 2008</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359775758770</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:29:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOS reported</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359779343746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:29:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359779606034-190</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst said onboard fires on a 787 is as bad as it gets Boeing stock down 2%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357636555656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 04:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOS harassment reported</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359779606034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:33:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359779876578-191</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst said onboard fires on a 787 is as bad as it gets Boeing stock down 2%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357636555656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 04:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bman42_01, well Boeing mismanagement are experts in cheap outsourcing they can find worse electronics than you can I guess funny</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359779876578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:37:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359780209997-192</Id><Topic><Title>From the 8th to today Ba is still a 74 dollar stock dead cat bounce</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359777421257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 22:57:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOS violation reported</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359780209997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:43:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359780780773-193</Id><Topic><Title>Analyst said onboard fires on a 787 is as bad as it gets Boeing stock down 2%</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1357636555656</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 04:15:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOS violation reported !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1359780780773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 23:53:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>