<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658326988-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ayn Rand understands the mind of a free man at a philosophical level better then almost anyone in history</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358658326988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:05:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658454784-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right. We voted to deny Ayn Ryand the vice presidency in the last election -- but because she lacked the nerve to resign her house seat in to devote full time to the campaign, we still have to put up with her in the House of Reps. Harharharhar</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358658454784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:07:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658530019-3</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing: 787 Production Continues As Planned</Title><Username>beancounter_2003</Username><Timestamp>1358458802332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is plenty of room to park 787s pending delivery in Don Shuper's backyard.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358658530019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:08:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358659128905-4</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing: 787 Production Continues As Planned</Title><Username>beancounter_2003</Username><Timestamp>1358458802332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 16:40:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at the moment BA cannot even run test flights of the type required before delivery- nor fly them out of Everett with test crew to seattle or wherever- Everett field is near full with the first dozen being reworked plus the production rate. BA **may** be able to run a few test flights - but at the moment its a no no</Msg><Username>donwshuper50</Username><Timestamp>1358659128905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:18:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358665677364-5</Id><Title>Production continues as planned, but it won't be cheap for Boeing</Title><Msg>It's not clear how long the investigation — or the fix — will take, but it won't be cheap for Boeing</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358665677364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 02:07:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358665957546-6</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am so sad, I got on Boeing Managment enabler 's thumbs down !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358665957546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 02:12:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358666247435-7</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner nighmare was due to poor company leadership</Title><Username>leftwinggunowner</Username><Timestamp>1358604730021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:12:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lefty, On what basis did you give that excessive and way too high D- grade to Boeing managment, why are you supporting chicago, this is not let all children pass school.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358666247435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 02:17:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358677986412-8</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can Boeing trust SPEEA? That's a laugh. You've got it backward MB. The question really is, can SPEEA and the employees it represents trust Boeing? Scientists, engineers, physicists, chemists and technicians are people who, by virtue of their personality type, aren't militant or prone to striking. So the question is this. What's going on at Boeing that may cause those very people to walk off the job en mass and go on strike. Here's the answer. At a time when the company's business climate has probably never been better (new all-time records for orders, deliveries, revenue and profit almost every quarter), at a time when we literally can't build the airplanes fast enough and the company is showering the executives with massive bonuses and salary increases, they want to bend us over a barrel and rape us. Put the blame where it belongs MB, on Boeing Corporate and its overpaid executives, the very people who are directly responsible for the 787 being three years late and billions of dollars over-budget. I and an entire army of engineers tried repeatedly to tell them that their global outsourcing business model was fraught with enormous risk and had virtually no chance of success, but it's not what they wanted to hear so they ignored every warning they were given. They created this mess, now they can lie in it.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1358677986412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 05:33:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358678432015-9</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. I couldn't have said it better myself. What there needs to be is a serious house cleaning at Boeing Corporate in Chicago, but I think we all know the chances of that happening are zero. Welcome to Corporate America.</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1358678432015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 05:40:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358681119146-10</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>phantomfield, the question is why is the Boeing management only number 2 on the list of highest corrupt Management Companies in the USA , and why do you continue to be the Boeing mismanagmement enabler, all you do is try to make excuses for Chicago bad mangement "Ranking: 2 Boeing Company Boeing is the world's leading aerospace company and the largest manufacturer of commercial jetliners and military aircraft, with capabilities in rotorcraft, electronic and defense systems, missiles, satellites, launch vehicles and advanced information and communication systems. Their reach extends to customers in 145 countries around the world, and they are the number one U.S. exporter in terms of sales. Federal Contract $: $19366.6m Total Number of Instances: 46 Total Misconduct dollar amount: $1054.5m</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358681119146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:25:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358681555971-11</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do certain posters, two in particular, go ballistic when there is any mention of Ayn Rand?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358681555971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:32:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358681740361-12</Id><Title>Best company in the USA!</Title><Msg>Boeing is what America is all about! The people that work at Boeing are going to make this company a major success. Its called NO failure. Working 24 hrs a day on the 787 and believe me, a great aircraft in the making!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358681740361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:35:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358683061464-13</Id><Topic><Title>Best company in the USA!</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358681740361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:35:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deludud DREAMER!</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1358683061464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:57:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358683520073-14</Id><Title>Being will survive because they build great aircraft!</Title><Msg>Boeing made one major mistake. They let Alan Mullaly walk out the door and turn Ford into a SUPER company! Boeing slapped Mulally in the face when he spent most of his life at Boeing and they made NcNurdy the CEO of BA . Everyone at Boeing believed in Mulally! Boeing has made many mistakes since NcNurdy has been in charge. Outsourcing much of the 787 was a major MISTAKE. When you build a new aircraft you need to build it in house and have total control of the build process and all the parts. Boeing will survive and thrive because they are 1 of only 2 aircraft companies in the world thanks to a duoply, not because they made a very bad decision about their CEO!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358683520073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:05:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358683931006-15</Id><Topic><Title>Best company in the USA!</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358681740361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 06:35:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>defense_junky you also said this remember " December 2008 buy ASME get in on the ground floor, and get in and watch the stock grow along with YGE same story. Your predictions suck , in 2008 ASME was trading about a million shares and sold at $16.45 and now trades at $2.79 cents and has gone down steady since 2008, the volume is down to 200,000 too. While solar has some great day trades it is not a buy and hold stock and your choice of yge is not by any means the best one. If your opinion of Boeing is as bad as your r knowledge of asme and yge , I take you opinion and go the other way. The workers are great, but like any great worker who is wasted, when the leaders of BOEING do not use them right, the whole Boeing company sucks . Read hart-Smith a Boeing Engineer and get the story right !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358683931006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:12:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358684287916-16</Id><Topic><Title>Being will survive because they build great aircraft!</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358683520073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:05:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope Allen Mulally was part of the problem, he went along with Stonecipher and the outsourcing business plan. He finally learned when he went to ford not to fight with the workers and set up monthly meeting with the unions to work together . Boeing is still stuck in the MD -GE midn set, they refuse to negotiate and actually sell their proposal to the american people not the private negotiation process. Allan Mulally pused the sonic cruiser for years and got zero customers, if boeing had been watching airbus and got it right the 737 would have been made more fuel effecient and the 777x would be done and the 787 ne sonic cruiser would have been stopped. Now the SPEEA and IAM are the best workers in the world but the worst employees in the world are in Chigago they are teh Boeing executives MD-GE mind set failures</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358684287916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:18:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358684474909-17</Id><Topic><Title>Being will survive because they build great aircraft!</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358683520073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:05:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well Being may survive then but we are not so sure about Boeing management</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358684474909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:21:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358684770414-18</Id><Title>safety board rules out excess voltage as the cause of a battery fire</Title><Msg>The National Transportation Safety Board has ruled out excess voltage as the cause of a battery fire on the Boeing 787 Dreamliner jet operated by Japan Airlines at Boston’s Logan Airport this month, the agency said on Sunday. Last week, governments across the world grounded the Dreamliner jet after a problem with a lithium-ion battery on a second 787 plane, flown by All Nippon Airways forced the jet to make an emergency landing in western Japan. The agency said in a statement forwarded by a Boeing Japan representative that examination of the flight recorder data from the JAL B-787 airplane indicated that the battery in the auxiliary power unit “did not exceed its designed voltage of 32 volts.”</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358684770414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:26:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358684776985-19</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one, thanks. I find "her" hypocrisy near the end of "her" life, as “she” was battling end-stage lung cancer, particularly amusing. "She" changed “her” name to “her” husband’s, and “she” wasn’t below becoming the same kind of parasite “she” always railed against.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1358684776985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:26:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358684821805-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... so that she could collect his benefits, of course.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1358684821805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:27:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358685043357-21</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the real story of Boeing is the Boeing management which is attempting to take all negotiation and then living wage away from the workforce, that is all this company has become a hate the living wage Management company, move to Carolina is a prime example</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358685043357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:30:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358685268266-22</Id><Topic><Title>Being will survive because they build great aircraft!</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358683520073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:05:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true, Mulally didn't leave Boeing by accident. Ford Jr. asked people in the car industry if there was anyone that could make Ford into a profitable company. Sources told him look at Alan Mulally. Alan turned down the offer twice. When Ford Jr offered Mulally a 26 million signing bonus he signed on! Ford got there man, and he has delivered BIG time!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358685268266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:34:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358686779479-23</Id><Topic><Title>Being will survive because they build great aircraft!</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358683520073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:05:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I love about Mulally. When he went to work for Ford he took all their cars to the people that write the car mags about performance. They all said Ford produces are #$%$ products and they wouldn't buy their cars if they were given them! Perception is in the eye of the beholder. A couple of years later they said they would buy a Ford. Two thumbs up for Mulally. He didn't do it at Boeing, but hes left a legacy at Ford!</Msg><Username>barbing1965</Username><Timestamp>1358686779479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:59:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358688244291-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Liberals FEAR Rand because they aren't really liberals." In order to fear mAyn Rand, one would have to take him seriously. And nobody with half a brain or a college BS in anything does... It's junk philosophy, whose sole purpose is to provide the greediest elements of society with a pseudointellectual justification for being a pig..</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1358688244291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:24:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358688994736-25</Id><Topic><Title>Being will survive because they build great aircraft!</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358683520073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 07:05:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mulally had no choice about out sourcing. Stonecipher was running the company, and he was a total jerk!</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1358688994736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:36:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358689312842-26</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Reaches Endgame, Culmination Of Decade Of Problems With 'Nightmareliner'</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358560772061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exactly</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1358689312842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:41:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358689727192-27</Id><Topic><Title>The real problem here...</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358631205916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:33:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many decades do we have to wait????</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1358689727192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:48:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358690192359-28</Id><Topic><Title>UNION MOOCHER BUILT</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1358636749411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:05:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HEY, Those union guys aren't moochers. They work very hard to maintain their laid back jobs. You can't have those easy jobs unless you are willing to fight for them every once in a while!</Msg><Username>sheepshearer48</Username><Timestamp>1358690192359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:56:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358690439002-29</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you fear Ayn Rand?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358690439002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358690492768-30</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you obsessed with Ayn Rand?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358690492768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:01:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358693514172-31</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, but Boeing execs might be thinking about what it may be forced to shell out to engineers and tech workers, about 26,0000 of them that may be demanding exorbitant pension plans for future employees. Maybe Boeing can significantly reduce the number of them and be none the wiser. Afterall Boeing is no GM that can look forward to a Gov't bailout. Nor is Boeing a gov't entitlement program.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358693514172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:51:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358694700874-32</Id><Title>A wave of local law enforecenemt are all saying NO to Illegal Gun Control attempts</Title><Msg>A wave of sheriffs, state legislatures and law enforcement figures have stood up to put the federal government on notice that they will NOT be involved in any disarmament measures or violations of the 2nd Amendment. Their courageous and patriotic actions are the very solution, grounded in the Constitution and Bill of Rights, that Sheriff Mack has been advocating for decades through his books, and his organizational work with the Oath Keepers, the Constitutional Sheriffs &amp; Police Officers Association (CSPOA.org) and more.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358694700874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:11:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358694769968-33</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moved the fat cats to "yuppieville," Chicago, too. Let all of these arrogant nerds (and their sugar wives) ROT.</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358694769968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:12:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358695364754-34</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are incredible. You know nothing about Boeing commerical or SPEEA.. You are not a member, you are not an engineer, you make unsubstantiated claims and for some reason think people should take you serious. If you want to take a cut in pay and benefits to help corporate then go ahead and leave us to make our own decisions about our jobs.</Msg><Username>skunked.again</Username><Timestamp>1358695364754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:22:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358695612341-35</Id><Topic><Title>UNION MOOCHER BUILT</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1358636749411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:05:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>• Re: ACI over ANR? Hey sizzlin2day, on March 13,2011 you said to buy two coal stocks remember , your opinion then was buy both Re: ACI over ANR? sizzlin2dayby sizzlin2day.Mar 13, 2012 11:28 AM.Permalink.Go to topic • “This is the time to load up on both, wait for big $$$$$$$$” • • Sizzlin2day, . I checked since you’re at a huge loss on your stock picking ability, I see that pattern continues on your opinion of Boeing workers. Both of your coal stocks went down in a straight line pattern so you were wrong on your coal stock buy recommendation. Coals are a day trade from time to time like when Romney was running against Obama for the last six weeks going into the election vote, and I posted that JRCC was a huge buy opportunity, and . I made over 100% on JRCCin 6 weeks. Sizzlin2day,, but your call on March 13, 2011 was 100% wrong .On March 13, 2011 ACI was $11.76 and today it is $7.65 a loss of 34% on your opinion, why would anyone care or think you have anything right on Boeing or on unions! Sisslin2day, you sure can’t trade a stock right! I guess you’re jealous that qualified and represented workers who Boeing hires and they then Boeing requires they pay Union dues and yes the workers make more money than you ever could. Boeing is responsible 100% for all worker selection and job offers, and no union is involved until the Boeing Company hires the worker and not for a 30 day trial period do the new employees have to pay or be represented by a union ..So • Boeing gets a 30 look see at their new workers first. Next, Boeing makes their workers pay union dues. So only a fool would not allow the Unions to represent them in collective bargaining. Sizzlin2day, if your ability to lose 34 cents on every dollar you invested in coal stocks is like your understanding of union workers then you have a very poor understanding of both stock selection and your own job ability I would guess does not rate a union job then !</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358695612341</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:26:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358695835294-36</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The answer was to go with the experts, the real Boeing SPEEA represented workers who would have built the 787 with 100% engineering control at a much higher standard for the original cost estimate 5 billion dollars and now there would be about 360 profitable flying 787 out there now. you keep making excuses for bad mangment decisions like making an excuse for a alcoholic's drinking behavior, until you start to get on the program nothing will get fixed.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358695835294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:30:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358696026031-37</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was a HOT HUNK, that's why. Any further questions?</Msg><Username>queen_of_fartz</Username><Timestamp>1358696026031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:33:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358696645930-38</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries probably made from CHINA</Title><Username>gowiththewave</Username><Timestamp>1358631362999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:36:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All four plants that GS builds lithium-ion batteries are located in Japan and the batteries supplied to the Dreamliners are made at a factory in its Kyoto headquarters. The electrical system, which the battery is embedded into, is manufactured by Thales, Europe’s biggest defense-electronics maker.</Msg><Username>jwu2556</Username><Timestamp>1358696645930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:44:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358698210049-39</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So explain to the public how SPEEA is being raped? New diffenition of Rape by SPEEA is above industry avarage pay raises every year of the new contract and "new hires" will enroll in 401K instead of getting pensions. As for health care, you get the best the industry has to offer and you damaged it by supporting Obama /care, not BAs fault. You guys are insane!</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1358698210049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:10:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358698274474-40</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While you geniuses are arguning wheter Ayn Rand took Medicare....Bernacke announces QE4-Ever. The point is that we are TRILLIONS in debt to foreign Globalist PRIVATE banks,,,,and we do NOT need to be. Ayn Rand may have been a hypocrite at the end of her life....on one occasion...but the Federal Reserve is robbing you blind and they are laughing all the way to the ...well..the bank......there is no need to even HAVE a debt if CONGRESS issued the currency...not the Federal Reserve...(about as Federal as Federal Express).....You #$%$ miss the point again</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358698274474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:11:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358698391826-41</Id><Title>Is BA like the GM of the auto world?</Title><Msg>union workers, lack of quality, poor products? Just curious. Not real familiar with aerospace sector.</Msg><Username>use.caution</Username><Timestamp>1358698391826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:13:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358698809350-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why do liberals FEAR Ayn Rand?</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358619649130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:20:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most people who know anything about her don't fear her ideas. I suspect that most people who idealize her don't know much about her. The kinds of individual freedom she championed is the kind that encroaches on a lot of other people's freedom at one time, like the right of a wealthy person to build a large, unsafe building in the middle of the city, or the right of an individual to dump their factory waste into the river everyone uses. But then she came face to face with the fact that some problems are just too much for a person to absorb alone. She got cancer and realized how expensive that can be. Because of that, she took Social Security &amp; Medicare. She had a choice, she could have said, if treatment is going to be that expensive, I just won't take treatment. But she did not. She took SS &amp; Medicare to protect her wealth, just like almost everyone else would do. A lot of ideas are better in theory than in practice. Almost everyone wants their freedom at the expense of others' rights and freedoms.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1358698809350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:20:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358700661770-43</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phantom - you should quit posting about Boeing - you have absolutely no idea how Boeingg works.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1358700661770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:51:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358700818332-44</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which movie do you like better, The Wizard Of Oz or Batman Rises?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358700818332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:53:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701877546-45</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If this was a fight only between union and corporate I would not have gotten involved. Unfortunately the consequences of this labor dispute affects go beyond the parties. Its affects lots of people lives including the worldwide airline industry and yes the US economy. Because of these concerns I put my 2 cents here. My point was to avoid a strike that would trigger bad consequences. But then it comes down to your pay dispute not mine Since you ask me to stay out and let you guys make your own decisions. I will no longer post on this dispute. All the best to all of you in arriving at a peaceful outcome.</Msg><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358701877546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:11:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701945272-46</Id><Topic><Title>If we’re going to have universal background checks on virtually everybody who buys a gun</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358594366486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:19:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah---when all else fails, Sparty returns to his birther roots. An improvement, I guess.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1358701945272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:12:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358702270435-47</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries probably made from CHINA</Title><Username>gowiththewave</Username><Timestamp>1358631362999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:36:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The battery charge electronics is made by Securaplane (Tuscon, Arizona), not Thales. Thales is the power storage subsystem integrator. The FAA made the announcement that the "battery did not exceed its designed voltage of 32 volts" - according to the downloaded data from the flight recorder. The issue for the safety of the battery is not only the total voltage being applied by the charger (in this case 32 Volts) but also the charge voltage at the individual cell level which must not exceed its rated amount, for the GP Yuasa cell that is 3.7 Vdc, otherwise the cell will fail and potentially burn up and explode. Like any battery, the cells are in a series string to create, in this case, the near 30 volt capability. The internet photo of the failed pack shows 8 cells (3.7 x 8 = 29.6). If the charge voltage for the pack is 32, then the individual cell charge is 32/8 = 4 volts, less some amount of loss. Let's say that each cell is supposed to see no more than .2 volts above its rated performance as well as not exceed a particular charge rate. (You have to apply a slightly higher voltage to a cell than its voltage state in order to push the charge into it - and then stop at the rated limit.) The charger must perform "balance charging" which means that the charger monitors the voltage of each cell in a pack and varies the charge on a per-cell basis so that all cells are brought to the same voltage. Not all cells are "alike" and their charge profiles are slightly different, meaning that the cells could get substantially "out of balance" relative to each other and a cell (or cells) might begin to see charge voltages in excess of their rating. Say, anyone of those cells "shorts" (a common failure mechanism), then the applied voltage to the remaining cells could, without individual or smart control, increase by the proportion of the lost cell to the pack. So, now we are talking about (8 x 3.9)/7 - 3.9 = .56Vdc over the nominal applied to each cell. Lead acid and Ni-Cad batteries would not care, but it may be enough to begin a catastrophic sequence of collateral cell failures over time for a Lithium-Ion battery. Each individual cell must have protection against collateral overvoltage - not just at the pack level. That is the job of the electronics that may be embedded in each cell along with the Securaplane charger. Securaplane claims that their charger keeps track of cell imbalance as well as other faults. But I was amused that Securaplane said as of today that they were not yet "involved" in the investigation. They should have been involved from day one. The Securaplane design needs to be gone over with a "fine tooth comb" by experts outside of Boeing's plane division and Securaplane. Boeing has folks in El Segundo that have designed such chargers for Li-ion batteries for satellites. And, separately, the battery cells (in use) need to be tested for premature failure or degradation - which means that "good" batteries of similar operational use and the same and different lots need to be examined. Further, since the other failure driver is being over-loaded (too high of a discharge rate), Boeing needs to do "use case" analyses to determine whether there is unanticipated high load conditions and how those are mitigated.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1358702270435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:17:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358702494047-48</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You #$%$ miss the point again" Bull $#%$! You pathetic followers of this charlatan can't accept the fact that she used the social safety net and yet you don't think there should even be one. That's disgusting.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1358702494047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:21:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358703006533-49</Id><Topic><Title>787 Batteries probably made from CHINA</Title><Username>gowiththewave</Username><Timestamp>1358631362999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:36:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jwu2556...Thanks for that info. Now let's find out what gives with this battery problem.</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358703006533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358703213925-50</Id><Title>Next theory</Title><Msg>Well let's try something else boys/girls. Because this ain't working. The U.S. National Transportation Safety Board ruled out on Sunday excess voltage as the cause of a battery fire on the Boeing Co 787 Dreamliner jet operated by Japan Airlines Co (JAL) at Boston airport this month.</Msg><Username>coderogers</Username><Timestamp>1358703213925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:33:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358703473757-51</Id><Title>Obama is closing Gitmo</Title><Msg>Any day now.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358703473757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:37:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358703890892-52</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is closing Gitmo</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358703473757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:37:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd rather he close his fat yap.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1358703890892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:44:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358704425344-53</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Buck Phantom pontificates on this often. He is especially blissfully unaware that the company knows long before presenting a "best and final offer" whether or not it will be accepted. The company forces strikes. Period.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1358704425344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:53:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358705457773-54</Id><Title>NTSB caving in to Boeing</Title><Msg>They will let Boeing do a cover up. So flyers will be on their own, at their own risk. Cessna was directed to replace their lithium batteries with either lead-acid or nickel-cadmium. The issue was a fire started when a ground power unit was plugged in when the battery was in a partially depleted charge state. The exact condition for the JAL battery fire. [[[A letter from Cessna to CJ4 owners after the incident cautioned: "Do not connect a ground power unit to the airplane if you have reason to believe the battery may be in a depleted state ... Do not leave the aircraft unattended with a ground power unit connected."}}} [[[ Boeing got regulators' permission to use lithium batteries in the jetliner in 2007, three years after U.S. passenger planes were barred from carrying non-rechargeable types as cargo because of their flammability.]]]</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358705457773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358707117101-55</Id><Topic><Title>If this EDSEL of an airplane has to be written offf ...</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358635914260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:51:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they ever fly again, I certainly won't fly on them!</Msg><Username>pacenet_2000</Username><Timestamp>1358707117101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:38:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358707993747-56</Id><Title>Rallies assail Obama's proposed gun curbs</Title><Msg>meanwhile wing-nuts Gun Show Shootings: At Least 5 Hurt In Accidental Incidents In Ohio, Indiana, North Carolina</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358707993747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:53:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358708109959-57</Id><Topic><Title>If this EDSEL of an airplane has to be written offf ...</Title><Username>boulmichone</Username><Timestamp>1358635914260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:51:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This #$%$ me off as I have my BA rally-hat on and some #$%$ battery-maker f. up'd</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358708109959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:55:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358708774554-58</Id><Topic><Title>A wave of local law enforecenemt are all saying NO to Illegal Gun Control attempts</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358694700874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:11:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Law enforcement is just that ENFORCEMENT. They have no say in what the laws are and if they openly state that they will not enforce laws that THEY do not agree with then they should and probably will be fired.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1358708774554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:06:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358709742948-59</Id><Topic><Title>A wave of local law enforecenemt are all saying NO to Illegal Gun Control attempts</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358694700874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:11:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Such naivety makes me laugh and I do enjoy laughing. There has been a gun ban in Chicago but criminals only have to pay the cops a street tax and the cops look the other way and go after law abiding citizens. Laws don't mean #$%$ anymore and nobody trusts cops as most are crooked, that's why guns are becoming more popular.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358709742948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:22:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358709827027-60</Id><Title>We don't need no Stinking Batteries in Airplanes</Title><Msg>Airplanes should be solar and wind powered. That's why we need subsidies for those industries.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358709827027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:23:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358710140993-61</Id><Title>Our government is not spending enough on the poor.</Title><Msg>The government needs to buy poor people new vehicles to drive, It ain't fair that we have to drive around in old junkers while people with jobs get to drive newer ones. The government needs to give poor people their fair share.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358710140993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358710336672-62</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, Biden take second-term oath</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358704264213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:51:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox news will not televise any inauguration stuff. Otherwise, 50% of their viewers would commit suicide and the Republican "base" will evaporate.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1358710336672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:32:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358710418875-63</Id><Topic><Title>Ya'all need to quit wasting your time Talking about Boeing</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358628011800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:40:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's exactly right. You whites boys would just as soon ignore us poor people. Well sorry about but you can't, because our vote counts just as much as yours.</Msg><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358710418875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:33:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358710551060-64</Id><Topic><Title>A wave of local law enforecenemt are all saying NO to Illegal Gun Control attempts</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358694700874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:11:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sparty true story: In my early twenties I stopped in a 24 hour Donut shop in Chicago with some buddies after a night on the town. Two of Chicago's finest were sitting near us and a dispatch came over the radio with a call of a home invasion with 2 suspects possibly armed within 6 blocks from the donut shop I was sitting in. The cops sat there for about 10 more minutes finishing their donuts and coffee before they decided to get up and respond to the call. I could have walked to this house and got there faster than the cops. I was young and naïve at the time but it was a great lesson for me.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358710551060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:35:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358710708457-65</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Pity is a useless emotion" Only if you don't have a soul.</Msg><Username>uncle_albert_01</Username><Timestamp>1358710708457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:38:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358711579343-66</Id><Topic><Title>Don't count Boeing out.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358646251322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:44:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are kidding yourself. Been in BA for many, many years. THis is a monster. Jimmy Mac hasn't done a thing for BA since his tenure started. This will not be a cheap fix.</Msg><Username>stillinshock</Username><Timestamp>1358711579343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:52:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358711826118-67</Id><Topic><Title>Rallies assail Obama's proposed gun curbs</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358707993747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:53:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he -ll is for heroes in love and war Love: Obama/Biden et al second term line my pockets with siver and bronze for the copper if had pockets</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358711826118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:57:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358712675223-68</Id><Topic><Title>a liberal nut on here thinks no consequences for a $21T debt which is what America is heading for. It must be thinking from those who max out thier credit cards</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1358712479090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:07:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Given the Repukes congress, Bushes wars and the financial disaster in 2008 under Bush only a Republican Congress and President would have that honor LOL</Msg><Username>averagecardplayer</Username><Timestamp>1358712675223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:11:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358712838945-69</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pity the poor soul for two bits... yo' momma</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358712838945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358712895592-70</Id><Topic><Title>Don't count Boeing out.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358646251322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:44:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you the electrical engineer that know's what went wrong and it isn't more that just a few airplanes that had a problem? If so, you should clue in Boeing and the FAA what went wrong so they can start flying and delivering planes. I'm sure they would pay you a premium to solve this.</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1358712895592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:14:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713178732-71</Id><Topic><Title>A wave of local law enforecenemt are all saying NO to Illegal Gun Control attempts</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358694700874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:11:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah...good story. Cops do NOT prevent crime...they INVESTIGATE crime. The only person you can count on is yourself for self protection...its true in Nature....its true with humans. Some of these idiots think that cops will save them...instead a punk with a shotgun will have their way with their wives while they wait for a cop to arrive. True insanity</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713178732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:19:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713279716-72</Id><Topic><Title>A wave of local law enforecenemt are all saying NO to Illegal Gun Control attempts</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358694700874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:11:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the Sheriffs have the backing of the local governments. Local governments will trump Federal power under the constitution and the 10th amendment...at the local level the Sheriff is the final arbiter of who would be disarmed.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713279716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:21:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358713372748-73</Id><Title>A common denominator of all the Mass shootings</Title><Msg>....is that they all took psychotropic drugs. You dont hear the politicians banning drugs do you ? Pharmacuetical companies are second to Banks and a little more powerful then the Oil lobby in this country.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713372748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:22:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358713388055-74</Id><Title>Bill Clinton On Gun Control: 'Do Not Patronize The Passionate Supporters Of Your Opponents'</Title><Msg>that is all...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358713388055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:23:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358713420749-75</Id><Title>Vatican Welcomes Obama Gun Control Proposal</Title><Msg>that is all...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358713420749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:23:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713990759-76</Id><Topic><Title>A common denominator of all the Mass shootings</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713372748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:22:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>defineiteley Lee Raymond deserevrd his $500M/half-a-billUSD reitrement 'package' for being one of o the ugliest and fatest RWJM sp ? u</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358713990759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:33:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358714016675-77</Id><Title>Solution to the Gun Debate</Title><Msg>More gun shows: At least five people -- three in North Carolina, one in Indiana and one in Ohio -- were injured after weapons went off at gun shows Saturday. Eventually there won't be any gun fanatics left.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1358714016675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:33:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358714045776-78</Id><Title>NBC Special Report: No assault rifle was used at Sandy Hook</Title><Msg>Why were we led to believe that all the children were killed by an assault rifle?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358714045776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:34:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358714104691-79</Id><Topic><Title>The real problem here...</Title><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358631205916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:33:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch the movie "Piecefull Warrior". Great movie!</Msg><Username>barbing1965</Username><Timestamp>1358714104691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:35:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358714614185-80</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's the short, simplified answer (the details are much more complex). Boeing wants to stop offering the pension to new hires. What's to not like you're thinking. If you're a current employee, it doesn't affect you. Oh yes it does. There's a long, well documented history in this country of the process used by companies and corporations when they want out of the "pension business". Step 1 is to stop offering the pension to new employees. Step 2 is to FREEZE the pension for all existing employees. Sometimes there's also Step 3, which is to sell off the pension fund and the pension obligation to some insurance company somewhere who usually turns it into an annuity. If you want to put an important part of your retirement at risk, if you want to see it drastically reduced or possibly disappear completely, that's a sure fire way to do it. I know people that have had this happen to them and I've had a lot of experience with insurance companies (had to hire an attorney and sue the last one to get them to fulfill their obligation). I don't want my pension frozen and I don't want an insurance company, ANY insurance company, anywhere near my retirement. They cannot be trusted with anything, at any time, and the same is true of Boeing Corporate. If Boeing wants out of the "pension business", then they need to alleviate that concern by putting the necessary language in the contract so that existing employee's are protected from this very real threat. About that 401K Boeing wants to offer new hires in place of the pension ... Boeing's own calculations show that it's worth 33% less than the pension. SPEEA's calculations put the difference at 40%. Regardless of the number, that's a BIG reduction in benefits for a company that just recently gave its executives bonuses equal to their yearly salary (read that, hundreds of thousands if not millions of dollars per executive). Do you think Boeing's executives would agree to such a reduction in THEIR retirement? Bet not. There's a LOT more to what Boeing wanted to do to us, but SPEEA's negotiation teams finally got them to back off most of it. Still, the pension issue remains and I for one am not voting to put an important part of my retirement at risk. Now, if you want to lead by example, spin the Roulette wheel on your retirement and show us all how there's really nothing to be concerned about, show us all how a multi-national corporation like Boeing would never do such a thing to its employees (history strongly suggests otherwise by the way), by all means go ahead. We'll be watching, with great interest. Many of us, myself included, have worked for Boeing not years but decades and we know better. They have taught us well. And you? How long have you worked for Boeing? Thought so ...</Msg><Username>vierzig_nachten</Username><Timestamp>1358714614185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:43:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358715731790-81</Id><Topic><Title>NBC Special Report: No assault rifle was used at Sandy Hook</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358714045776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>said it a few days ago...no lie is too bold now....SANDY HOOKJ DID NOT GO DOWN AS CIA/CNN said....Usual script..I was called a wackjob for even suggesting the assault rifle not used.. Of course there is an agenda.....before they can rob whats left of our pension funds and go to a cashless society to track everything we do, shut off the itnernet and put RFID chips in our kids....they HAVE to take the guns.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358715731790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:02:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358715795768-82</Id><Topic><Title>A common denominator of all the Mass shootings</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713372748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:22:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right and WHY do you think psychotropic drugs are being used by all the shooters.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358715795768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:03:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358716149704-83</Id><Topic><Title>A common denominator of all the Mass shootings</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713372748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:22:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because the pyschotropic drugs shred your molecules apart and make you see the truth in essence Re: A common denominator of all the Mass shootings :guns/bulletts/no love</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358716149704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:09:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358716457883-84</Id><Title>We play by the rules...</Title><Msg>of war</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358716457883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:14:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358716886216-85</Id><Topic><Title>Vatican Welcomes Obama Gun Control Proposal</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358713420749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:23:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when you have the Catholic Church on your side even if not Jesus it helps Helps! knock at his door and he let's you in</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358716886216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:21:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358717329942-86</Id><Title>A Call to Action</Title><Msg>This message is to all of the American workers that build the Boeing 787. Boeing workers are some of the smartest people in the American Work Force, weather you are a previous Rockwell, Mc Donnell Douglas or Hughes Aircraft employee. You can take pride in the products you have made. We have some of the smartest people in the industry working at Boeing. Yes there may be times when the employees and management don’t see eye to eye such as when negotiating for pay and benefits. But let me say that I speak for myself and many more of the Boeing workers that we will always produce our products so that our families and neighbors will always be proud of us. The attempt is always to make the best products that man is capable of making, and since many of these products are complicated to make, there will always be some hiccups here and there. But we are the American work force, and will always take pride in our work. Anyone wishing the Boeing Company harm will ultimately be disappointed. The workers at the Boeing Company will solve these issues, and most likely many more in the future. A proud Boeing Worker</Msg><Username>jigbuild</Username><Timestamp>1358717329942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358718476985-87</Id><Topic><Title>Can Boeing Trust SPEEA</Title><Username>phantomfield</Username><Timestamp>1358645060092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:24:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>four fingers and two thumbs on each hand with marginal markings = you stay in the unadopted kitty house even if free new at carl's jr the mega cheesy sirloin burger our house is a very,very fine house we have two four-toed black cats with eyes green as the summer lawn a pair of Norwegian forrest cats with good markings and a cat-carrier/vector should FT. Detrrick inquire</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358718476985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:47:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358718634131-88</Id><Topic><Title>We play by the rules...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358716457883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:14:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>which are ?</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358718634131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:50:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358718654243-89</Id><Topic><Title>We play by the rules...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358716457883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:14:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>defined by the rules...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358718654243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:50:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358718739951-90</Id><Topic><Title>NBC Special Report: No assault rifle was used at Sandy Hook</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358714045776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple acid test Dik...Google "Internet Kill switch"..or google "children expelled in texas for refusing RFID bracelet" etc etc ...Id post the link myself but Yahoo has already been strongarmed into getting rid of links.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358718739951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:52:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358718820529-91</Id><Topic><Title>NBC Special Report: No assault rifle was used at Sandy Hook</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358714045776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure you're thrilled that the truth came out. You would have believed that bazookas were used if it had come from Obama. Skepticism is preferable to brainwashed fanaticism like yours. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358718820529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:53:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358719108934-92</Id><Topic><Title>We play by the rules...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358716457883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:14:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jets on the moon...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358719108934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:58:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358719516253-93</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB caving in to Boeing</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358705457773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There seems to be nothing that Boeing won't do, no line that can not be crossed. One would think the NTSB would be the bridge too far, but know. These SO B Itches know no bounds. The concept Boeing is trying to apply is 'faster cheaper better'. That concept requires the acceptance that there will be failures and losses and you have to accept .</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358719516253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:05:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358719611617-94</Id><Topic><Title>A common denominator of all the Mass shootings</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713372748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:22:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think they will ever do a remake of the Wizard of Oz?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1358719611617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:06:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358720006290-95</Id><Title>BA Stock Up or Down tomorrow?</Title><Msg>Is it up or down tomorrow morning? By how much?</Msg><Username>ymsz</Username><Timestamp>1358720006290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:13:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358720041658-96</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Reaches Endgame, Culmination Of Decade Of Problems With 'Nightmareliner'</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358560772061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are other things that are popping up, fuel line fitting, and others, But things may not be so sweet for Boeing investors. That’s because the learning curve effects that investors expected for the 787 are not happening as fast at Boeing has said. More specifically, UBS analyst, David Strauss believes it will take Boeing until 2021, rather than 2015 — as Boeing predicts – to breakeven on the 787, according to the New York Times. Boeing told that Times on December 10 that it “remains confident [that it will earn] low single digit” profit margins on the first 1,100 planes, which includes deliveries into 2021. Strauss calls foul on that. He thinks the 787 will lose between $4 billion and $5 billion on the 787 over the next three years or it will take until 2021 to start making a profit on the 787, if ever. While the basic model – the 787-8 lists for $206.8 million, Strauss estimates that Boeing is charging early customers about $116 million — it costs Boeing 400 million to produce each plane leaving it with a $300 million loss on each 787 it makes. Could Boeing achieve its far more ambitious profit targets? Not likely since the problems keep the plane from doing anythinbg except losing money for Boeing sharesholders.In the meantime, there is an important lesson here for strategists and investors — learning curve effects don’t magically happen. They have to be managed aggressively. And judging by the way Boeing Management has flubbed the 787 so far, and so far been able to prove does not have the management chops to fix the 787′s technical glitches and earn back its shareholder, customer and the public's trust</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358720041658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:14:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358720192098-97</Id><Topic><Title>A common denominator of all the Mass shootings</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713372748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:22:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would appear now that psychotropic drugs were involved in Obama, Biden and most posters here believing that a ban on assault rifles would have prevented the Sandy Hook shootings. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358720192098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:16:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358720392626-98</Id><Topic><Title>A common denominator of all the Mass shootings</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358713372748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:22:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apparently Hennesy aka James Coburn bit the dust WHILE TRYING TO TAKE-OUT THE PILL BOX BOOM</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358720392626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:19:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358720393640-99</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so will this latest 787 problem be compensated as a bonus for the boeing CEO or will the refusal to bargain with his workforce mean more bonus for the CEO, for holding the line on his workers pension, while the CEO demonstrated the need by taking almost 20% yearly gain in wage, bonus and pension for himself</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358720393640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:19:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358720642023-100</Id><Title>It would have been easy to kill Adam Lanza and save the children at Sandy Hook</Title><Msg>Lanza had no body armor but didn't need any as he was protected by the fact that this was a gun free zone. This seems to be a common denominator in all these shootings as criminals always seem choose gun free zones for mass killings.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358720642023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:24:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358720940756-101</Id><Topic><Title>We play by the rules...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358716457883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:14:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SOME PEOPLE DISAGREE WITH CHRIST but then we try to make them No More with LOVE</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358720940756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358720995706-102</Id><Topic><Title>We play by the rules...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358716457883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:14:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and algerians</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358720995706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:29:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358721906305-103</Id><Title>it is not their eyes, their skin color, nor their brain-pan size</Title><Msg>so what is it Jesus ?</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358721906305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:45:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358722152963-104</Id><Topic><Title>NBC Special Report: No assault rifle was used at Sandy Hook</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358714045776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another "Prohecy of Spartacus." Wow. I'm underwhelmed.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1358722152963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358722156294-105</Id><Title>Boeing 787 memo and the Ford Pinto memo both fire starter deals for the passengers -</Title><Msg>According to a 1977 Mother Jones article by Mark Dowie, Ford allegedly was aware of the design flaw, refused to pay for a redesign, and decided it would be cheaper to pay off possible lawsuits. The magazine obtained a cost-benefit analysis that it said Ford had used to compare the cost of $11 repairs against the cost of settlements for deaths, injuries, and vehicle burnouts. The document became known as the Ford Pinto Memo.----[Boeing had to prove to the FAA that these batteries would never ignite as part of the 787 certification and if they did ignite they would not explode. Federal Aviation Administration 14 CFR Part 25 [Docket No. NM375 Special Conditions No. 25-359-SC]. I guess fire is ok then ! same deal cost compared to safety sure it is safe right ! If it is a Boeing 787 (outsourced design and not a SPEEA 100% managed design, then it is not a boeing plane and I am not going to get on the firestarter or drive to the airport in a pinto.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358722156294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358722171794-106</Id><Title>Would Adam Lanza have made it into the Obama girls' school?</Title><Msg>Sure he would have if it were a gun free zone. But since it is not a gun free zone and there are twelve armed security officers in the school that the Obama girls attend, the answer is that he would have not made it into the school alive.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358722171794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358722607889-107</Id><Topic><Title>BA Stock Up or Down tomorrow?</Title><Username>ymsz</Username><Timestamp>1358720006290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:13:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll bet you $100 that it stays flat tomorrow. My guess is it will close at $75.04</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358722607889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:56:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358722745125-108</Id><Topic><Title>Have they reached their $2 billion in share buybacks yet?</Title><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614513537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:55:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>punt</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358722745125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:59:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358723029355-109</Id><Title>So there we are...</Title><Msg>dead rasvens,,,, if</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358723029355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:03:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358723777983-110</Id><Topic><Title>So there we are...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358723029355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:03:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing has much character. Boeing is going to kick some serious butt. It's all about the technology!</Msg><Username>defense_junky</Username><Timestamp>1358723777983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358724434841-111</Id><Topic><Title>Would Adam Lanza have made it into the Obama girls' school?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358722171794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not armed gaurds, they are a secret service detail same as for EVERY PRESIDENT. The more you wing nuts argue and more comparisons you make the dumber and dumber you sound.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1358724434841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:27:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358724709149-112</Id><Topic><Title>Buy or Sell?</Title><Username>ymsz</Username><Timestamp>1358635130915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:38:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When investing why take risky bets? If they can't figure this out quikly or if it a major electrical system design problem your investment is at great risk. Boeing started a buy back program last week and THAT is what is keeping the price up last week.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1358724709149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:31:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358724773906-113</Id><Topic><Title>Would Adam Lanza have made it into the Obama girls' school?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358722171794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's difficult to believe ali_infesto could get any dumber than he sounds. But I guess there is always a chance.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1358724773906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:32:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725106487-114</Id><Topic><Title>NBC Special Report: No assault rifle was used at Sandy Hook</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358714045776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you so obsessed with his posts? Is it because you haven't been able to win a debate with him yet?</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1358725106487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:38:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725144992-115</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB caving in to Boeing</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358705457773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, please, what is your problem? After a year and a half and 50,000 hours of flying time they have an issue with a battery and you claim they are somehow trying to scam us? Are you another disgruntled, fired Boeing employee like Dell/Fred/Wayne with an ax to grind or what? Please take your meds and go back to bed. Is there any company or agency that pleases you?</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1358725144992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:39:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358725497817-116</Id><Title>there is half the problem</Title><Msg>bustin' off alcatraz with a spoon greg rolle treat a couple years later honey don;t</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358725497817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:44:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725739314-117</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 memo and the Ford Pinto memo both fire starter deals for the passengers -</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358722156294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya, Dell, I'm sure Boeing knew the battery had a problem and asked is it cheaper to fix the battery or pay for an airplane full of people going down! Are you really that dumb? And please, don't fly on this airplane, as I really wouldn't to take a chance on being seated next to you!</Msg><Username>custerisus</Username><Timestamp>1358725739314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:48:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358726038165-118</Id><Topic><Title>there is half the problem</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358725497817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"bustin' off alcatraz with a spoon...z" read it in the newspaper eating Kellog Corn-Flakes... on my way to school</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358726038165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:53:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358726339286-119</Id><Topic><Title>Would Adam Lanza have made it into the Obama girls' school?</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358722171794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is from the school web site: Special Police Officer Posted: August 10, 2012 Sidwell Friends School, a coeducational Quaker day school located in the Tenleytown area of Washington, DC, is seeking a full-time Special Police Officer. The ideal candidate will have above average computer skills and knowledge to assist security officers with security systems, reports on line, access control systems, video retention, camera surveillance and training of officers on maximum computer use for daily activities. Applicants must have a current SPO license; have the ability to pass criminal background checks &amp; drug/alcohol testing. The ideal candidate will have the ability to write clear concise reports, prepare preliminary investigative reports, as well as interview witnesses, suspects &amp; victims. This is a full-time hourly position which include free parking, lunch and an attractive benefits package, with retirement plan inclusive of employer match. Mail, fax, or email resume, information for three references and a copy of your current driver's &amp; Special Police Officer licenses to: HR@sidwell.edu Who qualifies as a Special Police Officer in DC? Use DC for example. There are close to 4,000 private police officers currently. They work for security companies who do business with the metropolitan police dept. I believe the one wishing to obtain the license must perform similar training and tests that sworn officers do, such as weapons training, through the dc police. I'm fairly certain the DC license entitles you to carry a weapon and make arrests (provided you are doing so under federal, state, and local laws). But as I said, these rights and your jurisdiction vary from state to state, 10 of which do not govern private security companies at all. If you are actually attempting to receive a license, a private company is the way to go.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358726339286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358726763693-120</Id><Topic><Title>there is half the problem</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358725497817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not really cut across Dr Booortz;s front yard past the Intel fpounders top of the hill hop skip and jump using the hypotenuesuese of the triangle theorem just to get to skool ligtht my fire</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358726763693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:06:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358727241400-121</Id><Title>Pall Mall</Title><Msg>...oh well eat ravens :par boiled and plucked turnip and cabbage</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358727241400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:14:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358727643078-122</Id><Title>Allop</Title><Msg>we have made it past most french thingsd and on our way to to blow gerermany to hell thnnx to thee battle of the bulge losers should we get some support beep hell is not made for heroes beep... from the moon... WE AS IN US R ON R WAY</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358727643078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:20:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358727973831-123</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the view again into that devoid soul. Enjoy your sad, empty, vacuous "life." Now it's time to thank the parents again for the values they instilled in me.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1358727973831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:26:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358728097285-124</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 memo and the Ford Pinto memo both fire starter deals for the passengers -</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358722156294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>custerisus, Agree with you strongly. Safety is more important than anything else.</Msg><Username>ngengee</Username><Timestamp>1358728097285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:28:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358728275110-125</Id><Topic><Title>Don't count Boeing out.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358646251322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:44:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They seem to be sure it's not an overcharging issue now. The batteries have a monitor almost like their own black box to confirm how much electricity passes and when.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1358728275110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:31:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358728301219-126</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB caving in to Boeing</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358705457773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>h_1, good to know. Thanks for the info.</Msg><Username>ngengee</Username><Timestamp>1358728301219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:31:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358729280077-127</Id><Title>INTERATIVE BA</Title><Msg>stuck inside these 4 walls maqy heaven help them if I ever get outta here corner of pacific ocean and the usa beep an beep yeah band on the run</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358729280077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:48:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358729725287-128</Id><Title>Lets get back to Boeing</Title><Msg>My pilot buddy who still works for a carrier I flew for and is a captain on the 777, and his wife who is a flight attendant told me the following. His buddies flying the 787 said it's the greatest plane they have ever flown. His wife who has flown as a flight attendant numerous times on the 787 said it's the best plane she has ever been on. Her comments were, #1 it is the smoothest plane in turbulance. #2 it takes off and climbs like your in an elevator. # 3 the passengers and crew love the 787. My buddy and his friends have mixed ideas on the battery problem. Bad battery, overcharging, charging malfunctions etc. The volt had a number of bad batteries. Could this be the same?? There are a lot of players in this game. The U.S., Japan, Boeing and China all have everything to lose if this problem is not solved soon. So what does this tell you? World wide they have the best minds working on this problem. It's only a matter of time and the 787 will fly again.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358729725287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:55:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358729903046-129</Id><Topic><Title>Don't count Boeing out.</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358646251322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:44:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know what is wrong and I'm not telling you. You will find out very soon.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358729903046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:58:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358730460703-130</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Boeing Site Services Director, Phila. is a disgrace, IMHO she is the worst in 40 years. she is being credited by Rick M with cleaning house. Twenty-five percent of her department (discussed with her) have taken positions in Charleston, some have been moved to management by Ric M. Does she have to sign the Ethics letter?</Msg><Username>vampyrr</Username><Timestamp>1358730460703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:07:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358730715410-131</Id><Topic><Title>Lets get back to Boeing</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358729725287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:55:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Understanding the pre takeoff charging is a key. In each case it was an APU charge prior to takeoff and on the ground in Boston. Yes, bad batteries could be a problem as well. Japan is dragging it's feet, knowing fully well that their countries battery company may be at fault. There are so many companies that could be at fault for this problem it is overwhelming. Time will tell. Every present operator of the 787 and future buyers are clamering to get this aircraft back in the air. Everyone want's it NOW.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358730715410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:11:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358731742844-132</Id><Topic><Title>We don't need no Stinking Batteries in Airplanes</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358709827027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:23:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... or spinning hamster wheels. LOL</Msg><Username>kipparoo2002</Username><Timestamp>1358731742844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:29:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358731901905-133</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do not reply to infester. Represents what is truly despicable about the country now.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1358731901905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:31:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358732226796-134</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Although pity may be confused with compassion, empathy, commiseration, condolence or sympathy (things I do value), pity is different from all of these. Nietzsche pointed out that since all people to some degree value self-esteem and self-worth, pity can negatively affect any situation. Additionally, pity may actually be psychologically harmful to the pitied: Self-pity and depression can sometimes be the result of the power imbalance fostered by pity, sometimes with extremely negative psychological and psycho-social consequences for the pitied party." You're not mindful enough to know the difference.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358732226796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:37:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358732506231-135</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this all so you can justify being a mooch to yourself?</Msg><Username>whrutter</Username><Timestamp>1358732506231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:41:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358732800421-136</Id><Topic><Title>Lets get back to Boeing</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358729725287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:55:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>laylow, Maybe not everybody wants the 787 to fly now before the problems are fixed. It is a good luxury plane alright, but too many un-needed luxuries, therefore too many problems. People seem to forget the purpose of an airplane, and demand more &amp; more complicated features onboard. That's no good. The purpose of an airplane is to get to Point-B fast. So, why need so many modifications for ? Just build it the old reliable way. Too much changes maybe not a good thing !!</Msg><Username>lnmkwan</Username><Timestamp>1358732800421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:46:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358732927629-137</Id><Topic><Title>Allop</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358727643078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:20:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>beep no lithium-ion batteries on the moon beep</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358732927629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:48:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358732969600-138</Id><Topic><Title>Vatican Welcomes Obama Gun Control Proposal</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358713420749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:23:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Opus Dei, Knights Templar, Illuminati and Skull and Bones welcome the plan as well.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358732969600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:49:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358732983403-139</Id><Topic><Title>We don't need no Stinking Batteries in Airplanes</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358709827027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:23:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That battery was made by a company in Arizona, right ?</Msg><Username>lnmkwan</Username><Timestamp>1358732983403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:49:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358733095810-140</Id><Topic><Title>Lets get back to Boeing</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358729725287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:55:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same thing with cars, the more simple the better.</Msg><Username>lnmkwan</Username><Timestamp>1358733095810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358733165717-141</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>James h You guys all need to get together and have a pity party for yourselves I think you've earned it for not knowing the difference between compassion and pity. What did pitying someone ever accomplish? A person who pities others is a person who looks down on others. Your judgment of me bathed in total ignorance about the negative consequences of pity are what is wrong with this country.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358733165717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:52:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358733332170-142</Id><Topic><Title>We don't need no Stinking Batteries in Airplanes</Title><Username>bigovbabe</Username><Timestamp>1358709827027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:23:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The battery is made by GP Yuasa of Japan The battery charge controller is made by Securaplane of Tuscon, Arizona The battery and controller are "subsystem engineered" by Thales Aerospace/Europe The power storage subsystem requriements are systems engineered by Boeing</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1358733332170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:55:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358734593920-143</Id><Title>‘Why me ?’ : Dealing with self-pity from a Buddhist perspective</Title><Msg>I mentioned in another thread that pity/self pity is a useless emotion and a gaggle of defenders of pity showed up. Apparently there are no other studiers of Eastern Philosophy than me on this board. Pity is condescending emotion that leads to negative consequences in one's life and thought patterns. Here is a Buddhist perspective on pity. There are also several books on the Russian philosopher G. I. Gurdjieff who established schools throughout the world that taught the way to a greater mind and higher consciousness should any of you be interested in freeing yourselves from your self imposed cave of victimization and darkness. "Bad things happening to good people, and good things happening to bad people can seem at times paradoxical for those of us who believe in some sort of a natural justice system that’s inbuilt in the way our universe works. After all, it might seem that the only reason for staying moral and righteous is to improve the odds that we encounter less of the undesirable things that constitute ‘suffering’. Only that, it dosen’t always work that way – suffering at times does not seem to discriminate between the good and bad, seemingly oblivious of a moral direction. Without doubt, bad undesirable things would happen to us, in ways that cannot be prevented : such is the nature of randomness of events that is an integral way of how the Universe works. Did the dinosaurs deserve to become extinct by a rogue asteroid (if indeed that’s why mass extinction happened), or did 6 million Jewish people deserve to be killed in the third Reich ? No logical explanation can override the fact, that many of our misfortunes are inevitably random, and no one’s fault. In Buddhism, this category of suffering is often called ‘suffering of suffering’ (1), an allusion to the element of inevitable misfortune at times that the very fact of our existence brings about. “Self-pity is easily the most destructive of the non-pharmaceutical narcotics; it is addictive, gives momentary pleasure and separates the victim from reality.” – John W Gardner One of the central goals of Buddhist practice is to deal with the problem of ‘suffering’ at the fundamental level of our awareness. There are two common routes : one is to adopt the hypothesis of Karma, in which every action of ours, conscious or unconscious, has a ripple effect that spans over multiple life-times, of one individual or many. The notion of Karma and re-birth was used by C. S. Jung to draw parallel to his theory of ‘archetypes’, a dynamic substrata of human experience in which humans are born into, thus giving rise to individual characteristics and psychological traits. (2) The source of these inherited archetypes arises in Jung’s view not from one’s personal Karma, but that from one’s ancestors. Karma in Jung’s view therefore does not have any super-natural elements of any re-incarnating element of human existence, but that of the effective of this ‘collective unconscious archetypes’ on our destinies. In this view therefore, our individual misfortunes and fortunes are just random ripples in a continued river of human consciousness, thus having no individual or personal significance. Our reaction should therefore logically be to counter such suffering with tolerance and forbearance, and make all efforts whenever possible to prevent recurrence of similar suffering to our future generations and also ourselves. In practice an operational understanding of Karma does not relieve suffering without a period of conditioning of our minds based on mindfulness and meditation, developing compassion for all living beings, whether they are more or less fortunate than ourselves. ‘Why me’ gets replaced by the broader concerns of ‘how can suffering be relieved for every being ?’ The second route is far more direct and philosophical, often based upon mystical traditions emphasized especially, but not exclusively, within esoteric teachings. The doctrine of emptiness (Diamond Sutra) for instance aims to replace the mundane concerns of existential suffering with a direct kind of happiness that arises out of an Unified sense of reality with the entire Cosmos, through a direct understanding of the inherently impermanent nature of events and things that we hold on to, to provide us with a false sense of stability and happiness. As the self itself is an impermanent entity, concerns for One’s self that bring unhappiness are perhaps way over-exaggerated. One should indeed work for one’s own welfare (as the Buddha emphasized) but in a manner that places spiritual concerns way before material concerns. One soon realizes that a lot of our suffering is brought about by attempting to cling on to things and states we crave for. ‘Why me ?’ is overshadowed by ‘How we are preventing ourselves from experiencing real happiness by excessive attachment to our petty concerns.’ Although Buddhism influenced psychotherapy is around for help, the Buddhist road to wisdom is essentially designed to be a journey we must experience for ourselves. Life is too short and evanescent for self-pity or continue to cling onto the bars of our psychological prison we impose by putting our own concerns above everybody else’s.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358734593920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:16:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358734804819-144</Id><Topic><Title>NBC Special Report: No assault rifle was used at Sandy Hook</Title><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358714045776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:34:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"haven't been able to win a debate with spartacus yet?" True...When the Raven on its like going hunting...hunting for Wild Bore.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1358734804819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:20:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358735066483-145</Id><Topic><Title>Lets get back to Boeing</Title><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358729725287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:55:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The old reliable planes had issues too, before they were solved.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1358735066483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:24:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358735361526-146</Id><Topic><Title>Ayn Rand is for children</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_333</Username><Timestamp>1358634137344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Jesus had pity on them and touched their eyes; at once they were able to see, and they followed him." Hooz, Jesus was a man nothing more! Are you stupid enough to believe that he made blind people see and dead people rise? You prove to me once again that you are a gullible fanatic. "Jesus can judge you." Well that is preferable to all the idiots on this board judging me. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1358735361526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:29:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358735697804-147</Id><Topic><Title>Allop</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358727643078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:20:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too rich ior charity as we fell into the sun the band on the run</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358735697804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358735763928-148</Id><Topic><Title>Allop</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358727643078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:20:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>must be nucleo-tide batteries on the moon... -the band oin the run</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358735763928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:36:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358736167039-149</Id><Title>No wonder...</Title><Msg>we been stuck frozen since the battle of the bulge oh well, you know how that turned out touch your lips with a magic kiss and you will will be a blue-bird too yeah yeah yeah BA</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358736167039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:42:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358737388990-150</Id><Title>Dreamliner probe widens after excess battery voltage ruled out</Title><Msg>"The NTSB wanted to set the record straight," said one source familiar with the investigation who was not authorized to speak publicly. U.S. safety investigators on Sunday ruled out excess voltage as the cause of a battery fire last month on a Boeing Co 787 Dreamliner jet operated by Japan Airlines Co (JAL) and said they were expanding the probe to look at the system wide failure if true the planes will not fly for a long time and the loss in share value will be huge . U.S. investigators have already examined the lithium-ion battery that powered the APU, where the battery fire started in the JAL plane, as well as several other components removed from the airplane, including wire bundles and battery management circuit boards, the NTSB statement said. Aviation Week quoted Airbus programs chief Tom Williams as saying "failure management" was key and with Boeing’s failed management the shareholders of Boeing have some serious issues with stock price going down meanwhile EADS stock price has gone up over 27% over a year while Boeing shareholders have lost money the stock has been down for over a year now.( .69%)</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358737388990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:03:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358737510358-151</Id><Topic><Title>NTSB caving in to Boeing</Title><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358705457773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:10:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That so called 50,000 hrs. was spread out over a number of test planes. That and fifty AP's now in service. its a drop in a bucket. Did you notice that this discrepancy didn't start occurring until passengers were using the AP's. Using the lighting and entertainment systems and recharging and using all their electronic devices?</Msg><Username>h_iamiam1</Username><Timestamp>1358737510358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:05:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358737662862-152</Id><Topic><Title>No wonder...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358736167039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:42:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>28-29 JAN 13 drop us some Specfifically: the the black cat with the summer greren lawn eyes.... fresh cold water</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358737662862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:07:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358738728394-153</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing Reaches Endgame, Culmination Of Decade Of Problems With 'Nightmareliner'</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358560772061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 20:59:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aviation Week quoted Airbus programs chief Tom Williams as saying "failure management" was key and with Boeing’s failed management has caused the shareholders of Boeing to have some serious issues with stock price going down. Meanwhil a socialistic company, EADS stock price has gone up over 27% over a year while Boeing shareholders have lost money(-.69%) the stock has been down for over a year now. The NTSB said they were expanding the probe to look at the system wide failure, if true the Boeing 787 planes will not fly for a long time and the loss in share value will be huge. Unlike the expert approach Latlow1991, is spinning the problem is too many outsourced parts all with the best minds working on them is the problem this also created the problem , it is a outsourcing failure. How can I tell , the 787 boeing plane is 3.5 years late and 30 billion over budget and now grounded, Mr Laylow1991, needs to learn how to spin a better story or quick the BS</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358738728394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358739297374-154</Id><Topic><Title>Dreamliner probe widens after excess battery voltage ruled out</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358737388990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:03:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"U.S. investigators have already examined the lithium-ion battery that powered the APU, where the battery fire started in the JAL plane, as well as several other components removed from the airplane, including wire bundles and battery management circuit boards, the NTSB statement said." Having worked in the aerospace industry for 35+ years and having participated in hardware and system failure investigations (in this case for satellites) for in-orbit and on-ground failures, I find that it is highly unlikely that government "investigators" (bureaucrats) have arrived at any conclusion that is credible relative to the lithium-ion battery. Especially since the maker of the charge controller, Securaplane, today said that they were not yet involved in the investigation.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1358739297374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358739317593-155</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing 787 memo and the Ford Pinto memo both fire starter deals for the passengers -</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358722156294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:49:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apparently custerisus has no facts just harassment, custerisus refuses to read and respond to the Boeing certification being defective, then makes a personal attack and that is a TOS violation , custerisus is making an excluse up for boeing Management that is called enabling the poor safety standards that Boeing has shown by the grounding of a Boeing and FAA certified plane, the certifications were unsafe custerisus, and all your enabling behavior will not change the facts . get used to it</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358739317593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:35:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358740068875-156</Id><Topic><Title>No wonder...</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358736167039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:42:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and black cats with eyes the color of a green summer lawn yes, them, not us...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358740068875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:47:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358742179874-157</Id><Topic><Title>Boeing stock value compared to Boeing Executive excessive incentive pay</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358631485511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 16:38:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boeing Management wants to take all rights away from workers and go back to the way workers in the USA were treated by the robber barons , They want the state taxpayer breaks, and the taxpayer money that the federal government gives Boeing, and the executives load up the pay of their own pensions and excessive bonus pay by robbing the stock investors. How can I tell, the Boeing company stock price has gone down for one year by -.69% but the Dow Jones average is up 8.51%.</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1358742179874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:22:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358743498213-158</Id><Topic><Title>Have they reached their $2 billion in share buybacks yet?</Title><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358614513537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:55:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>punt</Msg><Username>eucheme</Username><Timestamp>1358743498213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358743772182-159</Id><Topic><Title>Soschi 2014 - well alright</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1352278947632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 04:02:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>frozen tea-pots womens team that is the only way the former USSR will let me in from the west or as jack lemmon and what;s her faces; daughter once said or about ten times que s9ome like it muy caliente</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358743772182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:49:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358744099668-160</Id><Title>elle...</Title><Msg>from BA...</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1358744099668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:54:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>