<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365998680925-1</Id><Topic><Title>Everything they ever told Me was a Lie: Volume 1</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365957386389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's easy, floyd. The NRA is easily the most preposterous and laughable organization in the USA. Members send in their dues, and apparently never realize it is the BIG bucks of arms and ammo manufacturers that determine what NRA lobbying policy will be. What else would explain why the majority of NRA members support universal background checks, like the NRA itself did a decade ago, #$%$ Lapierre now opposes? Except for that, NRA members aren't fools. They just support a preposterous organization. When I think about it, I start chuckling. That probably comes through in my posts -- because you detected it, and God knows you are far from the sharpest knife in the drawer.</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1365998680925</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 00:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366012800665-2</Id><Topic><Title>Our Greatest President born on this date</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365872116253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:55:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems so obvious, nevertheless: well said.</Msg><Username>corned_beef_dude</Username><Timestamp>1366012800665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 04:00:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366013410723-3</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“They call us crazy, but no one — no other organization in the world — has spent more millions over more decades to keep Americans safe,” What a crock. The reality is, no one -- no other organization in the world -- has been responsible for more senseless murders than the NRA.</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1366013410723</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 04:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366018832655-4</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said Chairman Mao........or should we call you Adolph...........you anti-American skum bagg.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366018832655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 05:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366018896763-5</Id><Topic><Title>Everything they ever told Me was a Lie: Volume 1</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365957386389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think YOU are confused again, The Kent Bath House is the laughable organization.</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366018896763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 05:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366018996581-6</Id><Topic><Title>Our Greatest President born on this date</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365872116253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:55:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talking to yourself again?</Msg><Username>david_aames_12</Username><Timestamp>1366018996581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 05:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366019828138-7</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! :))) You're a very funny little repressed #$%$!</Msg><Username>cloroxcowboy</Username><Timestamp>1366019828138</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 05:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366021846357-8</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a pathetic little sissy.</Msg><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1366021846357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 06:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366022299107-9</Id><Topic><Title>Everything they ever told Me was a Lie: Volume 1</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365957386389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:36:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Founding Fathers put the second amendment right behind the first for a reason.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366022299107</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 06:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366022621692-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Kent Raven is orly taint and hooz</Title><Username>floydianslips</Username><Timestamp>1365395848946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 00:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By definition, a leftist is one who reveres the rights of the state over the rights of the individual. Conversely, right wing politics revere the rights of the individual over the rights of the state. Those who do not like the second amendment are by definition, Leftists. Chris Genna as an effeminate and a leftist is not news. Whatever opinions he has, his left leaning sensibilities are plain for all to see. Live by the government, die by the government.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366022621692</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 06:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366023630684-11</Id><Title>How far we have fallen as a Nation !!!</Title><Msg>Earlier this year when a sixth grade lesson plan asked elementary school students to create a communist flag of America, many parents were outraged. But don’t think for a second that it stopped there. In fact, the indoctrination of young minds supported by officials like Attorney General Eric Holder, who once suggested we must brainwash the second amendment out of American schoolchildren, continues without respite. In Jacksonville, Florida, a fourth grade student proves, once again, that progressive leaning educators are actively working to redefine what it means to be an American. The following note was found by the father of a student who recently attended a class in which the kids discussed the U.S. Constitution. “I am willing to give up some of my Constitutional rights in order to be safer or more secure.” give-up-rights (Image courtesy The Daily Sheeple) A Florida father is furious today after finding a note written in crayon in his son’s school book bag about his constitutional rights. … Aaron Harvey stated that when he went through his son’s backpack that he found a note written by his son in crayon reading,“I am willing to give up some of my constitutional rights in order to be safer or more secure.” Harvey reveals that this note was written after his son’s class had recently had a lesson about the U.S. Constitution. … Harvey reveals that he talked to his son about the note, who said his teacher had spoken the sentence out loud and told them to write it down. Harvey said he asked some of his son’s classmates and got a similar answer. … “I am strongly for proper education, for the freedom of thought so you can form your own opinion and have your own free speech in the future… [but] the education is, ‘when was the Constitution drafted, when was it ratified, why did this happen, why did we choose to do this… all these things, why did they particular choose those specific rights to be in our Bill of Rights.’” Examiner via The Daily Sheeple It’s one thing to educ</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366023630684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366023673370-12</Id><Topic><Title>How far we have fallen as a Nation !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366023630684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>educate children and expand their understanding of the various political systems. It’s a completely different matter altogether when progressive educators attempt to mold their minds without giving them the ability to think for themselves. Dictation without discussion is nothing more than brainwashing based on the principle of repeating the same message over and over until the target individual begins to believe it without question. Ronald Reagan once said, “freedom is never more than one generation away from extinction.” There are millions of people right now in America who are working hard to make sure the US Constitution and our rights to life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness go the way of the dinosaurs.</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366023673370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366024424067-13</Id><Title>firearms manufacturers to relocate their operations from gun-hating Connecticut</Title><Msg>At three major firearms manufacturers have announced plans to relocate their operations from Connecticut to another more gun-friendly state following the recent passage of what Connecticut legislators say is “the most far-reaching gun-legislation package in the country.” According to reports, one firearms company has already chosen Texas as its new home, and several others are currently in the selection process. On April 5, CBS DFW reported that Connecticut-based Colt Manufacturing, which manufactures AR-15 style rifles and various other firearms, will soon relocate its manufacturing plant from West Hartford, Conn., to Breckenridge, Texas, a small town located a few hours east of the Dallas metroplex. And just a few days later, Bristol-based PTR made a similar announcement, though the company is not yet sure which state it will choose. “We feel that our industry as a whole will continue to be threatened so long as it remains in a state where its elected leaders have no regard for the rights of those who produce and manufacture its wealth,” reads a recent statement issued by PTR. The Connecticut Valley, after all, has long been a hub for the gun industry, and the area’s rich firearms history dates back as far as the Revolutionary War. “We are making a call to all involved in our industry to leave this state, close your doors and show our politicians the true consequences of their hasty and uninformed actions,” the statement adds. “We encourage those in our industry to abandon this state as its leaders have abandoned the proud heritage that forged our freedom.” Connecticut’s assault on the Second Amendment has the entire firearms industry packing its bags Signed into law by Connecticut Governor Dannel P. Malloy on April 4, Connecticut’s sweeping new gun-control restrictions include universal background checks on all firearms purchases, and the establishment of a gun registration database that restricts who can purchase rifles, shotguns, or ammunition. According to The</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366024424067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366029779936-14</Id><Topic><Title>firearms manufacturers to relocate their operations from gun-hating Connecticut</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366024424067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like all liberals who are committed to their failed religion of liberalism, they make things worse, not better. Now Connecticut loses more business when they already are in debt, and in need of tax dollars. Remember how liberals came up with Cincy Sheehan, the extreme leftist against the war.? Where is she now? They are doing the same thing on gun control...appealing to emotion, and not the facts.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366029779936</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 08:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366030309066-15</Id><Topic><Title>How far we have fallen as a Nation !!!</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366023630684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the farther we fall the happier our deadbeat leftist friends are. That means the need for bigger, and bigger centralized govt that they luv. Self determining people are unwanted enemies of the far left.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366030309066</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 08:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366030372685-16</Id><Topic><Title>firearms manufacturers to relocate their operations from gun-hating Connecticut</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366024424067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I usually do not appreciate these non BA related posts on this board but I have to agree with both posters. Looks like the taxpayers in Conneticut will be taking another hit. HELLO, The Newton parents are being used and your state is going to get milked. You fools!</Msg><Username>rightstuff157</Username><Timestamp>1366030372685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 08:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366031665298-17</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why wouldn't you stick to the facts?</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366031665298</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 09:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366034204382-18</Id><Topic><Title>firearms manufacturers to relocate their operations from gun-hating Connecticut</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366024424067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so where are they moving to-- Mogadishu??? HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR AHR AHR AHR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366034204382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 09:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366034449741-19</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Dell George is it tru that Boeing now has more than 9000 737 aircraft of all types either sold, in manufacture or delivered since 1963??? tell us how many Air Blob hs sold by now HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366034449741</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366034454527-20</Id><Topic><Title>firearms manufacturers to relocate their operations from gun-hating Connecticut</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366024424067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only people being used are the NRA members - get a clue.</Msg><Username>oldbuck56</Username><Timestamp>1366034454527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366035311593-21</Id><Topic><Title>firearms manufacturers to relocate their operations from gun-hating Connecticut</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366024424067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>watsamatta joe dopes dont you like the truth to be known about the evil gun industry which sacrifices more than 20,000 American lives a year in providing and promoting massive gun sales and gun ownership in the United States- you are indeed a mowrawn- a true neanderthal and peopl like you continue to set Western Civilization back not decades but centuries</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366035311593</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366035630590-22</Id><Topic><Title>firearms manufacturers to relocate their operations from gun-hating Connecticut</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366024424067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your fairy tales which you try to bolster Wayne LaPierre's arguments about the futility of barring illegal gun sales is quite simply an evil lie. You think people are as dum b as you are and will believe your lies- If we enlarged the ATF and financed it to the point where we could have gun registration and database, along with owner registration and databases and if we had enough personnell we could stop a large percentage of the gun crimes- maybe half to three quarters of it. People like you and joe dope would be in jail for years every time you broke the gun laws and none of you would be able to get licenses That would be true progress HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR HAR AHR HAR AHR AHR HAR HAR</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366035630590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366036973528-23</Id><Title>ut oh</Title><Msg>NEW YORK/COLORADO SPRINGS, Colorado (Reuters) - U.S. regulators are discussing whether the batteries that burned on Boeing Co's 787 Dreamliner hold any lessons for other aircraft or vehicles. George Nield, associate administrator for commercial space transportation at the Federal Aviation Administration, said a dialogue is taking place about whether the overheating of two lithium-ion batteries on the 787 could have broader implications. "Everyone's looking to see if there are any lessons to be learned from this," Nield told Reuters during a conference hosted by the Space Foundation this week. The discussion marks a shift for the agency. Two months after the Dreamliner was approved for service in 2011, a lithium-ion battery caught fire on a Cessna business jet, prompting the FAA to order that lithium-ion batteries be replaced with less hazardous cells on all of those jets within a week. But the agency concluded there were no broader lessons to be learned for the 787 or other aircraft. Nield, who noted that the International Space Station is among the platforms that use the batteries, said the discussion is different now. "There might not have been a lot (of dialogue) in the past, but I can assure you there will be going forward," Nield said. Read mo http://www.foxbusiness.com/news/2013/04/13/faa-sees-lessons-from-boeing-787-battery-woes/#ixzz2QXk5XMPd</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366036973528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366037017183-24</Id><Title>Lion Air</Title><Msg>Plane has to be cut up to be removed from coral reef. Investigators will be giving serious consideration to wind shear.</Msg><Username>albucucu</Username><Timestamp>1366037017183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366037210499-25</Id><Topic><Title>Our Greatest President born on this date</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365872116253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 12:55:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're being pretty hard on this guy. He's not really smart enough to understand much. You may be judged by how well you treat idiots. There are so many now and they all need to be taken care of.</Msg><Username>zombiegrunt</Username><Timestamp>1366037210499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366037415583-26</Id><Topic><Title>ut oh</Title><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366036973528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps now we understand the reason for the additional 787 flights with FAA onboard. A switch to NiCad batteries?? Hope BA has a plan "B" already in place that provides a non-lion battery alternative. Anyone know the weight difference between the two and the potential extra weight penalty.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366037415583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:50:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366037687957-27</Id><Topic><Title>ut oh</Title><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366036973528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This goes way beyond a simple temp flight restriction for the existing battery system. A total redesign to something akin to NiCad batteries would require design, installation and a new round of flight testing for ETOPS. If this is the direction the FAA chooses stand the &amp;%$# by.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366037687957</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 10:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366038217138-28</Id><Topic><Title>Spazticus</Title><Username>censored50</Username><Timestamp>1365969468490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 15:57:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take your lithium, censored err fascist err bumper.</Msg><Username>demsfascists666</Username><Timestamp>1366038217138</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366039644800-29</Id><Title>Market correction has begun</Title><Msg>Ba under pressure on many fronts. Give me a thumbs down all day long but protect your gains. Don't be sheep. Nothing goes straight up.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366039644800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366040322701-30</Id><Title>Buy the Dips boys$$</Title><Msg>This is there routine morning rump shorts trying to get it down, Keep trying Shorties$$$</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366040322701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366042459965-31</Id><Title>787 flight scheduled for today (Monday)</Title><Msg>BOE5 787 is scheduled to fly again today at San Bernardino according to flightaware.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366042459965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366042613129-32</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What an utterly dumb reply! Druid</Msg><Username>druid.wilson</Username><Timestamp>1366042613129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366042868194-33</Id><Topic><Title>firearms manufacturers to relocate their operations from gun-hating Connecticut</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366024424067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 07:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NR(s)A. Nat'l Rifle (Selling) Association. Has been totally co-opted by business. Lost their way from their sane days.</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1366042868194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366043114091-34</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure what all the fuss is about. I'm a lifelong member of the NRA and support universal background checks 100% especially when these checks can penetrate the HIPPA balloon. Why wouldn't you want to know that your crazy neighbor had to at least go through a background check. As far as 30 round clips go...if you haven't hit anyone in the first 10 shots your probably dead. None of this is offensive to me. Well I'm not liking the national gun registry because from history I know where that list is going.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366043114091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366043215311-35</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight scheduled for today (Monday)</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366042459965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are your thoughts with the changing mood of the FAA and all the add-on flights.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366043215311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:26:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366043382958-36</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are kooks on both sides of the debate I see.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366043382958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366044218475-37</Id><Title>China GDP</Title><Msg>Bad news on our economy because China came out with a bad GDP report. Liberals want to beat up on China demanding they devalue their currency when reality shows we need China to do well as it relates to our economy. Think a liberal could comprehend what would happen to our economy if WalMart shut down, or moved oversees? Libs luv to bash WalMart for selling Chinese imported goods.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366044218475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366044712026-38</Id><Topic><Title>NRA Top Gun sticks to Cause</Title><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1365976466849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's good to hear from an NRA member with sense. As I understood it at one point in the debate, HIPAA could be got around or modified if a person had been ADJUDICATED as mentally unreliable (I don't know if I'm using the right term, but found by a public court or administrative body to be a danger to himself or others) -- not simply a person who had been prescribed Prozac or something. The "adjudication" bit more or less eliminates HIPAA concern for privacy, since his behavior or attitude would already be a subject of "public" (court or admin. hearing or psych eval.) discussion. I agree with you about a national gun registry, but I am not as sure about the details of this. If they want a list of every gun currently owned, that's government intrusion. But if an individual has broken the law or been somehow "adjudicated," I would expect a seach warrant could be executed on that person to record the serial numbers of all his firearms. Maybe even fired to collect ballistic evidence. This is one of the areas of the debate I once said that rational gun owners should be involved in; to simply refuse to particiapte would be to abrogate your rights to the gun lilys. I am a gun owner -- one who sees the need for some sense in ourt gun laws. No right granted by the government is absolute: We have free speech, but can't defame; We have the right to assemble, but not to riot or lynch; we have the right to be secure in our persons in possessions, but not to ignore search warrants. We can travel where we want to when we want to -- but we can't drive faster than about 70 mph :-)</Msg><Username>chris_genna2</Username><Timestamp>1366044712026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:51:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366045923199-39</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>father -zosima, I have always said the 737 is what is making most of the money for Boeing, I know I built them for years and then inspected them. the 787 is what is killing Boeing 33 billion out the door in cheap outsourcing, almost 4 years late and still a decertified plane, Bye the way , were you able to discuss the user comment with your neighbor, you know the one that calls you whistle, remember how impotent you are under your har har har institutional name "whsteffanms on his posts and MSFT, eh! 18-Jun-11 01:42 pm whsteffanms... I was wondering your IP address shows as Everett and you have 4528 update(6039)posts, with almost all of them containing slams and HAR HAR HAR and nothing of any value to anyone, how is it that you get along so well with Paul Allen? eh! Re: Microsoft Shows First Look at Windows 8 Interface VIDEO Whsteffanms said” dell george my address may be Everett, but my mansion is actually located over on Widbey Island( sure it is) and I get back and forth with my yacht( the full size scale model?)- I tie up next to Paul Allen a lot( a lot like never !) down in Elliott bay and confer( wow) with him quite a lot-- how do you like that eh ( just like all your other emails,, har, har , har ) Rating : (No ratings) Rate it: whsteffanms... Male Everett WA</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366045923199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:12:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366046015501-40</Id><Topic><Title>Buy the Dips boys$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366040322701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may wish to look at the history associated with the last major drop in gold prices in 1980 and you may have a different opinion on where the bottom of the dip IS and when to pull the trigger. I buy dips as well but the goal is to buy close to the bottom and that sir looks to be the million dollar question currently.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366046015501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366046326967-41</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hard to get excited about this crash with their safety record. Don't see too much risk to BA except from the sharks in the water. This will be weather and or pilot error. Sully had far less sink rate than this guy had.</Msg><Username>wearesoscrewed</Username><Timestamp>1366046326967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366046931825-42</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight scheduled for today (Monday)</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366042459965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Took off at 10:03 am PDT for a two hour flight.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366046931825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366046955785-43</Id><Title>NSTB focus on lithium battery</Title><Msg>In 2008 it lost a $350 million prototype of a stealthy mini-sub that burned up in a lithium-ion battery fire during routine maintenance. “It’s amazing how the failures are subtle and very unplanned,” Cook said. “Systems fail in ways the designers never envisaged.” for the Boeing Hacks, as I stated last week, in 5 trade days and out up 80% gain on STP and I told you I was short metal, it is down another 9% today. For the record your opinion of Boeing is a gain of 5.5% for 5 years while the stock chart shows a gain of 110% for Airbus use cnn stock charts, go to 5 years BA is Boeing eadsy is Airbus . Boeing Hacks you have a very costly opinion, I have a very profitable stock chart, no opinion needed . very simple you Boeing alter ego boys are opinion and critic experts who make no money. Thanks I really needed to know a almost 4 year late , decertified , 33 billion dollar over cost 787 is flying with no revenue producing passengers today fmh is really a huge joke to the thinking person not to mention sparti</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366046955785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366047012866-44</Id><Topic><Title>Buy the Dips boys$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366040322701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are right but not selling or buying it but waiting to add!!</Msg><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366047012866</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366048049705-45</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>300 mph in shallow water with no casualities the pilot is lucky sully could not have done better, try diving inot a shallow water shore compared to deep water ,plus sully had clear conditions the pilot on the 737 was in a rain storm with wind shear,most likely. Every one got lucky considering the plane crashed if the Boeing Hack somehow think a 737 crash is ok that is just another example of why I am up my short on metal another 9% today and made 80% on STP last week. Boeing Hacks make 5.5% return in 5 years on Boeing while Airbus investors make 110% in 5 years . A Boeing hack is not a stock investor just a lazy fearful opinion time waster .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366048049705</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366048063950-46</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell I know it causes you no end of jealousy to know that I have a mansion on Whidbey Island and have a lot of important guests like Paul Allen, Bill Gates, Steve Balmer and Jim McNerney (when hes in town) over for get togethers. No doubt the fact that in all your years at Renton as a urinal cleanup tech you never met anybody more important that your gai lover boi over there and folks like me get to associate with the truly rich and famous and important</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366048063950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:47:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366048257874-47</Id><Topic><Title>NSTB focus on lithium battery</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366046955785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FMH thanks I really needed to know the de certified , no passenger allowed 787 is still flying around almost 4 years after the fact of expected delivery not working right are you thinking at all? I am glad you occasionally read me, like I care and you get a laugh at me, wow am I hurt, as I make 9% today shorting metal and 80% gain on STP last week, I am hurt I tell you hurt that you get no money from boeing for 5 years that keeps pace with good stocks BA 5.5% return for 5 years Airbus 110% return for 5 years so sorry</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366048257874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366049118768-48</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whstlefanams or father z as you wish, once more your ignorant as usual, and do not know what your talking about , More Cessna 172s have been built than any other aircraft t and the company has fixed their lithium battery issue. So whstle-father Z time to get more advice from your special friend, har your neighbor Paul Allen. Or I can play this game with you all day long , er nope time to move on your back in your ignorant box you go their father har har har the only thing you taught me har har har is har har har</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366049118768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366050589547-49</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here’s Another Hurdle For Boeing’s Top Institutional Shareholders Just when Boeing was cutting the last strands of red tape following its 787 Dreamliner debacle, the Federal Aviation Administration has ordered the examination of some 1,000 Boeing aircraft, due to issues stemming from a faulty component that could cause pilots to lose control of the aircraft if it failed. ”We are issuing this AD (airworthiness directive) to prevent premature failure of the attach pins, which could cause reduced structural integrity of the horizontal stabilizer to fuselage attachment, resulting in loss of control of the airplane,” the FAA said in the directive issued on Monday. the problem could cost Boeing up to $10.1 million to fix, and affects the 737 models of aircraft. _ this is so much fun,,,,playing with OPM</Msg><Username>outoftheblueofthewesternskies</Username><Timestamp>1366050589547</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366050771709-50</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>musta been a helluva ride, er, landing worthy of injury but not death</Msg><Username>outoftheblueofthewesternskies</Username><Timestamp>1366050771709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366051413935-51</Id><Topic><Title>Buy the Dips boys$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366040322701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>didn't gold from $800 back to ? smell the fear</Msg><Username>outoftheblueofthewesternskies</Username><Timestamp>1366051413935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366051846564-52</Id><Topic><Title>China GDP</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366044218475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:43:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I tried the grocery shopping experience at a Walmart super center. Despite massive shelf shortages, long check-out lines lines, and poor produce...it totally grossed me out. You get what you pay for. Cina is like old S. Korea which is like old Japan, but china dint lose war....yet...</Msg><Username>outoftheblueofthewesternskies</Username><Timestamp>1366051846564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366051860825-53</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep stay our of Boeing the CEO has been raiding BA shareholder OPM for years and giving back only 5.5% in 5 years. Better off making your own money buy using a stock chart . A second way to increase your loss of your own money is listen to opinions fo the Boeing Hacks like FMH or the total brain dead worthless users like Father whstle or the custer or the semi intelligent but poor traders like sparti tell me about that stock you tossed up to me that was not a a real stock eh , the Boeing Hacks , that play around all day long. Between trades I like to comment as I am making short term gain today is a great short day and a buy the dip day for a few stock . How is that 787 decertified d plane doing today FMH we all just ned to know what a joke, BTW last week I pointed out I was short metals today I was up 9% make that 10% now</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366051860825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366052106120-54</Id><Topic><Title>Buy the Dips boys$$</Title><Username>tucsonlighting747</Username><Timestamp>1366040322701</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good one the 747 in the handle indicates a Boeign Hack who does not trade he is a dog and poney opinion guy facts BA up 5.5% in 5 years Airbus up 110% in 5 years opinions don't count a stock chart does count last week I pointed out I was short metals and today I am up another 10% on my short it is simple read a stock chart or opinion your money away and stay clear of Boeing it is a dead cat bounce stock not a long or a short just a big risk at least put yoru money in a FDIC insuraed bank if you cant read a stock chart .</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366052106120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366052316342-55</Id><Topic><Title>NSTB focus on lithium battery</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366046955785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hello sparti and Boeing hacks my short on silver is now over 10% gain for me today can you say Boeing decertified 787 ouch and bark</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366052316342</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 14:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366054037163-56</Id><Topic><Title>China GDP</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366044218475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:43:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Certain things, i suppose you get elsewhere, put our Walmart market is highly shopped. Much of the produce is the same everywhere, bundled, and wrapped. And ours has lots of checkouts...actually we have two WalMarts, but you grocery shop at low volume shopper time. I never have a problem. Price is a huge key. And fixed income folks have to stretch their disposable dollars farther which is harder, and harder to do when Obama takes much of it.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366054037163</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366054141063-57</Id><Topic><Title>58% of Americans see a 30% drop of stock index in 2013</Title><Username>spcrash</Username><Timestamp>1366040294735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 11:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least 58&amp; of Americans are low level information Obama supporters. That means nothing. As long as Obama trashes every other investment like he has, the stock market will continue to go up.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366054141063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366055635241-58</Id><Topic><Title>NSTB focus on lithium battery</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366046955785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 13:29:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as a direct shot at the Boeing Hacks the reason i mentioned I was short on silver and gold last week and told you" boye friends " it was too late for you, most shorts today can not short any any gold or silver stocks, it is call HDB no more short stocks are available. So for you Boeing Hacks , I have been short for 3 weeks now, so the one thing I have learned from you Boeing Hacks is the sarcasm so here it is! har har har today you no longer can short. And I am set for the bottom and the gains on shorting As I told you Boeing Hacks last week , it was too late for you to short I told you after the market was closed. I am up approximately 50% now on my shorts So here is all your Boeing Hacks have been able to teach me sarcasm, like whstle father z ---- har har har --- and is the decertified 787 flying today ----fmh---,sparti you cant even pick a stock that exsists to try to harass me me that is so sad, So father Z whistle you need to rtalk to yoru neighbor and personal friend , . Paul Allen and by all means use your big boat to visit him too what a joke on yourself BA down 2% today</Msg><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1366055635241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366055648728-59</Id><Title>This article was sent to 9,945 people who get email alerts on BA - what lies ahead</Title><Msg>One of the reasons that the company's shares remain unfazed from the events like safety concerns about the battery is the strong demand from its Asian clients. seeking alpha A surge in the number of orders: Boeing was successful in winning some major orders coming from the emerging economies. Turkish Airlines ordered 70 737 planes from Boeing and has an additional plan to buy 20 B737-800 jets, 65 B737-8 MAX aircraft and 10 B737-9 MAX planes. Boeing took an order of about 805 airplanes, worth $66 billion and delivered 477, worth $33 billion, during year 2012. In comparison, Airbus got an order for 1,419 (worth $70 billion) and delivered 534 of them (worth $32 billion). Therefore, in terms of the number of orders, Airbus is quite ahead but total value earned is greater for Boeing. Additionally, Boeing booked 14 firm orders for 737 jets from Sberbank Leasing, a part of Sberbanl Russia (AKSJF) and two from an undisclosed buyer. Boeing said its net orders for the 737 stand at 153 so far this year. The number of orders the company gains becomes a major boost for investor confidence in the company's stock. Fundamentals: Boeing has sound fundamentals that support the performance of its stock in the long term. With the price-to-earnings ratio at around 17, which is one of the highest amongst the industry players, this stock has maintained its price level to give its investors sufficient return. Factoring in the growth rate to its P/E, its PEG stands positive at 1. P/S of 0.8 shows the company has been able to maintain a healthy price level in comparison to its sales value. Industry dynamics and Boeing's innovation This industry is affected by various factors like fuel price, economic growth, environmental regulation and alternative modes of transportation. Boeing has been innovative enough to respond to the changes in these factors. With the rise in the fuel price, the company came up with more fuel-efficient airplanes such as the 787 and 737 MAX. This industry is</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1366055648728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366055912286-60</Id><Title>Dems quickly introduce bill to set limit of one bomb per marathon</Title><Msg>And, of course, it would first have to be registered</Msg><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1366055912286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366056195965-61</Id><Topic><Title>China GDP</Title><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366044218475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:43:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IAM sure yours has many checkouts, 1/20th which are staffed. Prices on most grocery items equaled or bettered by others. But if you need a mouse pad, an air filter, tire chains, some light bulbs, a hunting knife, some Slim-Jims, acheap turtlew enck made in China, and a Blow and Go all at the same place then Wally-mart may be for you. Otherwise I would stay away from their house-brand STUFF lol</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1366056195965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366056508533-62</Id><Topic><Title>Dems quickly introduce bill to set limit of one bomb per marathon</Title><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1366055912286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gov't conspiacy - all ken yans already finished and left</Msg><Username>db0865</Username><Timestamp>1366056508533</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:08:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366056747743-63</Id><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Msg>One person being forced to serve the needs of another man = involuntary servitude Involuntary servitude = Slavery Democrat's Motto = "From each according to his ability to each according to his needs." Democrat's motto = Advocating slavery.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366056777323-64</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does the girl with the dragon tattoo come too ?</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1366056777323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366056930078-65</Id><Title>Boston marathon bombing totally chickenshid</Title><Msg>maybe can blame on some chubby security guard like at the Atlanta Olympics</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1366056930078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366057416558-66</Id><Title>Obama will Save Us From Everything...He's a pillar of Strength</Title><Msg>Obama will reason with the terrorists.........I mean ........shucks.......their reasonable lunatics.</Msg><Username>jeepcreep111</Username><Timestamp>1366057416558</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366058077588-67</Id><Topic><Title>Dems quickly introduce bill to set limit of one bomb per marathon</Title><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1366055912286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Democrats want universal background checks on anyone who wants to purchase electrical wiring?</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366058077588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366058086259-68</Id><Title>chinook milestone</Title><Msg>RIDLEY TOWNSHIP, Pa., April 15, 2013 -- Boeing recently completed the first flight of the newest CH-47 Chinook heavy-lift helicopter for the United Kingdom's Royal Air Force. The March 15 flight, at the Boeing helicopter facility near Philadelphia, happened ahead of schedule and confirmed initial airworthiness for the Mk6 Chinook. "This is a truly impressive achievement for both Boeing and the project team," said Capt. David Childs, Chinook Team Leader, UK Defence Equipment &amp; Support. "To see the first aircraft fly less than 20 months after contract signature is a source of great pride for all those involved in this key project." The Mk6 Chinook features advanced technology including UK-specific avionics, a forward-looking infrared system, and interoperable communication and navigation equipment. It is undergoing comprehensive testing in Mesa, Ariz., before delivery to the UK later this year.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366058086259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366058715262-69</Id><Topic><Title>Boston marathon bombing totally chickenshid</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1366056930078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:15:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Centennial Olympic Park bombing Centennial Olympic Park was designed as the "town square" of the Olympics, and thousands of spectators had gathered for a late concert by the band Jack Mack and the Heart Attack. Sometime after midnight, Rudolph planted a green U.S. military ALICE pack (field pack) containing three pipe bombs surrounded by nails underneath a bench near the base of a concert sound tower. He then left the area. The pack had a directed charge and could have done more damage but it was slightly moved at some point.[2] It used a steel plate as a directional device.[3] Investigators were later to tie the Sandy Springs and Otherside bombs together with this first device because all were propelled by nitroglycerin dynamite, used an alarm clock and Rubbermaid containers, and contained steel plates.[4] Chubbu ecurity guard Richard Jewell discovered the bag and alerted Georgia Bureau of Investigation officers. Jewell and other security guards began clearing the immediate area so that a bomb squad could investigate the suspicious package. Alice Hawthorne, 44, of Albany, Georgia, was killed in the explosion when a nail from the bomb penetrated her skull. A Turkish cameraman, Melih Uzunyol, 40, had a heart attack while running to the scene.[5] The bomb wounded 111 others. As the park reopened following the bombing. President Bill Clinton denounced the explosion as an "evil act of terror" and vowed to do everything possible to track down and punish those responsible.[6] Despite the event, officials and athletes agreed that the games should continue as planned. [edit] Richard Jewell falsely implicated Main article: Richard Jewell Though Richard Jewell was hailed as a hero for his role in discovering the bomb and moving spectators to safety, four days after the bombing, and shortly after a brief, mistaken detainment of two juvenile persons of interest at the Kensington MARTA station, news organizations reported that Jewell wa</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1366058715262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366059022958-70</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are free to leave the country, any time you want. That alone means you are as far from a slave as it gets. Of course your brain is so fried, you will never understand this.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1366059022958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366059484526-71</Id><Topic><Title>Boston marathon bombing totally chickenshid</Title><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1366056930078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:15:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Though Richard Jewell was hailed as a hero for his role in discovering the bomb and moving news organizations reported that Jewell was considered a potential suspect in the bombing. Jewell, at the time, was unknown to authorities, and a lone wolf profile made sense to FBI investigators after being contacted by his former employer at Piedmont College. Though he was never arrested or named as more than a "person of interest", Jewell's home, where he lived with his mother, was searched and his background exhaustively investigated, all amid a media storm that had cameras following him to the grocery store. Eventually, Jewell was exonerated, and once again hailed as a hero. After his exoneration, Jewell filed a series of lawsuits against the media outlets which he claimed had libeled him, primarily NBC News and The Atlanta Journal-Constitution, and insisted on a formal apology from them. Jewell's attorneys contend Piedmont College President Raymond Cleere called the FBI and spoke to the Atlanta newspapers, providing them with false information on Jewell and his employment there as a security guard. Jewell's lawsuit accused Cleere of describing Jewell as a "badge-wearing zealot" who "would write epic police reports for minor infractions."[7] [edit] Eric Robert Rudolph Main article: Eric Robert Rudolph After Jewell was cleared, the FBI admitted it had no other suspects, and the investigation made little progress until early 1997, when two more bombings took place at an abortion clinic and a lesbian nightclub, both in the Atlanta area. Similarities in the bomb design allowed investigators to conclude that this was the work of the same perpetrator. One more bombing of an abortion clinic, this time in Birmingham, Alabama, which killed a policeman working as a security guard and seriously injured nurse Emily Lyons, gave the FBI crucial clues including a partial license plate. The plate and other clues led the FBI to identify Eric Robert Rudolph as a suspect. Rudolph eluded capture and became a fugitive; officials believed he had disappeared into the rugged southern Appalachian Mountains, familiar from his youth. On May 5, 1998, the FBI named him as one of its ten most wanted fugitives and offered a $1,000,000 reward for information leading directly to his arrest. On October 14, 1998, the Department of Justice formally named Rudolph as its suspect in all four bombings. After more than five years on the run, Rudolph was arrested on May 31, 2003, in Murphy, North Carolina. On April 8, 2005, the government announced Rudolph would plead guilty to all four bombings, including the Centennial Olympic Park attack. Rudolph is serving four life terms without the possibility of parole at ADX Florence supermax prison in Florence, Colorado. Rudolph's justification for the bombings according to his April 13, 2005 statement, was political:[8]</Msg><Username>black_mariah777</Username><Timestamp>1366059484526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366060304262-72</Id><Topic><Title>Dems quickly introduce bill to set limit of one bomb per marathon</Title><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1366055912286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They should have background checks for posting on yahoo , an IQ of at least 40 is required. You would only need 40 more points to post if that was the case.</Msg><Username>rockstar80333</Username><Timestamp>1366060304262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366060795260-73</Id><Topic><Title>Dems quickly introduce bill to set limit of one bomb per marathon</Title><Username>cws2012wc</Username><Timestamp>1366055912286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 15:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The mental midget of all mental midgets wants IQ testing...very funny.</Msg><Username>joedokes45</Username><Timestamp>1366060795260</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366061059206-74</Id><Topic><Title>07.22.13</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366060740486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:19:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>last you heard... from near Bisbee AZ it was</Msg><Username>somethingbigiscomingup</Username><Timestamp>1366061059206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:24:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366061171734-75</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>norivit....you make a good little #$%$ but there's a couple of things you didn't learn on your way to becoming a victim of socialized government education. First of all, you can leave all right but you're still a slave because the USA government can still tax you for 10 years after you leave. Secondly, people who don't like government policies don't have to leave anymore than the people Democrats fought a war to keep in bondage did. They can work to become free. The idea that you have no right of dissent is tyrannical to say the least and unAmerican at the outset........but certainly one Democrat love to promote......at least when they have a little power.</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366061171734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:26:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366061576939-76</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was that post supposed to be coherent? if it was, you failed miserably. If you LEAVE the country(change citizenship) then you have no tax obligation after you leave. Your second (alleged) point makes no sense at all."work to become free"? Are you a leftover from the administrator from the #$%$ concentration camps. I don't know who you think is quelling your right to dissent, but it is not happening in this country. If you are an example of a private education, then you got ripped of in a big way!</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1366061576939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:32:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366062240113-77</Id><Title>NASA and Strategic missile/defense systems center opened In Huntdville, Ala.</Title><Msg>HUNTSVILLE, Ala., April 15, 2013 /PRNewswire/ -- Boeing (BA) and Alabama leaders today officially opened a new complex in Huntsville that will advance Boeing's competitiveness and strengthen the company's commitment to the state. Boeing is the largest aerospace company in Alabama and one of the state's largest employers. Huntsville employees in leased facilities have begun moving into the first completed building of the Redstone Gateway complex, which is expected to house 1,400 Boeing employees in 363,000 square feet of space. "This is more than a new Boeing-owned office complex – today is a celebration of the investment Boeing has made in the ideas, innovation and inspiration rooted right here in Huntsville," Tony Jones, vice president and Boeing Huntsville site executive, said at a ribbon-cutting ceremony that included state and local leaders and customer representatives. The complex will be used for Boeing's work on NASA's Space Launch System and headquarters for the company's Strategic Missile and Defense Systems division.</Msg><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366062240113</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366062322893-78</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I told y'all norivit was a victim of socialized government education and sho-nuff he proved it. The problem with these victims is the have no clue how ignorant they are. "Section 2 of the Ex-PATRIOT Act amends 26 U.S.C. § 871(a)(2) to impose new taxes on certain "covered expatriates". In the new Subparagraph C, it defines the term "specified expatriate", a subset of "covered expatriate". A "specified expatriate" is defined in clause (i) as any "covered expatriate" who lost citizenship or permanent residence within the ten-year period before the bill's date of enactment, as well as future "covered expatriates". Clause (ii) exempts those who prove that their loss of citizenship "did not result in a substantial reduction in taxes". The new subparagraph A provides for the imposition of capital gains tax on "specified expatriates" at the same 30% rate as non-resident aliens who are present in the United States for more than 183 days in a tax year. Subparagraph B provides that the tax basis of a "specified expatriate" in U.S. property shall be the value of that property on the day preceding loss of citizenship.[5]"</Msg><Username>mediocreclassguy</Username><Timestamp>1366062322893</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366063059693-79</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good post guy.....norivit is good little N*Z*soldier. What ever der fuhrer says, he will support. He thinks anyone who doesn't support socialism/communist/fascism should just leave the country. He wants dissenters to just shut up while Democrats fundamentally transform America into a great big Cuba.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366063059693</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366063229228-80</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual, your pea brain misses the point in your misplaced excitement in thinking you have "scored" a point. This is there for people who change citizenship specifically with the intent to avoid taxes on money earned from activity in the US (and protected by US services). You know, the people you call "patriots". If you leave the country, pay the taxes on the money you earned from your activity here, and start new (job and/or business) in another country this doesn't apply. You would need at least another 100 IQ points to understand that, don't even try, you will hurt the three brain cells you have.</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1366063229228</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366063846323-81</Id><Topic><Title>A Letter Writing Campaign For The Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366063179551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or, as Sen. John Mccain, the son of an admiral, fifth from the bottom graduate of the Naval Academy, five-plane loser and former POW said about Obama late on the campaign trail 2008: "No. You are are wrong. Obama is a fine man. A good man. A good American. A good husband and father..." Thankfully we have Hillary 2016 to wear the pants</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366063846323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366064614271-82</Id><Topic><Title>A Letter Writing Campaign For The Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366063179551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't that inconvenience Barry and mess up his golf and vacation schedule?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366064614271</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366065920507-83</Id><Title>Democrats think an Expatriot is a runaway Slave</Title><Msg>US Citizens Now One Step Closer To Becoming Permanent Tax Slaves (Take a look at the Ex-PATRIOT Act)‘Ex-PATRIOT’ is an absurd acronym that stands for “Expatriation Prevention by Abolishing Tax-Related Incentives for Offshore Tenancy”. I call it the Tax Slave Act… and it proposes three key provisions: 1) Individuals who are deemed, in the sole discretion of the US government, to have renounced US citizenship in order to avoid US taxes, will be permanently barred from re-entering the United States. 2) Such individuals will also be required to pay a 30% capital gains tax to the United States government on ALL future investment gains derived from the US. Currently, non-citizens who do not reside in the US pay no US capital gains tax. 3) These proposals are RETROACTIVE, and, if passed, would apply to anyone who renounced his/her citizenship within the last 10-years. During a Sunday interview with ABC News, House Speaker John Boehner threw his support behind the bill… certainly a big step towards its eventual passage. Let’s pause briefly for a little history lesson– Dart Container Corporation was founded in 1960 by William F. Dart, the man who first perfected the design of styrofoam. Dart Container is today a multi-billion dollar family-owned company with thousands of employees and operations around the world. In the early 1990s, brothers Kenneth and Robert Dart, heirs to the family fortune, renounced their US citizenship and became citizens of Belize and Ireland, and set up residency in the Cayman Islands. Around the same time, several other wealthy Americans renounced citizenship, including Carnival Cruise Lines founder Ted Arison (who obtained Israeli citizenship), Campbell Soup heir John Dorrance (Irish citizenship), and fund manager Mark Mobius (German citizenship). President Clinton was furious, and in 1996, he pushed Congress to pass a series of financial penalties for people who renounce citizenship. At the time, a ‘renunciant’ had to continue filing US tax returns for 10-years after renouncing. Effectively, though, this penalty was a tax on worldwide income, not an exit tax on assets. Fast forward to the mid-2000s, a time when the asset bubble was at its peak; the stock market was at its all-time high and real estate prices kept going up. The Bush regime passed a series of changes to expatriation rules, dropping the income tax filing requirements in lieu of charging a one-time exit tax on assets. In this way, the government was able to derive a much larger payment up front based on total assets rather than chasing around a former citizen for a piece of annual income. In the years since the exit tax on assets was established, two things have happened: 1) The number of Americans renouncing US citizenship has risen steadily, from 235 people in 2008 to 1,780 last year (according to Schumer’s office). 2) The asset bubble has burst, and assets are worth much less than just a few years ago. As such, the government isn’t collecting as much revenue from the exit tax. My sense is that the government has been watching the number of expatriates rise over the years, and simultaneously watching the value of the exit tax fall… and they’ve been looking for an excuse to make sweeping (i.e. retroactive) changes. Eduardo Saverin is the perfect excuse. The Facebook co-founder’s recent renunciation of US citizenship has become a rallying cry for politicians to go back in time and steal money from former citizens retroactively…plus establish a larger base for future tax revenues. This is a truly despicable thing to do considering that these former citizens followed the appropriate rules at the time, paid the tax, and moved on with their lives. Now Uncle Sam wants to go back in time to unilaterally change the deal, and expect everyone to abide even though they’re not even citizens anymore. The arrogance is overwhelming. More importantly, this bill is also a major deterrent for people who are thinking about renouncing US citizenship today. The passage of this law will undoubtedly cause many people who were considering expatriation to abandon the idea altogether as the thought of being permanently barred from entry is too much to bear. It’s truly extraordinary that the Land of the Free has deteriorated to the point that the government must now resort to threats, coercion, and intimidation in order to keep its most productive citizens inside.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366065920507</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:45:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366067280287-84</Id><Topic><Title>concerning gun control, how about Obama running guns to the Mexican Cartels then hiding behind Executive Order</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366043042661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a marxist coward hiding behind presidential privilege. Give him enough time he and his media dogs will change reality.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1366067280287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 19:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366067956485-85</Id><Topic><Title>A Letter Writing Campaign For The Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366063179551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bad question. Far too many big words for the doofus population such as chemical ali infested.</Msg><Username>georgewbushisachickenhawk</Username><Timestamp>1366067956485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 19:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366068517210-86</Id><Topic><Title>A Letter Writing Campaign For The Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366063179551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't pick on chemical ali. He is a valuable resource at election time. When truly deranged folks like him blather, moan, cry, vomit, and "campaign," it is better for our side.</Msg><Username>sammy.shakedown</Username><Timestamp>1366068517210</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 19:28:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366070483230-87</Id><Topic><Title>My scorecard is busy</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366066600652</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 18:56:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So is your mouth.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366070483230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366070624811-88</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lame try.....face not saved.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366070624811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366071341569-89</Id><Title>How long</Title><Msg>How long before Spartakook posts something about a New World Order Mars Bars Arm &amp; Hammer Armond Hammer Trilateral Commission Faked Moon Landing New Coke Lindbergh Baby Conspiracy?</Msg><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1366071341569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366071898197-90</Id><Topic><Title>How long</Title><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1366071341569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:15:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll take 4 days in the board pool.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1366071898197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366072139535-91</Id><Topic><Title>A Letter Writing Campaign For The Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366063179551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, Sammy.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1366072139535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366072154523-92</Id><Topic><Title>How long</Title><Username>orly_taint</Username><Timestamp>1366071341569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:15:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or until buly-bob pops up about the mutual benefit of PG, JNJ, and BA or JESUS 4 days is but 1000 my 4 days/bet ?</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366072154523</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366072647567-93</Id><Topic><Title>The real reason for the 1962 break-out off Alcatraz</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366070647424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:04:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only one time was bare-feetin' Marilyn Monroe's footprints inside the foyer of the THEATRE AN ERECTION THE SIZE AND HARDNESS OF MONTANA ode to joy Why don't you young'uns step-outside until this ride is complete</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366072647567</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366073032183-94</Id><Topic><Title>Good Luck</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366072743335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And only one (1) Orly Taitz.</Msg><Username>jumbojetskl</Username><Timestamp>1366073032183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366073151891-95</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9/11 was far worse than this.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1366073151891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366073430104-96</Id><Title>I lokks like black Mariah has a new Name.....</Title><Msg>.....and a new hallucinogenic drug.</Msg><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073430104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366073554830-97</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bull. It was entirely Bush/Cheney's fault.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1366073554830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366073631532-98</Id><Topic><Title>A Letter Writing Campaign For The Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366063179551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Thankfully we have Hillary 2016" Indeed. And she will run and win.</Msg><Username>instant_karma48</Username><Timestamp>1366073631532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366074322915-99</Id><Topic><Title>concerning gun control, how about Obama running guns to the Mexican Cartels then hiding behind Executive Order</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1366043042661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>correct on all points</Msg><Username>spartacus67517</Username><Timestamp>1366074322915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366074379197-100</Id><Title>there were three 737's lined up to land minutes after each other</Title><Msg>us kids on the ground the last drive-in movie theater on prime bay-area (pinch nose closed land) they don;t half the senses to build stuff like that today ...UP I believe it was a doble feature I believe we ended up with some KFC some stepping on basketball jones's shoe strings @ Blockbusterr only to get/rent THE BIRDS</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366074379197</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:06:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366074386469-101</Id><Title>I know a person that saw Hillary without makeup</Title><Msg>The only thing uglier than that was her character. She made sure the W/H staff they knew they were dirt in her eyes. I never understood why Bill was wagging "little willie" at all the Southern Belles until I heard first hand stories about living with the witch from the North. In retrospect I can't blame Bill for seeking satisfaction elsewhere.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366074386469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366074684665-102</Id><Topic><Title>A Letter Writing Campaign For The Constitution</Title><Username>hoozdik_hertz_765</Username><Timestamp>1366063179551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 17:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree. I think she is all in, and is perfectly positioned to win.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1366074684665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366074857510-103</Id><Topic><Title>bulky-_bb ali_infesto has a message for you....</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366074536349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New ID contard?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366074857510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366074951048-104</Id><Title>Islamic ideology</Title><Msg>Islamic control of the world would send the democratic process back to the age of the Ancient Greeks 2500 years ago. Public beheadings and burnings would be a common procedure on those not Islamic. A purge not seen since the Roman Emperor Nero against Christians would be a way of life. Christianity is tolerance while Islam is intolerance.</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1366074951048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366074993522-105</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barack Obama doubled the S&amp;P 500. Bush returned virtually nothing in 8 years.</Msg><Username>the_loading_dock_01</Username><Timestamp>1366074993522</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366075248773-106</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Bin Laden who was also responsible for the Subprime Lending legislation" Wow. This one cannot be simply chalked up to kookdom. A new world record.</Msg><Username>letsmakecharts</Username><Timestamp>1366075248773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366075622878-107</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the first term was all Bushes fault according to all the BA Board progressives but you're happy with Bush doubling the S&amp;P in Barry's first term?</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366075622878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366076776678-108</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bizarre even for infested.</Msg><Username>jamesh8251</Username><Timestamp>1366076776678</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366076848766-109</Id><Topic><Title>If bulky_bob and Jesus showed up today for LARGE</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366075389548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turd polishers like you and Hooz would likely kill Jesus because he would be a threat as everyone would see what a real savior looks like and realize that Barry was nothing but smoke and mirrors. lol</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366076848766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366077184016-110</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there only a statute of blame limitations for Dems? Why does Barry get to blame Bush for everything but Bush doesn't get to blame the Clintons. To treat them unequally seems like fanatical adoration rather than logical thought.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366077184016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366077714536-111</Id><Topic><Title>Stnrgle the cat, burn the House Down, and live out my days</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366077295801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hooz if you're reading this how about a letter writing campaign to get some psychological help for contard here. Let's also make sure he has no guns as he's starting to to make Adam Lanza look sane.</Msg><Username>ali_infesto</Username><Timestamp>1366077714536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 22:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366078675999-112</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush was the worst President in my life time.</Msg><Username>charlesg50</Username><Timestamp>1366078675999</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 22:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366078951151-113</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Still Advocate Slavery</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366056747743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 16:12:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing lame here is your post.(and your level of intelligence)</Msg><Username>norivit</Username><Timestamp>1366078951151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 22:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366079789055-114</Id><Topic><Title>Stnrgle the cat, burn the House Down, and live out my days</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366077295801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:54:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do I know... ?!!! ? An odinary day...some kid handsnme something which I knowwehat it is...over recent ofemntire 90% OF THE worlds ansewrs and show-you-work which neither a page had beed tirn out5 of spiral notebook, three-ring binder letalone a corners bent or even a paper rumbled so, exactly what IS your problem....??? crumbvled, Buy gold beatch....</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366079789055</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 22:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366079877977-115</Id><Topic><Title>787 flight scheduled for today (Monday)</Title><Username>falmouthharbor</Username><Timestamp>1366042459965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would appear that either the original plan with two flights was too thin for the FAA or, they found something that required further testing. The last two flights were non-standard, 12,000 and 20,000 ft cruising. Most flight testing occurs either at normal cruising altitudes or landing. I would think it would have to have something to do with the battery venting system since it is likely that if the batteries did catch fire and were going to vent the aircraft would be in descent mode looking for a place to land.</Msg><Username>techpath2000</Username><Timestamp>1366079877977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 22:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366081988580-116</Id><Topic><Title>If bulky_bob and Jesus showed up today for LARGE</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366075389548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bisbee, I am kind of a "old fart" and maybe you could help me with the expression" for LARGE". Beyond that, I am surprised that you would pose, "If ... Jesus showed up today...". Fella, you need to get right with the Lord. Otherwise you would know that Jesus is ALWAYS there, here and everywhere. BB</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366081988580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 23:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366082633743-117</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can look at data many ways. Under Bush, the DOW had reached a peak of 14.1K late in 2007. In 2008, when it became apparent that the Democrats were going to win, the DOW dropped (precipitously plummeted) , and after Obama came to office, to 6.6K in March 2009. Now the DOW is back to a new peak of 14.8K, which is only 5% more than the peak under Bush. Cause for celebration, certainly, but not affirmation of Obama's policies.</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366082633743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 23:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366083210235-118</Id><Title>A matter of perspective</Title><Msg>It is tragic and we grieve for those who are wounded and have lost loved ones. A friend came over for dinner this evening. His former college classmate said that his daughter had just crossed the finish line when the bombs went off in Boston. They would have been at that very spot of the deadly explosion, like last year, had they not been engaged in the celebration of new life in the family. Fate? Or maybe it was not their time. "Why, you do not even know what will happen tomorrow. What is your life? You are a mist that appears for a little while and then vanishes." (James 4:14)</Msg><Username>bulky_bob</Username><Timestamp>1366083210235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 23:33:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366083453320-119</Id><Title>Weeks not Months- Who to Believe</Title><Msg>Mid march Boing said it was a matter of weeks before flying again, not months, What source should a person believe in "If the Federal Aviation Administration agrees (they had reps on board), the Dreamliner could resume commercial service by June, according to news reports." "</Msg><Username>cbx6cylinder</Username><Timestamp>1366083453320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 23:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366083524293-120</Id><Topic><Title>If bulky_bob and Jesus showed up today for LARGE</Title><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366075389548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 21:23:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>duane was let was left at the gate 9of motorcycly heaven these 'oldr fartsZ" sure aresmelly ABND IF IT MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER take their 'ead off</Msg><Username>bisbee_angler</Username><Timestamp>1366083524293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 23:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366084193168-121</Id><Topic><Title>New 737 crashes breaks into sections NTSB investigation , all is well, no passengers died</Title><Username>waynedickenson961</Username><Timestamp>1365873008139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 13:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fixed their lithium battery problem?? in the first place Cessna didnt have any lithium battery problem to fix - just like the flashlight makers and the tool makers like Black and Decker. Comparing the Cessna 172 to the 787 is like comparing a gnat to an eagle as there is no comparison between a 1000 lb airplane and a 250,000 lb airplane You could fold the wings of the 172 and store it and 15 more on the baggage deck of the 787. Since you know so little about aircraft I have come to doubt you worked at Renton even as a urinal cleanup man BTW the 172 has been in product for the past 40 years to deliver those numbers</Msg><Username>father_zosima</Username><Timestamp>1366084193168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 23:49:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366084682210-122</Id><Topic><Title>Bush kept us safe for 8 years, Obama has failed Americans</Title><Username>econprofhked</Username><Timestamp>1366073101852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>? ? Would you like to try that again?</Msg><Username>iamtheonetruespaz666</Username><Timestamp>1366084682210</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-15 23:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>