<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355405060804-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bear Market</Title><Username>eulaliarex925</Username><Timestamp>1323566081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-12-10 20:14:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>anniejoshep701</Username><Timestamp>1355405060804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 08:24:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355405383994-2</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney claim named 'lie of the year'</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355335233886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:00:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUT THERE WERE SO MANY!!!!!! It wasn’t Romney's first post-factual presidential campaign, after all. Whatever else the poll results tell us about the changing American electorate – that it is less white, less homophobic and more inclined than the defeated Republican nominee to protect the employment and reproductive rights of women – the outcome also confirmed that voters still know a lie when they hear one. No matter how often former Massachusetts Governor Mitt Romney repeated the lie that President Barack Obama robbed Medicare of $716 billion to pay for Obamacare, it did not change the fact that he had done no such thing. The Affordable Care Act does not cut Medicare benefits. That number is a projection of what the program will save by revising payments to insurers. Congressman Paul Ryan of Wisconsin, Romney’s equally duplicitous running mate and the House Budget Committee chairman, projected the same savings in his own House budget proposal last year. The failure of Romney’s unapologetically deceitful tactics could signal that voters have had enough of the “truthiness” dodge. Ryan proved especially adept at deceit, most notably at the Republican National Convention in Tampa where, among other whoppers, he blamed Obama for the shutdown of a General Motors plant in Wisconsin that had actually closed during the administration of President George W. Bush. Similarly, Romney’s oft-repeated and demonstrably false charge that the Obama Administration “gut welfare reform by dropping work requirements” did not stick. Obama did agree to the request of several governors, some of them Republicans, to grant waivers to the work rules spelled out in the 1996 law but only if they could demonstrate that their state plans would produce more jobs for recipients. Deceit was not ancillary to the Romney campaign; it was a founding principle. Romney’s first televised ad last year included an old video clip of Obama spliced to appear that he was speaking during the current campaign. “If we keep talking about the economy, we’re going to lose,” Obama is shown and heard declaring. The only problem is that Obama made that statement in 2008 and he was quoting an aide to Senator John McCain talking about the Arizona Republican’s then-collapsing presidential bid. Instead of pulling the ad, Romney scoffed at critics and praised the ad for hitting its target. “We obviously got under their skin because the last thing they want to be doing is talking about the economy and the president’s failure to get this economy turned around,” he said. Romney’s pollster, Neil Newhouse, summarized the campaign’s attitude toward the truth during a discussion with reporters at the Republican National Convention. “We’re not going let our campaign be dictated by fact-checkers,” he said. It was a remark reminiscent of that made to the journalist Ron Susskind by an aide to President Bush in 2002, dismissing reporters as part of a “reality-based community” of people who “believe that solutions emerge from your judicious study of discernible reality.” By Election Day, too many voters were onto the scam and offended by the insult to their intelligence. No one with a passing acquaintance with the history of political campaigning in the United States expects that 2012 will mark the end of all truth-twisting on the stump. But the failure of Romney’s unapologetically deceitful tactics could signal that voters have had enough of the “truthiness” dodge – what comedian Stephen Colbert defines as lies that have the ring of truth. Longtime Romney aide Eric Fehrnstrom, a master of the form, may have doomed the strategy last March by a little too casually describing the transition from the primaries to the general election campaign as an “Etch-A-Sketch moment” when his shape-shifting boss would moderate the “severely conservative” image he had been peddling to right wing Republicans. By Election Day, too many voters were onto the scam and offended by the insult to their intelligence. Romney sealed his fate with his final act of contempt for the truth – refusing at the end to take down a TV ad attacking Obama’s bailout of the auto industry that falsely accused General Motors of abandoning American workers to build cars in China. Even after the spokesman for GM called the ad “campaign politics at its cynical worst,” the Romney campaign kept it running. It was one lie too many</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1355405383994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 08:29:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355408406589-3</Id><Title>UE would have gone to 17% were it not for the Obama stimulus</Title><Msg>.....The first major act of the Obama administration was the economic stimulus—the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act—which focused on fighting the recession and mass unemployment. This $787 billion program of tax cuts and government spending measures aimed to brace the economy’s rickety floor and thereby preserve existing jobs as well as generate new ones in both the public and private sectors. The stimulus program did succeed in preventing a full-scale 1930s-style depression. A Wall Street Journal survey found that 75 percent of economists agreed that the stimulus succeeded in reducing unemployment. A detailed study by Alan Blinder, a Princeton economist and former Federal Reserve Vice Chair, and Mark Zandi, Chief Economist at Moody’s Analytics and an advisor to John McCain’s Presidential campaign, found that unemployment would likely have risen to nearly 17 percent in the absence of the stimulus. ........"</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355408406589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 09:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355408630849-4</Id><Topic><Title>Track Palin, oldest child of former Alaska Gov Sarah Palin ...</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355351913864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 17:38:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a great example of liberal logic that buckwheat thrives on. He has no problem with killing an unborn child but a young girl who gets pregnant should be publicly condemned along with her parents. What a sick SOB. Good thing he didn't have children, he might have had a daughter who got pregnant by Geo Zimmerman or worse, Trayvon.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1355408630849</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 09:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355408865968-5</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney claim named 'lie of the year'</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355335233886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:00:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pathetic loser. Probably work at Burger King. How about Obama's latest lie telling unions in Michigan that the new right-to-work law will mean lower paychecks. Actually since you won't be FORCED to join union, your check will be bigger...no dues paid to union gangsters. But that will take some time, because the union members will certainly threaten - more likely physically abuse - them so they be afraid to leave union. Yes the most devisive president of all times. He knows he has to divide us. First go after the rich like the Nazi's went after the jews. Then divide the non-rich. You simplistic brain certainly cannot decipher this.</Msg><Username>eddiekosmic</Username><Timestamp>1355408865968</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 09:27:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355414234503-6</Id><Topic><Title>Technical charting</Title><Username>pearliekollarkatd9365</Username><Timestamp>1305216428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-05-12 12:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the site</Msg><Username>anniejoshep701</Username><Timestamp>1355414234503</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 10:57:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355415080606-7</Id><Topic><Title>obama is the worst president in history!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355330439732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:40:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. The Jobs report shows manipulation. People who are unemployed are not counted. Good Jobs go to China. Minimum wage “service sector garbage” is the scourge being reported. The Real Unemployment level is over 14%, U6. If Americans were literate they would not believe lies.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355415080606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 11:11:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355415109385-8</Id><Topic><Title>Did you hear the news?</Title><Username>kiehnzth2207</Username><Timestamp>1346081346000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:29:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expecting more news</Msg><Username>anniejoshep701</Username><Timestamp>1355415109385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 11:11:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355415193039-9</Id><Topic><Title>Nearly carl's entire problem with Obama is................</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355333088299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:24:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, and DB, stop rating posts -with your multipul ID problem- it is childish!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355415193039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 11:13:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355416701391-10</Id><Topic><Title>Track Palin, oldest child of former Alaska Gov Sarah Palin ...</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355351913864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 17:38:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>teenage pregnancy in the god fearing, flag waving, every sperm is sacred household, just shows how the zero tollerance to sex before marriage is a colasal mistake. make contraception available to your kids and you will reduce teenage preganancy significantly. Or you can play that stupid 'just say no' game and pretend your kids don't have unprotected sex. I remember when the Surgeon General once promoted masturbation as being healthy and the GOP ran him/her out of town because it violated their social agenda.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1355416701391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 11:38:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355417070079-11</Id><Topic><Title>Track Palin, oldest child of former Alaska Gov Sarah Palin ...</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355351913864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 17:38:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee bagger... it would be fun watching you drown! That tens of thousands of decent good people will die today while human trash like you live on until tomorrow is a travesty! Comprende Chumpo!??</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1355417070079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 11:44:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355417105707-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Higher Taxes, More Spending, No Debt Limit, No Compromises</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1355337004939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:30:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i find it interesting that you somehow know what's on the table both parties haven't revealed much. We know what Obama wants but we don't really know what either party is offering.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1355417105707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 11:45:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355419480691-13</Id><Title>So Obama supports the Syrian rebels... funneling them $100s of millions and weapons</Title><Msg>and the CIA has known for months that Al-Qaeda has infiltrated the rebels leadership and fighters Just who is this Barack Hussein Obama? IF Obama has the American peoples best interests at heart... perhaps its time he takes his intelligence briefings in person</Msg><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1355419480691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 12:24:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355420545618-14</Id><Topic><Title>So Obama supports the Syrian rebels... funneling them $100s of millions and weapons</Title><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1355419480691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 12:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe he should take a chapter out the Bush book of foreign relations and call the rebels "freedom fighters" as bush did the Taliban.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1355420545618</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 12:42:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355423565178-15</Id><Topic><Title>liar bjspokesanimal lies and here is the proof (this time)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355346308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:05:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bjspokes job lies and is to cowardly to even apologize.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355423565178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 13:32:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355424918598-16</Id><Title>UH-BAMA</Title><Msg>Ever notice how many times that #$%$ says "UH" when he's speaking and not reading from a teleprompter?</Msg><Username>tomballz_butt_is_sore</Username><Timestamp>1355424918598</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 13:55:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355425047900-17</Id><Title>Bill Clinton Would Have Had a Deal By Now</Title><Msg>Bill Clinton was a GREAT negotiator and he got bi-partison solutions implemented. Barack Obama is a HORRIBLE negotiator... nothing got done, except the "fiscal cliff" in 2011... and nothing is getting done NOW. Bill Clinton was a GREAT president... Obama is a HORRIBLE president... and that's just the way it is, Virginia! S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1355425047900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 13:57:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355425275608-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Clinton Would Have Had a Deal By Now</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1355425047900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 13:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sire he would! Because he didn't have to deal with AAA Hooole left-wing Democrats!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1355425275608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:01:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355425862188-19</Id><Topic><Title>So Obama supports the Syrian rebels... funneling them $100s of millions and weapons</Title><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1355419480691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 12:24:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While ignorance is bliss.... your blissful ignorance cannot rewrite history... Bush funded and armed the Northern Alliance... the mortal enemies of the Taliban Its all irrelevant at this point.... Obama says in campaign rhetoric that Al-Qaeda is all but dead.... while at the same time funding and arming them thats called a pandering POS</Msg><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1355425862188</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:11:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355426468725-20</Id><Title>Clinton is against the tax cuts for the rich, fwiw and who cares anyway if he is soft on the gop?</Title><Msg>and sc re w the gop...... the tax cuts for the rich are over! history , too fricken bad and the gop can't do a thing about it... they expire jan 1 so adios.................(and then obama will offer a tax cut to the 98% retroactive to jan 1 and what is the gop going to do about it? throw a tantrum?)</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355426468725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:21:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355426623120-21</Id><Topic><Title>Polls: people blame the gop for the fiscal cliff mess</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1355194473298</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 21:54:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop deserves the blame for the mess for sure!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355426623120</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:23:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355426790796-22</Id><Topic><Title>liar bjspokesanimal lies and here is the proof (this time)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355346308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:05:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pants on fire liar: bjspokesanimal, he claimed the gop has offered exacty what obama has asked for!....jeez.... really? I don't remember ending the tax cuts for the 2%, agi $250K +, being part of the gop counter offer.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355426790796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:26:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355427403784-23</Id><Topic><Title>Track Palin, oldest child of former Alaska Gov Sarah Palin ...</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355351913864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 17:38:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kollestral with another mindless reply. This subject is not as simple as you are. Hundreds maybe thousands of young girls from good families get pregnant each year and choose to keep the baby.There lies the difference between the liberal solution and the pro-life proponents. Most parents would like their kids to be celebate but know that's not realistic. Look at the stats, younger and younger people are engaging. Then look at what kids see on TV and the movies. They get sex education in school and boys can get condoms anywhere but still won't use them. Those aren't forbidden. But lets blame the girl or her parents. You're as ignorant as buckwheat.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1355427403784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:36:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355427569471-24</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Clinton Would Have Had a Deal By Now</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1355425047900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 13:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... and together, the 4 of them balanced the budget. Today, Obama has practically shut the government DOWN and we've been running huge, Trillion dollar deficits for almost a half a decade now. Bill Clinton and Ronald Reagan were the 2, best presidents of the past 50 years... and Obama and George W Bush have been the 2 worst... and at least with Bush, the government actually FUNCTIONED, even though he didn't. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1355427569471</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:39:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355429449312-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Clinton Would Have Had a Deal By Now</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1355425047900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 13:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deal would have been consummated long ago, especially if Monica were involved.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355429449312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 15:10:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355429550692-26</Id><Title>Medicare has grown</Title><Msg>19,000 percent from 1967 to 2010. Think we might have a spending problem. And to the libiots, Bush's wars did not impact Medicare spending.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355429550692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 15:12:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355430236934-27</Id><Topic><Title>liar bjspokesanimal lies and here is the proof (this time)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355346308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:05:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The great expositor president wants unlimited power to raise our national debt limit. Could you imagine what our debt would be four years hence? Happy days are here again, a chicken in every pot, the great society all wrapped into one package.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355430236934</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 15:23:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355430529229-28</Id><Topic><Title>Polls: people blame the gop for the fiscal cliff mess</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1355194473298</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 21:54:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The nerve of the Republicans going against the wishes of the people. Those 47 per centers might have to start paying a few farthings in income taxes. And the 70 per centers who think the top 1-2 percent should pay more taxes. They only pay 50 percent of all taxes now. The nerve of those successful people. Shame on them for being rich and successful. Bad, bad people.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355430529229</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 15:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355430725417-29</Id><Topic><Title>obama is the worst president in history!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355330439732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:40:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama One will not be judged as the worst president ever in four more years. ObamaTwo will easily surpass him in all areas of incompetency.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355430725417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 15:32:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355430897504-30</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney claim named 'lie of the year'</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355335233886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:00:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biggest lies of all are that entitlements can remain unchanged for the future and Obummercare will not cost us more. Now those are whoppers that Burger King would be proud of.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355430897504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 15:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355432868500-31</Id><Topic><Title>obama is the worst president in history!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355330439732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:40:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chaffetz: State Dept Hiding Benghazi Survivors 2401 37 5551 Email Article Print Article Send a Tip by Kerry Picket 12 Dec 2012 636 post a comment Congressman Jason Chaffetz (R- UT) told Breitbart News on Wednesday that he has been “thwarted” by the State Department from seeing any Americans who survived the deadly attack on the U.S. diplomatic mission in Benghazi. Many people forget that there were Americans who survived the Benghazi attack, some of whom were badly injured and are still recovering. “My understanding is that we still have some people in the hospital. I’d like to visit with them and wish them nothing but the best but the State Department has seen it unfit for me to know who those people are—or even how many there are,” Rep. Chaffetz said. "I don’t know who they are. I don’t know where they live. I don’t know what state they’re from. I don’t even know how many there are. It doesn’t seem right to me." “This is so patently different than any other experience I’ve had. Unfortunately, people have been killed and maimed and in harm’s way in Afghanistan and Iraq and in points beyond. It’s typically been the case that they would release those names but in this case, they won’t. My challenge is to the media. You try and figure it out. They won’t let Congress know. They won’t seem to let the media know either.” Breitbart News sent an inquiry to the State Department regarding those who survived the attack in Benghazi and is awaiting a response.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1355432868500</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:07:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355432957201-32</Id><Title>See-ya Rice!! You Got What You Deserved For Lying...</Title><Msg>and pimping for your boy Obama!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355432957201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:09:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355433052654-33</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton is against the tax cuts for the rich, fwiw and who cares anyway if he is soft on the gop?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355426468725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously, Newt and his party of sanity had an impact on him. Libiots are idiots. Sounds better every time I sat it.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355433052654</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:10:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355433130006-34</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton is against the tax cuts for the rich, fwiw and who cares anyway if he is soft on the gop?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355426468725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just keep sating it to yourself, hope and change, hope and change, hope and change,..............................?..........................?.......................?.........................</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355433130006</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:12:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355433224687-35</Id><Topic><Title>dear ignoramus, fyi the debt ceiling is about PAYING EXISTING DEBT.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1355340424278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 14:27:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More hope and change from two libiots. Yeah boys, hope and change.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355433224687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:13:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355433302445-36</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton is against the tax cuts for the rich, fwiw and who cares anyway if he is soft on the gop?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355426468725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the GOP is gonna do is as follows... they will take Obama's proposal.... which constitutionally has to start (and pass) in the House as it is a tax or spending bill (power of the purse) amend it to include all 100% of Americans... and send it along to the Senate... the Senate can approve it and it goes to Obama for his signature.... or they reject it... or they attempt to change it But IF they change it.... it always has to come back to the House for a vote Obama can become pragmatic and find a compromise... or he can let taxes go up on all Americans... and tank the economy for the next 4 years Obama can flex his muscles... and the house can flex theirs</Msg><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1355433302445</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:15:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355434848967-37</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton is against the tax cuts for the rich, fwiw and who cares anyway if he is soft on the gop?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355426468725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 14:21:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tax cuts for the rich expire jan 1. obama will offer tax cuts for the middleclass then. and YOU say the gop will reject a tax cut? sure.....lol...... i wonder how middleclass republicans will like the gop voting down a tax cut for them.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355434848967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:40:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355436246667-38</Id><Topic><Title>Medicare has grown</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1355429550692</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 15:12:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ever a chicken little, you like squawking ridiculous and meaningless numbers. FYI the cost of medicare AND medicaid was about 5 cents of each dollar of USA gdp in 2010 (CBO) Why don't YOU do something about medicare like getting off it? you squawk but you are on it, you don't have to be, you can insure yourself you know, your type says all insurance is "socialism" anyway. and hey, do whine that the trillion bush blew in Iraq looking for wmd was 5 times the amount the USA spent for all of WW2.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355436246667</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:04:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355436278925-39</Id><Topic><Title>See-ya Rice!! You Got What You Deserved For Lying...</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355432957201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:09:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i could care less, but what hypocracy when the same Senators who were the ones' who stood behind Condelesa Rice who lied on behalf of the Bush administration about centrifuges.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1355436278925</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:04:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355437390694-40</Id><Title>thirty years of trickle down</Title><Msg>How has the middleclass done over the last 30 years of trickle down? C.E.O.’s of the largest American companies earned an average of 42 times as much as the average worker in 1980, but 531 times as much in 2001. Perhaps the most astounding statistic is this: From 1980 to 2005, more than four-fifths of the total increase in American incomes went to the richest 1 percent. OR In 2007 the richest 1% of the American population owned 34.6% of the country's total wealth, and the next 19% owned 50.5%. Thus, the top 20% of Americans owned 85% of the country's wealth and the bottom 80% of the population owned 15%. Financial inequality was greater than inequality in total wealth, with the top 1% of the population owning 42.7%, the next 19% of Americans owning 50.3%, and the bottom 80% owning 7%.[9] However, after the Great Recession which started in 2007, the share of total wealth owned by the top 1% of the population grew from 34.6% to 37.1%, and that owned by the top 20% of Americans grew from 85% to 87.7%. The Great Recession also caused a drop of 36.1% in median household wealth but a drop of only 11.1% for the top 1%, further widening the gap between the 1% and the 99%.[8][9][10] wiki</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355437390694</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:23:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355437421268-41</Id><Topic><Title>See-ya Rice!! You Got What You Deserved For Lying...</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355432957201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:09:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth my aszzs! You seek nothing but Pi.gg.shyt! Even Kay had serious suspicions... to say nothing about most Democrat Senators who fully agreed with the GOP... Kerry and Clinton among them! "Obeidi told CNN the parts of a gas centrifuge system for enriching uranium were part of a highly sophisticated system he was ordered to hide to be ready to rebuild the bomb program. "I have very important things at my disposal that I have been ordered to have, to keep, and I've kept them, and I don't want this to proliferate, because of its potential consequences if it falls in the hands of tyrants, in the hands of dictators or of terrorists," said Obeidi, who has been taken out of Iraq with the help of the U.S. government. Obeidi also said he was not the only scientist ordered to hide that type of equipment. "I think there may be more than three other copies. And I think it is quite important to look at this list so they will not fall into the hands of the wrong people," he said. Centrifuges are drums or cylinders that spin at high speed and separate heavy and light molecules, allowing increasingly enriched uranium to be drawn off. David Kay, who led three U.N. arms inspection missions in Iraq in 1991-92 and now heads the CIA's search for unconventional weapons, started work two days ago in Baghdad. CNN spoke to him about the case over a secure teleconferencing line. "It begins to tell us how huge our job is," Kay said. "Remember, his material was buried in a barrel behind his house in a rose garden. "There's no way that that would have been discovered by normal international inspections. I couldn't have done it. My successors couldn't have done it." Kay said he had mixed emotions when he saw the centrifuge components: "It was a realization that I hadn't gotten all the parts [of Iraq's nuclear program]. So there was a moment of regret, but there wasalso an exhilaration that now maybe we have a chance to take this to the very bottom."</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1355437421268</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:23:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355437662708-42</Id><Topic><Title>thirty years of trickle down</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355437390694</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's rediculous when conservatives say those people EARN their 400x the average employee. And when they get $40 million severance packages regardless of how the company performs the standard line is; "we're paying the standard pay for our industry" former Netflix CEO is a perfect example.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1355437662708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:27:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355437776664-43</Id><Topic><Title>See-ya Rice!! You Got What You Deserved For Lying...</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355432957201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:09:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>give it up pisghit - even fox news knows the Iraq plan for war was bogus. You're out in left field.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1355437776664</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:29:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355438957557-44</Id><Topic><Title>See-ya Rice!! You Got What You Deserved For Lying...</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355432957201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:09:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's the kicker, she's going to be appointed as National Security Advisor. Security, as in protecting national interests. And here she lied about a security matter. The Dems sure know how to look like idiots. Maybe Obama will appoint Charlie Rangel as Treasury boss.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1355438957557</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 17:49:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355440246814-45</Id><Topic><Title>See-ya Rice!! You Got What You Deserved For Lying...</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355432957201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:09:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree! There will be a nice payback for her lying to Americans and kissing Obama's azzs, like a good girl!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1355440246814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 18:10:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355440432075-46</Id><Topic><Title>See-ya Rice!! You Got What You Deserved For Lying...</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355432957201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:09:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i see you losers have gotten over the losing not lmfao at your losing ways with your loser party and your loser social agenda</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1355440432075</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 18:13:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355441491819-47</Id><Topic><Title>who will obama send to congress to address: YEllow Cake TWO?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355333146216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:25:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You live in a cave or something DB … IT`S ALL OVER THE NEWS!!!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355441491819</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 18:31:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355446840534-48</Id><Topic><Title>See-ya Rice!! You Got What You Deserved For Lying...</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1355432957201</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 16:09:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She'll be a czar of something so she can continue to slurp the Kool aid.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355446840534</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 20:00:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355446935573-49</Id><Topic><Title>who will obama send to congress to address: YEllow Cake TWO?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355333146216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:25:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was an F student. He's an Indonesian CIA operative Manchurian candidate.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355446935573</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 20:02:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355447214649-50</Id><Topic><Title>Polls: people blame the gop for the fiscal cliff mess</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1355194473298</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 21:54:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when the blame is really on Obama, Pelosi and Reid. things have progressively gotten worse since the Dems took control of Congress in 2007. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355447214649</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 20:06:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355447376686-51</Id><Topic><Title>liar bjspokesanimal lies and here is the proof (this time)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355346308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:05:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chavez’s surgery did not go well and no one knows if or when he may recover. He'll probably pop up tomorrow and proclaim he is cured!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355447376686</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 20:09:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355447537287-52</Id><Topic><Title>liar bjspokesanimal lies and here is the proof (this time)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355346308640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:05:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a chicken in every pot *** Now it's: A burrito in every bowl. Followed by the legal pot paradox. You can possess it but you can't grow it or buy it or sell it.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355447537287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 20:12:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355451349756-53</Id><Topic><Title>who will obama send to congress to address: YEllow Cake TWO?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1355333146216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 12:25:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had a good friend that retired from the Air Force as a full Col. He worked as an intekkigence officer in Riyadh. When my daughter went to Gulf War I in a medicak unit he loaned me an unclassified CIA book that gave assessments of all the Middle Eastern lands. One thing that stuck in my mind was that Iraq had plenty of uranium deposits. There was no need for them to go to the Congo to get any "yellow cake". ASnother Bush lie. Now Bongo Bongo is cooking up a similar lie about the Syrian government of Assad and chemical weapons as an excuse to intervene on the side of the Al Queda and other extremist groups that we have armed in Syria. More of the NWO corruption and murder.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1355451349756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 21:15:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355453217742-54</Id><Title>dear phony gop: don't authorize spending and then throw a debt ceiling tantrum</Title><Msg>how dishonest can you be? you sign off on defense spending, for instance, then later you threaten to not pay for it? .". Reagan raised the debt limit every five months, Bush every 13 months, and Obama every 15 months. (Clinton was every 24 months.) So, without the possibility of contradiction, the presidents who needed the debt ceiling raised the most often were Reagan and Bush, and the Republicans burbled happily as they did it. Suddenly though, in the middle of a global financial trauma, those same GOPers decided that now raising the debt ceiling mattered. And, somehow, they portrayed this as being representative of out-of-control spending by the Democrats. (I showed why that was bogus up above.) There were a few other things that the Republican talking points hid from America – raising the debt ceiling wasn’t about allowing future spending, it was about paying past bills. In other words, the money had already been spent – demanding cuts in future budgets did nothing to affect the structural debt.."eichenwald)</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355453217742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 21:46:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355453374616-55</Id><Title>gop cares not for the middleclass</Title><Msg>..: GOPers ranted and raved about the need for tax cuts for “job creators” but when the time came for a renewal of a payroll tax cut – which helped the middle class enormously but did almost nothing for the rich – the GOP fought it. When Obama proposed allowing the Bush tax cuts for the middle class to be renewed, the GOP refused, instead taking the proposal hostage in an attempt to force through tax cuts for the rich." Kurt Eichenwald</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1355453374616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-13 21:49:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>