<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349500535266-1</Id><Title>Big Bird is a Millionaire &amp; Billionaire Welfare Cheat who doesn't pay his fair share of taxes!</Title><Msg>If you recall, Barack Obama constantly complains about "millionaires and billionaires" who don't pay their fair share of taxes! Sesame Workshop (formerly the Children's Television Workshop, the owner of "Sesame Street" and Big Bird) complains that they don't get much money from the Federal Government. Thus they DO get some "welfare." They do report $118 million in income! As a nonprofit organization, they pay NO taxes! Zero! Zippo! Nada! None! Thus they are NOT paying their "fair share"! Especially when mom &amp; pop small businesses, who make $250,000 per year, thus defined by Obama as "millionaires and billionaires", are expected to pay extra taxes!</Msg><Username>wjkeck3</Username><Timestamp>1349500535266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 01:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349506271311-2</Id><Title>Jobless rate falls to 44-month low???????</Title><Msg>Talk about hype! When Barack Obama got the job in Jan-2009 the U/E rate was 7.8%. He advised us to do a big STIMULUS package so it would never go over 8%. It's been over 8% for every month since, until now! Now it's gone back to 7.8%, which is where we started with Barack Obama in Jan-2009. And we are supposed to be THRILLED? Mr. Affirmative Action has another great accomplishment??????</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1349506271311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 02:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349506993444-3</Id><Title>Obama claims Romney wants to cut taxes by $5 TRILLION for the rich</Title><Msg>This must be the most stupid Obama comment ever. (1) US tax revenue totals about $2.2 trillion per yer. What Obama is saying is that Romeny wants to give back "to the rich" more than TWICE our annual revenue. (2) Even if you assume this is over 10 years, it doesn't make any sense. This would average to $500 billion per year! In "give backs" only to the rich!!!! It is just not even PLAUSIBLE! Barack Obama is a hopeless LIAR! Maybe if Barack Obama participated in making a national budget (instead of campaigning or playing golf) he would understand some of these budget "details"!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1349506993444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 03:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349507382576-4</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless rate falls to 44-month low???????</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1349506271311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 02:51:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets remember that Our Fearless Leader did get Osama Bin Laden!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1349507382576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 03:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349521331697-5</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless rate falls to 44-month low???????</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1349506271311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 02:51:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some repubs are saying the jobs number was faked because it's so good....some repubs including romknee are saying the number isn't good and indicates bad recovery..which is it db's??? Again and again, repubs will say ANYTHING!</Msg><Username>dropkickcorpis12345</Username><Timestamp>1349521331697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 07:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349526460362-6</Id><Topic><Title>Jobless rate falls to 44-month low???????</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1349506271311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 02:51:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Talk about hype! When Barack Obama got the job in Jan-2009 the U/E rate was 7.8%. He advised us to do a big STIMULUS package so it would never go over 8%. It's been over 8% for every month since, until now! Now it's gone back to 7.8%, which is where we started with Barack Obama in Jan-2009. And we are supposed to be THRILLED? Mr. Affirmative Action has another great accomplishment?????? *** Didn't you enjoy the 4 years of horrible economy? Prolong the misery. Things will get worse after the election. They are holding back all the bad news until after the elections. Lemmings are so easily manipulated.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349526460362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349526561016-7</Id><Topic><Title>Saw A Great Bumper Sticker</Title><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1349455995916</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 12:53:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We don't get fooled again!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349526561016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349526807654-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Is A Fraud, Liar &amp; Fake And His 7.8% UE Rate Is Pure Pigshyt!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1349451934396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:45:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But Obama loves Conning and F'ing-over the Stupid White Mice of America... who are Fools! It's so easy to see how fascists like Mussolini &amp; Hitler got the backing of Stupid White fools... all you have to do is keep feeding them the same lies and promises over and over and over again... *** 7.8% is as good as it gets. Tax increases and budget cuts are already signed into law. Lawmakers don't have to do anything but blame the other guy. Obama is not a leader. He is a blamer, a basher, a loser. He talk like a black man when he want to.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349526807654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349528132121-9</Id><Title>OMG! USA will pay $53 TRILLION for defense!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>and that is with NO INCREASES.... that is just the current spending times the next 75 years or so. Romney and the gop must be crazy to INCREASE that....... and paid for with tax cuts?????</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349528132121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349528417967-10</Id><Title>ignorant republican congressman says earth is only 9,000 yrs old and science is the devil's tool</Title><Msg>"serving on the House Science Committee. This is irresponsible , should be criminal. It's the kind of backward thinking you'd expect from Iran not the U.S. and we need to fix it if we want to compete with the rest of the world. Rep. Paul Broun (R-GA): Evolution, Big Bang ‘Lies Straight From The Pit Of Hell’ Source: TPM Rep. Paul Broun (R-GA) tore into scientists as tools of the devil in a speech at the Liberty Baptist Church Sportsman’s Banquet last month. “All that stuff I was taught about evolution and embryology and the Big Bang Theory, all that is lies straight from the pit of Hell,” Broun said. “And it’s lies to try to keep me and all the folks who were taught that from understanding that they need a savior.” According to Broun, the scientific plot was primarily concerned with hiding the true age of the Earth. Broun serves on the House Science Committee, which came under scrutiny recently after another one of its Republican members, Rep. Todd Akin (R-MO), suggested that victims of “legitimate rape” have unnamed biological defenses against pregnancy. “You see, there are a lot of scientific data that I’ve found out as a scientist that actually show that this is really a young Earth,” he said. “I don’t believe that the Earth’s but about 9,000 years old. I believe it was created in six days as we know them. That’s what the Bible says.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349528417967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349530107599-11</Id><Title>Obama signed biggest tax increase in U.S. history into law</Title><Msg>Obama signed Bush Tax Cut expiration. Obama signed Payroll tax 2% increase. Obama signed Obamacare 3.8% tax increase. All set to kick in after the election Obama created the fiscal cliff. You will all PAY!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349530107599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349530606687-12</Id><Title>7.8% unemployment rate</Title><Msg>Whoa, what progress. Highest one month jump in 29 years. Amazing stuff. Obama is a phenom.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349530606687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349531528067-13</Id><Topic><Title>7.8% unemployment rate</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349530606687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even more amazing when the econony is growing at an almost non-existent 1.3%, the Fed just went for QE3 and Benanke calls the job situation grave! It's all but impossible!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349531528067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349531619991-14</Id><Title>Romney railing against EPA</Title><Msg>red meat for conservatives. Obama's EPA kill jobs. Killing the coal industry. Romney will use Executive Order to reverse damage caused by Obama's anti-business beliefs. Way to go Mitt. Keep it up. You cannot lose with that kind of talk.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349531619991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:53:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349532641232-15</Id><Topic><Title>7.8% unemployment rate</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349530606687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a liar you are...."Highest one month jump in 29 years".... straight from Tush Limpbalz rear end to your mouth... and it's a stinky lie as a quick check shows, for instance UE declined by the same 0.3% as now in apr may 2010 9.9----9.6--- and there are other recent years of the same and of course you liars never whined about the many rises in one month of the sam amount 0.3%</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349532641232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:10:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349532755913-16</Id><Topic><Title>ignorant republican congressman says earth is only 9,000 yrs old and science is the devil's tool</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349528417967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's amazing that such an ignorant person could be elected to high office, a man who says science is the tool of the devil........ jeez</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349532755913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349532970781-17</Id><Title>W took a projected $6 trillion surplus and turned it into a $5 trillion deficit</Title><Msg>just a reminder of how destructive the gop is. 24 February 2001 "President Bush said Saturday that the most important number in the budget he sends to Congress next week is the $5.6 trillion surplus it projects over the next 10 years. That huge projected surplus provides the underpinning of all the administration's tax-cut and spending plans, Mr. Bush said in his recorded weekly radio address."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349532970781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349532984483-18</Id><Topic><Title>7.8% unemployment rate</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349530606687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't get you Mesa. I praise Obama for wonderful progress on unemployment and you jump all over me. Sheesh!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349532984483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349533283240-19</Id><Topic><Title>7.8% unemployment rate</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349530606687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you forget that you LIED? liar seaburgc once again gets caught lying and laughs it off, showing that he has no regard for facts and that dishonesty is one of his basic character traits.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349533283240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349533327666-20</Id><Topic><Title>7.8% unemployment rate</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349530606687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa is still reeling from Obama's incompetent display Wed. night. Can he fix it, Mesa? Can Obama compete on Romney's level?? Huh Huh!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349533327666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:22:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349533383690-21</Id><Topic><Title>Is Romney a greek name?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349473333997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 17:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.........................is Romney promising something he knows that he and the gop won't deliver and is thus a liar?....... . i think that is the case..... Mitt is just a big liar on medicare.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349533383690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349533741172-22</Id><Topic><Title>7.8% unemployment rate</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349530606687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lied about what? Biggest one month jump in 29 years? It was reported in a survey. From tht survey: Maybe more shocking, total employment, as measured by the Household Survey, rose by 873,000 in September to 142,974,000, the biggest one month jump since June 1983. I'd ost the link but this new format won't allow it.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349533741172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349539614927-23</Id><Topic><Title>Is Romney a greek name?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349473333997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 17:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liker the Kenyan? He's already stolen 700 billion from medicare. Dems. are great at promises then taking it all back under some other guise. LBJ started stealing from SS to finance the illegal war in 'Nam and all the rest of the crooked pols have continued that up to now. Why is the P.O. broke? They've been stealing money there that should go for mail delivery. Well, the bill is coming due and you and I will pay for it whilethe shysters that engineered these thefts will live high on the hog. Both Dems AND Reps.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349539614927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349539941161-24</Id><Topic><Title>W took a projected $6 trillion surplus and turned it into a $5 trillion deficit</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349532970781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:16:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the Kenyan has added many trillions more to the deficit by giving it to the banksters to cover up the fraud they committed in the housing bubble. He also rewarded the main instigator of the derivitives fraud by making over 50 of their officers head of every government office that handles money. The "Fed", the Treasury and IRS heads are all officers from Goldman-Sachs. That should tell even an estupido like yourself somethings wrong.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349539941161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349542417223-25</Id><Topic><Title>7.8% unemployment rate</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349530606687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, it's not a lie , but it is dishonest spin. ...news buster spin on the on the improving job situation, and fyi, the 0.3% one month drop in UE is good news, not bad...... and of course a rebound in total employment after such a long period of even greater one month drops doesn't seem unusual.. just rightwing desperation that the jobs picture is getting better and it has nothing to do with the republican party...who btw cost several hundred thousand jobs when they threw their tantrum over the debt ceiling. What did the gop tantrum on debt ceiling accomplish? sabotage of the USA economic recovery. job gains 2011 feb 220000 jobs added mar 246000 " april 251,000 gop begins to make threats about the debt ceiling may - august never more than 100,000 jobs added per month sept-- a month after the gop debt ceiling tantrum was resolved 200000 jobs added What did the gop tantrum on debt ceiling accomplish? sabotage of the USA economic recovery........ and fyi the debt ceiling was about money already spend and had nothing to do with reducing future deficits.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349542417223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349543382711-26</Id><Title>Rasmussen: Romney 49. Obama 47</Title><Msg>reflect the Romney bounce from Obama's pee-poor performance. there in front of millions Obama demonstrated he's not that smart.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349543382711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349545158757-27</Id><Title>Gallup: Obama 49% Romney 46%</Title><Msg>Mitten's jumps a couple points on promises at the debate. Promises that he and the gop know they won't and can't keep, such as the whopper about medicare staying the same as it is now for everyone. Mitt promises that the medicare "entitlement", continues as is for all 55 and over...... and even all younger if they "choose" it, said Romney at the debate.........................is he promising something he knows that he and the gop won't deliver and is thus a liar?....... or is he like the greeks, who love their "entitlements" and who also like Romney and the gop love not paying for them? another whopper is this one: "i will not reduce the taxes paid by high-income Americans." Mitt Romney (reduce them from the 10 or 13% Mittens paid ?/..... and who knows if in the returns he hides he paid even less? )</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349545158757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349545846426-28</Id><Title>Mitter's now says he was 'Completely Wrong' on the 47%</Title><Msg>Romney on '47 Percent': I Was 'Completely Wrong' later i hope he admits he is wrong about most everything.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349545846426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349546195214-29</Id><Title>why does the gop have lie about the improving job numbers?</Title><Msg>" former BLS commissioner Keith Hall, now a senior scholar at George Mason University’s Mercatus Center, told McClatchy, “People shouldn’t think at all there is any bias in the numbers. This data is collected and examined by each state. . . . Hundreds of people at BLS help collect this data and compile it. If you wanted to try to mess with these numbers, you are talking a very difficult thing. It almost certainly would . . . be next to impossible.”</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349546195214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349547010031-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Is A Fraud, Liar &amp; Fake And His 7.8% UE Rate Is Pure Pigshyt!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1349451934396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:45:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Anyone but Obama Pumping Pigs and Fools know that it's total Crap... a LIE!" ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Where is your evidence?</Msg><Username>enkidu4500</Username><Timestamp>1349547010031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349548700006-31</Id><Title>Mitt betrays the lunatic right..... now he says he WAS WRONG about the 47%....lol</Title><Msg>rightie loons spouted off about how Mitt was right about the 47%, that mitt as a hero for being right about the 47% ...............rightie loons defended mitt for his 47% lies in front of a crowd of wealthy righties.......... but now Mittens says he was WRONG about that......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349548700006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:38:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349548827498-32</Id><Topic><Title>"I heart the 47%" Mittens Romney bumper sticker</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349456480947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 13:01:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mitt has changed his tune on the 47%, so there may be a "I heart the 47%" mittens bumper sticker!</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349548827498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349550323319-33</Id><Topic><Title>Gallup: Obama 49% Romney 46%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349545158757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, you think Romney gained on promises at the debate? Think again clown. Romney gained because folks saw the real Romney, and also the real Obama. They are not impressed with Obama.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349550323319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349550552955-34</Id><Title>Snoop Dogg</Title><Msg>I wish I could post the link of Snoop Doog's 10 reasons for voting for Obama and 10 reasons to vote against Romney. Check the language. Check the diction. It's no wonder he supports Obama.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349550552955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349552725687-35</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dogg</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349550552955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:09:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a funny coincidence. This morning I was conversing with a friend by e-mail and we were discussing things we didn't like about Michele Obama. Among other things, I said her wardrobe advisor must be Snoop Dogg. You heard of Ebonics? The Oakland school district a few years back said it was a real language that grew from the streets of poverty. They didn't persue the idea but it gained it's place in black hoods and history.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1349552725687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349554721539-36</Id><Topic><Title>Gallup: Obama 49% Romney 46%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349545158757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the "real Romney" making promises he has no intention of keeping. such as how medicare goes on unchanged for all over age 55, and even all younger if they "choose " traditional medicare over his vouchers. Isn't it amazing that Romney has taken medicare from near bk to go to go as is for everyone forever! wow!......amazing really...... the tax cuts pay for it right?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349554721539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349554816802-37</Id><Title>the "real Romney" ?? Which Mitt Romney are we talking about?</Title><Msg>ST Louis Post Dispatch ENDORSES OBAMA: "Romney will say anything that will help him win an election" Editorial: Obama for president: A second term for a serious man ................. As to Mr. Romney, we are puzzled. Which Mitt Romney are we talking about? The one who said of himself, in 2002, "I'm not a partisan Republican. I'm someone who is moderate and ... my views are progressive." Or is it the Mitt Romney who posed as a "severely conservative" primary candidate? Is it the Mitt Romney who supported abortion rights and public health care subsidies in Massachusetts or the one who is pro-life and anti-Obamacare now? Is it the Mitt Romney who wants to cut taxes by $5 trillion or the one who can't remember saying that now? Is it the Mitt Romney who said in May that 47 percent of Americans are moochers or the one who said last week that's not what he believes? Mr. Romney apparently will say anything that will help him win an election. As a president, he might well govern as a pragmatic chief executive, or he might sell himself to the plutocrats and the crazies who have taken over his party. He is asking Americans to take a lot on faith — there's nothing to see in his tax returns; he can cut taxes and whack away debt while trimming deductions he will not specify. .. .. . .</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349554816802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:20:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349554967435-38</Id><Topic><Title>ignorant republican congressman says earth is only 9,000 yrs old and science is the devil's tool</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349528417967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 09:00:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can such an ignorant bigot be on the House Science Committee?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349554967435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349555047087-39</Id><Topic><Title>the "real Romney" ?? Which Mitt Romney are we talking about?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349554816802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:20:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in favor of Romney. post debate poll. Mesa, can you count on Obama doing better going forward? If he can't have his teleprompter, the answer is no.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349555047087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349555276176-40</Id><Topic><Title>Mitter's now says he was 'Completely Wrong' on the 47%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349545846426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"i will not reduce the taxes paid by high-income Americans." Mitt Romney on '47 Percent': I Was 'Completely Wrong' Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney released an energy plan on Thursday that supports Washington's ethanol quota</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349555276176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349555628435-41</Id><Title>Mitt Wins All-Important #$%$ Contest but Romney told a series of outright lies</Title><Msg>Taibbi nails it: "Romney's performance was better than Obama's, but only if you throw out criteria like "wasn't 100% full of #$%$ from the opening bell" Mitt Romney Wins All-Important #$%$ Contest by Matt Taibbi I didn't watch the debate – I just couldn't. I read it in transcript form afterwards. I know it is widely believed that Mitt Romney won, but I don't agree. I think both candidates lost. I think they both sucked. Romney told a series of outright lies – the bit about the pre-existing conditions was incredible – while Barack Obama seemed unaccountably disinterested in the intellectual challenge of the exercise, repeatedly leaving the gross absurdities hurled his way by Romney unchallenged. Romney's performance was better than Obama's, but only if you throw out criteria like "wasn't 100% full of #$%$ from the opening bell" and "made an actual attempt to explain who he is and what his plans are." Unfortunately, that is good enough for our news media, which drools over the gamesmanship aspects of these debates, because it loves candidates who sink their teeth into the horse-race nonsense that they think validates their professional lives.....................</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349555628435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349557537421-42</Id><Title>Mittens lie: “pre-existing conditions are covered under my plan.” Nope, that's a lie</Title><Msg>"No. 1,” declared Mitt Romney in Wednesday’s debate, “pre-existing conditions are covered under my plan.” .............No, they aren’t</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349557537421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 17:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349560579713-43</Id><Topic><Title>the "real Romney" ?? Which Mitt Romney are we talking about?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349554816802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:20:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earthquake!!! A tectonic shift. Obama buried himself. The lemming's temple of Obama is crumbling.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349560579713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 17:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349560930411-44</Id><Title>Rasmussen: Romney 49% - Obama 47%</Title><Msg>The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Saturday shows Mitt Romney attracting support from 49% of voters nationwide, while President Obama earns the vote from 47%. Romney buries Obama after debate debacle. Obama can't get over 47%.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349560930411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349568761931-45</Id><Topic><Title>Rasmussen: Romney 49% - Obama 47%</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349560930411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen ---- Snicker, snicker!</Msg><Username>spam_buster_jr</Username><Timestamp>1349568761931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349569251858-46</Id><Title>Florida: Romney 49%, Obama 47%</Title><Msg>Michelle made B.O. take a day off for their 20th and it slipped away.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349569251858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349569584748-47</Id><Title>Speaking of WH humor</Title><Msg>Obituary: Davey Jones of the 60s singing group "The Monkeys" died recently. Newspaper headlines read "Head Monkey Dies" Joe Biden drops his paper and runs thru the WH yelling, "I'm the Pres, I'm the Pres" Obama said he made a mistake about his earlier comment that the Libya attacks were caused by an anti-moolsim film. He now says it was a high school production of "Fiddler on the Roof".</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349569584748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349575670652-48</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Wins All-Important #$%$ Contest but Romney told a series of outright lies</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349555628435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunatley, your babbling is meaningless and won't change anything. Fox News is joking about the liberal media redefining what a "lie" is. Soledad O'Brian referred to Romney saying one thing to one audience and something else to another, which was totally bogus and makes her the liar. Voila! Hasn't the screwball left learned anything from knee jerk reporting?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349575670652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349577392783-49</Id><Title>I am Mitt and I approve this message</Title><Msg>My ?itch got a dancing horse</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349577392783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:36:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349579001789-50</Id><Title>Congressman calls evolution lie from 'pit of hell'</Title><Msg>Congressman calls evolution lie from 'pit of hell' IDIOT #$%$ REPUB</Msg><Username>dropkickcorpis12345</Username><Timestamp>1349579001789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349579963179-51</Id><Title>obama is still ahead and will get farther ahead and will win by 5% rasmussen is nothing but republican</Title><Msg>Everyone knows romknee lied his corpiss off</Msg><Username>dropkickcorpis12345</Username><Timestamp>1349579963179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349580539688-52</Id><Topic><Title>obama is still ahead and will get farther ahead and will win by 5% rasmussen is nothing but republican</Title><Username>dropkickcorpis12345</Username><Timestamp>1349579963179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's a fact jack</Msg><Username>dropkickcorpis12345</Username><Timestamp>1349580539688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349581485983-53</Id><Title>LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Arkansas Republicans tried to distance themselves from other #$%$ repubs</Title><Msg>LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Arkansas Republicans tried to distance themselves Saturday from a Republican state representative's assertion that slavery was a "blessing in disguise" #$%$, all repubs are #$%$.</Msg><Username>dropkickcorpis12345</Username><Timestamp>1349581485983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>