<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350713626118-1</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Victims Outraged as Feds Refuse to Call Fort Hood Attack Terrorism Friday, 19 Oct 2012 04:50 PM Victims of the 2009 shooting at Fort Hood in Texas that killed 13 people and wounded dozens more are outraged that the Obama Administration refuses to classify it as an act of terrorism. About 160 victims and their families released a video on Thursday describing the shooting — in which Army Maj. Nidal Hasan allegedly opened fire on a room full of soldiers — and arguing why it should be classified as a terrorist attack. Hasan, an American-born Muslim, is accused of killing 12 soldiers and a civilian on Nov. 5, 2009, at the post’s processing center. Soldiers were preparing to deploy to Afghanistan and Iraq.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1350713626118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 02:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350713673017-2</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tragic ma: ‘optimal’ my #$%$ Slams Bam on death of Libya-envoy son By GEOFF EARLE Bureau Chief Last Updated: 2:03 AM, October 20, 2012 Posted: 1:02 AM, October 20, 2012 WASHINGTON — The grieving mother of one of four Americans slain at the US Consulate in Libya was furious yesterday that the government still can’t tell her what happened a day after President Obama strangely said the tragedy was “not optimal.” “Everyone’s giving me different answers. I don’t have good answers, and they are not giving me good answers. Some of the people [from the government] looked me right in the eye and lied to me,” said Pat Smith, the mother of Sean Smith, a State Department technology expert who died with Amb#$%$ador Chris Stevens and two security officials in the attack in Benghazi last month. GRIEF:Pat Smith (left) says the government has not given her a straight answer on the death of her son, Sean (right), who was killed in the attack on the US Consulate in Libya. GRIEF:Pat Smith (left) says the government has not given her a straight answer on the death of her son, Sean (right), who was killed in the attack on the US Consulate in Libya. “Somebody is lying, or else these crooks are running our country, and I don’t choose to believe that,” she told The Post by phone from her San Diego home yesterday. “My son is dead, and I don’t know why, and I don’t know why nobody went out to help my son.”</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1350713673017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 02:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350737132837-3</Id><Title>unemployment down in 41 states!</Title><Msg>BREAKING: Obama "cooks the books" in 41 states to make it look like their unemployment has dropped by Eclectablog The all-powerful yet strangely ineffective POTUS... Washington, D.C. - In an unprecedented display of raw power, President Barack Obama "cooked the books" in 41 of the 50 states to make it appear as if their unemployment rates had dropped in the past month. Republicans are shocked by this blatant political move and left Democrats wondering what the heck took him so long. House Speaker John Boehner issued a statement saying, "There's no way in heck "that one" could have reduced the unemployment rate. I mean we have done absolutely everything in our power to ensure he couldn't make a single move that would help the economy or American workers. It's simply not possible. Also, Obamacare." Congressman Eric Cantor, the House Majority Leader told reporters that the fact that seven of the states -- Colorado, Ohio, Florida, Iowa, Nevada, Wisconsin, and North Carolina -- are so-called "swing states" makes it "blatantly obvious" that these numbers from the Bureau of Labor Statistics are fabricated. "How on this God's earth could he have been successful at lowering the unemployment rate?" Cantor asked. "This is impossible. We haven't allowed him to accomplish anything for the past four years. Also, Kenyan Muslim." Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney spoke to a rally in Pennsylvania and pronounced the BLS report "another example of the ineffectiveness" of President Obama. "When I am CEO, uh, President, we will have lower unemployment in all 50 states, not just 41. Besides, these numbers can't possibly be true. My friends haven't been hiring anyone for the past four years. Also, birth certificate."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350737132837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350740048028-4</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrat tells moderator he's 'prettier' than Crowley On Politics Catalina Camia Share 1:45PM EDT October 19. 2012 - Democrat Richard Carmona, who is running for the Senate in Arizona, apologized for joking with the male moderator of a televised debate that the man is "prettier" than CNN's Candy Crowley. "I tried to tell a joke to lighten the mood in a debate. I shouldn't have, and I'm sorry," Carmona said in a statement. Things apparently got heated between Carmona and GOP Rep. Jeff Flake in their debate Thursday. Moderator Brahm Resnik of KPNX-TV at one point said: "Now I know how Candy Crowley felt, geez," in reference to the journalist who refereed the town hall debate this week between President Obama and Mitt Romney. "You're prettier," Carmona said to Resnik. The exchange was first reported by BuzzFeed. In the Arizona race, Flake has made an issue of allegations that Carmona has mistreated women. The Republican is running an ad featuring physician Cristina Beato, a former colleague of Carmona's, who says in the commercial that the Democrat "has issues with anger, with ethics and with women." Carmona has responded with his own ad featuring retired captain Kathleen Brennan, his former SWAT team commander, who says, "Rich treats everyone with respect. It doesn't matter whether you're male or female." Carmona, a former U.S. surgeon general, was encouraged by President Obama to seek the Senate seat of retiring GOP Sen. Jon Kyl. The Arizona race is closer than expected with Flake leading</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1350740048028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 09:34:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350741792248-5</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporatio - The Valuable Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>carsonwatkins813</Username><Timestamp>1350736282147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:31:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got one of five Willie Wonka golden tickets. What about you?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350741792248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 10:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350741960617-6</Id><Topic><Title>How do you get updates for the oracel products</Title><Username>farml1234</Username><Timestamp>1350700154442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i have never seen anything like this *** You don't get around much anymore</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350741960617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 10:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350744333508-7</Id><Title>Chronic Unemployed &amp; No Longer Counted UP In All States!</Title><Msg>Millions have been thrown out of the "Labor Force" because the Obama Regime decides they are "No Longer Looking"... which dramatically improves their Unemployment Rate... which is #$%$! 7.8% my azzs! Obama has been a Debacle for all working Americans... save, of course, for those in The Federal Government and Big Unions... the only people Obama actually cares about!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1350744333508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 10:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350746745245-8</Id><Topic><Title>We Getting Serious About ORCL</Title><Username>sheriemerson396</Username><Timestamp>1350736592417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voting for Romney will sure help!</Msg><Username>chronosthegrimreaper</Username><Timestamp>1350746745245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 11:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350747101803-9</Id><Topic><Title>Chronic Unemployed &amp; No Longer Counted UP In All States!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1350744333508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 10:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rumors from Libya... Hillary supposedly has copies of memos where she requested that Borat Obumbles beef up security in Benghazi but Obumbles refused. Our Dear Leaders in Washington DC were all watching the attack live, via drone cameras and security cameras. There is a video tape. There was a six hour lull in the attack where Chris Stevens begged for support and was denied by Obumbles himself. This is NOT an error or mistake. It is TREASON!</Msg><Username>chronosthegrimreaper</Username><Timestamp>1350747101803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 11:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350747179756-10</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>High crimes, misdemeanoers, sedition and treason!</Msg><Username>chronosthegrimreaper</Username><Timestamp>1350747179756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 11:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350748931304-11</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To paraphrse; "Why doth crime prosper? When crime prospers none dare call it a crime."</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1350748931304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350748959131-12</Id><Title>Bengahzi who?</Title><Msg>Politically active Ohio University students who support Obama but haven’t even heard of the Benghazi raid or cover up scandal. Why is this not a surprise? I’m not sure if this last Presidential debate on foreign policy will even matter. Most folks who keep abreast of world affairs have made up their minds already. For those who don’t, if they tune in at all it will be to catch one more glimpse of Romney, just to see if they can picture him as President. To them, how Romney comports himself means more than the subject of the debate.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1350748959131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350751509709-13</Id><Topic><Title>they were glad when Mitt left Ma... he had a 38% approval rating</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350698140011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:55:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why is mitt such a liar? one minute he says government doesn't create jobs, and the next he says he won't cut defense spending because that will cost jobs.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1350751509709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350751846345-14</Id><Topic><Title>will gop throw a tantrum over a Mitten's debt ceiling hike?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350668129279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:35:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop are such destructive hypocrites, liars and blowhards. THEY threw a disgraceful and non productive fit over the debt ceiling and now they refuse to abide by the agreement THEY made to get past the stink THEY made........................and no doubt if Mitt is elected the gop will not say a word about the NEXT and certain debt ceiling hike.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1350751846345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 12:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350752757908-15</Id><Title>Mitt lied: Uninsured DO Die From Lack Of Coverage</Title><Msg>GOP Rep. Contradicts Romney, Says Uninsured Do Die From Lack Of Coverage By Scott Keyes on Oct 17, 2012 at 4:00 pm HENDERSON, Nevada — Last week, Mitt Romney justified his desire to repeal Obamacare by arguing that “we don’t have people who die because they don’t have insurance.” And so on Monday, ThinkProgress spoke with Tea Party freshman Rep. Joe Heck (R-NV), a former emergency medicine doctor, at a candidate forum and asked him whether Romney’s comments jibe with his past experience. Heck took issue with Romney’s assertion that emergency room care for individuals without health insurance is a real solution. “I’ve seen people presented later in the course of their disease because they didn’t health insurance,” Heck said. At that point, “it’s certainly much more difficult for them and it’s much more costly to the system”: KEYES: You’re a doctor. Mitt Romney took a little heat the other day for saying that there aren’t any folks in the United States who have died because they don’t have health insurance. Is that something you agree with in your experience? What have you seen personally? HECK: I’ve seen people presented later in the course of their disease because they didn’t health insurance. So they put off getting help until they’re far along and then it’s certainly much more difficult for them and it’s much more costly to the system. Heck’s two-fold point — that individuals without health insurance put off getting care, and that delayed treatment in the hospital or elsewhere ends up costing everyone more — is one of the overarching reasons why lawmakers passed Obamacare. In addition to the 45,000 Americans who die every year — one person every 12 minutes — because they don’t have insurance, 50 million Americans are unable to receive proper care because they lack coverage. When they visit the emergency room, as Romney touted, for care that could have been prevented or better handled elsewhere, such as an asthma attack, those costs are passed on to everyone else through higher premiums."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350752757908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350760594222-16</Id><Title>Liberals LIED about Uninsured.</Title><Msg>Seems we had to pass Obamacare because 30 to 40 million people were uninsured. After we passed ObamaCare we were told there will STILL be 30 or 40 million uninsureed! LIARS! LIARS! LIARS! LIARS!</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1350760594222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350760594739-17</Id><Title>Liberals LIED about Uninsured.</Title><Msg>Seems we had to pass Obamacare because 30 to 40 million people were uninsured. After we passed ObamaCare we were told there will STILL be 30 or 40 million uninsureed! LIARS! LIARS! LIARS! LIARS!</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1350760594739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 15:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350760643424-18</Id><Topic><Title>We Getting Serious About ORCL</Title><Username>sheriemerson396</Username><Timestamp>1350736592417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are getting serious about making Obama an EV-president!</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1350760643424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 15:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350760876495-19</Id><Title>Obama loves the one percent!</Title><Msg>He wants to tax one percent to pay for energy "solutions" that provide less than one percent of our energy!</Msg><Username>googleguy000000001</Username><Timestamp>1350760876495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 15:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350762030127-20</Id><Title>Its clear -- Barack Obama has no second term agenda!!!!!</Title><Msg>Although President Obama won't lay out his plan for a second term, we already know what it will be -- a repeat of the last four years. We can't afford four more years of crushing debt and wasteful spending. We know what President Obama will do on taxes. He's already raised taxes 21 times -- and he'll raise taxes by $2 trillion more. Middle-class families will face a $4,000-a-year tax increase just to service his debt and spending proposals. As Governor of Massachusetts, I cut taxes 19 times. As president, I won't raise taxes on anyone; I will deliver tax cuts to the middle class; and I will simplify the tax code to make it simpler, flatter, and fairer. We know what President Obama will do on spending. President Obama's already increased our debt by $5.5 trillion -- and he'll let our national debt climb to $20 trillion by 2016. He's promised a second stimulus, yet we don't even know where the first one went. As Governor of Massachusetts, I balanced the budget every year without raising taxes and led our state to a credit upgrade. As president, I will cut and cap spending, restore our AAA credit rating, and set us on a path to a balanced budget. I have a clear plan to put America on a path to prosperity. Contribute now to help promote my clear vision for America. Thanks, Mitt Romney</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350762030127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 15:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350767493453-21</Id><Topic><Title>let Margaret &amp; Helen tell you about Mittens</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350697922644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:52:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Republicans say that Obama can’t run on his record. Really? You want to talk about records? Mitt Romney was born wealthy, married wealthy and will most likely die wealthy. Bully for him. The other guy is [a] black man born in America in 1961 to a single white woman. He went on to become President of the United States. I’d say there’s no contest. Thanks to Republicans, Obama inherited the biggest mess since the great depression and in his first year in office prevented a total economic meltdown. As for Mitt’s record---he was a bully in high school and got pretty upset when his father wasn’t elected President. At the age of 46 he was bored with making more money so he decided to become a Republican simply to challenge Ted Kennedy for the Senate. By the way, he claimed that he was more Pro-Choice than Teddy. He lost. Then he spent millions of his own fortune to get himself elected Governor of Massachusetts in 2002. Four years later he left with an approval rating so low he ranked 48 out of the 50 Governors. Most of the middle class in Massachusetts got frustrated with his taxes which Mitt called fees---license fees, gun fees, gas fees, college fees… He left with a 38% approval rating. "</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350767493453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 17:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350770495731-22</Id><Topic><Title>We Getting Serious About ORCL</Title><Username>sheriemerson396</Username><Timestamp>1350736592417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sure hate these off topic posts!!!!!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1350770495731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350770993333-23</Id><Topic><Title>they were glad when Mitt left Ma... he had a 38% approval rating</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350698140011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:55:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it when Mitt in debate or elsewhere at first says he's private biz man and all that and not in govt then minutes later he brags about being the greatest Gov EVER, repubs will say ANYTHING until ya tell them to #$%$.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1350770993333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350773508208-24</Id><Topic><Title>they were glad when Mitt left Ma... he had a 38% approval rating</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350698140011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:55:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>,,,,,,,,,,,,,and he raised taxes while gov but had said he wouldn't.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1350773508208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350773836530-25</Id><Topic><Title>they were glad when Mitt left Ma... he had a 38% approval rating</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350698140011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:55:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right and mesa again DROPKICKS! GD romn acts like he did well in ma. They hated the #$%$!,and the F raised the cost of living in Ma. for the people,,,,,,raused taxes and said he wouldn't.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1350773836530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 18:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350775606949-26</Id><Topic><Title>We Getting Serious About ORCL</Title><Username>sheriemerson396</Username><Timestamp>1350736592417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, add me to the list, just bought some today.</Msg><Username>castanedadella218</Username><Timestamp>1350775606949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350777290042-27</Id><Title>Pubs and libs need to get along</Title><Msg>So in the spirit of cooperation, here's the plan. All those in favor of a Romney presidency, drive with your headlights on during the day. All those in favor of Obama, drive with your headlights off at night. Fair enough.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350777290042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350777533473-28</Id><Topic><Title>they were glad when Mitt left Ma... he had a 38% approval rating</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350698140011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:55:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it when the Bummer said he would......... Never mind. Never did anything but destroy health care as America knows it and put us 5 trillion in debt. Can you libs say post turtle.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350777533473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 19:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350778202733-29</Id><Topic><Title>let Margaret &amp; Helen tell you about Mittens</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350697922644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:52:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me paraphrase you: he has been successful in every endeavor he attempted. Served his country for twenty years without pay. Gave his entire inheritance to charity. Tithes to his church. Saved an olympics. Wasn't responsible for 44 straight months of excessive unemployment. Dramatically improved Mass. standing in respect to employment as governor. Didn't waste 5 trillion that our kids and grandkids will suffer with. Never crooked. Is American. Has lived a life anybody would be proud of. Oh, he's rich. Also, he's smart. Got 2 advanced degrees from Harvard at the same time. Those are starters. Libs like to accentuate the unimportant stuff.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350778202733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350778764818-30</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt lied: Uninsured DO Die From Lack Of Coverage</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350752757908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:05:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Health care available to all Americans. It's a matter of priorities. If one cannot afford it, they should be on Medicaid.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350778764818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350780358045-31</Id><Title>Obama's biggest most disgusting Lie EVER</Title><Msg>The Quote of the Decade: "The fact that we are here today to debate raising America's debt limit is a sign of leadership failure. It is a sign that the US Government cannot pay its own bills. It is a sign that we now depend on ongoing financial assistance from foreign countries to finance our Government's reckless fiscal policies. Increasing America's debt weakens us domestically and internationally. Leadership means that, "the buck stops here.' Instead, Washington is shifting the burden of bad choices today onto the backs of our children and grandchildren. America has a debt problem and a failure of leadership. Americans deserve better." ~ Senator Barack H. Obama, March 2006</Msg><Username>att4glte</Username><Timestamp>1350780358045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350781740403-32</Id><Title>It's Clear Romney Has The Libs Convulsing</Title><Msg>You notice the more messy and the other goons rag about Romney, the higher he goes in the polls. Please don't quit.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1350781740403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 21:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>