<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352720951252-1</Id><Title>repubs you're still full of s, worse than ever</Title><Msg>"Gore lost his home state" you #$%$ couln't shut up about that. Last week little dumb punk ryan lost his home state.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352720951252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:49:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352722793235-2</Id><Title>republican SLAUGHTER</Title><Msg>THAT is how Scarborough described it last Tues night. I don't see it at all that way. "We" won by slight margin. RESULTS may be a slaughter.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352722793235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:19:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352722907540-3</Id><Title>Jeb bush F 'ed up Fl. and that includes education!</Title><Msg>Huntsman just claimed otherwise.. Repubs are 100% dishonest.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352722907540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:21:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352724560019-4</Id><Topic><Title>republican SLAUGHTER</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352722793235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:19:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>drop, results will be a slaughter, you said. What do you mean?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352724560019</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:49:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352728793842-5</Id><Topic><Title>repubs you're still full of s, worse than ever</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352720951252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:49:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, Ryan lost his home state, Romney lost both of his home states, the one he was born in and the one he was gov of.........he couldn't even hold all of the confederacy, the bastion of the gop.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352728793842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:59:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352729187453-6</Id><Title>after the pubs take us over the fiscal cliff to bully for tax cuts for the rich</Title><Msg>the bush tax cuts will be expired! then the dems will offer a new tax cut for those making less than 250K a year, retroactive to jan 1. This cut will expire when UE goes below 6%. The pubs will be even stinkier than they are now.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352729187453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:06:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352729699761-7</Id><Title>republican "godfather of neoconservatism" says raise taxes on the rich</Title><Msg>Weekly Standard Editor Bill Kristol said on Sunday that the Republican Party should stop defending “a bunch of millionaires” and let the Bush-era tax cuts expire for the wealthiest Americans. “It won't kill the country if we raise taxes a little bit on millionaires,” he said on Fox News Sunday. “It really won't, I don't think. I don't really understand why Republicans don't take Obama's offer to freeze taxes for everyone below $250,000.” He continued: “Really, the Republican Party is going to fall on its sword to defend a bunch of millionaires, half of whom voted Democratic and half of whom live in Hollywood?”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352729699761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:14:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734182005-8</Id><Topic><Title>after the pubs take us over the fiscal cliff to bully for tax cuts for the rich</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352729187453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:06:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hopefully the numbskull pubs won't take forever to figure out that they can't stop the bush tax cuts from expiring for the rich.....and the dems WILL get what is best for the nation, extending the cuts for the middleclass who spend the money which creates demand and jobs.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352734182005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:29:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352736391662-9</Id><Topic><Title>after the pubs take us over the fiscal cliff to bully for tax cuts for the rich</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352729187453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:06:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and your Red buddies need to move to China. The rulers there make sure everything is equal------except for them. They live like the Rajah's of old while their people work 12 hour days as slaves. That's what fat cat "llberals" want here. Billionaire "liberals" such as Diane Feinstein aid and abet the Red butchers in China by owning corporations there that ship their lousy junk to America and cost American jobs. Much of the profit goes to provide the military with arms. Your "adored" one, the Kenyan, fully supports this "O"bomination.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1352736391662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:06:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352736930156-10</Id><Topic><Title>after the pubs take us over the fiscal cliff to bully for tax cuts for the rich</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352729187453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:06:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>runners, you are still the biggest #$%$ and numbskull around! Please stop whining about the fact that W's idiot tax cuts for the rich are soon to be history.....so take your head out of Tush Limpbalz rearend and listen to an arch conservative: Conservative commentator and Weekly Standard editor Bill Kristol said Sunday the Republican Party should accept new ideas, including the much-criticized ggestion by Democrats that taxes be allowed to go up on the wealthy. "It won't kill the country if we raise taxes a little bit on millionaires," he said on "Fox News Sunday." "It really won't, I don't think. I don't really understand why Republicans don't take Obama's offer."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352736930156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:15:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352738780102-11</Id><Topic><Title>after the pubs take us over the fiscal cliff to bully for tax cuts for the rich</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352729187453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:06:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Kristol is the standard?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352738780102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:46:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352739688810-12</Id><Topic><Title>after the pubs take us over the fiscal cliff to bully for tax cuts for the rich</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352729187453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:06:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you say so, i guess. I guess you are also a numbskull who can't face up to the fact that W's tax cuts for the rich are history and they will expire as intended. btw if they were such a good idea why did bush and the gop make them temporary? " the answer is that President Bush and a complicit Congress didn’t want to show the magnitude of the deficits that would result from their tax cuts. To hide those deficits as they were pushing them through they used a variety of accounting tricks. One of those tricks was attaching expiration dates so that, on paper, there wouldn’t be any long-term costs. This made the long-term deficit picture look fairly rosy on paper even as it doomed Bush’s successor and the current Congress to cleaning up the mess."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352739688810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:01:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352741459627-13</Id><Title>food stamps application</Title><Msg>I'm thinking about applying for food stamps. The program is growing by leaps and bounds. Why not look into it. I don't need foodstamps by any means, but the gravey chain is growing, so why not? Huh, I could become a taker if I proceed with this. That's what you libs voted for, didn;'t you?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352741804268-14</Id><Title>Gingrich ‘dumbfounded’ by Obama win</Title><Msg>I KNEW Obama would win based on all HONEST polling,...of course Rasmussen NOT INCLUDED! The win should come as no surprise.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352741804268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:36:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741900445-15</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this 100% GD STINKING LYING CRAP from repubs claiming democrats don't work....f yourselves repub.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352741900445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:38:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352742374543-16</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh c'mon drop. Gimmee's are growing line crazy. Evidently it's the way to go. It's not that hard to apply. You can do it on-line. If you can't beat'em, join'em. If I get foodstamps and add a little to the national debt, will anyone notice? Nah!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352742374543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:46:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352742610960-17</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd have to fudge the truth to get foodstamps, however. Small hurdle it seems. However, the good news is that I'd become a taker. But you don't have a problem with that anyway, do you?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352742610960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:50:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743420950-18</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if I go thru with foodstamps plan, think of the stuff that I can buy that I don't already get on a routine basis? I'm thinking prime rib, New york strips, the best cuts of all meat. Fresh shrimp....oh my goodness. I even know of a local beer and wine store that takes foodstamps. Hmmmm!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352743420950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:03:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352743964655-19</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are such a sad and pathetic person that you whine and worry about the poor and unemployed getting some help feeding themselves.......jeez, you should be ashamed. here are the people you are attacking: 49% of all participant households have children (17 or younger), and 55% of those are single-parent households. 15% of all participant households have elderly (age 60 or over) members. 20% of all participant households have non-elderly disabled members. The average gross monthly income per food stamp household is $731; The average net income is $336. 36% of participants are White, 22% are African-American, 10% are Hispanic, 2% are Asian, 4% are Native American, and 19% are of unknown race or ethnicity.[11]</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352743964655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:12:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352744579170-20</Id><Title>seabugc military enlistment application</Title><Msg>seabbug says he is going to enlist. the military has been growing like crazy, about 70% more just during W's tenure., leaps and bounds!! the gravey chain is growing so seabug says he wants to chow down and this is what the pubs voted for, so he is going to enlist!!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352744579170</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:22:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352744651877-21</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not attacking anyone! I'd be joining them. So I add a little to the national debt. The people in control won't notice, or mind. Just thining of those free prime rib steaks. What's the matter with that?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352744651877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:24:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352744891397-22</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are a liar to say you are not attacking these people and that you really support helping these people: 49% of all participant households have children (17 or younger), and 55% of those are single-parent households. 15% of all participant households have elderly (age 60 or over) members. 20% of all participant households have non-elderly disabled members. The average gross monthly income per food stamp household is $731; The average net income is $336. 36% of participants are White, 22% are African-American, 10% are Hispanic, 2% are Asian, 4% are Native American, and 19% are of unknown race or ethnicity.[</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352744891397</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:28:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352745187781-23</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mesa, how do you know I don't belong to one of those compartments? You don't know me. You have no idea what my circumstances are. Consider that it's possibIe that I do belong to one of the groups you cite. Consider that up to now I've been too proud to accept government cheese. The country has changed. Last Tuesday said so.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352745187781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:33:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352745337517-24</Id><Title>Keynesian spending rebuilt Europe after WW2: Marshall Plan</Title><Msg>the USA fed and rebuilt europe with the marshall plan....... it was a HUGE success......today's whiny and stupid pubs would not have done that......... most likley they wouldn't have even opposed hitler, they sure whined when FDR began helping britain and europe, prior to germany declaring war on the USA</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352745337517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:35:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352745503964-25</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are such a stupid and whiny liar. if not, just state that indeed you do support the food stamp program, and that you take back everything negative you have said about it .</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352745503964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:38:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352745900901-26</Id><Topic><Title>seabugc military enlistment application</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352744579170</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:22:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>people like tush limpbalz and ted nugent and cheney and seabug are big pumpers of the gop's tough talk, war mongering, nation building, and desire to make the military even larger and more costly....... and they prove they mean what they say by refusing to serve and by whining about the taxes to pay for it.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352745900901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:45:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352746079638-27</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just state that indeed you do support the food stamp program, and that you take back everything negative you have said about it . ................................................................................................................................................................ fine with me. To the extent that I can personally benefit from food stamps just like millions of others, I support it. Why not? I pay plenty of federal taxes. For a change, why not get something back? Seems good to me.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352746079638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:47:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352746929372-28</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>afterall, Mesa, we are in the are of not what can I do for my country, what can my country do for me? So why not go with the flow? Making more and more sense. All I have to do is fudge/lie about the truth of my personal circumstances. A minor inconvenience. And it is doubtful that anyone will come after me. All I'd need to say is that I was responding to local advertising that I've seen on TV where they said they are looking for new welfare recipients. They'd buy that. No problem.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352746929372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:02:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352747874475-29</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my biggest issue with receiving government cheese is that I'd need to go to a grocery store well outside of my neighborhood where it is less likely that I'd run into anyone I know who would see me buying prime rib with food stamps.That is a much bigger risk than the government coming after me.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352747874475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:17:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352748777971-30</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know several people who eat steak and drink fine wines on food stamps. Great program. Shop at Mexican grocery stores for best deals.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352748777971</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:32:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352748891387-31</Id><Topic><Title>food stamps application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352741459627</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>true, no doubt. Then why not me?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352748891387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:34:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352749158717-32</Id><Topic><Title>Patreaus' affair now makes sense</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352672187667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 17:16:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know, I have to agree. Paula looks hot. Wife looks like a dry old dog.... definitely needs some hair color and a hair style makeover along with an attitude adjustment. She looks stern... like a military nurse.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352749158717</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:39:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352749652123-33</Id><Topic><Title>Krugman urges President Obama to go over the “fiscal cliff” if it’s necessary.</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352557555225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let’s Not Make a Deal .....So President Obama has to make a decision, almost immediately, about how to deal with continuing Republican obstruction. How far should he go in accommodating the G.O.P.’s demands? *** Debate (you call it obstructionism) is the crucible of democracy. Very important to prevent a rubber stamp dictatorship like the first two years of Obama. Bad things happen like $1.2T deficit with no budget for 4 years and more accumulated debt under Obama than under all prior Presidents since the founding of America. What Obama has done is create a fiscal disaster. Obama shows his incompetence for the job by resorting to partisan backstabbing instead of win-win negotiation.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352749652123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:47:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352749995213-34</Id><Title>Debate (you call it obstructionism) is the crucible of democracy</Title><Msg>#$%$! You know damn well what it is and what it isn't.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352749995213</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:53:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352750091424-35</Id><Title>I know several people who eat steak and drink fine wines on food stamps.</Title><Msg>FINE wines? You're full of s.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352750091424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:54:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352756625372-36</Id><Title>disregard seabuttc whining about food stamps, he is all for them</Title><Msg>"To the extent that I can personally benefit from food stamps just like millions of others, I support it." You see, it's all about him. Nevermind the poor elderly, children, disabled and those having a hard time in a tough economy........... seaburgc is THE taker..... he wants to TAKE even if he doesn't need it, and he is ONLY a taker..... when it comes to serving in the military he WON'T, even though he is a #$%$ talking gop hawk.... and he whines about paying for the military too. what a hypocrite. all of the taxes he has paid in his enire life and ever will pay in his entire life wouldn't even make a dent in the booze bill at the military's officer's clu#$%$ around the world.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352756625372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:43:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352756987805-37</Id><Title>give the tax whiners little plaques for the stuff they like</Title><Msg>a whiny brat in diapers like seabugc might be happier if there was a plaque in the bagdhad embassy saying thank you for all the taxes you have paid and ever will pay, you have helped buy .001% of the carpet in the hall ways.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352756987805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:49:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352757678862-38</Id><Topic><Title>disregard seabuttc whining about food stamps, he is all for them</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352756625372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course it's all about me. Just like all the other takers who want free stuff. Why should they get all the free stuff and not me? As I have paid plenty in tax, it's about time I get some free tangibles in return. I just need to go to a grocery way outside my neighborhood where I'm not likely to run into friends who might see me buying prime rib, filet mignon....stuff that I don't ordinarily eat. Why not?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352757678862</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:01:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352758378402-39</Id><Title>Obama Regime Makes Nixon &amp; Co Look Like Boy Scouts!</Title><Msg>News Flash! There is only one human being on the planet who could have approved this wide-ranging Cover-Up of the Petraeus Scandal and prevented critical information about the CIA Director from going immediately to the Heads of Justice, National Intelligence, Defense &amp; State and both Congressional Intelligencel committees. Only ONE... Barack Obama!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1352758378402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:12:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352758584432-40</Id><Title>on-line food stamp application</Title><Msg>Found this easy method to apply for foodstamps. It says: 1 in 7 Americans Have Received Food Stamps. Get Food Stamps Today. Nationwide food stamp applications and Electronic Benefit Transfer (EBT) applications have increased by 70% since 2007. 1 in 7 Americans are now benefiting from the Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program, also known as SNAP. State and federal grants that support SNAP get renewed regularly, and the SNAP budget recently received an increase of 11%. A family of six previously receiving 250 USD a month may now get 606 USD monthly. Why Apply For Food Stamps? •Because you can apply online, your application is processed faster. •The SNAP budget has increased so you can now receive more. •Thousands of food banks are available. •It is easier than ever to get food stamps! It is easier than ever to apply for food stamps today. State governments are processing food stamp applications faster because all you have to do is apply for food stamps online.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352758584432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:16:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352758915895-41</Id><Title>re: on-line food stamp application</Title><Msg>the website highlites the following: Thereyago folks, easier than ever it says. They must want me to have food stamps since it's so easy.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352758915895</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:21:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352758991689-42</Id><Topic><Title>give the tax whiners little plaques for the stuff they like</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352756987805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:49:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by now all the taxes seabuggerc has and will ever pay won't even cover the DoD toilet paper bill for a day, but i say give him a little plaque thanking him for paying for the programs he likes.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352758991689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:23:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352759120196-43</Id><Topic><Title>give the tax whiners little plaques for the stuff they like</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352756987805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:49:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well if you think I pay hardly anything in tax then you won't mind if I indulge myself on the free stuff I can get from food stamsp.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352759120196</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:25:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352759612486-44</Id><Topic><Title>give the tax whiners little plaques for the stuff they like</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352756987805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:49:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now what are you whining about? i said you deserve a plaque for paying for the stuff you like. no doubt all the taxes you have paid in your entire life won't even cover .001% of the carpet in W's 1 billion $ iraq embassy......or maybe your plaque can say "I didn't whine about helping a gop president pay do what was needed".... as in "unless money is loosened up, the sucker could go down"george w bush</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352759612486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:33:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352760509537-45</Id><Title>let's become 350 million whiny brat nations of one rather than the USA</Title><Msg>that way nobody will have to pay any taxes! we all can secede from counrty ,state, county and town, and nobody has to pay for #$%$ schools, roads, police, fire departments , courts, hospitals, airports and your disabled , elderly and poor........is that is pubbies?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352760509537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352760735000-46</Id><Title>repubs/////////ALL you should be saying IS........lets ALL TRY to get along!</Title><Msg>But.you're not////////////You're THEEEEEEEEE problem.....DUH!!!!!!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352760735000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:52:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352761139988-47</Id><Topic><Title>let's become 350 million whiny brat nations of one rather than the USA</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352760509537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see your point, Mesa. Someone has to pay for the food stamps that I plan on getting.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352761139988</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352762440573-48</Id><Title>republicans</Title><Msg>ALL you should be saying is...LETS TALK! If you aren't.....you're 100% F' ed up.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352762440573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:20:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352762721452-49</Id><Title>see your point, Mesa. Someone has to pay for the food stamps that I plan on getting.</Title><Msg>seebe, if ya think you have ANY point at all, you're an IDIOT! RED staes TAKE more tax $'s and give back LESS than blue states...like Alaska and Palin,.YA GOT NUTHIN! just say lets work together!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352762721452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:25:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352762799877-50</Id><Title>Oh,..hey seebe,..what happened with your prediction of romn win?</Title><Msg>You and Dick Morris????????</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352762799877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:26:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352764073682-51</Id><Topic><Title>see your point, Mesa. Someone has to pay for the food stamps that I plan on getting.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352762721452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:25:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>translation: I work with you. You don't work with me.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352764073682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:47:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352764887414-52</Id><Topic><Title>Krugman urges President Obama to go over the “fiscal cliff” if it’s necessary.</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352557555225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 09:25:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Krugman is the one who wants to use economic blackmail to achieve goals democrats lack the votes to achieve through the normal legislative process. Now the idiot recommends austerity! ...after recommending for years to spend as much as possible. There is no sign whatsoever that we wouldn't go back to a financial crisis were the deficit to become suddenly much smaller. Housing would resume its fall and banks right behind that.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1352764887414</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:01:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352765549504-53</Id><Title>rpubs,.ya got NUTHIN</Title><Msg>Nothing you're al not 100% guilty of yourselves.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352765549504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:12:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352772662738-54</Id><Topic><Title>see your point, Mesa. Someone has to pay for the food stamps that I plan on getting.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1352762721452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:25:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you've never worked in your life, that is obvious, you are a taker and moocher living off your mom's money.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352772662738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:11:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352773109477-55</Id><Topic><Title>on-line food stamp application</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1352758584432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:16:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all know that this crisis was created by people on food stamps, not by banksters earning $ millions. So why not give big bailouts to the banksters and remove food stamps to pay for it. This will make the incentives clear, right?</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1352773109477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:18:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352773232953-56</Id><Topic><Title>let's become 350 million whiny brat nations of one rather than the USA</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352760509537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>someone had to pay for roads, schools, police, fire depts, courts, defense, hosptals, airports, disabled , elderly, and poor; someone had to pay to defeat hitler and the marshall plan to rebuild europe and for W to toss billions of dollars on pallets in cash into iraq where it disappereard. Great that you are a watchdog barking over food money for the poor, disabled, unemployed and elderly though, keep up the good work! why don't you just go off and live in a cave and not worry about taxes anymore? All your yipping and yapping, a doofus rightwing chihuahua is really silly and pathetic Would you be happier if poor children go to bed hungry at night?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352773232953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:20:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352774331112-57</Id><Title>the USA spends .47% of its gdp on food stamps to help the poor</Title><Msg>that's a little perspective for the whiny wet diaper crybaby pubs here like seaburgc who seem can't stand helping feed poor families and whine incessantly about tax dollars being used for that. (and never mind that tax dollars once helped feed and house Mittens family) ( calculation based on $16 trillion gdp and $75 billion cost of food stamps)</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352774331112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:38:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352774380851-58</Id><Topic><Title>let's become 350 million whiny brat nations of one rather than the USA</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352760509537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better yet let's become slaves to the usurios banksters that control BOTH perties and continue to hock us, our children and grandchildren. These same swine are transferring our wealth to the Chi-coms. All the better to build their global plantation. All foretold in scripture which I doubt you've ever read.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1352774380851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352774677824-59</Id><Topic><Title>let's become 350 million whiny brat nations of one rather than the USA</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352760509537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you just go off and live in a cave and not worry about taxes anymore? All your doofus rightwing chihuahua yipping and yapping is really silly and pathetic . Would you be happier if poor children go to bed hungry at night? Is this part of your gop family values or part of your christianity or both or what?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352774677824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:44:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352775050812-60</Id><Topic><Title>the USA spends .47% of its gdp on food stamps to help the poor</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352774331112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"omg" the yippy yappy chihuahua rightwing guardians of the nation's money say. "we are spending 0.47% of the nations gdp on foodstamps to help feed poor families, and it's nearly time for thanksgiving and it's close to christmas!" "this must stop , who knows it might go up to 0.5% and it will be the end of civilization, omg!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1352775050812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:50:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>