<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344139472000-1</Id><Topic><Title>The important thing is what Obama's done in 3-3/4 years</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344108083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 15:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, the important thing is what Obama has done in 3-1/2 years. Whats a few months when we've had 47 months of record failure in this administration. You're an idiot. He's running out of time whether its 6 months or 4 and you're hoping he does something in the next 5 months to make up for the past 3-1/2 years? You can dump that dream, DA. I win, Buttkickuuuuuu!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1344139472000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 00:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344171076000-2</Id><Title>angel Moroni's face seen on chicken sandwich</Title><Msg>angel Moroni's face appeared on chicken sandwich, others said it was jesus's face. One person said it was moohammud, but all the others threw him out into the street. background info: " An angel named Moroni told Joesph Smith that some gold plates containing a sacred 1,400 year-old text were buried on a hill nearby. The angel told Smith to go dig on the hill, which he did. Smith dug up a box that contained the gold plates. " this became the source for book of mormon that Smith self published, and put his life back on track after his conviction for fraud.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1344171076000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 08:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344171525000-3</Id><Title>Fox news right to lie and distort &amp; weasel</Title><Msg>rightwing Fox news argued their modus operandi in court: the right to lie, distort and weasel in the typical gop manner. " a Florida Court of Appeals unanimously agreed with an assertion by FOX News that there is no rule against distorting or falsifying the news in the United States. Lawyers paid by Bill O'Reilly's bosses argued in court that Fox can lie with impunity. It's their right under the 1st Ammendment FOX asserted that there are no written rules against distorting news in the media. They argued that, under the First Amendment, broadcasters have the right to lie or deliberately distort news reports on public airwaves. During their appeal, FOX asserted that there are no written rules against distorting news in the media. They argued that, under the First Amendment, broadcasters have the right to lie or deliberately distort news reports on public airwaves. Fox attorneys did not dispute Akre’s claim that they pressured her to broadcast a false story, they simply maintained that it was their right to do so."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1344171525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344172713000-4</Id><Topic><Title>angel Moroni's face seen on chicken sandwich</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1344171076000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 08:51:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Telling children about this s should be child abuse" yep, it's a form of brain washing.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1344172713000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344172973000-5</Id><Title>Mitten's new healthcare plan</Title><Msg>"I’m pretty sure that Mitt Romney could rename the exchanges as “Ronald Reagan Insurance Marketplaces,” the subsidies as “Free Enterprise Vouchers,” and the individual mandate as, I don’t know, the “Stop the Free Riders Program” or something, and not one in a hundred conservatives would complain about the new plan. As I’ve said, they don’t mind the Affordable Care Act at all; it’s Obamacare that they hate. Which, perhaps, explains why Mitt Romney could get himself nominated in the first place despite never disowning his Massachusetts health care reforms."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1344172973000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344173623000-6</Id><Title>and for our Suday dinner</Title><Msg>crab cakes. 1 1/2 lbs lump crab meat mixed with decadent may, eggs, dijon mustard, worcester, chives, and paresly and bread crums. Made 8 huge cakes. Served with corn on cob, my own award winning cole slaw and my homegrown beets. Eat your hearts out!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344173623000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344173958000-7</Id><Topic><Title>decadent may</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344173853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mayo. Forgot. Also sauteed in butter.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344173958000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344174540000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Howmuch ya pay up there for 1lb of lump or just good crab?</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344173901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:38:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crab is expensive. This morning I paid $16 for 8 oz jumbo lump crab meat and $24 for pound of regular lump crab meat. I do this once per year in the summer. Just too expensive.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344174540000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344175535000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Howmuch ya pay up there for 1lb of lump or just good crab?</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344173901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:38:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Havre De Grace, gorgeous little town at the top of the Chesapeake Bay. On your way to NJ. Picturesque.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344175535000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344176119000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Howmuch ya pay up there for 1lb of lump or just good crab?</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344173901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:38:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cole slaw award winning. I awarded it to myself. Fresh head of cabbage. Diced cucumber. Carrot, celery and onion of course. Diced red pepper just for color and taste of course. Dressing made of red wine vinegar, dijon mustard, salt and sugar. 1/2 cup mayo and 1/2 cup sour cream. Gotta add fresh paresly and mix in caraway seeds and celery seeds. Very fresh and very tasty side. Looks nice too.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344176119000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344176910000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Howmuch ya pay up there for 1lb of lump or just good crab?</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344173901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:38:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor. Self-depracating humor is some of the best. Pols ought to try it. People relate better if you can poke fun at yourself.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344176910000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344177971000-12</Id><Title>ronnie reagan insurance marketplaces</Title><Msg>Mittens should rename the ACA health insurance exhanges as "ronnie reagan insurance marketplaces......... and the subsidies as "free enterprise vouchers.."................ and called the mandate the "stop the free riders program.."....... 99% of conservatives would approve of it. It's not the Affordable Care Act they hate at all...... they hate obamacare.......... maybe that explains how Mittens got nominated in the first place , since he wrote the blue print for the ACA, said it's the "responsible" way to go, and recently praised universal healthcare in Israel.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1344177971000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344178087000-13</Id><Topic><Title>The important thing is what Obama's done in 3-3/4 years</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344108083000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 15:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And buckwheat still can't come up with something Obama has done the past 3-1/2 years to cheer about. All he has is buckeroo is a db. Well, yes I am, proud to be a Dem Buster. You spout trash about Bush and Romney but have nothing good about Obama. You realize this makes you look like a fool with his finger in the dike. What a dope.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1344178087000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344179877000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Major Change In Trend Coming</Title><Username>tilliekdl412</Username><Timestamp>1344173781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:36:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post of the day! Thanks</Msg><Username>leroynoi408</Username><Timestamp>1344179877000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344187265000-15</Id><Title>dropkick, I must congradulate you!</Title><Msg>You single-handedly kicked One-Stars Axx!! I bet the loser is going insane trying to one star you!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1344187265000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344187478000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344185256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unfortunately the polarized tenor of this board leaves little room for humor. You spelled it "humour"...are you a Brit? The most humorless guy on this board is Mesa and his multiple IDs. Not only humorless he is, but always angry, always carrying on about some ancient injustice, some unfairness somewhere. That guy Mesa gets out of bed in the morning angry. It is characteristic of the hard left.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344187478000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344187550000-17</Id><Topic><Title>I have DROPKICKED ou liiars CONSTANTLY</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344186851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comrade, the sooner you abandon the Democratic Party the better. NONE of these presidents ever had the interests of the people at heart. NONE! They have all bled America of its wealth and industry! They have all involved the US as Global Murderer and Executioner! They have all taken away our FREEDOM. Why, comrade, if you look at the situation correctly, they are all ONE PERSON! A BIG Medusa-head of EVIL. They turn everything they look at to Stone! They even captivate the people for YEARS with election BS! WOW! I mean, I feel sorry for the people who are so deprived as to sit around and talk about Romney and Obama! BOTH TOTAL LOSERS! Comrades, it is time to: “ wake up and Smell the Coffee!”</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1344187550000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344187687000-18</Id><Title>Romney no chick-fil-A plans</Title><Msg>Here we have an issue that is ready made on which Romney can capitalize. Accordingto what I've read he does not plan to say anything about it. What a mistake! But that's the guy we got. We'll have to leave it to others to force him right. Because he won't do it on his own. What a shame.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344187687000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344187978000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344185256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comrade, “Anger” if properly utilized is a source of power and strength. Negatives are Positives if utilized correctly. I made a mint in the market by my negative nature. I am too conservative and I don’t trust anyone. I picked some good stocks years ago, by scrutinizing them, and I had a portfolio with over 800-percent gains. Years ago. I can smell Corruption. I can taste Murder! There is Blood in the Water, comrade, it is only a matter of time before the sharks get a sense of it.</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1344187978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344188905000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344185256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comrade, “Anger” if properly utilized is a source of power and strength. &gt; .................................................................. if you are into power. Carl, why not tell us about power? I hear power is like an aphrodesiac. I don't get it. I suppose you do. What is it about power that makes one want to control the every day behavior and habits of others?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344188905000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344189335000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344185256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many times have I told you to: “Hold My ….!!” I think that’s Humor!??</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1344189335000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344190353000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344185256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you learn that the idiocies of the 7-billion people on this planet will directly affect you, then you begin to understand, the importance of modifying the behavior of others. I am a Lion, Not a Sheep. I cannot survive on a Lambs portion; therefore, as a lion when I make a Kill … I LIVE … and those around me benefit from the Scraps, comrade! Power is Good.</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1344190353000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344191482000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344185256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you learn that the idiocies of the 7-billion people on this planet will directly affect you, then you begin to understand, the importance of modifying the behavior of others.&gt; .................................................................. yeah, plenty are idiots. Yet I would never ever try to tell someone else how to live their life. What they can do or not do. What car they can drive. What they eat. It's called freedom. A concept lost on you. You libs think everyone else are idiots. That only you know best because you are so much smarter than they. Screw that crap. I reject it. Freedom loving people reject that. The people will defeat it, at least in this country.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344191482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344192870000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344185256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, comrade, You are Dictated to every day! Go try and smoke some POT?? Hey, I know people that attest to its Religious power to give dreams and visions. Medically, Pot is Harmless. Try your Freedom there, comrade. Food, try and eat: “an endangered species,” or try, Try anything, because you are dictated to in every way, shape and form. Some Cheese from France could land you in Jail. Try fishing and watch how fast “You are dictated to” because you caught one too many, or too small, or some other dictatable Item; because “as we know,” America Created the Heavens and the Earth, and therefore, all belongs to America! Try and smoke a Cigarette?? Try and Order Cigarettes over the internet? You have no freedom, comrade, it is all part of your delusional thinking, as a lamb, you have no power; therefore, you pretend "all is well" and nothing is wrong in this world. Freedom … MY AXX!! See, comrade, at Dachau the camp guards funneled the sheep at the main gates, whipping them and dogs barking, but nobody had the sense to fight back, nobody. All sheep, and a Sheep asked Once: “where is this Freedom,” after reading the “WORK BRINGS FREEDOM” SLOGAN ON THE MAIN GATE. THE GUARD “LAUGHED,” POINTING TO THE SMOKE STACKS … Somke emminating from the stacks... “THERE IS YOUR FREEDOM!” THE SHEEP THOUGHT IT WAS A "WORK CAMP" and would bring freedom, THEREFORE, the sheep WENT SHEEPISHLY INTO AGREEMENT WITH HIS EXECUTIONERS. SAD, BUT TRUE. A GREAT MAN HAS RESPONSIBILITIES TO MODIFY THE BEHAVIOR OF OTHERS, COMRADE. A Lion would Fight!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1344192870000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344194183000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Phil, I have a big sense of humor</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344185256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, rules made by others who want to control what one does. I live under it. Some reasonable. Much not. Doesn't mean I like it.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1344194183000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344194505000-26</Id><Title>Jail Obama, Even the Media is Waking up!</Title><Msg>http://blog.alexanderhiggins.com/2012/08/05/arrest-dc-politicians-supporting-al-qaeda-161001/ I guess its all just too obvious!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1344194505000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344201992000-27</Id><Title>McCain would haqve been a better President!</Title><Msg>And Palin would have been a better vice President! Even Democrats agree!</Msg><Username>captain_cazo_schettino.the_brave</Username><Timestamp>1344201992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344202533000-28</Id><Topic><Title>angel Moroni's face seen on chicken sandwich</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1344171076000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 08:51:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>people are so gullible, not all though and hence joesph smith was convicted of fraud........ the gullible still fall for BS though, like Mitten's tax plan which doesn't add up... spend more for the military and no changes to SS for most of the boomers.......all paid for by extending the bush tax cuts plus cutting income taxes 20% more???? .......... jeez.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1344202533000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344203170000-29</Id><Title>demon moohammuds face appears on a pile of dog poo</Title><Msg>This is a fact! you can't make this stuff up!</Msg><Username>captain_cazo_schettino.the_brave</Username><Timestamp>1344203170000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344205444000-30</Id><Topic><Title>McCain would haqve been a better President!</Title><Username>captain_cazo_schettino.the_brave</Username><Timestamp>1344201992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plugs, the Plagiarist, Biden was such a good pick for Obama.</Msg><Username>goodgal000000001</Username><Timestamp>1344205444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344205776000-31</Id><Topic><Title>I have DROPKICKED ou liiars CONSTANTLY</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344186851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hahahahahahaha, Carter left the country with 15% interest rates and shortages of gas. Everyone had a job when Reagan was Pres, economy was recovering. People looking for jobs now are out of luck. One of the biggest reasons for many of the problems subsequently was Greenspan and his yoyo interest rates. Can you stop lying long enough to tell us what Obama has done that you approve of? Simple question, give it a shot. You don't know what a dropkick is, DA. Everything you babble is halfassed liberal head banging. But maybe I'll give you 1 star for effort. Hahahahahaha! DB (Dem Buster) on patrol.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1344205776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344206311000-32</Id><Topic><Title>I have DROPKICKED ou liiars CONSTANTLY</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344186851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only things you do constantly is spew, rant and rave.</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1344206311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344206565000-33</Id><Title>Republicans always make better Presidents</Title><Msg>Than Democrats.</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1344206565000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344206611000-34</Id><Topic><Title>McCain would haqve been a better President!</Title><Username>captain_cazo_schettino.the_brave</Username><Timestamp>1344201992000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Lefties hate Bush because he was a great President!</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1344206611000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344206680000-35</Id><Title>Anybody want to take bets?</Title><Msg>If Barack Obama is reelected, how long will it take his new Republican Congress to impeach him?</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1344206680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344209079000-36</Id><Title>IT IS OBVIOUS OBAMA HAST TO BE VOTED OUT</Title><Msg>Or our country will be ruined forever. Who ever thought that one president can do so much damage in 3 1/2 years. Carter did a lot of damage, but obama would get triple gold medal for ruining america.</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1344209079000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344210247000-37</Id><Topic><Title>I have DROPKICKED ou liiars CONSTANTLY</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1344186851000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buckwheat hits the bottle everyday about this time. "ou liiars" Being a liberal crackpot is one thing, but a drunk one is a crackup. Does anyone really think this goon has all his marbles?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1344210247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>