<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349607567367-1</Id><Title>Any idea which way ORCL will trade next week?</Title><Msg>I was watching some trade videos on TheContrarianTrader blog and found some great videos. His analysis was really good and be being new I got a lot out of them. I watched his older videos and his calls were accurate as well. I know there are a bunch of guys that pick stocks and send alerts but the contrarian trader puts himself out there to prove himself unlike other so called pros. Does anyone know of his paid services?</Msg><Username>jermain.mcbride</Username><Timestamp>1349607567367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 06:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349612548863-2</Id><Title>As always, repubs GOT NUTHIN! Jobless wise.......</Title><Msg>Not impressed with jobless numbers from when Obama started till now? Not improved enough? Yet you were impressed with reagan first 4 years? You're scummy hypocrite double talking stinking repub partisan liars...DROPKICK!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1349612548863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 08:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349614354987-3</Id><Title>Mitt's high on ethanol? . Mitt embraces ethanol subsidies.</Title><Msg>Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney released an energy plan recently that supports Washington's ethanol quota</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349614354987</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 08:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349614529778-4</Id><Topic><Title>LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Arkansas Republicans tried to distance themselves from other #$%$ repubs</Title><Username>dropkickcorpis12345</Username><Timestamp>1349581485983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:44:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitten's supporters: a Republican state representative’s asserted that slavery was a “blessing in disguise” and a Republican state House candidate advocates deporting all Muslims. The claims were made in books written, respectively, by Rep. Jon Hubbard of Jonesboro and House candidate Charlie Fuqua of Batesville.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349614529778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 08:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349616550746-5</Id><Title>$6 Gasoline in California -- QE3 is working</Title><Msg>Obama's socialist rhetoric functions as the ideological mechanism that obfuscates reality. Gasoline prices rose 4 cents overnight after going up 20 cents overnight on Friday. Hyper inflation!!! Obama has re-created the Wiemar Republic!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349616550746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349616811753-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, And "Trickle Down" Economics</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349210863126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over the past 30 years, the term "Trickle Down" economics was coined by American socialists to slam the power of Capitalism to build businesses and create jobs. It's been 6 years since the democrat left seized control of congress and declared everything Bush sent them "dead on arrival"... ... what will 4 more years of Obama's "trickle-down" economics give us???? GREECE, that's what! *** Obama has already signed into law higher taxes effective January 1st along with plans bigger government spending. Obama and the Dems created the fiscal cliff. They aren't re-negotiating anything if Obama is re-elected. Obama is turning America into Greece and Spain. Prolong the misery. 4 more years. You v*ill ALL be EQUAL!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349616811753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349617125035-7</Id><Topic><Title>obama is still ahead and will get farther ahead and will win by 5% rasmussen is nothing but republican</Title><Username>dropkickcorpis12345</Username><Timestamp>1349579963179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:19:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BWHHAHHAHHAHHAHHAAAAA!!! Jesse Jackson is in hiding. No one watches Oprah anymore. People are fleeing the stock market. Hugo Chavez will go down. He is a cancer. Chavez, Saddam Huessein, Gaddafi and Iran have all conspired to raise the price of oil to $100 per barrel. Soon we shall all be free.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349617125035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349617313674-8</Id><Title>earth is 9000 yrs old says gop science committee member</Title><Msg>"It seems to be, first of all, from what I understand from doctors, it’s really rare. If it’s a legitimate rape, the female body has ways to try to shut the whole thing down.” Akin......gop science committee member “I don’t believe that the earth is but about 9,000 years old." Rep. Paul Broun, who sits on House Science Committee , “I’m not anti-science, I’m pro-science. But we ought to have some believable science,” Ralph Hall gop chairman of science committee</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349617313674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349617602378-9</Id><Title>Rebublican leader compares women to farm animals who should be forced to do what farmers make livestock do</Title><Msg>if farmers have to “deliver calves, dead or alive,” then a woman carrying a dead fetus, or one not expected to survive, should have to carry it to term. Rep. Terry England (R-</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349617602378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349618178720-10</Id><Title>gop leader says slavery was a blessing, another gop leader said rape is a blessing</Title><Msg>only rebublicans would spout off such contempable nonsense as that rape and slavery are blessings.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349618178720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:56:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349618371755-11</Id><Title>What do you do with a drunken sailor</Title><Msg>early in the morning.... Put him in in the shower with Jerry Sandusky. Obama's economy has slowly been getting worse since early 2010 when Obamacare was passed.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349618371755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349621483231-12</Id><Title>Rep Hank Johnson (D-GA) claimed Guam may capsize</Title><Msg>Because USA has too many military personnell on the island. Don't everybody walk to the same side of the island! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349621483231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349622126000-13</Id><Title>Our real Presidential choise is between Mitt Romney and Joe Biden</Title><Msg>Because Barack Obama will be impeached within a year: (1) Fast &amp; Furious (2) Libyan Embassy (3) Many other reasons</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349622126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349622386106-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, And "Trickle Down" Economics</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349210863126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama believes in an economy where the Government tinkles down on the people.</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349622386106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349623931927-15</Id><Title>Obama spending binge never happened....Government outlays rising at slowest pace since 1950s</Title><Msg>Obama spending binge never happened Government outlays rising at slowest pace since 1950s WASHINGTON (MarketWatch) — Of all the falsehoods told about President Barack Obama, the biggest whopper is the one about his reckless spending spree. As would-be president Mitt Romney tells it: “I will lead us out of this debt and spending inferno.” Almost everyone believes that Obama has presided over a massive increase in federal spending, an “inferno” of spending that threatens our jobs, our businesses and our children’s future. Even Democrats seem to think it’s true. But it didn’t happen. Although there was a big stimulus bill under Obama, federal spending is rising at the slowest pace since Dwight Eisenhower brought the Korean War to an end in the 1950s. Even hapless Herbert Hoover managed to increase spending more than Obama has. Here are the facts, according to the official government statistics: • In the 2009 fiscal year — the last of George W. Bush’s presidency — federal spending rose by 17.9% from $2.98 trillion to $3.52 trillion. Check the official numbers at the Office of Management and Budget. • In fiscal 2010 — the first budget under Obama — spending fell 1.8% to $3.46 trillion. • In fiscal 2011, spending rose 4.3% to $3.60 trillion. • In fiscal 2012, spending is set to rise 0.7% to $3.63 trillion, according to the Congressional Budget Office’s estimate of the budget that was agreed to last August. • Finally in fiscal 2013 — the final budget of Obama’s term — spending is scheduled to fall 1.3% to $3.58 trillion. Read the CBO’s latest budget outlook. Over Obama’s four budget years, federal spending is on track to rise from $3.52 trillion to $3.58 trillion, an annualized increase of just 0.4%. There has been no huge increase in spending under the current president, despite what you hear. Why do people think Obama has spent like a drunken sailor? It’s in part because of a fundamental misunderstanding of the federal budget. What people forget (or never knew) is that the first year of every presidential term starts with a budget approved by the previous administration and Congress. The president only begins to shape the budget in his second year. It takes time to develop a budget and steer it through Congress — especially in these days of congressional gridlock. The 2009 fiscal year, which Republicans count as part of Obama’s legacy, began four months before Obama moved into the White House. The major spending decisions in the 2009 fiscal year were made by George W. Bush and the previous Congress. Like a relief pitcher who comes into the game with the bases loaded, Obama came in with a budget in place that called for spending to increase by hundreds of billions of dollars in response to the worst economic and financial calamity in generations.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349623931927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349624835418-16</Id><Title>increase in federal spending under Obama is dwarfed by W's colossal increase</Title><Msg>the increase in federal spending under Obama is dwarfed by the colossal increase under President Bush. Don't believe it? Let's go to the chart. Here's Federal Expenditures from 2000-2011 (quarterly figures, annualized), from the St. Louis Fed: As you can see, from 2000 to 2008, under President Bush, Federal spending rose by $1.3 trillion, from $1.9 trillion a year to $3.2 trillion a year. From 2009 to 2011, meanwhile, under President Obama, federal spending has risen by $600 billion, from $3.2 trillion a year to $3.8 trillion a year. It has also now begun to decline. ($3.59 trillion for 2012) In other words, federal government spending under President Bush increased 2X as much as it has under President Obama.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349624835418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349628126885-17</Id><Topic><Title>increase in federal spending under Obama is dwarfed by W's colossal increase</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349624835418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:47:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, BOTH are beholden to the nice shylock banksters. Bush's grand daddy was in bed with Brown Brothers Harriman Bank which was charged with aiding Hitler in 1940. The Kenyan is in bed with Goldman-Sachs Bank and has appointed about 50 of their officers to run ALL the countriy's money affairs. Oh, did I mention, Goldman-Sachs is the front for the Rothschilds in this country. Oh, it's so nice having shylocks and usurors running our finances. They can steal you blind without you even knowing.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349628126885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349631887151-18</Id><Title>over 20% of deficit is due to Bush &amp; gop tax cuts</Title><Msg>So republicans, please consider that before you throw another destructive tanturm over the debt ceiling. The Congressional Budget Office has calculated that........expiration of the Bush tax cuts....would reduce the deficit by $221 billion. ...... the components of the fiscal cliff from smallest to largest. As you can see, the expiring Bush-era tax cuts are by far the biggest component, totaling $221 billion. By comparison, the sequester would save $65 billion.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349631887151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349632439372-19</Id><Topic><Title>Rep Hank Johnson (D-GA) claimed Guam may capsize</Title><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349621483231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being he's black and a politician, he must have been schooled in Chicago.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349632439372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349632740769-20</Id><Title>Smoochers and freeloaders</Title><Msg>My ?itch got a dancing horse -- Mitt</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349632740769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:59:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349637312438-21</Id><Title>100% of the Annual Deficit is due to Excessive Democrat SPENDING!</Title><Msg>And Obama STILL doesn't know why Romney CAN'T give $5 trillion in tax cuts to the rich on an annual revenue of $2.2 billion. Obama dhas never done a budget so he doesn't KNOW that our annual revenue in only $2.2 trillion. BOZO the OBOOBOO!</Msg><Username>goodgoi000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349637312438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349637524902-22</Id><Title>Obama's increase in federal spending last year is DWARFED by Obama's COLOSSAL increase in federal spending this year!</Title><Msg>And its even worse next year!</Msg><Username>goodgoi000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349637524902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349637596622-23</Id><Topic><Title>Our real Presidential choise is between Mitt Romney and Joe Biden</Title><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349622126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:02:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An obvious typo you ignorant ding-a-ling!</Msg><Username>goodgoi000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349637596622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:19:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349637698733-24</Id><Title>dropkick now has five variations of his yahoo fake id</Title><Msg>As if one wasn't dumb enough.</Msg><Username>goodgoi000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349637698733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349639088789-25</Id><Topic><Title>dropkick now has five variations of his yahoo fake id</Title><Username>goodgoi000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349637698733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And he couldn't dropkick a balloon full of s**t.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349639088789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349643104131-26</Id><Topic><Title>increase in federal spending under Obama is dwarfed by W's colossal increase</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349624835418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:47:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W's 1st budget ...$1.9 trillion W's last budget....$3.2 trillion obama's 1st....$3.2 trillion ...............2012..$3.6 trillion kinda obvious who did the bigger increase of spending, isn't it? the increase in federal spending under Obama is dwarfed by the colossal increase under President Bush.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349643104131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349643900897-27</Id><Topic><Title>over 20% of deficit is due to Bush &amp; gop tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349631887151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:44:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop threw a tantrum over the debt ceiling. and now refuse to make the spending cuts they agreed to make to end the tantrum they threw in the first place. They say cutting defense will cost jobs....... they say that even though they rejected a veterans jobs bill because they say govenment spending must be cut....... except for their spending , of course.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349643900897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349645021982-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, And "Trickle Down" Economics</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349210863126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RE: Stockman Sometime a person realizes that statements he has made to the public, while believing them at the time he made them, were completely wrong. Some people just forget about it --- after all everyone is wrong more or less infrequently. Others feel ethically obliged to admit to their mistake and try to correct, to the extent possible the misimpressions of others. It seems some Repubs either haven't received the message --- or have choosen to ignore it.</Msg><Username>economist_too</Username><Timestamp>1349645021982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349646575080-29</Id><Title>Ryan compares Romney's debate performance to Reagan</Title><Msg>#$%$ repubs will SAY ANYTHING! Obama debate was like reagan 1984 first debate when we all knew the #$%$ reagn definitely had ALHZHIEMERS!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1349646575080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349646766559-30</Id><Topic><Title>dropkick now has five variations of his yahoo fake id</Title><Username>goodgoi000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349637698733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five? You'll just see one at a time.. I've not written down my passwords because I'm not a #$%$ anal repub like you and I've been busy. Repubs got NUTHIN,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1349646766559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647095111-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama spending binge never happened....Government outlays rising at slowest pace since 1950s</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349623931927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mesa dropkicks you db's with every post//////you db's got NUTHIN.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1349647095111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:58:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657088518-32</Id><Topic><Title>dropkick now has five variations of his yahoo fake id</Title><Username>goodgoi000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349637698733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shut it Charles Dickens... you're not getting paid by the word. He posts the same thing over and over.... Obama says the same lie over and over like a 5th grader because he thinks if he keeps repeating it lemmings will believe. That's why lemmings on the street in Harlem believe Obama is Mormon.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349657088518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657177057-33</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan compares Romney's debate performance to Reagan</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1349646575080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:49:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He exposed Obama as a blow hard. Knock out punch. Romney: 52% Obama: 47%</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349657177057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657339627-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, And "Trickle Down" Economics</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349210863126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:47:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it trickles down her leg. Obama signed the biggest tax increases in the history of America into law. All of Obama's tax increases kick in after the election unless you vote for Romney. Obama created the fiscal cliff. He will make you pay.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349657339627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657487197-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama spending binge never happened....Government outlays rising at slowest pace since 1950s</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349623931927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>• In the 2009 fiscal year — the last of George W. Bush’s presidency — federal spending rose by 17.9% from $2.98 trillion to $3.52 trillion. Check the official numbers at the Office of Management and Budget. The problem with the 2009 budget is that Barack Obama became president in Jan-2009 and he collaborated on the budget after winning the election in Nov-2008. Furthermore, when unemployment reached 7.8% in Jan-2009 Obama proposed an $800 Billion Stimulus package that passed in Feb-2009 and became part of the 2009 fiscal year budget. As of Jan-2009 Obama &amp; the democrats controlled both houses of congress. If Obama had problems with anything in the 2009 fiscal year budget, he could have and should have changed it. Further, the increase difference of about $540 billion (3.52 - 2.98 = 0.54) was about the price of the TARP program, which Obama &amp; the Democrat Congress collaborated on and all agreed on. ****** • In fiscal 2010 — the first budget under Obama — spending fell 1.8% to $3.46 trillion. • In fiscal 2011, spending rose 4.3% to $3.60 trillion. • In fiscal 2012, spending is set to rise 0.7% to $3.63 trillion, according to the Congressional Budget Office’s estimate of the budget that was agreed to last August. ****** I believe the 2009 fiscal year budget was THE LAST BUDGET passed by congress. Again, Obama had control of both houses of Congress until Jan-2011 and he could have gotten budgets passed if he desired. He did not desire. And we had no budgets. He was busy pushing ObamaCare, golfing, campaigning or doing apologize for America global tours. The other problem here is that federal revenue persisted at around $2.2 trillion per year. Thus the annual deficit per year was: o 2010 =~ $1.26 trillion o 2011 =~ $1.40 trillion o 2012 =~ $1.43 trillion I am apparently over-estimating the annual revenue, since these deficits total to a little over $4.0 trillion and more like $5.0 trillion was added to the national debt. I am pretty sure the deficit for one year was somewhat over $1.6 trillion. The fact is these are the largest deficits in history, especially in a row. (As much as Democrats scream about Ronald Reagan, Regan's total deficit for eight years was less than Barack Obama's deficit for one year.) ***** • Finally in fiscal 2013 — the final budget of Obama’s term — spending is scheduled to fall 1.3% to $3.58 trillion. Read the CBO’s latest budget outlook. Once again, the final budget under Obama was for fiscal year 2009. The USA does not have a budget. Just rampant uncontrolled spending. The three biggest blocks have been: Barack Obama, Harry Reid &amp; the Democrats in Congress. So what we have the CBO has estimated final SPENDING. Last I heard revenue was still around $2.2 trillion so Harry Reid &amp; Barack Obama will give us a deficit this year of about $1.38 trillion. And if I recall correctly, the decrease in spending is due to the Republicans in the House. ***** So what we have here is the CBO documenting Obama's abject failure as a president and as a leader.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349657487197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349657498559-36</Id><Title>Millennials living at home working part time</Title><Msg>He's 25, lives with his parents and works three part-time jobs. Millennials helped elect President Obama. Now, Millennials can't get a job due to Obama's financial repression policies. We don't get fooled again. Prolong the misery for 4 more years?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349657498559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657661980-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama spending binge never happened....Government outlays rising at slowest pace since 1950s</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349623931927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No budget for 4 years $1 Trillion deficits each year What a way to run a country -- like a banana republic.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349657661980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657878679-38</Id><Topic><Title>dropkick now has five variations of his yahoo fake id</Title><Username>goodgoi000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349637698733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:21:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would expect your password to be "epiwssa" or "gabehcuod". Both are appropriate. A guy in my office used "F*** Y**" and I guessed it easily.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349657878679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349659042240-39</Id><Title>Exit polls show Chavez has been defeated</Title><Msg>Could it be?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349659042240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>