<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348374283327-1</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..and I'll do the job fo free. Neither mean anything since I won't be president either.</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348374283327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 00:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348403671982-2</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GALLUP SATURDAY: O 47% R 47%... RASMUSSEN: O 46% R 46%...</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1348403671982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 08:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348410451619-3</Id><Title>Prolog the misery</Title><Msg>Loretta Mitchell is 100 percent sure she's going to vote in the presidential race come November. She doesn't have a clue who'll get that vote. Are you really going to vote for Obama again to prolong the misery? Really? BWHAHHAHHAHHAHHAHHAHHAHHA!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348410451619</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348410847538-4</Id><Title>Biden is a clown</Title><Msg>He was in charge of the Stimulus Package and it failed. He should be fired! OUT OUT OUT Throw the bas*tud out!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348410847538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348411129492-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama About To Get Exactly What He Deserves!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1347640152855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 12:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obummer and the Fed in no mans land on economy. That's being charitable, I think btw are clueless. Post turtle time. *** Nobama definitely a post turtle. Uncle Ben is my friend. He can't do any more. He's all in. Regime change is the answer otherwise global depression and war with Iran. It's an easy choice. Do you really want to prolong the misery?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348411129492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348412326281-6</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure Pigshyt!! Indeed, Democrat PC trash are little more than Slave Masters... using money they steal from Working Taxpaying Americans to enslave their mindless minions... and Jeeeews like Paul Krugman are among the worst of the Slavers!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1348412326281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348416025310-7</Id><Topic><Title>Libyan Islamist militia swept out of Benghazi bases</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348356003780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:20:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy are you delusional. Close your eyes to all the bad news and believe the lies. You’re doomed, comrade. You are FREAKING MAD!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348416025310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348416193215-8</Id><Title>dead us ambassador to libya was sodomized!</Title><Msg>Beaten and Dragged through the streets just like gadaffi! Hey, Hillary, You #$%$ Why don’t you go to Libya and run your trap down there? Obamas foreign policy is an Abomination!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348416193215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348416340169-9</Id><Title>the libyans destroyed US war graves over a year ago!</Title><Msg>This is all about Americas Murder. How many Libyans were killed? Why is Barrat killing for POLLS. THE PEACE PRIZE KID!!! Al Quadea is Barracks friend. America, YOU know what to do.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348416340169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348416849556-10</Id><Title>End all welfare!</Title><Msg>GO REPUBLICANS ... YOU CAN SELL IT ON BK!!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348416849556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348417894012-11</Id><Topic><Title>dead us ambassador to libya was sodomized!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348416193215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:03:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>was CNN not Yapping about those animals sodomizing Gadaffi? Did not Ameirca, watch every detail and salivate to the grotesque Barbarism? Now, You got it back, You asked for it!!! Where is Hillary now ... BEEEAAACCCCHHH!!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348417894012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348418027564-12</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny, I was a "card carrying Republican" for quite a while. Worked for wages and never had a business. Always felt at home with most people that had businesses including some quite wealthy ones. After retiring from two jobs I did do some "time and materiels" work as I had no contractors license. Never heard a single employer ever express "disdain" for an employee that performed their work. The large corporation I worked for went out of their way to keep from firing anyone. Some should have been fired. I have worked for government some too. Several summers on a fire suppression crew, U. S. Forest Service. I've found that if you do what you are paid to do most employers treat you well and show NO "disdain". I have run into "liberal" snobs though that show "disdain" for anyone that questions their super knowledge of most everything.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348418027564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348418126314-13</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess that's why the Kenyan is in bed with so many ultra rich pigs like George Soros. It feeds his ego.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348418126314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348422032785-14</Id><Title>Bimbos of America Taking Obama To Victory!!</Title><Msg>Too bad there's not more Real American Women... who don't need Big Government to care for and coddle them, cradle to grave! Women's "Liberation" is has become pathetic Joke! The only thing these losers want to be liberated from is personal responsibility! Bimbos worship slavery... and they're counting on The Angel Barack to take them to the Promise Land!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1348422032785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348422079581-15</Id><Title>As If We Haven't Heard Enough From Liberal Crackpots</Title><Msg>This was in the news a few days ago. Some DA liberal principal at some school wants to ban peanut butter and jelly sandwiches claiming they represent racial disparity. Huh? How the hell did she get her position?? This is why kids are so messed up when a sandwich becomes a bad influence. Why not ban fried chicken and tacos too. The parents should get together and organize all the kids for a protest march. "Dump the Spinach, Not the Good Stuff" . If this is an example of the people in charge of educating children, They don't deserve a raise.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348422079581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348423678552-16</Id><Title>Texas Mom angry that male vice principal spanked daughter</Title><Msg>Shucks, they didn't even show pictures of the girl's blistered bottom!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1348423678552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348423692825-17</Id><Title>Texas Mom angry that male vice principal spanked daughter</Title><Msg>Shucks, they didn't even show pictures of the girl's blistered bottom!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1348423692825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:08:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348439374576-18</Id><Topic><Title>Big options traders got their butterflys, condors, iron condors, collars, strangles, straddles spreads covered calls and covered puts out there for the fireworkds-</Title><Username>whsteffanmsn</Username><Timestamp>1348169853863</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 15:37:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the people who wrote the calls..</Msg><Username>faithfullover31</Username><Timestamp>1348439374576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348444507546-19</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>September 23, 2012 7:22 pm The US economy is still in a sorry state Edward Luce By Edward Luce Matt Kenyon illustration In a waning presidential first term nothing compares to the importance of securing another one. In Barack Obama’s case, there is an added spur to his drive for re-election. The president believes the American economy will spring back to life over the next four years and cannot abide the thought of Mitt Romney reaping the credit. Mr Obama’s impulse is more than understandable. However unearned, an economic revival that coincided with a Romney first term would easily be marketed as a “Romney boom”. But even if – as many expect – Mr Obama wins on 6 November, he should be wary of the growing belief in America’s impending manufacturing renaissance. Too much of it is based on hope. America’s pallid – and again waning – economic recovery is already into its fourth year. The typical length of the business cycle is about seven years. It requires optimism at this stage to believe the patient is about to arise and go for a jog. Here is the case for America’s coming manufacturing boom. First, the US is in the early stages of an energy windfall that will transform its attractiveness as a location to do business. In addition to the unfolding energy supply shock, which will lower the cost of electricity and the feed-in stock for many kinds of production, the cost of American labour looks increasingly attractive next to wage inflation in China and other emerging market economies. According to the Boston Consulting Group the US could create between 2m and 5m new direct and indirect manufacturing jobs between now and 2020. That would make up for about one-third of what it has lost in the past decade. On top of that, the US housing market has finally bottomed out and is likely once again to become a net plus to US growth. Finally, as Roger Altman recently argued in the FT, Washington could surprise us all by skirting the cliff and striking a fiscal deal that would rekindle America’s animal spirits. Much of this is indisputable; the US is well on the way to a new era of energy abundance. Estimates of its impact range from mildly positive to something far bigger. Much of it is also probable: it would take a huge shock to push the US housing market back into free fall. Some of it is less so: it would be a surprise if Congress struck an intelligent fiscal bargain in the coming months. Should the Republican “fever break” – as some Democrats describe the anticipated Republican change of heart – it would certainly qualify as a positive shock to the economy. Both Moody’s and Standard &amp; Poor’s, the two biggest credit rating agencies, cite political risk as America’s chief vulnerability. Yet it is hard to get excited about a revival based on so many ifs and buts. Even if the rosiest forecasts prove correct, they are based on sobering assumptions. First, the boom would be based on the continued decline in US unit labour costs. By 2016, according to Boston Consulting Group, the gap with China would have narrowed to just seven cents an hour. These would be neither the high-tech jobs of the future nor the golden middle class jobs of the past. Rising US labour productivity growth will play its part. So too will declining US wages. Hourly pay for new “two-tier” hires in US auto assembly plants and elsewhere is roughly half that of the original tier (and with a fraction of the benefits). None of this would alter the calculus for the higher-tech manufacturers, such as semiconductors and robotics. At a typical Intel plant, whether in China or America, labour costs amount to just a tenth of total overheads. Tax rates, market access and the cost of land are far more important factors. Second, the hollowing out of America’s middle class – still politely described as median income stagnation rather than “decline” – is accelerating rather than slowing. According to the US Census last week, the US median household is 4.8 per cent poorer now than at the start of the recovery in 2009. Median incomes have now fallen to the pre-internet level of 1993. All of the gains of the Clinton years have been lost. The decline in the past three years follows a 3.2 per cent drop during the recession, which itself followed a shrinkage during the 2000-2007 cycle. Far from a new dawn of broad-based growth, America’s middle class decline is getting worse. Recent days will chiefly be remembered for Mr Romney’s decision to stand by his disparaging comments about the 47 per cent of Americans who pay no federal income tax. They will also be remembered for the release of his full 2011 tax return , which showed that the former Bain Capital executive pays a lower overall rate than the poorest fifth of Americans. In an era of increasing economic insecurity, Mr Romney has made a hash of his campaign. Were he a better politician, Mr Romney would have seized on a report earlier this month that showed a sharp fall in US competitiveness. In 2007, the US was ranked first by the World Economic Forum, which published the report. By 2011 it had fallen to fifth. This year it dropped to seventh. The chief culprits are bad governance, macroeconomic instability and declining infrastructure. Here, too, the American trend points the wrong way. Should he still pull off a victory, Mr Romney’s tax plans would skew the fiscal system even further towards the wealthiest. If, as Mr Romney says, Mr Obama is a “redistributionist”, then he is clearly not a very effective one. Whoever wins the 2012 election, America can certainly rely on a coming energy boom – in fact it is already well under way. Most of the rest looks like either hype or hope.</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1348444507546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348444589432-20</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that where the deficit's hiding? Obama whips out massive wad of cash to pay for sausages at deli By Daily Mail Reporter PUBLISHED: 19:10 EST, 22 September 2012 | UPDATED: 04:10 EST, 23 September 2012 Comments (294) Share Wherever Barack Obama goes, he is accompanied by a huge entourage of aides, Secret Service and campaign staff. But when the President goes shopping, he still has to handle his own cash, as he showed on Saturday when he bought sausages from a Wisconsin store following a campaign stop in key swing state. Mr Obama pulled out a wad of bills that looked almost large enough to make a dent in the national debt as he browsed for pork treats alongside Milwaukee mayor Tom Barrett. Scroll down for video Flush with cash: Barack Obama, pictured with Milwaukee mayor Tom Barrett, pulls out a wad of bills to pay for a purchase of sausages at a Wisconsin deli Flush with cash: Barack Obama, pictured with Milwaukee mayor Tom Barrett, pulls out a wad of bills to pay for a purchase of sausages at a Wisconsin deli Bonanza: Despite his huge entourage, the President clearly has no one to carry his wallet for him Bonanza: Despite his huge entourage, the President clearly has no one to carry his wallet for him After his visit to Usinger's Famous Sausage, the President was given a bratwurst hot dog in a pretzel roll with spicy mustard by a local deli worker. The commander-in-chief appeared to enjoy his meaty snack, giving an emphatic thumbs-up to supporters and photographers as he chowed down on the delicacy. More... Paul Ryan courts Cuban-American voters in Miami with promises to end Obama's 'policy of appeasement' towards Castro...while president campaigns in VP candidate's home state Now it's Biden's wife making gaffes as she makes accidental X-rated joke about her husband He also managed to meet deli customers who were visiting from Ohio - another swing state seen as a must-win if Mr Obama is to stay in the White House after November's election. During an earlier campaign speech, the President criticised his Republican rival Mitt Romney for advancing a top-down economic approach that 'never works.' 'The country doesn't succeed when only the folks at the very top are doing well,' he said. 'We succeed when the middle class is doing well.' Shopping: Mr Obama browsed at Usinger's Famous Sausage following a campaign appearance Shopping: Mr Obama browsed at Usinger's Famous Sausage following a campaign appearance Try before you buy: The President chews on a sample sausage during his deli visit Try before you buy: The President chews on a sample sausage during his deli visit With just six weekends left before Election Day, both candidates were devoting considerable time to raising cash to continue bankrolling the deluge of ads already saturating hotly contested states. Baseball great Hank Aaron supplied the star power at Mr Obama's Milwaukee fundraisers. 'As one who wore the number 44 on his back for decades, I ask you to join me in helping the 44th president of the United States hit a grand slam,' said Mr Aaron. Mr Romney, who is expected to launch a more aggressive campaign schedule in the coming week, hunted for West Coast cash at a private fundraiser near San Diego and then headed for another in Los Angeles. Some Republicans have grumbled that he is not spending enough time with voters in swing states, and Mr Romney seemed to take note of that sentiment. 'I've got good news: This is the last fundraiser in San Diego,' he told supporters. 'I'm not even going to be able to go home today. We're just coming to town to see you and keep the campaign going. It's nonstop.' Delicacy: Outside the store, Mr Obama was handed a bratwurst in a pretzel bun with spicy mustard Delicacy: Outside the store, Mr Obama was handed a bratwurst in a pretzel bun with spicy mustard Chowing down: The President was happy to try out the pork snack on the campaign trail Chowing down: The President was happy to try out the pork snack on the campaign trail Success! The Democrat poses with Andy Fronek, who gave him the sausage from Milwaukee Brat House Success! The Democrat poses with Andy Fronek, who gave him the sausage from Milwaukee Brat House Romney adviser Kevin Madden said the GOP nominee would begin 'a really intense battleground state schedule.' The former Massachusetts governor will campaign in Colorado, Ohio and Virginia in the coming week. With running mates Joe Biden and Paul Ryan campaigning in New England and Florida, respectively, the presidential campaign was spread far and wide - both geographically and strategically. Mr Biden revved up union activists poised to canvass for votes in New Hampshire while Mr Ryan appealed to Hispanic voters in Miami and discussed space policy in Orlando.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348444589432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348455352939-21</Id><Title>'Game Change' wins best miniseries or</Title><Msg>Palin was worth SOMETHING.</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348455352939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348455623528-22</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repubs are the most idiotic f'ed up people EVER/ #$%$!</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348455623528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348456920343-23</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lewcor is runners? Same kinda DB. Most employers treat you well if you do what paid to do???? maybe....maybe not. "MOST"? I take issue with that. The best part of my life has been the last half of my working years being self-employed. I can say no employer of mine EVER treated me as they should have all things considered. Bottom line, working for other people never paid off as it should have..and I was the most loyal hard working person anyone could be. Look at how people treat peopel in general.....why the F would you say people working for others are treated well? People get mistreated every day all the time at work and not at work..you runners idiot.</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348456920343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348457118224-24</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When bush wrecks something,..it's pretty well wrecked.</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348457118224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348458834152-25</Id><Title>•Ann Coulter: 'Democrats are dropping the blacks'</Title><Msg>What a dumb thing to say and an even dumber way to say it from a very stinking dummy ugly repub beach lady. Can anyone be more obnoxious than a republican? Nope!</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348458834152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>