<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348826266304-1</Id><Title>Nikual Nikula (sp)</Title><Msg>Nikula Nikula, the guy who made the movie that Obama says incited Muslim violence, is in jail on a probabtion violation. Recall they came after him when Obama blamed the movie. He is in jail because of a probation violation. The terms of his probation were that he could not use the internet which he violated. The judge says that he is such a flight risk that he must remain in jail. That poor slob.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348826266304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348826348771-2</Id><Topic><Title>Hey gop whiners and cowards on the ME</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348751049347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bummer stood by his inane remark but other Donkeys like you won't. Your bozo is bit a community organizer, admit it libiots.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348826348771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348826485411-3</Id><Topic><Title>Nikual Nikula (sp)</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348826266304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:57:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The libs are slowly eroding our basic freedoms. First it was large sized sodas, then freedom of speech. What next?</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348826485411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348826492816-4</Id><Topic><Title>candidates gaffes</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348771525219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perception, Mesa, perception. The people don't care about context. Besides, if the context was roads and bridges, Obama left the impression that business owners do not also pay taxes to build roads and bridges.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348826492816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348826620605-5</Id><Topic><Title>Congratulations to Barack "Apologize, Appease, and Bend Over with Sphincter Spread Wide" Obama</Title><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1348789367073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:42:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got news for you Messsssssebird. The Bummer ain't building, he's destroying the basic foundation of America. A community organizer, but a clueless one at that.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348826620605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348826743592-6</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cannot wait for the Ryan/Weasel debate on Medicare. Who might you think has a clue? I got news for you libiots, it would not be the Weasel VP.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348826743592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348826890893-7</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens used to "harvest" companies while at Bain.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1348781487167</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:31:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad the MSM did not go back 25 years and vet the Bummer. Guess it would have been tough seeing him through all that MJ smoke.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348826890893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348827989493-8</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens used to "harvest" companies while at Bain.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1348781487167</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:31:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And somebody explain to me, why do libiots hate success?</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348827989493</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:26:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348828095448-9</Id><Title>Where's Jimmy</Title><Msg>Where is Hoffa buried? Giants Stadium, Florida swamp, Michigan swimming pool. Dem union boys sure do play rough.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348828095448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348828268244-10</Id><Topic><Title>Politifact rates Mitt's you didn't build it nonsense. FALSE</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348777659954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:27:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, they rated the statement true you bozo. You lie more then the Bummer.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348828268244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348828371959-11</Id><Topic><Title>Politifact rates Mitts comment on the 47%........ FALSE.... ZERO truth on the truth 0 meter</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348778482206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong again. They rated it true. You are still a bozo.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348828371959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348828690605-12</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libiots would never understand trickle down, they believe in trickle up poverty.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348828690605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348828948362-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama sticking to silly movie excuse</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348676874158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:27:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bull kaka from the head libiot. The Bummer and his merry band of incompetents carry on, trying their best to ruin American standing in the world. Even you libiots should see this.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348828948362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348829702355-14</Id><Title>Bummer mum on Middle East policy now</Title><Msg>Since all of the ME countries are shouting " death to America ". Bit they still love us despite killing our ambassadors and their staff. Iran about to get the big bomb. Even India hates us now. Great Middle East policy.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348829702355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348831388101-15</Id><Title>The Nobel Peace Prize winning Chimp in Chief's promises 4 years ago:</Title><Msg>1. Obliterate the deficit in half... OOOPS!!! 2. "A new beginning" with the mudslum scourge (sphincter licking in Cairo, 2009)... OOOPS!!! 3. "A new tone" in Washington. OOOPS!!! 4. A stimulus package that would squish the unemployment rate. $800,000,000,000. OOOPS!!! Why did the Nobel Peace prize winning feces throwing, chest pumping Chimpanzee choose to ignore the Green Revolution in Iran.... back the mudslum brotherhood in Egypt and al queeda in Libya... and ignore everyone in Syria? When will the #$%$ in Chief do SOMETHING about Iran? In another 4 years? After the mudslum leadership hands over a nuke to heezboollah? Why didn't the ObungaBongo adminstration tell the public that an American Ambassador was SODOMIZED, TORTURED, and DRAGGED THROUGH THE STREETS by mudslum hordes? Why did the Monkey in the White House APOLOGIZE for American values before pretending to be outraged? Why doesn't the Orangoutang in Office APOLOGIZE to the Copts who are being slaughtered on daily basis in Egypt? Why doesn't the Magic Monkey of the United States tell us what really happened in Libya? He says he wants to wait for all THE EVIDENCE to come out but he sure had no problem condemning a Cambridge Police Officer who was assaulted by a fellow monkey before THE EVIDENCE proved the "Professor Gates" (thank you, affirmative action) to be just typical thug from a culture of thugs... AND the Chimp in Chief sure had no problem announcing to the world that the dead thug, traycoon martin, looked just like his son, before THE EVIDENCE was released... The First Monkey sure is quiet now that THE EVIDENCE is proving the dead thug, traycoon martin, to be a violent drug user and thief. This president is worth as much to this nation as is what I'm about to drop in the toilet after a big breakfast.</Msg><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1348831388101</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 07:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348836395430-16</Id><Topic><Title>candidates gaffes</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348771525219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The people don't care about context" Funny how YOU speak for the "people".....jeez....... and YOU are saying they don't care if what the gop tells them and what they think is a lie. And btw the a lot of people know that the whole gop nonsense on " i built that" is a lie..... Politifact says it's false and a lie and nailed Romeny for repeating the lie, I think a lot of people are quite aware that the "I built that " theme of the rnc is just a typical gop lie and distortion. I think Romney is done for and he knows it.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348836395430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348838095039-17</Id><Topic><Title>here is one of many of bjspokeanimals LIES</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348695376700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 17:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i guess bjspokeanimal ran away and refuses to take responsibility for his statement</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348838095039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348839598023-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama sticking to silly movie excuse</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348676874158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:27:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Netanyahu, Romney to Speak Friday 12:00 AM, Sep 28, 2012 • By DANIEL HALPER Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts THE WEEKLY STANDARD has learned that Israeli prime minister Benjamin Netanyahu has scheduled a phone call for late morning Friday with Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney. romney and netanyahu President Obama refused to meet with Netanyahu on his trip to the United States, and the Israeli government presumably thought a meeting with the opposition candidate in the absence of one with the sitting president would be too provocative. But there was apparently an eagerness on the Israeli prime minister's part to talk with Romney in order to help win as broad American support as possible for the red lines he outlined in his United Nations speech with respect to the Iranian nuclear program. As for Romney, he expects to explore Netanyahu's understanding of the red lines, and also, we are told, wants to hear Netanyahu's perspective on developments elsewhere in the Middle East. Apparently at the request of both principals, neither of their offices has put a hard-stop on their schedules for this call, so the discussion is likely to be both substantive and substantial. It will be interesting to hear the readouts tomorrow from both the Netanyahu and Romney camps after the "principals only" phone call—and to see the White House reaction, as well. In the summer, Netanyahu hosted Romney in Israel for dinner, hours after Romney delivered an address in Jerusalem. Related Stories “Mitt, I want to thank you for those very strong words of support and friendship for Israel and for Jerusalem that we heard today in your speech by the walls of Jerusalem,” Netanyahu told Romney as he welcomed him to the prime minister’s residence. “Jerusalem today is marking the destruction of the city thousands of years ago. As you see it’s been rebuilt by the Jewish people, open to all the three great faiths, vibrant, bustling, and as you said, Jerusalem is the capital of Israel, and Jerusalem will always be the capital of Israel. So welcome to Jerusalem, Mitt.” Netanyahu and Romney have known each other for almost 35 years, having worked together at Boston Consulting Group in 1976.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348839598023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348841126874-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama sticking to silly movie excuse</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348676874158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:27:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If not for sports champions and terrorists, President Obama’s public schedule for September would be nearly empty of official events, as he devoted most of his time to campaigning for re-election. On Sept. 6, Mr. Obama accepted the Democratic Party’s renomination in Charlotte, N.C. In the 21 days since then, the president has had a total of 14 events on his White House schedule, not including regular daily briefings and occasional lunches with Vice President Joseph R. Biden. In the same period, Mr. Obama’s other two “jobs” — campaigner and fundraiser — crowded out his White House schedule. As the first incumbent president to forgo public financing, Mr. Obama has held 24 campaign events this month, from Colorado to New Hampshire, from rallying auto workers to raising millions of dollars with pop diva Beyonce. Six of the president’s official events were the result of terrorism — four on Sept. 11 to commemorate the 11th anniversary of the terrorist attacks, and to pay respect to veterans of the Iraq and Afghanistan wars. He also held two events, on Sept. 11 and Sept. 14, in response to the deaths of four Americans in an attack on the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi, Libya, including Ambassador J. Christopher Stevens. As have all recent presidents, Mr. Obama set aside time this month to welcome sports heroes to the White House. On Sept. 14, he greeted U.S. athletes from the 2012 Olympics and Paralympics, and met with the 2011 WNBA champion Minnesota Lynx on Sept. 18. The decisions over splitting the president’s valuable time between campaigning and governing came into sharp focus this week when Mr. Obama was criticized for shunning one-on-one meetings with foreign leaders at the United Nations in New York at the same time he booked an appearance with first lady Michelle Obama on “The View,” a daytime chat show popular with female voters. White House officials defended Mr. Obama’s schedule, saying he is always attentive to his duties no matter where he is or what he is doing. “He is intensively engaged in matters of national security and foreign policy as he has been throughout his presidency,” White House press secretary Jay Carney said this week, responding to more than a dozen questions from reporters about the priority given to “The View.” One journalist noted that last year, when Mr. Obama wasn’t campaigning for re-election, he held 13 bilateral meetings with foreign heads of state at the U.N. Of the past four incumbent presidents who attended the U.N. General Assembly while running for re-election, only one, George H.W. Bush, held no bilateral meetings. George W. Bush held four such meetings in September 2004, Bill Clinton held one in 1996, and Ronald Reagan held three in 1984, including a high-stakes encounter with Soviet Foreign Minister Andrei Gromyko. Amid the criticism of Mr. Obama’s light diplomatic schedule this week, he did meet briefly with the president of Yemen and the secretary-general of the U.N.</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1348841126874</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348842450701-20</Id><Title>Get better for ORCL energetic authority. Decide in beneath wraps the Oracle Corporatio</Title><Msg>If you are nervous about a massive obstacle and for the stock that mounts 54 - 204% in a day go after that view at 4107216bond sum for Oracle Corporation Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- goo.gl/J0FQq</Msg><Username>kingfabian681</Username><Timestamp>1348842450701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348845627466-21</Id><Topic><Title>candidates gaffes</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348771525219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is not done, Mesa. The popular polls out there are skewed toward dems. They are using they 2008 model while ignoring what happened at the polls in 2010. Is the environment of 2012 closer to that of 2008 or 2010? I feel very comfortable that Romney will win and it won't be that close. 57-43 in a ARomney win is not unreasonable. Shoot, the margin of victory will be too big even for a massive dem effort to cheat.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348845627466</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348845680370-22</Id><Title>Mitten's wrecked his chances and also exposed the greedy ugly core of the new conservatism</Title><Msg>" assuming he was speaking privately to like-minded multi-millionaires, the Republican presidential candidate told the $50,000-a-platers what they wanted to hear: that he hasn’t any intention of helping the 47 per cent of Americans too poor to pay income tax. “My job is not to worry about those people.” With this truthfulness caught on tape, Romney has probably done more than incinerate his own presidential bid. He has so vividly exposed the cynicism and greed that lies at the heart of what is now called “conservatism” that he may have inadvertently begun its undoing." Linda Mcquaig</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348845680370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348846212308-23</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wrecked his chances and also exposed the greedy ugly core of the new conservatism</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348845680370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The guy is holding a fundraiser in China. The same guy who says he's going to be tough with China is now accepting payments from anyone who wants to buy his allegance.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1348846212308</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348846319990-24</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wrecked his chances and also exposed the greedy ugly core of the new conservatism</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348845680370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leno: ‘We Wasted Four Years Waiting For Obama To Do Something About The Economy’ By Noel Sheppard | September 28, 2012 | 11:03 Jay Leno took some surprising shots at President Obama Thursday night. During the opening monologue of NBC's Tonight Show, the host said Americans wasted four years for the current White House resident to do something about the economy (video follows with transcribed highlights and commentary): "I love how the politicians capitalize on this kind of thing," teased Leno. "Like the minute the replacement refs were fired, President Obama said, 'See, sometimes losing jobs can be a good thing. It's a good thing.'" When the laughter subsided, Leno continued, "A new survey out today shows how much time we waste every day in our lives. For example, we waste seven minutes in line every time we go to get coffee, 28 minutes getting through airport security, four years waiting for Obama to do something about the economy. Every year, we waste a lot. We wasted a lot of time." Yes we did. It's about time media members began telling the nation that.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1348846319990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348846498862-25</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wrecked his chances and also exposed the greedy ugly core of the new conservatism</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348845680370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's workers vs. investors It's the interests of the many vs. the interests of the few Tax cuts for the rich don't help the economy they only help the rich, and lack of tax income leads to layoffs of teachers or to more debt. The quote you have is one of the few moments of truth we see, otherwise the right-wingers are bullshltting about everything. Screw them all. Can't wait for the older whities to die off so we don't have to deal with these self-centered awholes anymore.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1348846498862</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:34:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348846690543-26</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wrecked his chances and also exposed the greedy ugly core of the new conservatism</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348845680370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is not a dictatorship Congress is held in deep disgust by the public because they are not doing anything except obstruction. Methinks they are most of the problem. And they are all sold-out to special interests so they can't make proper decisions.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1348846690543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348847036659-27</Id><Title>Romney vs.military spending cuts</Title><Msg>Comment from some other board: +++++++++++ Silly Mitt: "They would make devastating cuts to our military. It's a strange proposal in the first place, even stranger that it's being put in place," Romney said. "The impact will be immediate, and significant right here in Virginia: 136,000 jobs will be lost in Virginia as a result of this move." Everyone knows the government doesn't create jobs, the private sector does.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1348847036659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348847344774-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wrecked his chances and also exposed the greedy ugly core of the new conservatism</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348845680370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "older whities" you refer to built this country. Too bad they defeated Hitler and Tojo. People like you wouldn't be here if they hadn't. Hey, maybe that would have been good. There were no parasites in either Germany or Japan during the thirties.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348847344774</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348847507549-29</Id><Topic><Title>candidates gaffes</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348771525219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many gaffs are due to being very tired on the campaign trail. Everyone mis-speaks from time to time. Like the Kenyan's slip about "57 states". He may be stupid but not that stupid.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348847507549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348850118903-30</Id><Topic><Title>Increase your portfolio by checking out these guys right now.</Title><Username>danielshropshire975</Username><Timestamp>1348151260038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:27:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice pic of Sofia Vergara's wardrobe malfunction. Real cheeky. Thanks for the analyst prediction of a big blowup that'll increase your portfolio. Good call.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348850118903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348850292673-31</Id><Title>Bush Has The Last Laugh</Title><Msg>If Obama is re-elected, just think about the mess he'll inherit this time. SMACK!!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348850292673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:38:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348850303133-32</Id><Topic><Title>The Nobel Peace Prize winning Chimp in Chief's promises 4 years ago:</Title><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1348831388101</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 07:23:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. Obliterate the deficit in half... OOOPS!!! 2. "A new beginning" with the mudslum scourge (sphincter licking in Cairo, 2009)... OOOPS!!! 3. "A new tone" in Washington. OOOPS!!! 4. A stimulus package that would squish the unemployment rate. $800,000,000,000. OOOPS!!! Why did the Nobel Peace prize winning feces throwing, chest pumping Chimpanzee choose to ignore the Green Revolution in Iran.... back the mudslum brotherhood in Egypt and al queeda in Libya... and ignore everyone in Syria? Why didn't the ObungaBongo adminstration tell the public that an American Ambassador was SODOMIZED, TORTURED, and DRAGGED THROUGH THE STREETS by mudslum hordes? *** Heard he died of smoke inhalation. Did Obama not give us the real story? You can't trust Nobama. Spanish banks only need $60 Billion Euro bailout. Buy the dip. The crisis is over.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348850303133</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348850588429-33</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wrecked his chances and also exposed the greedy ugly core of the new conservatism</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348845680370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fyi, the gi generation is mostly gone (someone 20 in the late 1930s would be 90+). Do note that the gop wants to undo what they did. THEY were big on the new deal and social security and they did medicare in 1965..They paid far higher income taxes than now and they put FDR in office with huge landslide wins in 32, 36 , and by a large margin of 55% in 40.......... and compare the conservative eisenhower who supported social securlty and labor unions to the gop now that hates those.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348850588429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348850601806-34</Id><Topic><Title>"Fiscal Cliff"</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348759453199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:24:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>France passes new tax raise on the wealthy. Top rate for millionaires goes to 75% from 56%. 30,000 millionaires in France are now moving out of the country and buying real estate in New York. Rich Spaniards are also leaving and taking money out of the country in droves. This is the type of activity (rats leaving the ship) you see when all is well as Obama says. The crisis is over. The recovery is really kicking on now.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348850601806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348851317230-35</Id><Topic><Title>"Fiscal Cliff"</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348759453199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:24:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will you just shut up with your idiot lies about how we are like the Weimar Republic? It is just a stupid idea. FYI, the weimar republic had no economy, get it? The USA has a HUGE economy and produces trillions of $$ worth of goods and services each year. USA debt is a problem, but a managable one. USA debt/gdp has been far higher than now and it wasn't the end of the world. USA debt/gdp was higher than now from about 1945 to 1955........ Great britain has had debt to gdp well over 100% for about half of the last 170 years....... Japan has had debt/gdp from 100 to 200% for more that 20 years and their world hasn't ended. and FYI : "debt held by the public....[is] an estimated 73 percent of GDP this year" CBO june 12, 2012</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348851317230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348851763872-36</Id><Title>Corporations ARE running America</Title><Msg>"our economy is dominated by corporations that make their own investment and hiring decisions. Two-thirds of the tens of millions of low-wage workers are employed by fifty large corporations, such as Walmart and McDonald’s. Thirty million American workers are laboring between the federal minimum wage of $7.25 per hour and what the minimum wage, adjusted for inflation from 1968, should be now – about $10 per hour. These companies are successfully opposing in Congress any increase in the minimum wage to such catch up with 1968. By the way, you favored an inflation-adjusted minimum wage for years. During the Republican primaries earlier this year, you changed your long-standing position and now oppose raising the minimum wage. Moreover, many companies are sitting on more than $2 trillion in inactive cash reserves. I have no power to get more of that capital invested, other than to appeal to their USA corporate patriotism. I could also use that patriotic appeal to urge them to increase their dividends to shareholders which would pump tens of billions of dollars into our consumer economy to encourage much-needed spending. Some of these successful companies like Google, EMC and others offer no dividends at all to their owners. Those exhortations are just exhortations. CEOs can do what they want..." Nader</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348851763872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348852018754-37</Id><Title>just trust mittens, the bum who hides his tax returns and banks in the caymans like OJ and like ken lay did</Title><Msg>i can't wait. Mitt's easy as pie, no pain, cash back fix for everything: more tax cuts on top of the bush tax cuts.......... Medicare, fixed!... and no changes to it for most boomers who will be on it out to the 2040s!.... SS... fixed!....... plus increased military spending and lots of deficit reduction too!! however a Romney advisor has said that if "broadening the base" ie raising taxes on the poor and middleclass doesn't make up for the tax cuts to the rich Mitt... "will give on the tax cuts"..... get it? ................... Just Trust Mitt...... but he is already weaseling out of his promises</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348852018754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348855944713-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare... the "anti-jobs" entitlement</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348507971847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The magnitude at which the fed is flooding reserves into the banking system (eg: printing money) is VERY un-precedented. The magnitude of the FISCAL stimulus (eg: the $1.2 trillion deficits) is ALSO un-precedented. Yet, all it's producing is 1.3% GDP, and un-employment that remains above 8%... ... IT'S NOT WORKING! The private sector is scared to death of Obama and our capitalist system has completely seized-up as a result... NO amount of keynsian stimulus is going to outweigh that... THAT's why the course that Obama and Bernanke have us on is COMPLETELY HOPELESS.</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348855944713</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348857048686-39</Id><Title>gop caught for voter fraud in Florida</Title><Msg>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — What first appeared to be an isolated problem in one Florida county has now spread statewide, with election officials in at least seven counties informing prosecutors or state election officials about questionable voter registration forms filled out on behalf of the Republican Party of Florida.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348857048686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348860455114-40</Id><Topic><Title>gop caught for voter fraud in Florida</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348857048686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:30:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote for Obama and get a cell phone. Quid pro quo. Blatant bribery. Put Axelrod in jail!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348860455114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348860669893-41</Id><Topic><Title>Nikual Nikula (sp)</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348826266304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:57:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new Mooslim Brotherhood president of Egypt asked Obama to censor any free speech that makes fun of Mooslims. Obama apologized to the Mooslims for America and then he bashed Catholic and Je*wi*sh organizations and refused to change his schedule to meet with Ne*tan*yahu --- instead he appeared on The View with his black wife who has a big ash and no teats.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348860669893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348860768965-42</Id><Topic><Title>Congratulations to Barack "Apologize, Appease, and Bend Over with Sphincter Spread Wide" Obama</Title><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1348789367073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:42:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tim Cook apologized for the cr*appy new maps app on iPhone5 -- he sounds like Obama. Weak. Steve Jobs never apologized for anything.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348860768965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348860949484-43</Id><Topic><Title>Are you so dumb that you think DEMOCRACY is what will result in the Middle East?</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1348712859924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:27:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Europe and Iran are waiting for the day after the election to let out the bad news. Path of least resistance is to do nothing so you can expect that the fiscal cliff will happen. Taxes and spending cuts are already law. No need to change anything. It's exactly what Obama promised. Prolong the misery. 4 more years.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348860949484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348861014179-44</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Jimmy</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348828095448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Obama put those toxic Chinese solar panels back on the White House yet? Another broken promise. He's talks out his ash hole.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348861014179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:36:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348864867770-45</Id><Topic><Title>Nikual Nikula (sp)</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348826266304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:57:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stupid person, that scumgag is in jail because he violated the terms of his parole...... I guess now you support criminals violating their parole terms and not going back to jail.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348864867770</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348864993797-46</Id><Topic><Title>bush on spreading democracy in the mid east</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348678311204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bush kicked off "spreading democracy" in the mid east.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348864993797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348865328015-47</Id><Title>will you neo loons with islam on the brain disease just move over there ?</Title><Msg>Nobody is stopping you from charging off to the mideast. You can redistribute your weath and your life in YOUR cause of controlling 100s of millions of people in several countries over there, and good riddance to you. SO GO and Built it yourself, On your OWN, just form a brigade of "democracy spreaders" volunteers and get your whiny lazy cowardly rear ends over their and fight for your favorite dictator, monarch or maybe join up with the IDF, in which case maybe YOU can murder Americans citizens like Rachel Corrie or the 3 dozen crew of the USS liberty murdered with napalm and machine gun fire in a deliberate attack. "three Israeli French-made Mirage III fighters attacked with 72 rockets, napalm and machine guns. They wounded McGonagle and killed the chief NSA officer Allen Bloom. The attack was filmed in its entirety through the Andrew Jackson’s periscope. Documents released in 1977 under the Freedom of Information Act show clearly that Israel knew the Liberty’s identity and that General Moshe Dyan ordered the sinking over the protest of close advisors. "</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348865328015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348868652900-48</Id><Topic><Title>Nikual Nikula (sp)</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348826266304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 05:57:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah he violated the terms of his parole. But the judge said he is a flight risk and a danger to society. Really Mesa? So this poor slob remains in jail.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348868652900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:44:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348870382929-49</Id><Topic><Title>time has passed for Akin to drop out</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348772681542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:04:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I put him on Iggy, quite a while ago? So I have to wonder if he's really dumber than Van sniff, AKA the post turtle.</Msg><Username>spam_buster_jr</Username><Timestamp>1348870382929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348871600080-50</Id><Title>Obama's Phonearama</Title><Msg>When I watched the video of the black woman praising Obama for giving her a free phone, I wondered if she actually knew how to use it. Part of the reason given for free phones, aside from emergencies, was looking for a job. Right, these anti-work, welfare addicts are going to look for jobs with their free complimentary phones. Funniest report since ACORN gave advice on opening a ho-house.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348871600080</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348873361139-51</Id><Title>Obama Cover Up Libya Terror Attack</Title><Msg>Does the buck stop with Obama or is he throwing Hillary under the bus. She was working too hard. Yeah, he'll throw Hillary under the bus but he'll keep Eric Holder because he's a token black stooge.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348873361139</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348873591712-52</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt will preserve the Bush tax cuts. Obama will let them expire. Congress will only be in session for 10 days at the end of the year. The law is already passed. Path of least resistance is to let the tax cuts expire and then blame the Republicans. It's going to get real ugly. Obama won't do jack. Everybody has known about the tax cuts expiring for years. Obama has said nothing about avoiding the fiscal cliff. Time to pay the piper sukkas!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348873591712</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348877464705-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Cover Up Libya Terror Attack</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348873361139</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:02:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kenyan and his gang supplied the weapons to the Muslim extremists that killed the ambassador. Just like they supplied the Mexican drug lords with the weapons that killed 300 Mexicans and one of our own Border Patrolmen. The Ambassador that was killed was actually in a "safe house" used to hide people opposed to Khadaffi. He had been trying to get back any arms identifiable as coming from the U.S., He had been instrumental in supplying them in the first place. He got what he deserved. To bad the drug lords didn't take care of some of the "Fast and Furious" criminals.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348877464705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348877757743-54</Id><Topic><Title>will you neo loons with islam on the brain disease just move over there ?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348865328015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:48:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry about Muslims. The Kenyan is importing them here as rapidly as he can. Soon you'll have all you can stomach and then some. All part of the NWO plan and Soros's plan to "Bring America down. Google "George Washington's Vision." You'll see what's coming.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348877757743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348878870381-55</Id><Topic><Title>will you neo loons with islam on the brain disease just move over there ?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348865328015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:48:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have ruined the old European countries already, why not us. After all, the Mooslims have produced all those Nobel Prize winners for decades. The Jews, nah. They don't have any Nobel Prize winners in medicine, physics, chemistry, economy. Just look it up.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348878870381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348879191092-56</Id><Topic><Title>bush on spreading democracy in the mid east</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348678311204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better than the Bummer bringing them to America to ruin our country like they have so many others. Iraq doing better though than the Bummers conquests like Libya, Syria, Yemen, and Iran. They really love us there. So much, they are killing our ambassadors and other Americans.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348879191092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:39:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348879536630-57</Id><Topic><Title>gop caught for voter fraud in Florida</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348857048686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:30:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats register Tiger Woods and Phil Mickelson by name. But it was not really them, just two guys carrying a golf club.just part of the 46,000! New Yorkers registered in both New York and Florida.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348879536630</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348879700550-58</Id><Topic><Title>just trust mittens, the bum who hides his tax returns and banks in the caymans like OJ and like ken lay did</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348852018754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:06:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obummer picture in the dictionary - a weasel. Blames everyone else for his stupidity. A community organizer, that's all folks. And you libiots think he's cute.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348879700550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348880080813-59</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wrecked his chances and also exposed the greedy ugly core of the new conservatism</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348845680370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:21:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Special interests don't vote. Lobbyists don't vote. The problem can be pinpointed to members of Congress who have so far wasted 16 trillion smackers with little to show for it. The Fed just keeps rolling it out and the Bummer and cronies just keep spending it. Obstruction is best for US now. And will be until we get spending in order. If Great Britain can do it, why not us.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348880080813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348880435904-60</Id><Topic><Title>Corporations ARE running America</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348851763872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trickle up poverty is the answer. Just ask a homeless person for a job, that works every time. You obviously have never run a business, or ever been employed except by the govt or a union. What a complete inane, total garbage piece of crap statement.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348880435904</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 21:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348881243285-61</Id><Topic><Title>Bummer mum on Middle East policy now</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348829702355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 06:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>since you are one of the biggest lunatics who thinks the USA can control the lives of hundreds of millions of muslims in several countries, why don't you and your ilk just own it and "build it" all on your own, you can volunteer and go there to support your favorite dictator, monarch, or perhaps join the IDF, in which case at least you will get Israel's universal healthcare with free abortions.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348881243285</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 21:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348881364254-62</Id><Topic><Title>Corporations ARE running America</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348851763872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here is your trickle down #$%$: "Two-thirds of the tens of millions of low-wage workers are employed by fifty large corporations, such as Walmart and McDonald’s. Thirty million American workers are laboring between the federal minimum wage of $7.25 per hour and what the minimum wage, adjusted for inflation from 1968, should be now – about $10 per hour. These companies are successfully opposing in Congress any increase in the minimum wage to such catch up with 1968." Nader</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348881364254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 21:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348881595239-63</Id><Topic><Title>will you neo loons with islam on the brain disease just move over there ?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348865328015</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:48:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just what the nazis said about the warsaw ghetto: "They don't have any Nobel Prize winners in medicine, physics, chemistry, economy. Just look it up." you POS</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348881595239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 21:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348882218858-64</Id><Title>vansniff is a cartoon nazi</Title><Msg>he is so stupid he doesn't realize everyone laughs at his ridiculous goosestepping bigotry and ignorance.He irons his KKK sheets everynight and wears them in the privacy of his trailer, yellow pee stains and all.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348882218858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 21:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348887983299-65</Id><Topic><Title>Politifact rates Mitts comment on the 47%........ FALSE.... ZERO truth on the truth 0 meter</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348778482206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney called the election. Obama will get 47% of the vote to Romney's 52%. Vote for Obama if you want to go over the fiscal cliff. Obama can't wait to raise your taxes due to the crisis that he created by spending like a drunken sailor without a budget for 4 years. Going back to the Clinton tax rates and spending levels during a recession will create a global depression. Follow the lying clown. All is well.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348887983299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348888267871-66</Id><Title>Obama will say anything to get re-elected</Title><Msg>Axelrod is a bullsheet spinmeister chief teleprompter writer. Only a da*mn fool would get fooled again. Vote for Obama and get a free cell phone. Call me.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348888267871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>