<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349758393694-1</Id><Title>IMF warns of global recession</Title><Msg>...caused by Nobama's taxmageddon policies and drunken sailor spending, failed wars, failed policies, failed presidency</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349758393694</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:53:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349758469916-2</Id><Topic><Title>Jerry Sandusky gets ugly on his way down</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1349747948742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 21:59:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barney Frank will visit him in the slammer.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349758469916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349758753127-3</Id><Topic><Title>6 Years ago, Democrats seized control of congress...</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349727991031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and the democrats have wielded IMMENSE POWER since the democrats first swept into control of congress 6 years ago and neutered George Bush... ... yet, here we are with HUGE fiscal stimulus ($1.2 trillion deficits) and HUGE monetary stimulus (0% fed funds rate and QE3)... and after all that and 6 years of democrates... our economy is growing at a paltry 1.3% GDP, and steadily getting WORSE. 4 more years THIS??? We'd be out of our MINDS to do THIS for 4 more years! *** Agreed. Only complete #$%$ or dependent lemmings would vote for Obama. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!! IMPEACH HOLDER NOW!! IMPEACH REID NOW!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349758753127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 00:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349780589292-4</Id><Topic><Title>6 Years ago, Democrats seized control of congress...</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349727991031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It should come as no surprise that President Obama will raise taxes if he is re-elected. But here’s the shocker: He will invite the United Nations to tax Americans directly. And the proceeds would go directly to the Third World. In this way, Barack Obama will, indeed, realize the dreams of his father. In our new book, "Here Come the Black Helicopters: UN Global Governance and the Loss of Freedom," Eileen and I describe how there is now pending in the U.N. all kinds of plans to tax Americans and redistribute their wealth – not to other Americans – but to other countries. These taxes will not be like our U.N. dues paid by a vote of our Congress. Nor akin to foreign aid which we choose to give. They would be mandatory levies imposed by treaty on American citizens. And, since they would be enumerated in a Treaty – not an act of Congress -- only the president and the Democratic Senate need be on board. The Republican House has no role in the Treaty-making process. (Of course, we do not believe that actual black UN helicopters will land in our midst to take over our country. But we use the symbolism to warn that the liberal, bureaucratic elites in the UN, enabled by Obama and Hillary, mean to create global governance to override American self-rule and independence). Here is what we say in "Black Helicopters" that Obama, Hillary, and the UN are planning for us: A “Robin Hood” tax on financial transactions. Every time you buy or sell a stock or a bond or exchange money while travelling, you’d be hit with a financial transactions tax (a percentage of your transaction) that would go to the UN. A global tobacco tax with the funds to flow to the World Health Organization (WHO). A UN-imposed tax on billionaires all over the world. And don’t delude yourself for a moment that it is only the 1600 current billionaires who will be hit. Once the precedent of a UN tax on US citizens is approved, it will gradually grow downwards to cover more and more Americans. Again the funds will go to the UN. Under the Law of the Sea Treaty – up for Senate ratification in December of the lame duck session – offshore oil and gas wells would have to pay a proportion of their revenues to the International Seabed Authority, a UN-sponsored organization, which would distribute the loot to the third world. A carbon tax on all U.S. or other foreign commercial or passenger aircraft flying to Europe. Nominally to fight climate change, these revenues would also go to the third world. A mandatory assessment to be imposed on the U.S. to compensate third world nations for the costs of reducing their carbon output. These taxes are, of course, only the first steps. Once the principle is established of UN taxation of American citizens, the sky is the limit. Is there any organizations less worthy of our trust to spend our money wisely than the United Nations? Beset by almost constant scandal, bereft of any in-house oversight or even audit, the UN is one of the most corrupt of all international organizations. In "Black Helicopters," we document how pervasive this corruption really is.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349780589292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 07:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349785011822-5</Id><Topic><Title>6 Years ago, Democrats seized control of congress...</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349727991031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and it's been triple black down-hill ever since... and now going off the cliff!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1349785011822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349786392951-6</Id><Title>Great Info On ORCL... Check It!</Title><Msg>I have been able to get in and out of this thing over and over and score some big wins with this anlaysis on ORCL... I hope it helps you guys! Let me know what you think and if anyone has any suggestions, I am all ears... Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- mcaf.ee/hgiem</Msg><Username>salinaschristina992</Username><Timestamp>1349786392951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349786784916-7</Id><Title>gop lie machine on US deficits</Title><Msg>the fact is the first ever trillion $ plus deficit was the one done by george w bush for fy 2009. and about $221 billion of each of the last 4 years of trillion $ plus deficits are DUE TO the BUSH TAX CUTs ........ and that is nearly $ 1 trillion .......... in other words Bush IS directly responsible for almost half of the deficits of the last five years of so. {The Congressional Budget Office has calculated that........expiration of the Bush tax cuts....would reduce the deficit by $221 billion. }</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349786784916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349788529340-8</Id><Topic><Title>gop lie machine on US deficits</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349786784916</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:46:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the fact is the first ever trillion $ plus deficit was the one done by george w bush for fy 2009. and about $221 billion of each of the last 4 years of trillion $ plus deficits are DUE TO the BUSH TAX CUTs ........ and that is nearly $ 1 trillion .......... in other words Bush IS directly responsible for almost half of the deficits of the last 4 years of so. 2009...... a W budget and a $trillion plus deficit 2010 2011 2012..............4 years of trillion plus deficits.........1 year was W, and $882 billion of the 4 was due to the bush tax cuts alone........</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349788529340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349788541715-9</Id><Topic><Title>Hurry Time Is Ticking``</Title><Username>ruffersantony863</Username><Timestamp>1349787832746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't touch -- high viral load. West Nile. Obama really worried about Romney -- and he should be. OUT OUT OUT THROW THE BAS*TUD OUT!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349788541715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349788621692-10</Id><Topic><Title>6 Years ago, Democrats seized control of congress...</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349727991031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>POLL: Obama loses lead on key voter issues: Economy, national security... President releases new ad -- featuring Big Bird... ... Sits for interview -- with NICKELODEON I'm Only Going To Win If 'Everybody Is Almost Obsessive'...</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1349788621692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:17:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349788825823-11</Id><Topic><Title>Banks witgh Nine Largest Derivative Exposures</Title><Username>wjkeck3</Username><Timestamp>1349746983142</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 21:43:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. This is really important information. The 3 biggest are covered by Dodd Frank too big to fail coverage. GS is on their own and HSBC is Chinese.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349788825823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349789492296-12</Id><Title>Bush and his tax cuts are directly responsible for 43% of US deficits 2009-2012</Title><Msg>2009 bush budget......deficit $1.413 trillion 2010.Obama..........................$1.293 2011........................................$1.3 2012.........................................$1.327 Since The Congressional Budget Office has calculated that........expiration of the Bush tax cuts....would reduce the current deficit by $221 billion. that means that of each of those 4 years about $221 billion was due to the bush tax cuts...... a total of $882 billion..........hence bush and the bush tax cuts are responsible for $2.295 trillion of the total deficit for those 4 years which is 43% of it. and of course if Romney is elected he will balloon the deficit with more tax cuts, and then the gop will go back to saying "deficits don't matter, Reagan proved that" as Cheney used to say.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349789492296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349789537968-13</Id><Title>Merkel Supreme Ruler or Europe visits Greeks</Title><Msg>She tells them -- no more deals. Time to pay. Greece runs out of money after U.S. election and needs another bailout. No more yearly bailouts for Greece. They just don't get it. Ban on protests in Athens but crowds are attacking the building where Merkel is speaking.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349789537968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:32:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349789590574-14</Id><Title>Time to raise the carbon tax</Title><Msg>That will just put a nail in any industrial recovery.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349789590574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349789752874-15</Id><Title>Earnings Season: Worst Outlook In 3 Years</Title><Msg>Stock market should take off from here. Buy before the election. Don't miss the boat.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349789752874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349791470105-16</Id><Title>No more gifts for Greece</Title><Msg>No more money. Fire the tear gas.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349791470105</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349791529305-17</Id><Title>Obama had all the answers in 2008</Title><Msg>...but his answers were all wrong. Obama has never been re-elected. Throw the bas*tud out!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349791529305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349791679190-18</Id><Topic><Title># ORCL Featured on Squawk Box #</Title><Username>tonyjefferson976</Username><Timestamp>1348245999301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome</Msg><Username>gabianderson410</Username><Timestamp>1349791679190</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349792412375-19</Id><Topic><Title>Bush and his tax cuts are directly responsible for 43% of US deficits 2009-2012</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349789492296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The main reason for deficits IS NOT tax cuts. It's excessive spending of "Fed" fairy tale dollars that they collect vigorish on. The thieves that run government will use any excuse to spend more and borrow more. Get an honest money system and quit spreading America's wealth all over the world. BOTH Dems. and Reps. are guilty and most should be in prison for their crimes against the American people.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349792412375</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349793224299-20</Id><Topic><Title>Bush and his tax cuts are directly responsible for 43% of US deficits 2009-2012</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349789492296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, interest in the debt is a lot, but so is the $221 billion a year the bush tax cut costs. it is silly and of no help to blather about "crimes " and "vigorish'........ the fact is tax must be raised and progressively so ; and spending has to get cut. btw, the total USA interest paid for 2012 was the lowest since 2005 as per Interest Expense on the Debt Outstanding, treasury direct dot gov</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349793224299</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:33:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349793344840-21</Id><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Msg>or anywhere else in the Islamic world! Buy their oil, kill any threats and leave them to rot! Wasting precious blood and money for this rat-hole is a crime against humanity! They are human #$%$... at least most of the men! The only good reason to stay is to kill half the men and virtually all the mullahs!! "Taliban gunmen in Pakistan shot and seriously wounded on Tuesday a 14-year-old schoolgirl who rose to fame for speaking out against the militants, authorities said. Malala Yousufzai was shot in the head and neck when gunmen fired on her school bus in the Swat valley, northwest of the capital, Islamabad. Two other girls were also wounded, police said. Yousufzai became famous for speaking out against the Pakistani Taliban at a time when even the government seemed to be appeasing the hardline Islamists." I can only hope that the sub-human F'ers who did this or support those who did this rot in the depths of HELL!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349795069116-22</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waiting for Romney and Ryan to withdraw and lose Afghanistan? Bush should have done what obama did instead of invading and occupying and installing Karzai, and blathering for years that we had to train an afghan army to defend karzi........why didn't bush leave afghanistan in 2008? then he could have lost afghanistan........</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349795069116</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349795651823-23</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Obama promised to end the war in Iraq 4 years ago - Palin, the GOP and Fox all said Obama was "waiving the white flag of surrender" - it's that kind of rhetorec that has many thinking we need to endlessly police the middle east and as Romney now pumps "shape the values of freedom in the middle east" they no longer mention "beacons of democracy" becuase they suddenly realized the majority are muslim.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1349795651823</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349796135224-24</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Save us your ignorant Pigshyt on Bush, Romney and Ryan! Why the F is your Nobel Peace Prize Pig still keeping us in that Rat-hole of Humanity... sending guys over to get shot in the back by some Islamic #$%$! I guess his best Intelligence is telling him to expect an imminent Taliban Invasion of America!? Oh right.... Afghanistan is his "Good" F'ing War! Total Crap! The only GOOD reason to be there ended in early 2002!! Indeed, the only good strategy for the Islamic world is to kill the threat and leave! Since then, and certainly today, there is NOTHING to "Lose" by leaving Afghanistan because there is NOTHING to "Win" by staying!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1349796135224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349796405988-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bush and his tax cuts are directly responsible for 43% of US deficits 2009-2012</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349789492296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure Pigshyt!! The only reason Interest is low is because Bernanke drove rates down to near ZERO! But Obama will soon take care of that with Trillions more in DEBT, a Fed Res that is virtually bankrupt and skyrocketing inflation!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349796405988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349797045342-26</Id><Topic><Title>Bush and his tax cuts are directly responsible for 43% of US deficits 2009-2012</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349789492296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bla bla bla, you bum. "deficits, don't matter, reagan proved that" remember? and if you are worried about debt , you would not advocate more tax cuts. the ONLY way to go is to end the bush tax cuts , as obama said, first for the rich..... and then to make some spending cuts.. the gop want to do the very same baloney that they and bush did before...... still believing in the miracle of the trickle..... just like they count dinosaurs on Noah's ark and insist the earth is 9000 yrs old, they insist on their childish, refuted economics on a napkin, laffer's curve which says 4-1 = 5.........................</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349797045342</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:37:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349797282518-27</Id><Title>Obama economy creating part time jobs</Title><Msg>at Wal Mart and MCDonalds without benefits *** Miserable, slow, desperate, financial repression. Prolong the misery. 4 more years.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349797282518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349797821155-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama economy creating part time jobs</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349797282518</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we all know Romney can do better with all those Cadillacs that need waxing and lets not forget the lawn in the Cayman Islands that needs mowing.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1349797821155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349798015285-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bush and his tax cuts are directly responsible for 43% of US deficits 2009-2012</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349789492296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rates? you want to talk about rates? who pumped sub-prime while people were buying inflated homes with zero down? told everyone "the economy is fundamentally sound" right up to TARP? who ? who? who? who?</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1349798015285</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349798081192-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bush and his tax cuts are directly responsible for 43% of US deficits 2009-2012</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349789492296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:31:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how can you say it's not both? who offers cuts while engaging in a trillion dollar war that's not budgeted for?</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1349798081192</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 11:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349798553296-31</Id><Title>Romney and Obama tied in Ohio</Title><Msg>Obama's lead is evaporating as people come to their senses. Biden gaffes at debate will sink the ship.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349798553296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349798750864-32</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and Obama tied in Ohio</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349798553296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:02:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Daily Swing State Tracking Poll Swing State Tracking: Romney 49%, Obama 47% in Politics Email thisShareThis Related Articles Daily Presidential Tracking Poll 2012 Electoral College Scoreboard 2012 Senate Balance of Power 37% Say U.S. Heading in Right Direction Generic Congressional Ballot: Democrats 44%, Republicans 43% Consumer, Investor Confidence Dips Slightly But Still Up From Jobs Report Sign up for free daily updates Tuesday, October 09, 2012 The full Swing State tracking update offers Rasmussen Reader subscribers a combined view of the results from 11 key states won by President Obama in 2008 and thought to be competitive in 2012. The states collectively hold 146 Electoral College votes and include Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Michigan, Nevada, New Hampshire, North Carolina, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Virginia and Wisconsin. If you do not already have a Rasmussen Reader account, subscribe now. Platinum Members have access to detailed demographic information. In the 11 swing states, Mitt Romney earns 49% support to Obama’s 47%. One percent (1%) likes another candidate, and three percent (3%) are undecided. This is the first time Romney has led the daily Swing State Survey since September 19. Until today, the president had led for 17 of the previous 19 days, and the candidates had been tied twice. This survey is based on findings from the previous seven days, with most of the responses now coming since Romney’s debate win last Wednesday night. Forty-six percent (46%) of these Swing State voters are now “certain” they will vote for Romney and will not change their minds. Forty percent (40%) are certain they will vote for the president.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349798750864</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349798971435-33</Id><Title>Obama signed fiscal cliff into law</Title><Msg>Cracks are showing all over. They purposely pushed all the bad news until after the election. Obama, Pelosi and Reid planned the largest tax increase in American history to kick in right after this election. People are fleeing California due to high taxes. You can get 4 burritos for a gallon of gasoline. Bozo is going the wrong way. Don't be a bagholder.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349798971435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349799249905-34</Id><Title>Sandusky gets 30 years</Title><Msg>Why hasn't Holder prosecuted the 9/11 terrorists yet? Or the Fort Hood shooter? Are they getting a taxpayer paid vacation at Gitmo? Obama ain't done nuttin but apologize for America.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349799249905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349799776974-35</Id><Title>you Obamazombies</Title><Msg>it is over for you. Short of a disaster on Romney's part, Obama cannot recover. You lefties created in your parallel universe some kind of super hero in Obama. You built him up to invincibility. Similarly you created in your parallel universe your own caricature of Romney. All that came down during the debate. Millions saw the real Obama. Millions saw the real Romney. Game, set, match for Romney.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349799776974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349799787668-36</Id><Title>Obamacare is cause of increase in part time workers</Title><Msg>Prepping for Obamacare, Chain Cuts Workers' Hours Darden, the owner of Olive Garden and Red Lobster (a favorite of blacks) restaurants is putting more workers on part-time status in move at limiting the impact of looming health coverage requirements under Obamacare. Darden Restaurants is increasing the number of workers on part-time status, meaning they work less than 30 hours a week. Under the new health care act, companies will be required to provide health care to full-time employees by 2014. That would significantly boost labor costs for businesses.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349799787668</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349799907936-37</Id><Topic><Title>you Obamazombies</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349799776974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a stupid little #$%$ you are!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349799907936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349800392741-38</Id><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Msg>favorable......unfavorable rating Obama's rating is better, 55-44 percent Romney 47-51 percent Mitt Romney reached his highest personal popularity of the election campaign among registered voters in the latest ABC News/Washington Post poll - but not by enough to lift his head above water, nor to surpass Barack Obama, who reached his own best favorability rating of the season. Night-to-night data indicate a sizable boost for Romney, and drop for Obama, on Thursday night, a day after their first debate, which Romney widely is seen as having won. But both of those trends subsequently subsided in this poll, conducted Thursday through Sunday. latest ABC News/Washington Post poll - .A Popularity High for Romney - but Ditto for Obama By Gary Langer | ABC OTUS News – 5 hrs ago.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800431415-39</Id><Topic><Title>you Obamazombies</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349799776974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beat it Mesa, you little piece of crap. Obama is a socialist crumb. We will kick his rear end out of office. People are on to him. How does a 55-45 Romney win feel? Mesa, your brand of presidential politics is finished.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349800431415</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800536502-40</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's rating is better, 55-44 percent *** You are confused. 55-44 was the fake result of the Hugo Chavez socialist dictator re-election. Romney leads Obama by 4 points and is surging in Ohio and Florida.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349800536502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800573165-41</Id><Topic><Title>you Obamazombies</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349799776974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your clown car boiled a circus down to a gaffe machine bent on more war and tax breaks for the wealthy</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1349800573165</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800773984-42</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If people are heavily persuaded by a take no prisoner approach to the debates then that's what you should see from Obama next debate. He really does need to remind everyone of the similarities of Bush and Romney and how Romney is bent on sending more troops to the middle east and really has no plan.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1349800773984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800894117-43</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While saying nothing of his own record of the past 4 years.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349800894117</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349800980908-44</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has anyone noticed how the press treats Obama like the candidate and Romney like the incumbent? Very interesting.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349800980908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349801039038-45</Id><Topic><Title>you Obamazombies</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349799776974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weasel seabug farts and interprets it as a voice from god telling him to put on mormon underwear and just trust mitt. Romney promises everyone 55 and older that medicare stays just the SAME as it is now for them. and those who are younger? Romney promises those younger that they CAN CHOOSE medicare AS IT IS NOW.....(or a voucher). so if everyone chooses traditional medicare over the romeny voucher.... then in effect medicare stays same as it is now!...... but how does Romney pay for it?........ with tax cuts ? or trickle down? do you true believers even care or bother to think about the nonsense that Romney spews? weasel man sebug has no idea, he is just an a s s whisperer and cheerleader for the guy who hides his tax returns, banks in the caymans and lies about most everything. for instance the 47% .... who know he says he was wrong about..... just like he was wrong about romneycare, i guess..... and wrong that his plan covers people with preexisting conditions..... it does't... that was a lie.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349801039038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349801367304-46</Id><Topic><Title>you Obamazombies</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349799776974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, watch for much of that 47% to vote for Romney.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349801367304</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349801447367-47</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fyi bush increased gov spending more by far than obama has, and obama is the one who got bin laden, all you bums did was blow trilliions looking for wmd in iraq. but sure, cheerleader man. wave your pom poms and shake your rear....funny, both bush and romney were cheerleaders too. maybe one day you will anwer up on the issues, but i doubt it, you are just too darn stupid. here, try this one, bimbo : Romney promises everyone 55 and older that medicare stays just the SAME as it is now for them. and those younger? Romney promises those younger that they CAN CHOOSE medicare AS IT IS NOW.....(or a voucher). so if everyone chooses traditional medicare over the romeny voucher.... then in effect medicare stays same as it is now!...... but how does Romney pay for it?........ with tax cuts ? or trickle down? do you true believers even care or bother to think about the nonsense that Romney spews?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349801447367</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349801766062-48</Id><Topic><Title>you Obamazombies</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349799776974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:22:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A big leap in women favoring Romney. When all is said and done by the leftwing press, (petty attacks, phony poll numbers and avoiding the Libya fallout), Obama is no match for real leadership. The next debate will be the Dems Waterloo.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349801766062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349802000491-49</Id><Title>If Romney wins it will be bad for the nation, a worse disaster than bush most likely</Title><Msg>but, heck.... I guess i will just have to take my Romney tax cuts on top of my bush tax cuts and add them into the unchanged , as is, "entitlement" Romeny and the gop promise me. Thanks gop, you will own medicare and social security and you have promised them as is for most of the boomers who will be on them out into the 2040s...... and you promised the same traditional medicare for all younger than 55 if they "choose" it............ so finally, if Romney wins the gop will have to shut up about the "entitlements" which are no longer a problem.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349802000491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:00:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349803273231-50</Id><Title>1st debate gets biggest audience....</Title><Msg>next we get Ryan schooling Biden on the #s... talk about a disaster for Obama/Biden then Obama will look dumber still as he tries to defend his Foreign Policy Before you know it Chris Mathews will be talking about the tingle in his leg when he thinks about voting for Romney</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1349803273231</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349804336466-51</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey, retard, how many little girls were fried by your gay drones? WAKE UP AND SMELL THE COFFEE, #$%$ if SHE WAS DUMB ENOUGH TO SPEAK OUT AGAINST MEN WHO ARE RISKING THEIR LIVES TO PROTECT THEIR BELIEFS, THEN SHE DESERVED WHAT SHE GOT. HEY, DIP, SOON THEY WILL HAVE YOU WORSHIPPING SODOMITES, AND IF YOU SAY A WORD AGASINT them , they will cut off your balls!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1349804336466</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349804804416-52</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Carl, Glad to see you are back from vacation. You didn't eat the sushi! Did you?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349804804416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:46:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349806822586-53</Id><Title>Prolong the misery 4 more years</Title><Msg>We need a President who will do nothing and who will blame everyone but himself. That's real leadership!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349806822586</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349806881685-54</Id><Topic><Title>Great Info On ORCL... Check It!</Title><Username>salinaschristina992</Username><Timestamp>1349786392951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:39:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>add me to the list of bagholders! I am up enough that I have to stay to watch the end of this one</Msg><Username>puckettn38</Username><Timestamp>1349806881685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349806921935-55</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Has anyone noticed how the press treats Obama like the candidate and Romney like the incumbent? Very interesting. *** Romney looks like the President. Obama looks like a clown with big ears who smiles at his wife.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349806921935</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349807327805-56</Id><Title>Greece needs 3rd bailout by November</Title><Msg>The IMF forecast that Greek public debt will rise to 171 percent of gross domestic product (GDP) this year and 182 percent in 2013. Greeks in Na$zi uniforms greet Merkel. Greece needs a 3rd bailout. They just want ECB for forgive all the debt, after all they already wrote off 80% of it. Greece is being propped up by ECB. 5 years of recession and things keep getting worse. There's no way out! Greece needs 30 billion Euro after U.S. election or the party's over. Does Merkel save Greece (where they don't like her) or does she save Spain, Cyprus, Ireland and Italy?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349807327805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349808482082-57</Id><Title>Obama focuses on Big Bird instead of real problems</Title><Msg>The economy is tanking and Obama keeps talking about Big Bird. Companies are switching employees to part time status because of Obamacare and Obama does a victory lap because the UE rate went down. Things are getting worse. You can't trust Nobama. He signed the largest tax increase in the history of the USA into law. We don't get fooled again.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349808482082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349808947138-58</Id><Topic><Title>SHORTS</Title><Username>samspade_44</Username><Timestamp>1215098014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2008-07-03 11:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going short TODAY. My target is $28.2! :-) (1/2 of the work, for guys who like puts).</Msg><Username>hacisback</Username><Timestamp>1349808947138</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349808986191-59</Id><Title>Sesame Street requests Obama take down Big Bird ad</Title><Msg>Big Bird don't like Nobama! The production company behind Sesame Street is asking political campaigns to refrain from using their characters in campaign ads — including an Obama campaign ad that uses Big Bird.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349808986191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349809175092-60</Id><Topic><Title>SHORTS</Title><Username>samspade_44</Username><Timestamp>1215098014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2008-07-03 11:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also shorting OXY today -- :) posting the target on OXY's msg board momentarily. hacisback</Msg><Username>hacisback</Username><Timestamp>1349809175092</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349809599624-61</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And as for you, Vlad, you stinking piece of human fungus, God Willing you will suffer an even worse fate! You fully deserve it... you ugly MF'ing Russian Pig!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1349809599624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349810112075-62</Id><Topic><Title>Great Info On ORCL... Check It!</Title><Username>salinaschristina992</Username><Timestamp>1349786392951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:39:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>been a custermore for years, no reason to leave</Msg><Username>hal.smith63</Username><Timestamp>1349810112075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349810126277-63</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama did not end the Stupid War of Nation Building in Iraq one day earlier than Bush would have.... he just F'ed up the end process and left us with Jackshyt save a Shia Iranian take-over... and endless Blood Baths with Sunnis!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1349810126277</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:15:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349811574217-64</Id><Title>New nickname for Obama: Big Bird</Title><Msg>Many still call him Robin Hood.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349811574217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349812158756-65</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney signs defaced with excrement in Virginia By David Sherfinski - The Washington Times October 9, 2012, 01:12PM A conservative radio host based in central Virginia, has posted a video on his website of a GOP office with its window smashed in, expletive-laced rants presumably delivered at Republicans, and Mitt Romney/Paul Ryan signs torn down, defaced and smeared with what appears to be human excrement. The clip (prefaced with a warning of "extremely graphic content") on the "Schilling Show" blog, written by radio host Rob Schilling, begins with President Obama on the campaign trail telling attendees to "argue with them and get in their face," a phrase he used in 2008 to encourage his supporters to talk to friends and neighbors about voting and accurately delivering his message, whether they were Republican or independent. The clip then shifts to an expletive-laced rant labeled "Actual phone call received at Albemarle County, Virginia GOP Headquarters — September 11, 2012." It goes on to show a man tearing down yard signs at an Americans For Prosperity event in Charlottesville while screaming obscenities, then a montage of Republican political signs that have been defaced — in one case with excrement — and Nazi imagery plastered onto an AFP sign. The video ends with the words "Don't let Democrats, vandals, thieves, oppressors, intimidators, and tyrants silence you … Remember, NOVEMBER IS COMING." Virginia is a critical battleground state, with the Charlottesville and Albemarle area — where the video was filmed — essentially the only Democratic stronghold in the state's expansive southside 5th Congressional district. Sign wars are a traditional part of campaigning, and operatives use all sorts of tactics to try to put up as many signs as they can, and to protect their signs from vandalism by angry opponents.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349812158756</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349812407510-66</Id><Topic><Title>Great Info On ORCL... Check It!</Title><Username>salinaschristina992</Username><Timestamp>1349786392951</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 08:39:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have 2 accounts...have had them for years..and I am not going anywhere</Msg><Username>marlin.moore90</Username><Timestamp>1349812407510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349816559681-67</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could "liar, liar" backfire? The Obama campaign's feverish bid to cast Mitt Romney as "dishonest" on his tax-plan claims is running into headwinds ahead of the vital second presidential debate. Fact-checkers have been heavily scrutinizing the Obama campaign's logic. One economist chided the team for using his research to claim Romney's pushing a middle-class tax hike. And Republicans claim the "liar, liar" strategy is a sign of desperation after a tough debate, with just four weeks left on the clock until Election Day. "This business of just going out and calling a candidate for the president of the United States a liar, just saying liar, liar -- that in my view ... this is a new low," Sen. John McCain, the 2008 Republican nominee, told Fox News on Tuesday. "It means that they're out of ideas." Ann Romney, in an interview with Fox News, also questioned the Obama campaign claims. "This is what (Romney) believes. These are the policies. These are his statements. I mean, it's sort of like someone in the sandbox who lost the game and kicks sand in someone's face and says 'you liar'," she said. "To me it's poor sportsmanship." The campaign is not quite calling Romney a liar, though it's come close. Obama advisers and President Obama himself insist that Romney last week was peddling a platform that diverges from what he's been selling on the stump these past many months. Central to that argument is their claim he wants a $5 trillion tax cut, which Romney denied last week. The Obama campaign argues that while Romney says his plan is deficit-neutral, there's no way he'd be able to find enough loopholes and other benefits to sacrifice in order to make up the difference. Therefore, Obama says, the plan would end up either raising taxes on the middle class or adding to the deficit. The Obama campaign launched an aggressive effort to cast Romney as untruthful in the aftermath of the debate. Adviser Robert Gibbs told "Meet the Press" on Sunday that Romney will "say anything to get elected." A new Obama TV ad declared Romney's tax claims were "dishonest." But fact checkers returned fire. The AP said Obama's claim "doesn't add up." Politifact deemed the president's claim "half-true," calling it "accurate but misleading." Could Romney's tax cuts by themselves add up to $5 trillion? Maybe. But he also pledges to close loopholes and deductions to make up the difference, though he hasn't offered many specifics. Obama acknowledges this, but still calls it a $5 trillion tax cut. "The $5 trillion figure accounts for only half of Romney's plan," Politifact notes. The campaign on Sunday released a breakdown of how it got to the $5 trillion number. It counted $2.5 trillion from Romney's plan to lower rates by 20 percent across the board. It included $1.1 trillion from a corporate tax cut, and $150 billion from a repeal of the estate tax, among other things. "Even the studies that Romney has cited to claim his plan adds up still show he would need to raise middle class taxes," the campaign said in a statement -- claiming Princeton economist Harvey Rosen found "paying for Romney's tax cuts would require large tax increases on families making between $100,000 and $200,000."</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349816559681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349817865079-68</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mitt is proven a liar. recent mitt lies: 1.he has no plan for prexisting conditions, 2. the ACA is the same as Romneycare, based on private insurance, not a gov "take over". 3. he lied about the 47% and so what if he now admits he lied. 4. He lied about more taxcuts..... or is he lying now when he says the wealthy will not get any more tax cuts. 5. he is likely lying about his previous tax returns, hence he only show recent obviously window dressed ones.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349817865079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:24:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349818353307-69</Id><Title>on the subject of lunatic conservatives: gop politician claims Jesus was pro slavery.....</Title><Msg>Arkansas State Rep: ‘If Slavery Were So God-Awful, Why Didn’t Jesus Or Paul Condemn It?’ After Arkansas Republicans disavowed a book by state representative Jon Hubbard (R-AR) claiming slavery was “a blessing in disguise” for African Americans, Hubbard’s colleague, state Rep. Loy Mauch (R-AR) has been outed by the Arkansas Times for his pro-slavery, pro-Confederacy letters to the editor over the past decade. Mauch’s run for reelection this year is backed by the Arkansas Republican Party. In letters to the Democrat-Gazette, Mauch vehemently defended slavery and repeatedly suggested Jesus condoned it: If slavery were so God-awful, why didn’t Jesus or Paul condemn it, why was it in the Constitution and why wasn’t there a war before 1861?The South has always stood by the Constitution and limited government. When one attacks the Confederate Battle Flag, he is certainly denouncing these principles of government as well as Christianity. His other letters call Abraham Lincoln a Marxist and celebrate the Confederate flag as “a symbol of Christian liberty vs. the new world order.” He also organized a conference in 2004 praising John Wilkes Booth and calling for the removal of an Abraham Lincoln statue. Mauch has been supported mainly by contributions from the Republican Party and other Arkansas candidates. Now, the state GOP is pulling all funds from Mauch, Hubbard and another state legislative candidate, Charlie Fuqua, who wants to expel all Muslims from the country and thinks rebellious children should receive the death penalty.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349818353307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349819150491-70</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and Obama tied in Ohio</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349798553296</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:02:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rassmussen, snicker, snicker!</Msg><Username>economist_too</Username><Timestamp>1349819150491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349820658196-71</Id><Topic><Title>6 Years ago, Democrats seized control of congress...</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349727991031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The debt commission... 6 GOP and 6 DEM... couldn't agree on anything and created the "fiscal cliff"... which is $800 billion out of domestic spending and $800 billion out of defense. That cliff hits on January 1st along with big tax increases stemming from the expiration of bush's tax cuts. Here's the thing: 13 months ago, OBAMA COULD HAVE GOTTEN INVOLVED. He could have "LED"... and he didn't. Obama hasn't "led" anything in 4 years. He just talks... every DAY... he TALKS. Same with the 9/11 Libyan disaster... no leadership... no preparation... just "hope". Romney, at least, is a LEADER. He has "led" his entire career... Bain, the Olympics, Mass... all of them pretty much successfully. The contrast between these 2 candidates is IMMENSE!</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349820658196</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349822016784-72</Id><Topic><Title>New nickname for Obama: Big Bird</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349811574217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some call him: Big Turd!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349822016784</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349822312519-73</Id><Title>Have you noticed hardwaredummyfromleftfield's MO?</Title><Msg>He says stupid stuff on one day. Every sane person refutes him. Next day he says the same stupid stuff again as if nothing happened. Everybody refutes him again. Third day he says same stupid stuff again as if it was new and fresh. REAL DUMMY!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349822312519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349823238197-74</Id><Title>New Nickname for Obama</Title><Msg>Don't insult Big Bird. Next thing you know, Obama will send out orders to occupy seseme st. Burt and Ernie said they are going to run for Pres and VP on the Party of the Party ticket. Cookies for everyone. I think they would make Obama and Biden look like muppets. Hey why not, Rosanne Barr and Cindy Sheehan are on the ballot under Peace and Freedom. As liberal voters go, they just might pull it off.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1349823238197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349823720348-75</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong catfish breath. 1) He has plans for every possible occurrence, both domestically and nationally. 2) Obummercare is a national takeover of medical care by it's very nature of affecting all 57 States. Romneys plan was Mass. only and was not 2700 pages long and did not entitle the head of HHS and other federal bureaucrats to make medical decisions which would affect all Americans. 3) He was right about the 47 percent and only said he could have stated it more delicately. 4) Looney left are the only ones who said he lied about tax cuts. Romney knows the only. way out of this mess is to grow our economy. Remember, govt consumes, the free enterprise system, which has served America well for the past 240 years produces. All the wealth the Bummer wants to take from the most successful Americans ( top1-2 percent) would run this country for 5 days. Big deal 5) Class warfare by the Bummer and MSM would only be exacerbated if they saw how Successful he really was.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349823720348</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349824065347-76</Id><Title>Obama wishes Vladimir Putin a Happy 60th Birthday!</Title><Msg>And promises to betray America for him after the election.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349824065347</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349824104663-77</Id><Topic><Title>What The Hell Are We Still Doing In Afghanistan!??</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1349793344840</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:35:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ASK BGROUP.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1349824104663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349824891468-78</Id><Topic><Title>Have you noticed hardwaredummyfromleftfield's MO?</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349822312519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because he's stuck on DA. What he posts over and over is meaningless anyway, just humor him or skip him.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349824891468</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:21:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349827694503-79</Id><Topic><Title>mitt's bounce is mostly gone already....Obama is rated more favorable by 8 points</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349800392741</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:33:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1) Bull kaka. Will cost an extra 50 billion a year minimum. Where is that in Bummer's budget. 2) Bull kakis squared - 2700 pages of govt takeover of medicine in America compared to one little state. HHS director will make all important decisions, not physicians. 3) You got it, bull kaka cubed. He was right, just not politically correct 4) Hogwash. Trillion a year deficit so any tax cuts inconsequential. 5) Class warfare stance</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349827694503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349829953098-80</Id><Topic><Title>Have you noticed hardwaredummyfromleftfield's MO?</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349822312519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is rather funny! Sorta like an Axlerod on Prozac.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349829953098</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349830068154-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wishes Vladimir Putin a Happy 60th Birthday!</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349824065347</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:07:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least we know Putin is a Russian.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349830068154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349830173127-82</Id><Topic><Title>on the subject of lunatic conservatives: gop politician claims Jesus was pro slavery.....</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349818353307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 17:32:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody forgot to take their Prozac this morning.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349830173127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349830252072-83</Id><Topic><Title>Sesame Street requests Obama take down Big Bird ad</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349808986191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obummer is Big Bird incognito.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349830252072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349831752611-84</Id><Title>Now We Know The Reason</Title><Msg>Why Obama kept looking down at the debates. He has one of those new belt buckle teleprompters.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349831752611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 21:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349838672059-85</Id><Topic><Title>Sesame Street requests Obama take down Big Bird ad</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349808986191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Bird ad was a "jump the shark" moment for Obama. proof that he's got nuttin'!!!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349838672059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349839497438-86</Id><Title>Obama getting illegal donations funneled through China!</Title><Msg>US citizen in China owns the rights to [moc-tod-amabO] and donations that site are funneled through Chinese banks. Little is done to check that donations are proper and legal and not being made on temporary gift type credit cards. Most donations are under $200 and get little checking. Obama Campaign did this in 2008. It was discovered so late that little was done about it. And McCain Campaign was a wimp about it.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349839497438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349839556674-87</Id><Topic><Title>Obama getting illegal donations funneled through China!</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349839497438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Similar web sites exist for MyObama-dot-whatever.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349839556674</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>