<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351685903525-1</Id><Topic><Title>Fatso Crisco loves the OBAMA administration.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351655512280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:51:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bummer is a weasel.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351685903525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351686312493-2</Id><Topic><Title>A little more from Thomsas Jefferson....</Title><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1351630988369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 17:03:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jefferson , Obama, Pelosi, and Reid are of the same mold. Add Madison, Adams, Jay, and the like. I suggest you read the Federalalist Papers to get a clue about our forefathers and their thought on America. Didn't see anything in there about food stamps, kumbaya metrics, or Mooslims.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351686312493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351687264436-3</Id><Topic><Title>Thomas Jefferson supported progressive taxation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351620692202</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:11:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the product to the treasury is not so great as when they are confined within proper and moderate bounds ( Madison in The Federalist Papers ). Moderate was not confiscation in the neighborhood of 50 percent of ones earnings.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351687264436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351687355536-4</Id><Topic><Title>Fatso Crisco loves the OBAMA administration.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351655512280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:51:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And now New Jersey will probably vote donkey. What a shock.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351687355536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351687706158-5</Id><Title>Retired military</Title><Msg>Overwhelmingly supports Mitt. Active military cannot speak out for fear of reprisal, but hundreds of retired military like Tommy Franks voice their support for Romney. They know the Bummer is a clueless American leader. But a community organizer.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351687706158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351687819490-6</Id><Title>Sweaty Mitts &amp; Ryan will gut medicare in 2016, even those on it will see huge cuts.</Title><Msg>Romney's big medicare lie: nothing changes for those on or near on being on it if sweaty Mitts repeals the ACA, then medicare would benefits have to be cut immediately in 2016. Mitt's would have Romensia about his promise that medicare would stay the same...... or he would say oops.....and of course the gop in conrgress would not vote any tax increase to bolster medicare, so electing Mitt's means a huge medicare cut for those ON it , and of course everyone who will go on it. this is how the gop likes to do things, folks, they lie, mislead, the bully and then next thing you know, oops there were no wmd, oops reagan never proved deficits don't matter and oops, there goes medicare, sorry . The ACA keeps medicare as is until 2024 or so, and the dems will do the right thing, raise some taxes make some cuts and keep medicare good to go for generations., there is plenty of time for a rational and bipartisan remedy. Nobody in their right mind could possibly think the Mitts medicare promise is anything but a cynical lie. sure, easy to promise that he fixes it and the fix costs nothing.... cash back in fact...tax cuts.... and yet his no cost fix promises that medicare will not be changed for those on it or near being on it.... most of the boomers who will be on it out into the 2040s.......paid for how? tax cuts. Nope Mittens and Ryan will gut medicare in 2016 for those on it and everyone else too. /</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351687819490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 08:50:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351690782410-7</Id><Topic><Title>Fatso Crisco loves the OBAMA administration.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351655512280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:51:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christie doesn't much like Romney. Christie wants to run clean of everything for Prez in '16 and a Romney win would ruin that for him.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351690782410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351690871889-8</Id><Title>sweaty Mitts will gut and end medicare by 2016</Title><Msg>his promise of no change for all on it and all near.........is just horse manure</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351690871889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 09:41:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351692366028-9</Id><Title>sweaty mitts will destroy medicare by 2016</Title><Msg>if sweaty Mitts repeals the ACA, then medicare benefits would have to be cut immediately in 2016. Mitt's would have Romensia about his promise that medicare would stay the same...... or he would say oops.....and of course the gop in conrgress would not vote any tax increase to bolster medicare, so electing Mitt's means a huge medicare cut for those ON it , and of course everyone who will go on it. this is how the gop likes to do things, folks, they lie, mislead, the bully and then next thing you know, oops there were no wmd, oops reagan never proved deficits don't matter and oops, there goes medicare, sorry . The ACA keeps medicare as is until 2024 or so, and the dems will do the right thing, raise some taxes make some cuts and keep medicare good to go for generations., there is plenty of time for a rational and bipartisan remedy. Nobody in their right mind could possibly think the Mitts medicare promise is anything but a cynical lie. sure, easy to promise that he fixes it and the fix costs nothing.... cash back in fact...tax cuts.... and yet his no cost fix promises that medicare will not be changed for those on it or near being on it.... most of the boomers who will be on it out into the 2040s.......paid for how? tax cuts? Magic? Nope Mittens and Ryan will gut medicare in 2016 for those on it and everyone else too.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351692366028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351692555203-10</Id><Title>Mitts:I care for 100% of the people..really. i mean it, i'm not lying</Title><Msg>Mitt: i care for 100% of the people..... trust me............... in mitt horse manure talk trust me means " s.c r ew you"</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351692555203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351693652540-11</Id><Title>Mitt: corporations are people......special people like me and not little people like you</Title><Msg>so what if some of these special "people" are bullies and traitors Of course, corporate chieftains say they're not making threats — just suggestions. As Boss Siegel disingenuously put it: "There's no way I can pressure anybody. I'm not in the voting booth with them." But, of course, he can see (or be told by watchful managers) if any employee dares to sport an Obama campaign button, bumper sticker or lawn sign. And he can find out if any rebellious worker has gone to a Democratic Party event, volunteered in the wrong campaign or made a donation to Obama (now there's a chilling irony — under Citizens United, Siegel can secretly shovel a million bucks or more straight out of the corporate treasury into an anti-Obama campaign group, but a regular person's $200 donation has to be disclosed for all to see, including the boss). So, sure, this is America, where we're all equal as citizens — you, me and the Fortune 500. And don't forget that you're perfectly free to defy the guy who can fire you for whatever reason he makes up — or for no reason at all. Good luck with that. "</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351693652540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351694681560-12</Id><Title>Mor Sandees ta cum n de footure.... ;-) I pray daylee fa THE ARMMAGGEDDION,.... ;-) ...AMEN... ;-)</Title><Msg>GJA ... ;-) ... and hypocrites everywhere.... ;-)</Msg><Username>beethovenwasablack_m_a_n</Username><Timestamp>1351694681560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351695456208-13</Id><Title>hitler was a white christian and the pope and priests and all the germany clergy seig heiled him</Title><Msg>hitler was a white christian and the pope and priests and all the germany clergy seig heiled him i point this out to the racist scumposter who calls himself beethovenwasablack_m_a_n.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351695456208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351695726467-14</Id><Topic><Title>Fatso Crisco loves the OBAMA administration.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351655512280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 23:51:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crisco hates Mittens and wants him to lose, then Crisco will run next time.</Msg><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1351695726467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351696495995-15</Id><Title>willard milton cornwallis romney</Title><Msg>return of the red coats and white wigged foofy aristocrat phonys</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351696495995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351697479452-16</Id><Title>Grover Glenn Norquist, Reinhold Reince Priebus and Willard Milton Romney</Title><Msg>Grover Glenn Norquist rynce priebus and willard milton romney have denounced Little Lord Fauntleroy as a pretender and not a real aristocrat</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351697479452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:31:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351697502306-17</Id><Topic><Title>hitler was a white christian and the pope and priests and all the germany clergy seig heiled him</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351695456208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt, you #$%$ Hitler was Occultist, a Mystic, like most of the upper echelon of the 3rd Reich... and saw Christianity as dead meat, in its last days! But like any slick lying politician he used it when it benefited him.... just like your High Priest, Obama!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1351697502306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351699133041-18</Id><Topic><Title>hitler was a white christian and the pope and priests and all the germany clergy seig heiled him</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351695456208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There have been many lies told about Germany and the NSDAP ("Nazis"). Most simply swallow what our own "Dr. Goebbels" tell them. Interesting article in the New York Times in 1947 about certain populations before and after the war. Those figures don't jibe with the lying prpaganda. They were taken from a certain group that published a year book. I had the set from 1915 to 1952. This is where the Times got their figures. Get any good book on war time propaganda. Read especially the lies told about "The Huns" during WW1. Many were dressed up and used over in WW2.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351699133041</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 11:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351699779633-19</Id><Title>I Was Hoping</Title><Msg>That Sandy would wash Snooki and that freak show out into the Atlantic and be stranded for about 6 months on a barge that happened by. Christi gave Obama a few accolades because he finally did something right. 1 in the done column, 25 in the undone column. Not going to be enough to be re-elected. The Libya fiasco and Obama's deficit will bring it to an end.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351699779633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351700058484-20</Id><Topic><Title>hitler was a white christian and the pope and priests and all the germany clergy seig heiled him</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351695456208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>German troops wore belt buckles inscribed with "god is with us" ,just about the entire german clergy supported hitler..... and that fact is only surprising to rightwing pubs here who must overlook that christian europe had been murdering jews for centuries.... martin luther was a notorious anti semite and Kristallnacht was a nazi celebration of their christian heritage "Martin Sasse, bishop of the Evangelical Lutheran Church in Thuringia and leading member of the German Christians movement, published a compendium of Martin Luther's writings shortly after the Kristallnacht; Sasse "applauded the burning of the synagogues" and the coincidence of the day, writing in the introduction, "On 10 November 1938, on Luther's birthday, the synagogues are burning in Germany." The German people, he urged, ought to heed these words "of the greatest anti-Semite of his time, the warner of his people against the Jews."[42] Diarmaid MacCulloch argued that Luther's 1543 pamphlet On the Jews and Their Lies was a "blueprint" for the Kristallnacht"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351700058484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351700365410-21</Id><Topic><Title># ORCL Featured on Squawk Box #</Title><Username>tonyjefferson976</Username><Timestamp>1348245999301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>interesting report</Msg><Username>bostonalonso</Username><Timestamp>1351700365410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351702041398-22</Id><Title>bad news for willard milton Romney jr III</Title><Msg>A new Ohio poll released on Wednesday morning by CBS News, The New York Times and The Quinnipiac University Polling Institute showed Obama maintaining a 5 percentage point advantage over Romney in Ohio, the same margin as on a previous CBS/Quinnipiac survey conducted in the state two weeks ago.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351702041398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351702389972-23</Id><Topic><Title>hitler was a white christian and the pope and priests and all the germany clergy seig heiled him</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351695456208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:57:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who the F cares what the Na.zis wore on their f'ing belt buckles... it has nothing to do with your trying to define Hitler as a "Christian", you ignorant POS! He was anything but... although his parents were Roman Catholic, at least in name! Indeed, a number of scholars think Hitler had Jewish roots... from one or both of his parents.</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1351702389972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351702481679-24</Id><Title>Geezers: Mitts will destroy your medicare by 2016</Title><Msg>a mitt repeial of the ACA means medicare will face huge cuts in benefits by 2016. and never mind that mitts promised you your medicare would not be changed, it is a lie..... and don't thing a gop congress and mitt will raise any taxes to keep their promise...... medicare will be gutted and they will say "oops".</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1351702481679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351703452658-25</Id><Title>A Reminder by Ted Nugent</Title><Msg>Have a great day and #$%$ off a liberal.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351703452658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351704576779-26</Id><Title>Obama on storm: we leave no man behind</Title><Msg>Obama actually said that. In the wake of Benghazi (which he hasn't yet addressed) Obama said that in such circumstances we come together as Americans and we leave no man behind. You can't make this stuff up.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351704576779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 13:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351706975027-27</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update for ORCL. Read Now!</Title><Username>luisanderson380</Username><Timestamp>1350042834701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consider yourself one of the fortunate kinds. These folks are the strongest stock newsletters out right now.</Msg><Username>jamestanner40</Username><Timestamp>1351706975027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351707866400-28</Id><Title>old folks: Mittens will destroy medicare before 2016</Title><Msg>.....If Mittens repeals the ACA , medicare will have to make huge cuts in benefits by 2016. Romney will just say "oops" about his promise to leave medicare as is for all on it an all near being on it. His promise is horse manure.... .... he doesn't even bother to show how he pays for his promise..... and the gop in congress aren't going to raise taxes just to keep the promise to medicare , so expect big cuts to your medicare if sweaty mitts is elected.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351707866400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351707904683-29</Id><Topic><Title>bad news for willard milton Romney jr III</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351702041398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:47:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama maintaining a 5 percentage point advantage over Romney in Ohio, the same margin as on a previous CBS/Quinnipiac survey conducted in the state two weeks ago.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351707904683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351708044713-30</Id><Topic><Title>Geezers: Mitts will destroy your medicare by 2016</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1351702481679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a mitt repeal of the ACA means medicare will face huge cuts in benefits by 2016. and never mind that mitts promised you your medicare would not be changed, it is a lie..... and don't think a gop congress and mitt will raise any taxes to keep their promise...... they don't care about you moochers on medicare and can't wait to say "oops", sorry but we have to cut your benefits and NOW.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351708044713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351710468625-31</Id><Title>NTWK $6.45 up 5%......Preannouncement today: Record Fiscal 1Q 2013 of up to $11M vs. $6.2M in 1Q 2013..... Analyst expects 20c/share net income in 1Q 2013 vs. 30c/share loss in 1Q 2012.......Guidance for 2013 is strong with 30 - 40% revenue growth and $1/share net income.....Cloud Divisions growing exponentially........4M share float</Title><Msg>Target: $10+ after earnings November 14 Analysts increased their average target price to $16 and max to $21/share after September FY 2012 earnings report. ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ . Preliminary earnings preannouncement today is the reason for today's start of a pre-earnings rally: Pre- Announcement: NetSol Technologies Expects Record First Quarter Revenue - Total Preliminary Revenue Expected in the Range of $10 to $11 Million - To Hold Fiscal 2013 First Quarter Results Conference Call on November 14 CALABASAS, Calif., Oct. 31, 2012 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- NetSol Technologies, Inc. (NTWK), a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions, today provided preliminary revenue results for the first quarter ended September 30, 2012. Preliminary revenue results indicate the company's strongest first quarter ever, with revenue expected in the range of $10 million to $11 million. --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- An analyst recently upped its earnings projections for NTWK based on significant increased global demand for all of its software products and services (legacy and cloud) Analyst comments: All business lines are very strong growth across the board. Significant demand for all legacy and cloud products. Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 net income projections. EPS forecast of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. . NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. Regarding the fast-growing high margin Cloud Divisions: The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. MORE NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide and Riyadh.</Msg><Username>ntofive</Username><Timestamp>1351710468625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351710669957-32</Id><Topic><Title>Intensity for Mitt Romney Equals Ronald Reagan’s</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351627850471</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 16:10:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With apologies to Lloyd Bentsen: I watched Ron Reagan's movies, and Mitts no Ron Reagan.</Msg><Username>spam_buster_jr</Username><Timestamp>1351710669957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351710783024-33</Id><Title>sweaty mitts: bin laden was no big deal it's "not worth moving heaven and earth" to capture bin Laden</Title><Msg>sweaty mitts: bin laden was no big deal it's "not worth moving heaven and earth" to capture bin Laden. nice call Mr "iran has no access to the sea" Mitt........... and now you are all sour grapes about "bin laden dead, GM alive"......... now you say you would have done just what Obama did.........</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351710783024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351711518138-34</Id><Topic><Title>the great republican Teddy Roosevelt supported progressive taxation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351620935908</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-30 14:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt wouldn't like having his phoony "capital gains" taxed at the same rate as ordinary income!!!</Msg><Username>spam_buster_jr</Username><Timestamp>1351711518138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351711841279-35</Id><Topic><Title>sweaty mitts will destroy medicare by 2016</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351692366028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:06:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surely you don't doubt that Romney/Ryan aren't Compassionate Conservates like W. Do you???</Msg><Username>dumb_quest</Username><Timestamp>1351711841279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351715495241-36</Id><Title>Obama's Massive Deficits and Stagnant Growth Would Ruin America</Title><Msg>When you look at these HUGE $1.2 Trillion Deficits, year-after-year, and the sluggish 1 to 2% growth... it's absolutely NAUSEATING! In any other economic cycle with similarly huge fiscal and monetary stimulus, our economy would be growing at 7 to 9%. Obama has completely decapitated the "private sector" with his daily threats to tax the CR@P out of anybody with any investment capital to invest in job-creating, American industry. The latest report on "capital equipment" spending was horrible. This is NOT a normal election. Clearly, another 4 years under the boot of an anti-capitalist like Obama will absolutely RUIN THIS COUNTRY! NEVER, has an election been this important. Our children will look back on this year 10 or 20 years from now and understand that it was THESE DEFICITS and THIS "CAPITAL FLIGHT" that ruined America... unless we hire a proven leader like Romney to turn it around. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351715495241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351716283795-37</Id><Topic><Title>sweaty mitts will destroy medicare by 2016</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351692366028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:06:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>electing Mitt's means a huge medicare cut for those ON it , and of course everyone who will go on it. this is how the gop likes to do things, folks, they lie, mislead, the bully and then next thing you know, oops there were no wmd, oops reagan never proved deficits don't matter and oops, there goes medicare, sorry .</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351716283795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351716349779-38</Id><Topic><Title>sweaty mitts: bin laden was no big deal it's "not worth moving heaven and earth" to capture bin Laden</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351710783024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sweaty mitts want to do more nation building. sweaty Mitts is just creepy and insane.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351716349779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351716549484-39</Id><Topic><Title>Geezers: Mitts will destroy your medicare by 2016</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1351702481679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a mitt repeal of the ACA means medicare will face huge cuts in benefits by 2016. and never mind that mitts promised you your medicare would not be changed, it is a lie..... hint: this is why mitt can't show how he PAYS FOR keeping medicare unchanged for all on it and all being near on it.............. he just says "trust me" which when translated from gop horse manure into english means #$%$"</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351716549484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351716630412-40</Id><Title>Bin laden is dead, GM is alive</Title><Msg>sweaty mitts would have done the reverse.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351716630412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351720090386-41</Id><Topic><Title>Bin laden is dead, GM is alive</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351716630412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:50:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa ALWAYS dropkicks you repubs.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1351720090386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351720158899-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Massive Deficits and Stagnant Growth Would Ruin America</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351715495241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:31:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>repubs, ya go NUTHIN! You're to blame and guilty for evrything bad that has ever happened.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1351720158899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351720403237-43</Id><Title>Polls: Obama Maintains 5-Point Lead In Ohio,</Title><Msg>Polls: Obama Maintains 5-Point Lead In Ohio, and old folks are on to mitt's wanting to gut medicare by 2016, which is what will happen if he repeals the ACA and does not come up with a some medicare tax hikes...........</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351720403237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351720726534-44</Id><Topic><Title>sweaty mitts will destroy medicare by 2016</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351692366028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:06:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan trotted his geezer mom out to reassure old folks that they can trust Mitt to keep his promise that medicare will remain unchanged for all on it and all near being on it....... a promise that is a lie, because he also promises to repeal the ACA which means medicare has to start cutting benefits by 2016.......... and mitts and the gop are sure not going to raise a dime in taxes..... so guess what happens to your medicare? it gets gutted and not way out in the future.. YOUR medicare will be cut.......(which pubs, you deserve since you thought you would get yours and the cuts would affect future generations, but you better take a closer look, mitts and ryan are going to cut your medicare soon.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351720726534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351720919384-45</Id><Topic><Title>sweaty mitts: bin laden was no big deal it's "not worth moving heaven and earth" to capture bin Laden</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351710783024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 15:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitts is such a zombie he doesn't even know there is a persian gulf, and the gulf of Oman , and the arabian sea........ mitts thinks Iran is landlocked , he said that at a DEBATE where he was prepared to rattle sabers on Iran........</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351720919384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351722072632-46</Id><Topic><Title>Bin laden is dead, GM is alive</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351716630412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:50:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like you baggerboy, Mesa is a stupid F'ing sophmoric lying Pig!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1351722072632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351723781755-47</Id><Topic><Title>Bin laden is dead, GM is alive</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351716630412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 16:50:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GM dead in Europe. Selling lots of cars to govt. Still deeply in debt. Volt a bigger joke than Messsssssebird.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351723781755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351723865322-48</Id><Topic><Title>Polls: Obama Maintains 5-Point Lead In Ohio,</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351720403237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libya will be a killer. Ignorance is bliss.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351723865322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351724110410-49</Id><Topic><Title>sweaty mitts will destroy medicare by 2016</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351692366028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 10:06:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As this jerk off knows, Medicare 60 trillion in arrears. The Republicans have the cajones to address the problem. Donkeys will kick it down the road like all other American problems. Typical of a gutless administration. Appeasers all.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351724110410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351724303718-50</Id><Topic><Title>bad news for willard milton Romney jr III</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351702041398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 12:47:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buckeyes not so stupid as to make the same mistake twice.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351724303718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 18:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351726035501-51</Id><Topic><Title>Polls: Obama Maintains 5-Point Lead In Ohio,</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351720403237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 17:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as hard as they try Mesa, few are buying this. I wholeheartedly doubt that Romney is behind by 5 now. A few days agao he was up or even. Such a change would require a substantial happening? What has happened and changed? Obama's preseidential stance on the hurricane? Hardly. That would not cause that type of swing. Romney will win in OH.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351726035501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351726774590-52</Id><Title>ORCL Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Msg>See all ORCL charts - all on one screen - for free. I use this free standalone lightweight tool (does not install anything on your web browser or computer - this is not an annoying browser toolbar nor an add-in). It is called Yahoo Finance 7 Ways and lets me see all charts (e.g. 1 day, 5 days, 1 month, 3 months, etc.) on the same page for any given security. Do a web search for the website RSTNL and download it from the Downloads section of that website. You can also go to the website CNET, do a search for Yahoo Finance 7 Ways in the downloads section, and download it from there.</Msg><Username>royinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1351726774590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351727460030-53</Id><Title>Liberal Logic 101</Title><Msg>Your greatest accomplishment in office is a program you exempt yourself from. Conservative Logic---If you want free birth control, Fluke, wear a Nancy Pelosi mask.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351727460030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351733989055-54</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>royinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1351726774590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:39:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it works... cool!</Msg><Username>itsacalabreeze</Username><Timestamp>1351733989055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351735155605-55</Id><Title>956 Romney grandchildren endorse Romney</Title><Msg>biblical David had a slew of kids; Shammua Shobab Nathan Solomon Amnon Daniel Absalom Adonijah Shephatiah Ithream Ibhar Elishua Eliphelet Nogah Nepheg Japhia Elishama Eliada Jerimoth David also had at least one daughter, Tamar, daughter of David and Maachah and the full sister of Absalom, who is later raped by her brother Amnon</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351735155605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 21:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>