<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351485260787-1</Id><Title>Rape is *God's Will* but homosexuality is a personal *choice*</Title><Msg>Talk about making stupid stuff up as you go along.</Msg><Username>azhdarchid.quetzalcoatlus</Username><Timestamp>1351485260787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 00:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351485452147-2</Id><Topic><Title>If republicansmussen poll has romne only ahead by 3%</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1351441196796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 12:19:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Polls are all jury-jiggered to favor the Democrats. If any poll says Romney is ahead by 3 it is more likely he is really ahead by 6, or more. This election may turn out to be like a replay of Nixon v. McGovern. A total wipe out for the Democrats.</Msg><Username>azhdarchid.quetzalcoatlus</Username><Timestamp>1351485452147</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 00:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351485674117-3</Id><Topic><Title>free birth control would cut abortion rate by 70%</Title><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1351442216169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 12:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Topic title says "would" but text of message says "could" which means they're making up nonsense from liberal gibberish. After all, maybe it "wouldn't" or "couldn't" either!</Msg><Username>azhdarchid.quetzalcoatlus</Username><Timestamp>1351485674117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 00:41:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351485809908-4</Id><Topic><Title>free birth control would cut abortion rate by 70%</Title><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1351442216169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 12:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact that Barack Obama was an "unwanted baby" makes me wish free birth control, and abortions were available in Hawaii about a dozen years earlier.</Msg><Username>azhdarchid.quetzalcoatlus</Username><Timestamp>1351485809908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 00:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351485970768-5</Id><Topic><Title>free birth control would cut abortion rate by 70%</Title><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1351442216169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 12:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*-** They found that the program reduced the abortion rate among these women by 62 62 WHAT? 62% != 70% 62 abortions is not very many. 62 WHAT?</Msg><Username>azhdarchid.quetzalcoatlus</Username><Timestamp>1351485970768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 00:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351509956373-6</Id><Topic><Title>free birth control would cut abortion rate by 70%</Title><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1351442216169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 12:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Free abortions too!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1351509956373</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 07:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351511412960-7</Id><Title>Tips for the Apocalypse</Title><Msg>There are priceless doom-lifting nuggets like “Get a dog” (Kurt Vonnegut) and “Brace yourself: The idiots are coming.” One of my favorites is a Mother Nature Network slideshow called “Top 10 ways to prepare for the total breakdown of society without looking like a (complete) lunatic.” #1 tip includes “Get solar panels” Obama still has not installed the toxic solar panels on the White House. You're going to need 'em now bozo. Sandy is Obama's Katrina. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351511412960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 07:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351511560092-8</Id><Topic><Title>Rape is *God's Will* but homosexuality is a personal *choice*</Title><Username>azhdarchid.quetzalcoatlus</Username><Timestamp>1351485260787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 00:34:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A tsunami is building to sweep Obama out of Washington. He has brought God's wrath upon America. Liars never succeed. OUT OUT OUT THROW THE BAS*TUD OUT!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351511560092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 07:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351512202155-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama can't stop disaster</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351436274315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In this case, seas will be amped up by giant waves and full-moon-powered high tides. That will combine with drenching rains, triggering inland flooding as the hurricane merges with a winter storm system that will worsen it and hold it in place for days. Louis Uccellini, environmental prediction chief for the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, told The Associated Press that given Sandy's due east-to-west track into New Jersey, that puts the worst of the storm surge just north in New York City, Long Island and Northern New Jersey. "Yes, this is the worst case scenario," he said. In a measurement of pure kinetic energy, NOAA's hurricane research division on Sunday ranked the surge and wave "destruction potential" for Sandy — just the hurricane, not the hybrid storm it will eventually become — at 5.8 on a 0 to 6 scale. Obama's Katrina has arrived. Obama suk balz.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351512202155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351513677564-10</Id><Title>gop &amp; sweaty mitts build the JEEP lie</Title><Msg>GOP constructs the Jeep LIE Mitt Romney Releases Auto Ad That Misleads On Facts Posted: 10/28/2012 2:27 pm EDT Updated: 10/28/2012 5:01 pm EDT WASHINGTON -- The Mitt Romney campaign, still attempting to turn the politics of the auto bailout in its favor, is out with a new television ad that dramatically bends both historical record and current news to fit its narrative. The ad, which was not announced by the campaign, makes no direct claim that can be called a lie. But that's primarily because it's so clever with its wording. For starters, the ad's narrator says that President Barack Obama "took GM and Chrysler into bankruptcy." That's true. But that was also the plan that Romney prescribed at the end of 2008 and the beginning of 2009. The difference is that Obama supported a bridge loan from the government to help the auto companies go through bankruptcy, while Romney wanted the private sector to pick up the tab. But as basically every principal involved in rescuing the auto industry said at the time, there was no money available from the private sector during the height of the recession. When Dan Akerson, CEO and chairman of General Motors since September 2010, was asked what would have happened had Romney's plan been followed, he responded that GM "would have been in bankruptcy for years and I think you could have written off this company, this industry and this country." The Romney ad also cites his endorsement from the Detroit News without noting that that same endorsement accused him of "wrong-headedness on the auto bailout." Finally, the ad accuses Obama of selling "Chrysler to Italians who are going to build Jeeps in China." Again, this is technically true, but only according to a narrow reading of the language. Fiat, the Italian company that now owns Chrysler, is building Jeeps in China. But the company is not moving jobs from America to do it. Instead, Fiat is expanding current production in China for the purposes of catering to a growing Chinese market. Where the ad goes from misleading to something more nefarious is in the text it shows. At one point, it displays a line from a Bloomberg story stating that Chrysler "plans to return Jeep output to China," the implication being that the company is moving operations there as opposed to expanding operations that are already there. Romney has cited this report on several occasions while campaigning and has been summarily criticized for doing so. Chrysler has denied the report, and multiple news outlets have called out the Romney campaign for using it in on the stump. So what rationale is there for using it in an advertisement? The Huffington Post reached out to the Romney campaign on Sunday morning to get its side of the story. The campaign sent back a sheet of data points, including press reports showing that Obama did force Chrysler and GM into federal bankruptcy. No one, of course, is disputing that. In response to the claim about Chrysler building Jeeps in China, the Romney email again cites the Bloomberg article. A Romney campaign official would not add anything more on the record, save to repeat, on condition of anonymity, the same exact text from the Bloomberg report. The campaign's defense, in the end, rests on the fact that the ad never technically says that Chrysler is moving production to China -- just that it is going to build Jeeps there. “Mitt Romney’s new ad is a sure sign that he knows he’s in trouble in Ohio," Obama campaign spokesperson Lis Smith said in a statement. "When the American auto industry and a million workers’ jobs were on the line, Mitt Romney turned his back. Now he’s pretending it never happened and is trying to scare Ohioans by repeating a blatant falsehood that Chrysler is moving its Jeep operations to China. Even the Detroit News, which this ad cites, condemned his plan that would have let Chrysler and GM go under and praised the President for his ‘extraordinary’ rescue of the industry. Mitt Romney might be willing to do anything to close the deal, but Ohioans know where he stood when it mattered most and won’t be fooled by his dishonest ads in the final days of this campaign."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351513677564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:27:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351513984719-11</Id><Title>some thoughts of 77 yr old white male from the south</Title><Msg>Some thoughts of 77 yr old white male from the south I am a Caucasian male, 77 years old. I’m NOT one of the 1%ers. I’m retired, living on a small pension and social security. My wife also has a pension from her job as well as social security. We do pay federal, state, sales, property tax, etc.; however, we seem to have been included in the 47%ers Romney doesn’t care about. How can that be? The GOP seems be going after the white male voters because it hates blacks, and Romney thinks all white male voters should also hate them. I was raised in a small Virginia town, and my parents, as I realized years later, were bigots of the worse kind. When I was growing up, race and segregation were just not discussed. I just kind of knew that the blacks lived in a certain part of town, the whites in another, with only a few exceptions. (eg. A few black families lived in converted chicken coops in alleys behind white folks houses.) I played with a couple of the children from these ‘coops’. I never thought anything about it, until one day a child’s mother came out and asked me if my parents knew I was playing with her son. I said I had never had occasion to mention it, and she responded “please don’t tell them, because my son likes playing games with you”. As I got older and into high school, I did occasionally hear some of my classmates saying don’t ever go into the black section nor ever talk to one of the girls there, else we might get beaten up. I went into the army after high school. In basic training, there were only two blacks in our company, one of them next to me in the same barrack. The first weekend we were given weekend passes, he asked around wanting to borrow $20. He wanted to go home and just wanted to make sure he had enough money to get back. I loaned him the money, and a LOT of the other guys jumped all over me saying ‘you’ll never see that $20 again, and never see the black dude again either’. Well, of course he came back on Sunday evening, and the first thing he did was to return the same $20 bill I had loaned him. Needless to say, no one ever said a word to me about that! The point I’m making is that I never had any reason to dislike any one based on color. I judge people for who they are, how they act, their honesty, dependability, etc…! So when Obama ran for president 4 years ago, I never ever gave his color a thought, and I still don’t. WHY ARE IS GOP SO AGAINST THE BLACKS, LATINOS, ASIANS, INDIANS, etc. Why is the GOP also against gays/lesbians? Why do so many republicans actually believe all the lies Romney/Ryan tell. How do the republicans even KNOW what R/R’s policies are, since they seem to change not only from month to month, not only from day to day, but many times they change on the same day! How was Obama was able to hire many women for his staff , and he didn’t even HAVE a “binder of women”. Why doesn’t saving the auto industry seem to count? How can the number of unemployed go down, but they are not giving any credit to Obama? Why is the economy going up, but Obama isn’t getting any credit? How can Romney personally send many many jobs to China? And that makes him a good person to run our country? How come he puts a very large chunk of his money in tax haven countries (Cayman Islands, Bermuda, Switzerland), but this makes Romney a “patriotic” candidate? How come a man has gone through his religion’s rigorous ceremony where he vows his faith first to his religion, then his family, but the vow is to also make this a Mormon country, NOT a democracy?".</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351513984719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351515646773-12</Id><Title>magic underwear, secect temple vows, polygamy,religious bigotry</Title><Msg>cayman island bank accounts and lie after lie after lie Rick Perry, attacked Romney by telling reporters the Mormon Church is “a cult” and “Mormonism is not Christianity.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351515646773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351515802976-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama can't stop disaster</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351436274315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New Projection: Romney 52, Obama 47 5:00 AM, Oct 29, 2012 • By FRED BARNES Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts The bipartisan Battleground Poll, in its “vote election model,” is projecting that Mitt Romney will defeat President Obama 52 percent to 47 percent. The poll also found that Romney has an even greater advantage among middle class voters, 52 percent to 45 percent. Obama and Romney While Obama can close the gap with a strong voter turnout effort, “reports from the field would indicate that not to be the case, and Mitt Romney may well be heading to a decisive victory,” says pollster Ed Goeas. Should Romney win by 5 percentage points, it would increase Republican chances of gaining control of the Senate. His coattails would help elect GOP Senate candidates in Virginia, Wisconsin, Ohio, Pennsylvania, and Florida. “Republicans are now certain to hold the House,” Goeas said, “regardless of how the presidential race turns out.” The poll’s election model takes into account variables including voter intensity, age, and education, and voters who are certain in their vote. The race “remains very close in the surface,” Goeas said, “but the political environment and the composition of the likely electorate favor Governor Romney.” The projected outcome by the Battleground Poll is close to that of the Gallup Poll. Last week, Gallup said Romney leads Obama 49 percent to 46 percent in its model of the electorate’s composition on November 6. The Battleground Poll is conducted by Goeas of the Tarrance Group and Celinda Lake of Lake Research Partners. Goeas is a Republican, Lake a Democrat. The survey is affiliated with Politico and George Washington University.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351515802976</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351515943543-14</Id><Topic><Title>some thoughts of 77 yr old white male from the south</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351513984719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:33:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is injustice every place you look, right Mesa. It's your reason to get out of bed in the morning, right Mesa? It's your central reason for living, right Mesa.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351515943543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351516654643-15</Id><Topic><Title>some thoughts of 77 yr old white male from the south</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351513984719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:33:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is your "central reason for living"?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351516654643</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351517133181-16</Id><Title>GOP economic con men and snake oil peddlers</Title><Msg>(good article) Romney's Other Credibility Problem: Glenn Hubbard Mitt Romney has a credibility problem. He changes his beliefs like laundry (abortion, medical insurance, whether Bin Laden was worth killing, attacking Iran), refuses to disclose his tax returns, and won't explain how he could possibly pay for the tax cuts he proposes. But there is another scandal in Romney's campaign -- namely Glenn Hubbard, Romney's chief economic advisor, who was chairman of the Council of Economic Advisors under George W. Bush, and is now Dean of Columbia Business School. I interviewed Hubbard for my documentary film Inside Job, and analyzed his record again for my book Predator Nation. The film interview became famous because Hubbard blew his cool after I interrogated him about his conflicts of interest: "This isn't a deposition, sir. I was polite enough to give you time, foolishly I now see, but you have three more minutes. Give it your best shot." But the really important thing about Hubbard isn't his personality; it's that as an economist and an advisor, he is a total, unmitigated disaster. First, Hubbard has an abysmal track record in economic policy, including the very issues that Romney has made the pillar of his Presidential campaign. Second, like Romney, Hubbard refuses to disclose critical information about his income, conflicts of interest, and paid advocacy activities. Third, both in public statements and in my personal experience, Hubbard has been evasive, misleading, and even dishonest when discussing both policy issues and his own conflicts of interest. And last but not least, those conflicts of interest are huge: Hubbard has long advocated policies that Wall Street loves, often without disclosing that he is, in fact, highly paid by Wall Street. Let's start with tax cuts, since Romney claims that he can cut tax rates sharply without increasing the deficit, and without benefiting the rich. Mr. Romney claims that tax cuts will be fully paid for by closing loopholes and deductions, and will not add to the deficit; Hubbard has publicly supported Romney's claims. Interestingly, Mr. Hubbard has quite a record on this very issue. Shortly after becoming chairman of the Council of Economic Advisors in 2001, he spearheaded the Bush administration's tax cuts, and he said lots about them. How did that work out? First, we now know that over half of the benefits of the Bush-Hubbard tax cuts went to the top 1% of the population. In part to benefit the wealthy, the tax cuts were also structured to reward investment in financial assets, rather than either consumer spending or real capital investment. As a result, the tax cuts caused huge budget deficits, yet did little to stimulate growth or job creation: There were basically no new jobs created during the Bush administration, despite adding trillions to the national debt. That is not, however, what Hubbard said would happen. On August 22, 2001, he published an article in the Wall Street Journal entitled "Tax Cuts Won't Hurt the Surplus." Oops. In the article, Hubbard also predicts that his tax cuts would preserve the Clinton budget surpluses by causing GNP to grow 0.3% per year faster. Hubbard also co-authored an article with William Dudley, then the chief economist of Goldman Sachs, entitled "How Capital Markets Enhance Economic Performance and Job Creation." It was published by the Goldman Sachs Global Markets Institute in 2004, just as the housing bubble was getting seriously crazy. In my filmed interview, here's how Hubbard described the article: INTERVIEWER: In 2004 you co-wrote a paper with William Dudley, who was then the chief economist of Goldman Sachs. What do you think about the arguments you made in that paper? GLENN HUBBARD: As I recall that paper, the arguments were basically to the effect that healthy capital markets are important for the economy, views that I held before and certainly hold after. Well, here's what that paper really said. Hubbard wrote that "The ascendancy of the U.S. capital markets" had yielded "enhanced stability of the U.S. banking system... more jobs and higher wages... less frequent and milder [recessions}... a revolution in housing finance." Later in the article: "The capital markets have helped make the housing market less volatile... " Next, "Credit crunches... are a thing of the past... " and my personal favorite, "The revolution in housing finance has also... been important in making the economy less cyclical." In other parts of the article, Hubbard and Dudley specifically praise credit default swaps for their role in reducing and spreading risk. Like wow, man. Hubbard refused to tell me whether he was paid to write that article; no payment is disclosed in the document itself, nor on Hubbard's CV. Which brings us to Mr. Hubbard's many, many disclosure problems and conflicts of interest. After the release of my film Inside Job, Columbia University was forced to establish disclosure requirements for the first time for its professors. At the time, Hubbard stated that he welcomed them. Well, it wasn't quite that way in our interview. Here are some selections, verbatim and unedited: INTERVIEWER: Let me go back to your own personal business involvements. I'm looking at your résumé now, and I guess it looks to me as if the majority of your outside activities are consulting and directorship arrangements with the financial services industry. Would you not agree with that characterization? GLENN HUBBARD: Not to my knowledge. I don't think my consulting clients are even on my C.V. INTERVIEWER: Who are your consulting clients? GLENN HUBBARD: I don't believe I have to discuss that with you. You have a few more minutes and the interview's over. Slightly later: INTERVIEWER: Okay. Who are you a director of? GLENN HUBBARD: I don't believe I have to answer that question. Well, actually, now that Columbia had adopted disclosure regulations, we now know at least something about Hubbard's income sources, and the overwhelming majority of them are in the financial sector. The HTML version his CV (which you can read here) does not fully disclose his activities, but if you click on the PDF version, you see more. And what you see is that at least two thirds of his literally dozens of consulting, advisory, speaking, and directorship arrangements over the last decade are with the financial sector -- MetLife, KKR, Goldman Sachs, Freddie Mac, JPMorgan Chase, Citigroup, Bank of America, the list goes on and on. Until Columbia adopted its disclosure policy, Hubbard had never disclosed most of those relationships, either in his publications or when making public statements about policy issues affecting Wall Street. Even Columbia's new policy, moreover, does not require Hubbard to disclose how much they pay him; all we know currently comes from required SEC disclosures of his director's fees from the boards of three financial sector companies, which pay him over $700,000 per year. His total financial sector income, including consulting and speaking, is undoubtedly much higher. Yet here's how he described his income in our interview, once again verbatim and unedited: INTERVIEWER: Forgive me, but I'm going to be direct: How does your personal income compare, your private income as opposed to your university salary? GLENN HUBBARD: Vastly times more, because I write textbooks, so that's much more remunerative than being a professor. INTERVIEWER: How about your consulting income from the financial services industry, and your directorships? GLENN HUBBARD: I don't do much consulting in the financial services industry. I do have some directorships, but the income from those would be modest compared to my other income. Textbooks. You read that correctly. As for not doing "much" consulting for the financial sector, I counted consulting or directorships with 29 financial sector firms on your CV. And your more than $700K per year directorship income is "modest" compared to the other stuff? Really, now, Glenn. But we're not done yet. There is a lot more that Hubbard still hasn't disclosed, and refused to disclose to us when we were making Inside Job. On his CV, Hubbard lists The Analysis Group as a consulting client. That is misleading at best. The Analysis Group is one of a half dozen major firms that specializes in matching private companies and lobbying groups, who are the real clients, with professors who they pay to support their positions in regulatory, policy, Congressional, and legal disputes. It was The Analysis Group, for example, that arranged for Hubbard to testify on behalf of two Bear Stearns hedge fund managers who were prosecuted for securities fraud in 2009. Hubbard was paid $100,000 for his testimony. Hubbard has been affiliated with the Analysis Group for many years, but when we asked him, he refused to disclose who he had worked for or what he had done. He also refused to provide us with a copy of the Federal financial disclosure form he was required to submit in 2001; we couldn't obtain it from the White House, because they had already destroyed it (yes, that IS interesting, isn't it). Nor has Hubbard provided his total consulting income, his tax returns, or a comprehensive list of his income sources and clients for the period since he left the White House in 2003. So the next time you hear Mitt Romney refuse to release his tax returns, and then tell you that he can cut taxes and balance the budget while creating lots of jobs, well... I would ask you to remember that standing behind every great con artist is someone like... Glenn Hubbard.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351517133181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351517266200-17</Id><Topic><Title>Given What We Now Know Of The Benghazi Debacle...</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1351455895913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:24:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yo, Idiot, I`ve been saying iit from the beginging! Obama is a Murderer! If you had a brain you would understand that Obama armed Al Quadea to Murder Gadaffi. Lubya is now in total Chaos! Obama did it for poll numbers and he is hiding it for his re-election. Nothing can stop him now, because You brain dead Republicans are IMBECILES BEYOND ANY DOUBT .... ALL OF YOU!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351517266200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351517428765-18</Id><Topic><Title>$$$ This group of stock braniacs nailed ORCL in advance of everyone. $$$</Title><Username>david_vanhoy</Username><Timestamp>1351514793367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:46:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey guys. Thanks for this one. Almost missed it.</Msg><Username>joe.glass43</Username><Timestamp>1351517428765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351517509742-19</Id><Topic><Title>GOP economic con men and snake oil peddlers</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351517133181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glenn Hubbard, Romney's chief economic advisor, sweaty Mitt's top economic advisor was a big pumper and liar about W's tax cuts just like he is now for sweaty mitt...... look at what he said then: "That is not, however, what Hubbard said would happen. On August 22, 2001, he published an article in the Wall Street Journal entitled "Tax Cuts Won't Hurt the Surplus." Oops. In the article, Hubbard also predicts that his tax cuts would preserve the Clinton budget surpluses by causing GNP to grow 0.3% per year faster." and ntm: "Hubbard has long advocated policies that Wall Street loves, often without disclosing that he is, in fact, highly paid by Wall Street."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351517509742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351517788065-20</Id><Topic><Title>some thoughts of 77 yr old white male from the south</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351513984719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:33:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for my wife, my kids, myself. I enjoy life. I doubt that you do. I don't waste my time worrying about "binders" and free birth control, or gays. You spend your every waking moment gnashing over some perceived injustice. I don't. I take life as it is and I do not get twisted up in some notion of fairness.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351517788065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351517905544-21</Id><Title>"tax cuts won't hurt the surplus" Mitt's chief economic advisor said than in 2001</Title><Msg>sweaty Mitt's top economic advisor also pumped gop horse manure for W......now he pumps it for Mitt.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351517905544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:38:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351517939097-22</Id><Topic><Title>$$$ This group of stock braniacs nailed ORCL in advance of everyone. $$$</Title><Username>david_vanhoy</Username><Timestamp>1351514793367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:46:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>woop i'm in. This is free?</Msg><Username>thomasdees35</Username><Timestamp>1351517939097</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351518288832-23</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report ORCL</Title><Username>paul_truby</Username><Timestamp>1351187234961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. Subscribed just now.</Msg><Username>thomasdees35</Username><Timestamp>1351518288832</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351518480815-24</Id><Topic><Title>some thoughts of 77 yr old white male from the south</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351513984719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:33:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you were the liar who posted that the "libs" in DC had outlawed killing rodents. the kind of stuff you worry about. lol</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351518480815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351519341444-25</Id><Topic><Title>some thoughts of 77 yr old white male from the south</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351513984719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:33:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why not stay on topic? You're all about fairness and equality, right? Do you worry about some person you don't know, never met, and never will meet as you are about your own family, if you have one? I worry about the well being of my family not yours. It's much better that way. If everyone did that we'd be so much better off. Sadly, there are plenty who do not even care about their own children. Yet, people who think as you do hold me more responsible fort their well being more than their own parents. Bizarre thinking.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351519341444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:02:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351519697861-26</Id><Topic><Title>voting for Obama likened to losing virginity</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351293431879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 19:17:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey stupid, reagan was the first to use that joke......per you .."What do you think of it? Intelligent? Effective? What say you? Desperation I think."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351519697861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:08:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351519824026-27</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan was the first to compare voting to virginity, you idiot whiners</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351365743170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan was the first to compare voting to virginity, you idiot whiners, so i am rubbing your nose in your own horse manure hypocrisy</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351519824026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351519937898-28</Id><Topic><Title>voting for Obama likened to losing virginity</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351293431879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 19:17:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? reagan was the first? I'm not aware that he even heard of Barck Obama. You idiot!</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351519937898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351520078438-29</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update for ORCL. Read Now!</Title><Username>luisanderson380</Username><Timestamp>1350042834701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dont concern my dude, simply make certain to look at the up coming article as soon as possible.</Msg><Username>thomasdees35</Username><Timestamp>1351520078438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351520139140-30</Id><Title>Romney 52 Obama 47</Title><Msg>The bipartisan Battleground Poll, in its “vote election model,” is projecting that Mitt Romney will defeat President Obama 52 percent to 47 percent. The poll also found that Romney has an even greater advantage among middle class voters, 52 percent to 45 percent. The gap widens. Romney pulling away.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351520139140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351520216899-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has lowered taxes for the middleclass</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351460651295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 17:44:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop lower taxes for the rich and wants to kill social secuity and medicare so the rich can get more tax cuts........ they lied about W's tax cuts and they are lying about Mitt's tax cuts, just like they lied about wmd, selfinancing Iraq occupation and so forth..... Mitts chief economic advisor said this stupid lie in 2001: "tax cuts won't hurt the surplus" ............oops, he missed that by $5 trillion plus the worst recession since the great depression...... which it would have turned into had mccain won.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351520216899</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351520495001-32</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL info</Title><Username>katherynglip25723</Username><Timestamp>1351518023241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just subscribed. I am hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>darylmdd9686</Username><Timestamp>1351520495001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351520511223-33</Id><Title>electoral votes: Obama 265 Romney 206</Title><Msg>The TPM Electoral Scoreboard , the most accurate and up-to-date poll tracking and averaging service on the web. Obama 265 Romney 206 electoral votes 270 to win</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351520511223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351520737954-34</Id><Topic><Title>Given What We Now Know Of The Benghazi Debacle...</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1351455895913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:24:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Father of Slain Benghazi SEAL to Obama: “It’s Better to Die a Hero Than Live a Coward” (Video) Posted by Jim Hoft on Monday, October 29, 2012, 7:43 AM The father of former Navy SEAL Tyrone Woods sent this message to Barack Obama last night on Geraldo at Large: “It’s better to die a hero than live a coward.” Well said. Yesterday, former National Security Adviser Bud McFarlane added this on Obama’s non-response to the Benghazi 9-11 terrorist attack: “To have known what he had available, to have known that Americans were under fire, and to have done nothing, is dereliction of duty that I have never seen in a Commander in Chief from a president of any party. Outrageous.”</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351520737954</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351520813535-35</Id><Topic><Title>voting for Obama likened to losing virginity</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351293431879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 19:17:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are just plain stupid, stupid. Reagan , compared voting for him for the first time like getting screwed for the first time....lol..... so you got you panties in a hypocrite wad for something Ronnie Raygun did too...... in fact Ronne said it himself......ha ha ha "This isn’t the first time that analogy has been used; in fact, Ronald Reagan made a similar comparison in 1980 while he was reaching out to blue-collar voters. Here’s what Reagan said: “I know what it’s like to pull the Republican lever for the first time, because I used to be a Democrat myself, and I can tell you it only hurts for a minute and then it feels just great.” Now compare that to what Dunham said: “Your first time shouldn’t be with just anybody. You want to do it with a great guy … someone who really cares about and understands women.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351520813535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351520864164-36</Id><Topic><Title>electoral votes: Obama 265 Romney 206</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351520511223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:21:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>electoral votes: Obama 265 Romney 206...........poor , poor sweaty mitts</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351520864164</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351520919237-37</Id><Topic><Title>$$$ This group of stock braniacs nailed ORCL in advance of everyone. $$$</Title><Username>david_vanhoy</Username><Timestamp>1351514793367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:46:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can't believe these guys aren't charging for their picks yet. </Msg><Username>donald.edwards11</Username><Timestamp>1351520919237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351520971970-38</Id><Topic><Title>"tax cuts won't hurt the surplus" Mitt's chief economic advisor said than in 2001</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351517905544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:38:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W's "tax cuts won't hurt the surplus" Mitt's chief economic advisor W's "tax cuts won't hurt the surplus" Mitt's chief economic advisor</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351520971970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351521375193-39</Id><Topic><Title>gop &amp; sweaty mitts build the JEEP lie</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351513677564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 08:27:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sweaty Mitt's spouts off lies all time.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351521375193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351522675329-40</Id><Topic><Title>electoral votes: Obama 265 Romney 206</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351520511223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:21:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Election 2012: Ohio President Ohio: Romney 50%, Obama 48% Daily Presidential Tracking Poll 2012 Electoral College Scoreboard 2012 Senate Balance of Power Virginia: Romney 50%, Obama 48% Florida: Romney 50%, Obama 48% Wisconsin: Obama 49%, Romney 49% Sign up for free daily updates Monday, October 29, 2012 The race for Ohio’s Electoral College votes remains very close, but now Mitt Romney now has a two-point advantage. The latest Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of Likely Ohio Voters shows Romney with 50% support to President Obama’s 48%. One percent (1%) likes some other candidate, while another one percent (1%) remains undecided. (To see survey question wording, click here.) Ohio remains a Toss-Up in the Rasmussen Reports Electoral College Projections.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351522675329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 10:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351523985895-41</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL info</Title><Username>katherynglip25723</Username><Timestamp>1351518023241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>giannaayc857</Username><Timestamp>1351523985895</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 11:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351524380586-42</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL info</Title><Username>katherynglip25723</Username><Timestamp>1351518023241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 09:40:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>giannaayc857</Username><Timestamp>1351524380586</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 11:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351529082357-43</Id><Title>Ohio according to Rasmussen</Title><Msg>The latest Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of Likely Ohio Voters shows Romney with 50% support to President Obama’s 48%. One percent (1%) likes some other candidate, while another one percent (1%) remains undecided ............................................................ Not bad. Not bad at all. As predicted by the folks who know this stuff, the undecideds have broken to Romney.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351529082357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 12:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351529527710-44</Id><Title>Barack Obama "The Weatherman"! Finally A Job He Can Handle!</Title><Msg>In a couple of weeks he can begin his interviews!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1351529527710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 12:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351529690736-45</Id><Title>hey gop, you constanly said medicare and social security were bankrupt</Title><Msg>but if sweaty mitts is elected they are good to go AS IS, no changes for most of the boomers.....and everyone gets cash back in more tax cuts???? when was the miracle? were you lying when you said the demographic bulge of the boomers would finish off the already bk medicare and social security? NOW, sweaty Mitts promises on his web site that: medicare •Nothing changes for current seniors or those nearing retirement social security no change in benefits for those at or near retirement, plus tax cuts, increases military spending and more nation building....... you republicans aren't lying again like you did about wmd and iraq and like mitts chief economic advisor did back then about W's tax cuts "tax cuts won't hurt the surplus".. or that "reagan proved deficits don't matter......... or are you?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351529690736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 12:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351530615720-46</Id><Title>Obama job approval</Title><Msg>down 7% in 3 days. Any guesses as to why? My guess is Libya. That whole episode make zero sense. He could have been the hero. A no-brainer for most. But he acted contrary to common sense. I can't help but think there is much more to this story that we don't know. I mean, the facts that have come out and have helped sink Obama may be the tip of the iceberg. We'll find out after the election. But that doesn't matter. Enough damage has been done.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351530615720</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351530752131-47</Id><Title>Obama up in Ohio &amp; already has a HUGE lead in actual votes</Title><Msg>Obama up in Ohio Time: Obama 49-44% &amp; Among respondents who say they have already voted, Obama holds a two-to-one lead over Romney, 60% to 30%.” And the gender gap in Ohio is real: Obama’s up 56-37% with women Also helping Obama: He gets 43% of the white vote. That’s the SAME percentage he got in Ohio in 2008.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351530752131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351530837499-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama up in Ohio &amp; already has a HUGE lead in actual votes</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351530752131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go obama!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351530837499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351531233819-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama up in Ohio &amp; already has a HUGE lead in actual votes</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351530752131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, in the end your head will explode. Dems have blown its wad early. O won't win. Not in Ohio, not in the country.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351531233819</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351531964076-50</Id><Topic><Title>Who Will Pay for Hardwareguru's Food Stamps when the Taxpayors are Gone</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351457426879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 16:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama never counted my soaring health insurance rates as part of the cost of his "affordable" care act (sic). When the CBO determined that it would take 10 years of higher taxes to pay for 6 years of Obamacare, they didn't COUNT my jump in premiums in the calculations! Alcoa Aluminum company has already charged over a $billion to the added cost of coverage for their employees due to Obamacare... ... NONE of that cost was included in the cost calculations in 2009... NONE OF THEM!</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351531964076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351531988587-51</Id><Title>gop: medicare and SS BK ponzis today but tomorrow they are good to go, as is, stronger than ever!</Title><Msg>gop preached that medicare and SS are bankrupt. but Mitt and the gop say now that these programs will stay JUST the SAME for most boomers who will be using them out into the 2040s and beyond................................. so, these programs are "strenghened" by more tax cuts?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351531988587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351532336311-52</Id><Title>seabugc and blwjbspokanimal refuse to say how medicare goes from BK to good to go, strengthened by sweaty mitts</Title><Msg>gop always said these programs are bankrupt ponzis..... now the gop says these programs are GOOD to go AS IS..... for most of the boomers who will be on them out to the 2040s and beyond..... not bad for bankrupt ponzis....... huh, seabugc? Mittens will strenthen them with tax cuts, huh? easy fix, no cost , cash back.... you pubs must have been lying before about the dire condition of these programs..... heck they were fixed and the fix is better than free, you get cash back....</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351532336311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351532582956-53</Id><Topic><Title>seabugc and blwjbspokanimal refuse to say how medicare goes from BK to good to go, strengthened by sweaty mitts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351532336311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:38:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you, Mesa, haven't posed a word about Benghazi. Which of our points trump which? Mesa, you lose.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351532582956</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351534872442-54</Id><Topic><Title>seabugc and blwjbspokanimal refuse to say how medicare goes from BK to good to go, strengthened by sweaty mitts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351532336311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:38:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you first, and do stick to the topic and not change the subject as per your demand on a previous post. and btw, as you know Romney agreed with everything that Obama has done on foreign policy and wouldn't have done anything different. As i said, the gop are such liars that one day medicare and SS security are "bankrupt ponzis" and the very next, they are good to go, as is , for most of the boomers who will be on them out the to 2040s. and it is such an easy problem to solve that it costs nothing , better, everyone gets cash bank of more tax cuts. It is obvious why you run away from your guys miracle fix, because it is complete horse manure....</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351534872442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351535464163-55</Id><Topic><Title>seabugc and blwjbspokanimal refuse to say how medicare goes from BK to good to go, strengthened by sweaty mitts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351532336311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:38:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Mesa, you still lose. The SS and medicare numbers are so arcane that people can't keep up, me included. On the other hand, Libya is front and center . It's been drip drip drip since 9/11. In 6 weeks the story has not gone away and indeed has grown more intense. The dramatic story is there for people to see. Which trumps which? You lose! Obama has lost big too! Mesa, he could have been a hero. He chose instead a twisted tale. Why? Take a stab at that question, Mesa.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351535464163</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:31:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351536277944-56</Id><Topic><Title>seabugc and blwjbspokanimal refuse to say how medicare goes from BK to good to go, strengthened by sweaty mitts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351532336311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:38:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what? are you saying Mitt is lying that medicare and social security will stay the same for everyone 55 and above? that is what he says...... others say the medicare will be broke in 2016 if Mitt and the gop repeal the ACA. i guess you are more worred about affairs in libya than in the most important issues at home. but that does not let you escape the responsiblity for understanding the PROMISES that YOUR candidate makes......... as i said Mittens PROMISES that medicare and SS will be the SAME for all 55 and above, who will be on these programs out to the 2040s..... and YOU apparantly believe that the fix is so easy it costs nothing, less than nothing you get cash back..... i think that is absurd and a typical gop, the very same way they sold W's tax cuts with a lot of lies.......... and you are such a schmuck that you won't even bother to defend your own candidate, it's all beyond you, just too much , too 'arcane" well, Mitt's and the gop talk is not 'arcane'..... recently they said medicare was bankrupt.... now Mitt's says it can go on as is , no change for most of the boomers, that's his promise.....so either you all were wrong about the dire and bk condition of medicare, or you have way to finance it. and what are the details of how Mitt's finances Medicare as is for the boomers? with tax cuts???????</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351536277944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351536791394-57</Id><Topic><Title>Obama up in Ohio &amp; already has a HUGE lead in actual votes</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351530752131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Politics of insult' alive and well despite Obama's 2008 lament Published October 29, 2012 Four years ago, then-candidate Barack Obama decried what he described as "the politics of insult." "You don't deserve a bunch of name-calling," he told a Virginia crowd in the summer of 2008. "You don't deserve a bunch of mudslinging." But lately, there have been more than a few insults flying on the 2012 campaign trail. Whether it's with cute turns of phrase like "Romnesia" or more serious invective, the president's campaign has gotten increasingly aggressive over the last few weeks in its denunciation of Mitt Romney. The tone likely reflects the polls, which have been tightening ever since the Republican nominee's opening debate performance. Whatever the reason, it's evident that the "politics of insult" have not faded. The following were overheard on the 2012 campaign trail: "Bullsh--ter" The president took a rip at Romney after a recent interview with Rolling Stone. In the article, published over the weekend, writer and historian Douglas Brinkley said that editor Eric Bates told the president that when he asked his six-year-old daughter if she wanted to say anything to Obama, she said: "Tell him: You can do it." According to the piece, Obama then said: "Kids have good instincts. ... They look at the other guy and say, 'Well, that's a bullsh--ter, I can tell.'" Obama later explained in an interview with a Denver reporter that the comment came during a "casual conversation" after the formal interview ended. The president appeared to defend the sentiment, though, saying people know that he means what he says. "The basic point I've been talking about in this campaign -- people know what I mean," he said. "Romnesia" First came "Big Bird," then "binders full of women." But another favorite quip of late on the Obama campaign trail has been "Romnesia." It's the campaign-invented term for the condition that makes the Republican nominee allegedly forget or ignore his past positions. And the delivery of that punch-line has become increasingly involved. "In the closing moments of the election, Governor Romney is hoping you, too, will come down with a severe case of Romnesia," Obama told a Cleveland crowd last Thursday. "So I'm here to tell you, Cleveland, if you start feeling a temperature, if you're eyes are getting a little blurry and your hearing is getting a little muffled, if you're feeling a little weak, you need to know that whatever the symptoms are, don't worry, Obamacare covers preexisting conditions. We can fix you up." "Romney Hood" At an Aug. 6 campaign stop, the president added a new zinger to his repertoire. He said Romney's tax policies were like "Robin Hood in reverse." He had a name for it - "Romney Hood." Romney, though, returned the insult. In an interview with Fox News, Romney said that if he were to coin a term "it would be 'Obamaloney.'" A felon? In a July conference call responding to a Boston Globe piece that questioned when Romney actually left his old private equity company, Obama Deputy Campaign Manager Stephanie Cutter raised some serious claims against the GOP nominee. She said he was either "misrepresenting" his position at Bain Capital in filings to the Securities and Exchange Commission, "which is a felony," or he was misrepresenting his position to the American people. While the Romney called the comment over the line -- with Republicans saying Cutter had effectively called the Republican nominee a potential felon -- Cutter said that wasn't what she was going for. Her advice for Republicans was to quit "whining." Tied to a woman's death? An August ad from Priorities USA, the biggest Obama-supporting super PAC, made waves when it featured a former GST Steel employee talking about how his wife died of cancer after he lost his job and benefits -- when Bain Capitol closed down the factory. "I do not think Mitt Romney realizes what he's done to anyone, and furthermore, I do not think Mitt Romney is concerned," Joe Soptic said in the ad. The suggestion that the Republican nominee was tied to Soptic's wife's death drew outrage from Republicans. But Priorities USA co-founder Bill Burton defended the ad, and said it wasn't trying to blame Romney for her death. "Vampire" Another, prior, ad about the demise of GST Steel featured Joe Soptic again, and other ex-employees, bashing Romney and Bain Capital for making money off their plant and then allegedly leaving it behind. They compared Bain -- and by extension, Romney -- to a mythical monster. "It was like a vampire, it came in and sucked the life out of us," former steelworker Jack Cobb said in the video. "Liar" Charges of being dishonest were hardly uncommon this year, during the Republican primary and later in the presidential race. After the first presidential debate, Philadelphia Mayor Michael Nutter said on CNN that Romney put out "lie after lie after lie" to look good. The Democratic National Committee's Brad Woodhouse was quoted in The Wall Street Journal saying people "have pointed out what a liar Mitt Romney is." Obama adviser David Axelrod, in a conference call after the first debate, used the more Dickensian term, "artful dodger," to describe the challenging candidate. While Romney's campaign complains that Obama has made the race about small things, the Obama campaign for its part has similar gripes against team Romney. Over the weekend, after the Romney campaign mocked Vice President Biden for mistakenly referring to former Virginia Gov. Tim Kaine as "Tom Kaine," Obama spokeswoman Lis Smith retorted, "Once again, Mitt Romney's campaign is showing their focus on the big things -- like one letter in Tim Kaine's name."</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351536791394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351537051094-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obama up in Ohio &amp; already has a HUGE lead in actual votes</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351530752131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen: Romney Takes Lead in Ohio, 50-48 Monday, 29 Oct 2012 12:37 PM Share: More . . . Electoral College votes remains very close, but now Mitt Romney now has a two-point advantage. The latest Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of likely Ohio voters shows Romney with 50 percent support to President Obama’s 48 percent. One percent likes some other candidate, while another one percent remains undecided. Ohio remains a toss-up in the Rasmussen Reports Electoral College Projections. Based on the current projections, Romney would have to win Wisconsin if he loses Ohio in order to move into the White House. The candidates have been locked in a very tight battle in Ohio since August. A week ago, Romney and Obama were tied in the Buckeye State with 48 percent support each. This is the first time Romney has taken even a modest lead in the race. Nearly one-in-three Ohio voters (32 percent) have already cast their ballots. Obama leads 62 percent to 36 percent among these voters. Romney has a large lead among those who still plan to vote. The question of who wins Ohio may come down to whether enough Romney voters get to the polls on Election Day to overcome the president’s lead among early voters. Among all Ohio voters, Romney now has a 12-point lead over the president in voter trust – 53 percent to 41 percent - when it comes to the economy. Last week, he had just a seven-point advantage among voters in the state when they were asked which candidate they trusted more to deal with the economy. Romney’s also trusted more by eight points in the areas of job creation and energy policy but leads Obama by just two when it comes to housing issues. National security has been an area where the president has typically had an advantage over Romney this year. But, the Republican challenger now has a 52 percent to 42 percent advantage on the issue. Obama carried Ohio by a 51 percent to 47 percent margin in 2008, but just 46 percent of the state’s voters now approve of the job he is doing. Fifty-one percent (51 percent) disapprove. This includes Strong Approval from 29 percent and Strong Disapproval from 44 percent, giving the president a slightly worse job approval rating in Ohio than he earns nationally. Forty-seven percent have a favorable opinion of the president and 52 percent have an unfavorable view. Those figures include 32 percent with a Very Favorable opinion and 42 percent who have a Very Unfavorable view of him. Romney is viewed favorably by 53 percent and unfavorably by 45 percent, including 40 percent with a very favorable opinion of the former Massachusetts governor and 32 percent with a very unfavorable one. Romney leads by 14 points among male voters in Ohio but trails by eight among female voters. Voters not affiliated with either of the major parties prefer the president 50 percent to 46 percent. Fifteen percent of all voters in the state now rate the U.S. economy as good or excellent, while 49 percent view it as poor. But 41 percent consider their own finances good or excellent, compared to 17 percent who regard their finances as poor.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1351537051094</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351538569293-59</Id><Title>October jobs report may be delayed until after election...</Title><Msg>Due to Hurricane Sandy. How convenient is that for Mr. Obama?</Msg><Username>turbotaxkid</Username><Timestamp>1351538569293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351541707956-60</Id><Title>Romney-Ryan: Send FEMA "Back to the Private Sector"</Title><Msg>tornado, hurricane... don't expect the USA to help you, call wal mart or goldman sachs or bain.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351541707956</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351542288646-61</Id><Title>"Big Breakdown" My Azzs! Nothing But Big Lies!</Title><Msg>for six weeks... day after day after day!! Go to Hell Obama! Four Americans dead because YOU did Jackshyt!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1351542288646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351544484172-62</Id><Topic><Title>Minnesota</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351542948432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Minnesota is a statistical tie. It's been counted as solid blue for decades. Obama running like the underdog. He has the real numbers. The end is near. Obama is in full cover-up mode so the true facts are covered up. Obama is imploding.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351544484172</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351544627565-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama up in Ohio &amp; already has a HUGE lead in actual votes</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351530752131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is not what a re-election looks like. So far, 28 newspapers that endorsed Obama in 2008 have switched to Romney for 2012.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351544627565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351545014064-64</Id><Title>Obama looks tired and whipped</Title><Msg>This is NOT what a re-election looks like. Obama campaigning desperately like an underdog. The end is near. He's not gaining on Romeny anywhere. He's slipping everywhere. Gone with the Wind. Too much bullsheet out of Obama's mouth.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351545014064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351545326456-65</Id><Title>GM CEO: under Romney "you could have written off this company, this industry and this country."</Title><Msg>"Did President Obama save General Motors?" "Without the money, without the funding, it would have been very problematic," said Akerson. "At the risk of alienating a whole lot of potential customers, I would say the Obama administration did a good job." Republican presidential hopeful Mitt Romney and other critics have argued the bailout was unnecessary, and that the regular bankruptcy process would have made GM and Chrysler stronger companies. "Would that have happened?" Reynolds asked. "Not in my opinion," asked Akerson. "It would have been in bankruptcy for years and I think you could have written off this company, this industry and this country."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351545326456</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:15:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351545383332-66</Id><Topic><Title>Minnesota</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351542948432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:35:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phil, you are peeing into the wind. Give it up, BOY</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351545383332</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351545529325-67</Id><Topic><Title>Unlike Gearge W Bush during Katrina,Obama as President, is</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351542791176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 16:33:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be my guest Phil. Hang your hat on Obama's response to Sandy. You have no idea of what's about to happen.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351545529325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:18:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351545681943-68</Id><Title>Jennifer Granholm: Romney Stuck 'A Knife In Our Back' With Auto Bailout Opposition</Title><Msg>fmr governor of michigan knows Romney is a big fat liar and this is why obama is winning in Ohio: When Michigan was on our knees in our darkest hour in December 2008 ... Mitt Romney took the political assessment of how the public felt about [the] bailout," Granholm said. "And decided that the state that he grew up in ... was not important enough for him to be able to stand with this industry, to stand with the people who are employed there, and so he decided that he would stick a knife in our back when we were on our knees." "That example of his cravenness should be and is," she said on the call, "why the president is winning in Ohio."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351545681943</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351547614804-69</Id><Title>This is NOT what a re-election looks like</Title><Msg>Incumbents under 50% the week before the election go down to defeat. The end is near.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351547614804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351547701048-70</Id><Topic><Title>Jennifer Granholm: Romney Stuck 'A Knife In Our Back' With Auto Bailout Opposition</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351545681943</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:21:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Granholm!?? LOL! A whackjob top to bottom!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1351547701048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351552456154-71</Id><Topic><Title>October jobs report may be delayed until after election...</Title><Username>turbotaxkid</Username><Timestamp>1351538569293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 15:22:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's already lost. The truth comes out after the election. Truth is global recession. Greece is out of Euro. Fiscal Cliff is austerity just like they got in Europe. Suck it up boys and girls.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351552456154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351553769690-72</Id><Title>Obama Incentivizes WalMart Shoppers, but NOT Employers</Title><Msg>It's easy to see why there are no jobs in America... you can literally SEE the reasons in virtually EVERY Obama Policy. For example, when they lowered the FICA (social security) tax to stimulate the economy, they lowered it from 6.2 to 4.2% for EMPLOYEES, so that they'd have more money to take to WalMart and spend on Chinese stuff... .... but Obama WOULDN'T lower it for EMPLOYERS, so they have no additional incentives to hire more Americans. Same with Obamacare: Obama requires any employer with more than 50 employers to provide health insurance... so all kinds of companies are looking at laying off enough employees to get their headcount UNDER 50 in cases where the steep cost of health insurance would substantially hurt their ability to compete... especially against foreign countries with fewer taxes and mandates like Obamacare. Obama has refused to lower the U.S. highest-in-the-world corporate tax... so corporations are sitting on tons of cash overseas instead of re-patriating it back to the U.S. into jobs-producing investments. The list of anti-jobs policies from Obama are ENDLESS... ... why won't Obama supporters out there LOOK at his horrible policies instead of just reacting to 1-liner Obama commercials in the middle of their latest Oprah Winfrey episode. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351553769690</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351561179774-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Incentivizes WalMart Shoppers, but NOT Employers</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351553769690</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 19:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh please... don't give us the #$%$ that if *only* we did even more for US companies then they would hire. Profits at large US companies are at all times record or close to that. They are sitting on record cash amounts. Effective corporate tax rates are at record lows. Companies like GE or Google pay almost no taxes. And we are not doing enough for them? And this extra money spent by consumers is going mostly to US companies doesn't it? (WMT) What are they doing with it? In spite of all that, they don't hire. Why? Because American consumers have been defrauded and abused at every turn. Most of them are living pay check to pay check... assuming they still have a job, many of which were off-shored for a short term corporate profit. If there is no demand, companies don't NEED to hire. This is really that simple. Supply side economics are a silly answer to a demand problem.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1351561179774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351562744535-74</Id><Title>Sweaty mitts flip flops on Fema and admits he was an ajole before</Title><Msg>Romney campaign: No cuts to FEMA Despite once saying that disaster relief would face the knife, the candidate now says FEMA is safe</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351562744535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351562890923-75</Id><Title>The Useful Goons</Title><Msg>messy still hoping for the impossible. Nothing Obama can scrape up at the last minute will absolve him of the horrendous situation he's put upon the American people. Even counties in Calif that have been liberal for decades are favoring Romney. The job situation has not improved no matter how they minimize it. They've lied to give Obama some traction in the last stretch. His has been the most corrupt and dishonest campaign ever.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351562890923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351563330029-76</Id><Title>dear stupid bjspleanimal who just denounced a tax cut for the middleclass</Title><Msg>without demand there is no job creation. The fica tax holiday puts money in the pockets of working people who spend every dime and thus create demand for products which creates jobs. The tax cuts for the rich gave more money for the rich to send to their cayman island bank accounts. get the picture? republicans are such #$%$ to hate tax cuts for the middleclass for working people.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351563330029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351563839444-77</Id><Title>. "Syria is Iran's only ally in the Arab world," he said, "It's their route to the sea."</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney's foreign policy has never been more than a laundry list of tough-talk. He reliably repeats the same jingoistic claptrap every time he hits the national stage</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351563839444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351564170851-78</Id><Title>Romney: "go to the hospital..you get treated..and it's paid for by the..hospital"</Title><Msg>free healthcare for all!!!!! go sweaty mitts "You go to the hospital," Romney says. "You get treated, you get care, and it's paid for, either by charity, the government or by the hospital</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351564170851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 22:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>