<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351947628590-1</Id><Title>Mr. Putin, mitt's, my dad will say anything to get a vote so pay no attention</Title><Msg>Matt Romney Goes To Russia, Secretly Sends Message To Putin To Ignore Dad’s Campaign Rhetoric By Hamed Aleaziz on Nov 2, 2012 at 12:42 pm This week Mitt Romney’s son Matt traveled to Moscow for business and, reports say, allayed any concerns the Russian government had about his father’s harsh stance on Russia. When it comes to Russia, Mitt Romney has been brash, at one point labeling Russia “without question our number one geopolitical foe” and “a geopolitical adversary.” He’s also repeatedly lashed out at President Obama for allegedly being weak on Russia. But according to a New York Times report, Matt Romney is trying to convince Russia that the tough talk is just talk: “But while in Moscow, Mr. Romney told a Russian known to be able to deliver messages to Mr. Putin that despite the campaign rhetoric, his father wants good relations if he becomes president, according to a person informed about the conversation.” Romney’s statements have drawn negative feedback from Republicans like Sen. Richard Luger, who called Romney’s statements on Russia “discredited objections.” Others, like former Secretary of State Colin Powell have gone even further, urging Romney to develop more nuance on the issue. In May, Powell said: “I think he really needs to not just accept these cataclysmic sort of pronouncements. I think he really needs to think carefully about these statements because they’re now on the wall for people to see. … Let’s not go creating enemies where none yet exist. Does this mean that we should trust Putin or Medvedev? No. Let’s be mature people and look at the reality of the situation and not find ways to see if we can hyperbolize the situation.” Russia experts were dismayed at Romney’s harsh stance. Steve Pifer, the Brookings Institution’s Arms Control Initiative director, told the New York Times in May that Romney’s arguments “left people scratching their heads.” Romney’s stance even “set off disagreements among some of his foreign policy advisers” according to the New York Times and signaled to some of his inner circle his view of “foreign policy conflicts as zero-sum negotiations.” One foreign policy adviser told the Daily Beast that “the campaign should have walked it back and moved on.” Some Russian officials weren’t amused by Romney’s words. In July, a top international affairs official said of Romney’s words: “If he is serious about this, I’m afraid he may choose the neocon-type people…In the first year of his presidency, we may have a full-scale crisis.” Dmitri Medvedev, Russia’s former president and current prime minister, commented too: “My other advice is to check their clocks from time to time. It is 2012, not the mid-1970s.” But Vladimir Putin, Russia’s current president, dismissed Romney’s statements as “pre-election rhetoric.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351947628590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351949096718-2</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Putin, mitt's, my dad will say anything to get a vote so pay no attention</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351947628590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt sends Matt to su.ckup to Putin Romney's Son Asks Putin For Some Flexibility.............how many jobs will that cost the USA?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351949096718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351949362777-3</Id><Title>Tush Limpbalz attacks Christie. Tush must have had a hemorrhoids flare up or something</Title><Msg>Conservative radio host Rush Limbaugh, who normally reserves his derision for Democrats, went so far as to say of Christie: “He’s fat and a fool. Don’t listen to Governor Christie. He doesn’t know what he’s talking about.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351949362777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351949500004-4</Id><Title>Mitt Blames Obama For Closed BBQ Restaurant With Repeated Health Violations</Title><Msg>Romney Campaign Blames Obama For Closed BBQ Restaurant With Repeated Health Violations new ad by the Romney campaign, titled “Bill’s BBQ,” highlights a small chain of barbecue restaurants in Richmond, Virginia, which closed in September. The ad argues that the 82-year-old company went out of business because President Obama has not improved the economy. But a ThinkProgress review of news reports and public health records suggest the company may have had other problems — and that other similar restaurants in the same area are doing quite well</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351949500004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351951192238-5</Id><Topic><Title>the union thing seabug is talking about is a lie.</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351888862619</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 16:41:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hardly a lie BOY! Utility crews from several states East of the Mississippi River hit the road this week to volunteer their time and talents in Northeastern states hit hard by Hurricane Sandy. But crews from Alabama got the shock of their lives when other workers in a coastal New Jersey town told them they couldn’t lend a hand without a union card. Derrick Moore, who works for Decatur Utilities in Decatur, Ala., told WAFF-TV in Huntsville that crews in Seaside Heights, N.J. turned him and his crewmates away, saying they couldn’t do any work there because they’re not union employees. As a result, crews from Decatur and Huntsville left the Jersey shore and headed to Long Island to pitch in. WAFF’s Mark Thornton reported that Moore and his coworkers “are frustrated being told, in essence, ‘thanks, but no thanks.’” Another nonunion Decatur Utilities crew is idling in Roanoke, Va., waiting for instructions from Seaside Heights. The town asked them days ago for help, but later told the workers to stand down. Electric repair work for public utilities in New Jersey is dominated by the International Brotherhood Of Electrical Workers, a unit of the politically powerful AFL-CIO. Many parts of coastal New Jersey are projected to be without electric power for at least seven to 10 more days.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351951192238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351958008421-6</Id><Topic><Title>Tush Limpbalz attacks Christie. Tush must have had a hemorrhoids flare up or something</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351949362777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:29:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Christie is like most pols. He'd throw his own mother under the bus to get what he wants. He wants to be President. If Romney is elected he probably will serve 8 years. If the Kenyan is elected Christie has a shot in four years.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351958008421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351958364492-7</Id><Topic><Title>Florida voter officials slowing down</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351953359551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not so fast, Phil. This poll has Romney up be 6. You gotta watch more than just CNN Florida continues to look good for Mitt Romney. The Republican holds a 6-point lead in the state essential to his hopes of defeating President Barack Obama, according to a new Tampa Bay Times/Bay News 9/Miami Herald poll. The poll shows slight tightening, with Romney's 51-45 lead down 1 percentage point from the Times' statewide poll a month ago. Other Florida surveys show a tighter contest and both campaigns are blanketing the state with appearances geared toward scraping together every last vote.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958364492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351958672066-8</Id><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Msg>believable? conceivable?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351959191546-9</Id><Topic><Title>Remember voters:</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351952702070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:25:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is one of your dumber statements, phyllis. It's easy to tell you just parrot what you hear from other goons. Obama did not save Americas "auto industry". He bailed out one company. Actually GM is having problems. He did try to save the solar industry but 4 companies that he gave millions to are now OOB. For usefull dummies that means "Out Of Business" The better question is what would America be without liberal goons? Heaven I suppose and not broke.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351959191546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:13:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351959555369-10</Id><Topic><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>examples from twitter of talks of rioting If Romney win , me obama and 2 chainz going to start a riot and shoot his #$%$ ! 2 Nov 12 Reply Retweet Favorite imz@turn2two If Obama lose it's going to be the biggest riot in history… Beacause, I'm going to start it! 2 Nov 12 Reply Retweet Favorite K.dot@BanitaApplebumm 2 Nov 12 If Romney were to win, I feel like ppl are gonna riot the streets.. The Sage⚡@ChuckRaging yup, thas me. RT @BanitaApplebumm: If Romney were to win, I feel like ppl are gonna riot the streets.. 2 Nov 12 Reply Retweet Favorite JayBabyyyy@JayBae813 I Swear If Romney Win Imma Start A Mothafuckin Riot 2 Nov 12 Reply Retweet Favorite IG: @Perfectly_Badd_@Perfectly_Badd_ If Romney win we should start a riot 2 Nov 12 Reply Retweet</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351959555369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351959602760-11</Id><Topic><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess Romney better not win, huh.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351959602760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351960090980-12</Id><Topic><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let them, It would be good to see some heads cracked. This results of the class warfare Obama has perpetuated. . No riots when Obama was elected and his platform was wealth distribution. These goons better be careful where they riot, armed citizens will back the police if they're out numbered. Bet on it.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351960090980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351960315960-13</Id><Topic><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where they riot? If it happens, they'll burn their own neighborhoods. That's where.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351960315960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:31:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351960568809-14</Id><Title>Michael Barone says Romney</Title><Msg>Barone is a very smart guy. He is an expert on every voting district in the country. No one tops him in that regard. He says: Fundamentals usually prevail in American elections. That's bad news for Barack Obama. True, Americans want to think well of their presidents and many think it would be bad if Americans were perceived as rejecting the first black president. But it's also true that most voters oppose Obama's major policies and consider unsatisfactory the very sluggish economic recovery -- Friday's jobs report showed an unemployment uptick. Also, both national and target state polls show that independents, voters who don't identify themselves as Democrats or Republicans, break for Romney. That might not matter if Democrats outnumbered Republicans by 39 to 32 percent, as they did in the 2008 exit poll. But just about every indicator suggests that Republicans are more enthusiastic about voting -- and about their candidate -- than they were in 2008, and Democrats are less so. That's been apparent in early or absentee voting, in which Democrats trail their 2008 numbers in target states Virginia, Ohio, Iowa and Nevada. The Obama campaign strategy, from the beginning, has recognized these handicaps, running barrages of early anti-Romney ads in states that Obama carried narrowly. But other states, not so heavily barraged, have come into contention.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351960568809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:36:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351962718462-15</Id><Title>seburgc the stupid liar.</Title><Msg>he lied about the utility workers being turnaround. the ultility in questions stated clearly that their workers had not been turned around and in fact , they are working in NJ and NY.. other utilities said the same....... the station that first.."broke" the story also updated and said the person they were talking to was just plain wrong....</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351962718462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351962778930-16</Id><Topic><Title>"at no time were our crews "turned away" from</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351890074427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 17:01:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>update for the liar seabubc</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351962778930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351963485093-17</Id><Topic><Title>seburgc the stupid liar.</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351962718462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh I see. The audio I heard on the radio where union types called other workers scabs, #$%$. Get out of town etc., was just my imagination huh. I didn't hear what I heard, right?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351963485093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351963666652-18</Id><Title>Ala. utilities: Our crews not turned away from N.J. (seabugc says he is right they are wrong)</Title><Msg>CBS/AP/ November 2, 2012, 2:00 PM Ala. utilities: Our crews not turned away from N.J. Alabama power companies are denying a local TV station's report that linemen who had traveled to New Jersey from Alabama (a right to work state) to help restore power to those hit hard by Superstorm Sandy were told they could not work there because they were non-union. The report by WAFF TV quotes a worker from Decatur Utilities saying he was told by crews in New Jersey they could not work there, after the utility receiving a call to assist in Seaside Heights, N.J. The Decatur employee told WAFF that crews were told to stand down, and that linemen from Trinity, Ala.-based Joe Wheeler are already headed back home. Moore said they are frustrated being told, "Thanks, but no thanks." However, Ala. utilities: Our crews not turned away from N.J. To be clear, at no time were our crews "turned away" Utilities from other right-to-work states have also reported their crews working in New York and New Jersey, including repair crews with Electric Cooperatives of Arkansas assisting in New York State. Florida Power &amp; Light sent more than 860 employees and contractors to assist seven utility companies from Virginia to New Jersey</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351963666652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351964123322-19</Id><Topic><Title>seburgc the stupid liar.</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351962718462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dear STUPID, person, who knows what #$%$ audio you heard, maybe it was 100% phony same as when faux news showed photos of the guy wearing an outlandish "pimp costume" in an acorn office when the fact is THAT NEVER HAPPENED ,that person was always dressed in business attire in the acorn offices and the "pimp" costume was only worn in a studio...... but it was shown and implied as otherwise............. I have NO idea what you heard or what it was.... but the fact is, the alabama utility in question has stated clearly that "To be clear, at no time were our crews "turned away" ..... and fyi "Utilities from other right-to-work states have also reported their crews working in New York and New Jersey, including repair crews with Electric Cooperatives of Arkansas assisting in New York State. Florida Power &amp; Light sent more than 860 employees and contractors to assist seven utility companies from Virginia to New Jersey" btw what station were you listening to?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351964123322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351964365405-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ala. utilities: Our crews not turned away from N.J. (seabugc says he is right they are wrong)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351963666652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so this guy lied when he reported the following: He was there. First hand account. Interesting contrast. Derrick Moore, who works for Decatur Utilities in Decatur, Ala., told WAFF-TV in Huntsville that crews in Seaside Heights, N.J. turned him and his crewmates away, saying they couldn’t do any work there because they’re not union employees. As a result, crews from Decatur and Huntsville left the Jersey shore and headed to Long Island to pitch in.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351964365405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351964539903-21</Id><Topic><Title>seburgc the stupid liar.</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351962718462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:11:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thse people talking of riots if Obama loses. Fake or real. Believable or incredible?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351964539903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351965139067-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ala. utilities: Our crews not turned away from N.J. (seabugc says he is right they are wrong)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351963666652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dear STUPID PERSON.... Mr Moore WAS 100% WRONG, and is no doubt also a stupid person. and HE is the ONLY person that THOUGHT he was being turned around...., based on his own stupidity........ but..... his bosses cleared it up and they have said AFTER all the knee jerk right wing ashley todd with a letter B on her face kind of panywad hysteria: his utility has said : Nov 02, 2012 By NBC News UPDATE: Alabama utility company helps in northeast after Sandy UPDATE - To be clear, at no time were our crews "turned away" from the utility in Seaside Heights" the release explained.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351965139067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351965290364-23</Id><Title>Faux news has a long history of distorting , lying using fake videos, false info, and cutting and pasting from the gop</Title><Msg>just a small list of fauz news lies, and other rightwing media do the same: Fox News' year in apologies: Fake videos, false info, cutting and pasting from GOP Fox News presents year-old Palin footage as new Palin book tour crowd Fox passes off GOP press release as its own research -- typo and all Stewart blasts Hannity for using old video footage to inflate Bachmann rally attendance Fox News' Garrett apologizes for fake HBO-Obama story -- which Fox News repeated days later Fox News presents deceptively cropped 6-month-old Biden clip as new</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351965290364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351965467064-24</Id><Topic><Title>Ala. utilities: Our crews not turned away from N.J. (seabugc says he is right they are wrong)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351963666652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so they say. Moore was there. The utility execs were not. The company probably didn't want to be in the middle of a controversy. So they deny what Moore saw and heard. And prob told Moore to shut up. That stuff happens all the time. Happening in politics right now re Benghazi. Or maybe you're not aware. It wouldn't surprise me.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351965467064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351966130281-25</Id><Topic><Title>Ala. utilities: Our crews not turned away from N.J. (seabugc says he is right they are wrong)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351963666652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>moore is the sc.re.w up and people WHO were there say so , and ntm, the fact that HIS bosses "Decatur Utilities, based in Decatur, Ala., denied the Moore's) report. To be clear, at no time were our crews "turned away" from the utility in Seaside Heights" they said. the fact is Moore turned his 6 man crew back from viginia, because of his own stupid misunderstanding........ and this private utilitly contractor refutes what Moore said: George Kitchens, GM and CEO of Joe Wheeler EMC ...- told CBS News that the initial report that Joe Wheeler linemen had been turned away was "completely off-base." (Moore had said they were turned away) Kitchens said eight linemen from Joe Wheeler were among 145 Alabama linemen who traveled to Maryland and Virginia in response to calls for help with repair efforts. "They rode out the storm, and then did repair work there," Kitchens said. "Our people are on the way back home, [but] it's not from being turned away." Huntsville Utilities also said their workers were not turned away and are working in storm-ravaged areas. Utilities from other right-to-work states have also reported their crews working in New York and New Jersey, including repair crews with Electric Cooperatives of Arkansas assisting in New York State. Florida Power &amp; Light sent more than 860 employees and contractors to assist seven utility companies from Virginia to New Jersey. (did you get an anonymous phone call or what?...lol)</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351966130281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 14:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351967585898-26</Id><Title>it was an ashlely todd kinda thing... the 1 non union guy who threw a fit or whatever</Title><Msg>funny that a tv camera was on this guy Moore, who had it all wrong and it turns out NO CREWS were turned back......... he turned his own crew back from virginia...... but they were'nt needed anyways since OTHER out of state and non unions crews did the job, amoung the thousands of non union from out of state who are helping out......... George Kitchens was there with Moore , and he said there were a 145 Alabama linemen there (only moore and his 6 man crew left) "They rode out the storm, and then did repair work there," Kitchens said. "Our people are on the way back home, [but] it's not from being turned away." Huntsville Utilities also said their workers were not turned away and are working in storm-ravaged areas. Utilities from other right-to-work states have also reported their crews working in New York and New Jersey, including repair crews with Electric Cooperatives of Arkansas assisting in New York State. Florida Power &amp; Light sent more than 860 employees and contractors to assist seven utility companies from Virginia to New Jersey</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351967585898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 14:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351969733999-27</Id><Title>bottom line on the utility worker panty wad</Title><Msg>one guy, turned his crew back, because of HIS own misunderstanding., his own stupidity,...... one 6 man crew... and oddly enough there was a tv camera there for the one guy to spout off HIS idiot misunderstanding and his obvious bias........and rightoff his boss is on fox business news (and later had to retract ).. one 6 man crew ......out of the thousands of out of state and non unions electric workers who were and are working in NY and NJ and elsewhere.........jeez.......... and worse..... his misunderstanding came from what he THOUGHT were documents from a union, but they turned out to be from "Electric Cities of Alabama, a coalition of the state's municipally owned utilities." this update is from NBC "General Manager Ray Hardin appeared on Fox Business Channel Friday morning saying, "We were presented documents from IBEW that required our folks to affiliate with the unions and that was something we could not agree to." (that turned out to be not true) Decatur Utilities later released a statement expanding on that, "Upon arriving at a staging area in Virginia, crews were held in place pending clarification of documents received from IBEW that implied a requirement of our employees to agree to union affiliation while working in the New York and New Jersey areas. It was and remains our understanding that agreeing to those requirements was a condition of being allowed to work in those areas." Late Friday at a press conference, Hardin said the documents actually came from Electric Cities of Alabama, a coalition of the state's municipally owned utilities. Bottom line, it appears now that Decatur Utilities wrongly assumed they would have to agree to the union contract before traveling to New Jersey to help with recovery efforts. The IBEW said in times of crisis, help is welcomed from union and non-union utility workers."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351969733999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 15:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351970821746-28</Id><Title>some NYers have the right idea</Title><Msg>though I'm sure law enforcement frowns on it. Pity the guy who takes a shot at a punk. He'd be going to jail. Hardened New Yorkers are ready to battle lowlife criminals to protect their homes and stores in storm-ravaged areas plagued by looting and break-ins. In Coney Island, several residents were loading up their guns, sharpening their machetes and brandishing other deadly weapons. Jacinto Gonzalez, 42, picked up a baseball bat and stood guard outside his two-story rowhouse on West 27th Street near Neptune Avenue with his family. Another Coney Island resident, Roberto Aviles, brandishing a rusty 3-foot machete and warning he has a gun, who has lived in Coney Island since 1995 with his wife, says he’s ready to take on phony burglars posing as Con Ed workers. “I’m prepared inside here,” the 76-year-old Aviles said, showing off his rusted, three-foot machete and warning he had a gun. Chris Lane, a 50-year-old resident of the Coney Island Houses, put together a small arsenal with his double pump action gun. Lane said he scared off a bunch of thugs skulking around the hallways of his building when the storm struck Monday night. “They were roving in packs, not just one or two people. I had more than a little something, too,” Lane said, referring to his weapons. “I let it be known that my floor is off limits.” A sign outside a home in Long Beach, LI, summed it all up for storm weary New Yorkers. It read, “Looters will be shot by local vet.”</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351970821746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 15:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351976580129-29</Id><Topic><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope if they do riot they do it close to me. I have the solution for it. A 12 ga. with #1 shot. Years ago when they had riots in Detroit, Life Magazine had a picture of a row of looted shops. One shop on the corner hadn't been touched. The owners were sitting in front of their store, each with a shotgun. During the Rodney King riots a similar thing happened. A whole row of businesses looted except one. The Korean business man had armed himself and his clerks with AK-47's and placed them on the roof. His store wasn;t touched. During the Watt's riots of the 60's I remember a Black newsman that had covered the other riots stating that L.A. was the only place he had seen people driving across town in Cadillacs to loot.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351976580129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:03:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351976899796-30</Id><Topic><Title>Faux news has a long history of distorting , lying using fake videos, false info, and cutting and pasting from the gop</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351965290364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 13:54:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "Lamestream Press" never lies? How about the "Tonkin Gulf Incident?" How about the attack on the U. S. S. Liberty? How about the lies about Saddams WMD's? How about the fact that Osama Bin Laden died in Dubai in 2001 of Marfans Disease? I could add many more, especially the most recent about the men's death in Benghazi. I thgink you just have a sore head because you lost your job at Finnochios in San Francisco when they closed.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351976899796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351978004850-31</Id><Title>Poll Shock: Obama could lose Illinois</Title><Msg>North Korean lib media has suppressed polls showing Romney winning in a landslide in downstate Illinois and suburban Chicago. Independents and women are breaking for Romney.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351978004850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351978083819-32</Id><Topic><Title>some NYers have the right idea</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351970821746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 15:27:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Second storm coming up the coast on Election Day. Punch Obama OUT!!! FEMA HELP US!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351978083819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351979356943-33</Id><Title>talk of mass hysteria, panty wetting and whining if Sweaty Mitts loses</Title><Msg>based on an anonymous phone call to rightwing 'daily caller'</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351979356943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351979396599-34</Id><Title>Axelrod to shave mustache if Obama loses</Title><Msg>He's getting a blonde wig too.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351979396599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351979716072-35</Id><Topic><Title>talk of mass hysteria, panty wetting and whining if Sweaty Mitts loses</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351979356943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:49:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Campaign 2012: When an incumbent Democratic president is virtually tied in a congressional district he carried by high double digits in 2008, and is losing in the suburbs of his hometown, there could be trouble brewing. This is not what a re-election looks like. In August, a poll by the Joliet, Ill.-based polling firm of McKeon and Associates, found President Obama leading challenger Mitt Romney in Cook County, which includes Chicago and its suburbs, by a 12-point margin 49-37. That would seem to be a comfortable edge, but it is significantly smaller than traditional margins needed to outweigh the more Republican downstate vote. "He has to come out of Cook County with a big lead or he's gonna have problems downstate," explained McKeon, who said that based on the numbers he's seen, Obama polled only in the 40s in downstate Illinois. If his poll is accurate, Obama would be in some trouble. In the city of Chicago itself, McKeon found Obama with a 60-29 lead over Romney. But Romney led 45-38 in the surrounding areas. Across the county as a whole, Romney led 43-31 among independent voters and held a 44-38 lead among male voters. McKeon noted that in the 2010 gubernatorial race Republican Bill Brady came within a single percentage point of now-Gov. Pat Quinn because Brady won most of the downstate counties that have traditionally resisted and resented being dominated by upstate Chicago politicians. Now comes a new poll from WeAskAmerica that finds Obama with just a 2-point lead over Romney, 47-45, in a suburban Chicago congressional district that Obama won in 2008 by 23 points. Voting is the best revenge. Punch Obama OUT!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351979716072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:55:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351979829652-36</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA LEADING EVERYWHERE BY</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351951773672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney leads or is tied in FL, VA, IA, OH, WI, CO, NV, NH. OUT OUT OUT PUNCH OBAMA OUT!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351979829652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351980067769-37</Id><Title>Israel's oldest newspaper and one of it's most influential, has endorsed Barack Obama for reelection</Title><Msg>The article was published as an editorial today, titled "Obama is good for Israel." Haaretz, Israel's oldest newspaper and one of it's most influential, has endorsed Barack Obama for reelection (......So much for sweaty mitt's nonsense about Israel, it was on a par with him saying that iran is landlocked............smart people know that mittens is a phony , and who would trust him?)</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351980067769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351980241129-38</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Putin, mitt's, my dad will say anything to get a vote so pay no attention</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351947628590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 09:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this sure underscores what a phony sweaty mitts is on foreign policy..... after pretending to be the tough guy on Russia in the debate, next thing you know Mitt sends Matt to kiss Russia rear end, and beg for money.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351980241129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351981951389-39</Id><Topic><Title>mesa is single handedly DROPKICKING 100 million repubs!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1351897962548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:12:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and menstrual are tweetle dee and tweetle dumb! The two of You together couldn’t drop kick a midget in an AXX kicking contest! Wake up and Smell the COFFEE, #$%$, Your boy “Obama” is bush spray-painted Black! GO BAIL OUT WALL STREET AGAIN, FOOLS!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351981951389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351982493162-40</Id><Topic><Title>mesa is single handedly DROPKICKING 100 million repubs!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1351897962548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:12:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think i heard that seabugc was caught crying "fire" in a crowded theater. He claimed he heard it from an anonymous phone call that rightwing 'daily caller' said they got.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351982493162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 18:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351984965546-41</Id><Topic><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Readiy, waiting and armed! Just bought a couple extra clips!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1351984965546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351985366389-42</Id><Topic><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the people talking of rioting are your soulmates, Phil. What's the problem?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351985366389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 19:29:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351993282048-43</Id><Topic><Title>talk of rioting if Romney wins</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351958672066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 12:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Refuses to Answer About Storm Victims’ Frustrations by Keith Koffler on November 3, 2012, 10:44 am President Obama this morning ignored a reporter’s question about the mounting frustration victims of Hurricane Sandy are having with the response to the storm, refusing to let a question from the press interrupt a FEMA photo op in which he was on display taking action. An excerpt rom the press pool report, which starts with a quote from Obama: “There is nothing more important than us getting this right. And we’re going to spend as much time, effort and energy as necessary to make sure all the people of New York, New Jersey and Connecticut know that the entire country is behind them in this difficult recovery effort.” He spoke for about five minutes. Pool asked about frustrations of people, particularly Staten Island. He did not respond. No doubt aware of the political perils – and potential benefits – of the fallout from the hurricane, Obama arrived at FEMA with multiple members of his Cabinet in tow in a massive display of presidential concern. Even Cabinet secretaries you wouldn’t expect to be involved in hurricane relief – such as the Secretary of Labor and the Small Business Administration Administrator – have been enlisted and were at this morning’s meeting. Obama’s effort will indeed have some practical effect – anytime a president shows he is personally engaged in an issue, it helps get the various agencies involved into a higher gear. But with scenes of devastation proliferating on voters’ TV screens around the nation and evidence mounting of an insufficient response, Obama obviously felt he had to be seen at FEMA for a second time this week before heading back out to campaign. After the visit to FEMA, Obama departed for</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1351993282048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 21:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351995685221-44</Id><Topic><Title>talk of mass hysteria, panty wetting and whining if Sweaty Mitts loses</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351979356943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 17:49:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"believable? conceivable" asks seabugc,?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351995685221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351996313652-45</Id><Title>Minnesota at risk -- going Romney!!!</Title><Msg>Barack Obama and Mitt Romney are separated by just 1 point in Minnesota, effectively making the race there a toss-up, according to polling taken for the conservative American Future Fund. A bastion of liberalism is repudiating Obama. Romney takes 46 percent of the vote to Obama's 45 percent in the poll, which was conducted by the GOP firm NMB Research and shared with POLITICO. The Republican presidential nominee is up 13 points among independents, ahead of Obama 49 percent to 36 percent. Axelrod is going to have to shave his mustache and his balz!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351996313652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351996387288-46</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA LEADING EVERYWHERE BY</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1351951773672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 10:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phil... that's why you can't get laid. You are a putz. You are out of touch.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351996387288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351996506145-47</Id><Topic><Title>mesa is single handedly DROPKICKING 100 million repubs!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1351897962548</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 19:12:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I laugh in your face like Joe Biden. You menstrual clown. BWHHAHHAHHAHHAHA!!!!! Wake and smell the coffee you lemming fool!!! Lean forward over the fiscal cliff while I kick you in the ash whole!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351996506145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 22:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>