<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348483521742-1</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both Obama and Ahmadinejad Liken Israeli Concerns Over Nuclear Iran to 'Noise'...</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1348483521742</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 06:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348483641167-2</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CBS Doesn't Air Obama Admitting Mistakes in Campaign Ads 10:39 PM, Sep 23, 2012 • By DANIEL HALPER Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts Tonight, CBS aired a 60 Minutes interview with President Obama. But curiously enough, the news magazine show did not air a clip of Obama admitting to interviewer Steve Kroft that some of his campaign ads contain mistakes and that some even "go overboard." 60 Minutes did, however, post the clip online: CBS describes the clip this way: "President Obama says some of his campaign ads might 'go overboard' or contain mistakes, but most of them simply highlight the differences between him and Gov. Romney." "Look, the fact-checkers have had problems with the ads on both sides," Kroft says to Obama in the unaired clip, "and say they've been misleading and in some cases just not true. Does that disturb you? I mean, some of them are your ads." Obama responds: "Do we see sometimes us going overboard in our campaign, are there mistakes that are made, areas where there is no doubt somebody could dispute how we are presenting things? You know, that happens in politics." Kroft responds: "Aren't the American entitled to the truth? Or a better version of it?"</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1348483641167</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 06:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348487939186-3</Id><Title>Obama announces war with Iran</Title><Msg>He blamed it on Romney.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348487939186</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 07:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348488015836-4</Id><Topic><Title>Texas Mom angry that male vice principal spanked daughter</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1348423692825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:08:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And she loved it. She didn't tell her mother the rest of the story.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348488015836</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348488097984-5</Id><Topic><Title>End all welfare!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348416849556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:14:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make welfare monkeys work for their welfare check instead of staying home gang bangin.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348488097984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348488176325-6</Id><Topic><Title>dead us ambassador to libya was sodomized!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348416193215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:03:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama apologized. That'll stop 'em.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348488176325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348491959269-7</Id><Title>Romney is the tax preacher ( gospel of snake oil)</Title><Msg>who would listen to a preacher that does not do as he preaches and show ten years of tax returns? Or who banks in tax evasion Cayman islands.? Or who obviously window dressed his 2011 tax return...... Kinda like listening to the preacher in church that everyone knows is a drunk and diddling some of the gals in the choir.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348491959269</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348495487966-8</Id><Title>Obama announces he WILL RAISE TAXES</Title><Msg>BWHHAHHAHHAHHAHHAAA!!! He needs more of your money to blow. Obama snake oil salesman is causing a global economic depression.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348495487966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348495554592-9</Id><Topic><Title>dead us ambassador to libya was sodomized!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348416193215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:03:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both Obama and Ahmadinejad Liken Israeli Concerns Over Nuclear Iran to 'Noise'...</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1348495554592</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348495686174-10</Id><Topic><Title>gop disdain for working people</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348343590365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:53:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Full audio of 1998 ‘redistribution’ speech: Obama saw welfare recipients as ‘majority coalition’ Published: 4:39 AM 09/24/2012 The Daily Caller has obtained a complete audio recording of the October 19, 1998 Loyola College forum on community organizing and policymaking during which a future President Barack Obama said he favored the government redistribution of wealth. The audio demonstrates the context of that remark and reveals other far-left positions that Obama held as a state senator. Those positions encompass issues as wide-ranging as gun control, universal health care and welfare reform. Obama also said he viewed welfare recipients and “the working poor” as “a majority coalition” that could be mobilized to help advance progressive policies and elect their champions. Last week the liberal Mother Jones magazine published video footage, shot during a campaign event, showing Republican presidential hopeful Mitt Romney opining that 47 percent of Americans are captive Democratic voters because they receive government benefits without paying income taxes. (RELATED: Romney controversy points to power of viral video) Loyola College refused repeated requests from TheDC for a copy of the full one-hour and 42-minute videotape from 1998. But a source in Chicago who gained permission to view it recorded the sound secretly, confirming the accuracy of — and expanding on — initial accounts that featured only a brief audio excerpt. “I actually believe in [wealth] redistribution,” Obama said in that 96-second excerpt, published September 18 on YouTube. “At least at a certain level, to make sure that everybody’s got a shot.” The following day, NBC News said it had obtained what it called “the entirety of the relevant remarks,” and complained that Republicans had taken the original lines out of context. NBC published only 35 seconds of video, however, more than half of which overlapped with the YouTube audio from a day earlier. The news agency claimed the full context demonstrated that Obama only “seems” to support “redistributing wealth.” (RELATED: 1998 audiotape surfaces: Obama urged “trick” to aid wealth redistribution)</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348495686174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348495716583-11</Id><Title>Romney has 14 point lead among middle class</Title><Msg>Romney leads by wide margin with veterans Romney leads by wide margin with seniors Romney leads in campaign contributions Obama getting desperate.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348495716583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348496058405-12</Id><Title>Romney next president will win swing states 52 - 47</Title><Msg>Romney is likely to capture most of the undecided votes and could win swing states collectively by at least a 52 percent to 47 percent margin. That would likely lead to Romney winning Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Nevada, New Hampshire, North Carolina, Ohio, Virginia and Wisconsin while having a competitive chance in Michigan and Pennsylvania. Negative bashing by Obama will be the cause of his defeat. As these polls stand today, the election of Mitt Romney as our next president looks likely.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348496058405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348496713843-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama About To Get Exactly What He Deserves!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1347640152855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 12:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will this cause a stock market rally?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348496713843</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348497866734-14</Id><Title>NTWK $6.85...Up 3%......Breakout Alert!!......Hottest NASDAQ stock….Up every day since record earnings......Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts with $21 max target......In 2010 it went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenues…..Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....Only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average......Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income due to strong global demand for its Legacy and Cloud software solutions</Title><Msg>Short-term Target: $16 per Upgrade………Take a look at incredible NTWK chart. In 2010 NTWK went from $8 to $24 in a few weeks. Today NTWK is a much stronger company with far more revenue sources including new Cloud Divisions. Unlike 2010, NTWK today has the flexibility to deliver reliable software products and services not only from Pakistan but also from excellence centers located in Bangkok, Beijing, the US, and the UK. The float today is 1/10 of what it was then and 2013 revenues are expected to breakaway into the mid $40 million for the first time in company history. During 2010 (and 2007) NTWK's market cap reached over $100 million on 50% lower revenues of what is projected for 2013. During the September 4Q CC NTWK officials stated that revenues are expected to reach $100 Million in 2015 up significantly from the $38 Million reported in 2012. They also expect margins to continue to go up as the high-margin Cloud divisions keep continuing exponentially to revenues. MUST READ ……This Week’s Analysts Comments on Upgrade: We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant NFS legacy customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively. The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 projections. We are forecasting EPS of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. The company guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013. NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. === MORE NTWWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others…and a few more coming in quarters/years ahead. - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide, Rio de Janeiro, and Riyadh</Msg><Username>d.malkkey</Username><Timestamp>1348497866734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348498053064-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney has 14 point lead among middle class</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348495716583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you got that info by palpating your morning crap, right? Do you also read chicken entrails?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348498053064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348498485689-16</Id><Topic><Title>Romney has 14 point lead among middle class</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348495716583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft Accidentally Tweets Anti-Ann Coulter Message to Nearly 300,000 Followers Posted on September 23, 2012 at 6:37pm by Erica Ritz Erica Ritz Comments (243) Microsoft Accidentally Tweets Anti Ann Coulter Message to Nearly 300,000 Followers Ann Coulter was reportedly insulted in a Microsoft tweet on Saturday. (AP File Photo) Politico is reporting that Microsoft accidentally delved into the world of partisan politics over the weekend after tweeting out a message insulting conservative author and syndicated columnist Ann Coulter. In response to liberal economist Robert Reich’s tweet that he would be visiting his granddaughter and sitting on a panel with Coulter over the weekend, the tech giant’s official Twitter feed reportedly responded: “@RBReich your granddaughter’s level of discourse and policy those of Ann Coulter.” Here is a purported image of the tweet: Microsoft Accidentally Tweets Anti Ann Coulter Message to Nearly 300,000 Followers The tweet was deleted immediately, according to Politico, and was accidentally written by one of the individuals who manages the company’s Twitter account. Microsoft spokeswoman Christina Pearson added: “One of the people who manages our corporate twitter account thought he was tweeting from their personal twitter account on Saturday morning but tweeted from our corporate account by mistake…That person immediately realized his mistake and deleted the tweet from our corporate account. We have taken steps to help ensure that this kind of mistake doesn’t happen again.”</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1348498485689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499500867-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama About To Get Exactly What He Deserves!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1347640152855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 12:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhinos are nothing more than PC Pig Democrats with some brains... Country-screwers all!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1348499500867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499817572-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama About To Get Exactly What He Deserves!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1347640152855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 12:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>09/24/12 CHICAGO - President Barack Obama's campaign is launching a new offensive Monday against Republican Mitt Romney, blasting the GOP nominee for criticizing Americans who don't pay income taxes without having "come clean" about his own. The campaign started the new push with a television advertisement, its first spot using Romney's comments that 47 percent of voters pay no income tax, and believe they are victims and entitled to government assistance. The ad was to begin airing in Ohio — a crucial swing state where Romney was campaigning this week — but was also expected to be part of the campaign's final push elsewhere between now and Election Day. "Maybe instead of attacking others on taxes, he should come clean on his," the ad's narrator says of Romney. The Democrats will try to portray Romney's generous charitable contributions as a means for him to control those who are Government dependent.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1348499817572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348500444156-19</Id><Title>Obama leads Romney among NASCAR entusiasts</Title><Msg>Obama leads Romney 49 to 42 percent among NASCAR enthusiasts, according to a new Zogby poll by JZ Analytics. turn out the lights the party's over you lost the latino vote, gay vote, women vote and now you've lost the NASCAR vote? this is getting to be kind of funny.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1348500444156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500615481-20</Id><Topic><Title>Romney has 14 point lead among middle class</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348495716583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fuzzy math fox news aint even talking about a Romney lead - Obama's desperate? is that why Romney's campaign VP quit last week? lol</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1348500615481</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348502370207-21</Id><Title>Middle Class families give Romney 14 point lead</Title><Msg>Romney will lower regulation, lower taxes, lower spending instead of continuing runaway spending and much higher taxes pushed by Obama. We're broke. You gotsa stop spending massa or we're going Greek. BTW, the Europeans admitted today they are holding back the really bad news until after the U.S. elections. Greece, Spain, Italy, Ireland are collapsing. China and Australia are imploding. Chinese always give you a fake GDP story. Actual growth there has slowed dramatically. Recession started in January/February 2012.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348502370207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505795762-22</Id><Topic><Title>Romney has 14 point lead among middle class</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348495716583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both Obama and Ahmadinejad Liken Israeli Concerns Over Nuclear Iran to 'Noise'... OBAMA DOWNGRADES ISRAEL ALLIANCE... 'One of Our Closest Allies in the Region'...</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348505795762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506228406-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Consider this 54 year old Grandmother of 8</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348242046063</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You had to have spent the last few years under a ROCK not to have known about this program. You're going to have to find somebody else's posts to find in-accuracies... I only post facts, my friend. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348506228406</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:03:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348507084463-24</Id><Title>Iran prepares for Israeli attack</Title><Msg>Obama blames Romney. BWHHAHHAHHAHHAHHA!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348507084463</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348507290688-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... you actually learned something about WHY 47% of Americans don't pay federal income taxes. In Washington State, the limit for AFH's is 6. That's true of them in most states but it can be different. The 6 resident limit is a "state" law. The 5 resident federal clause means that once you qualify on that basis, ALL revenues derived from medicaid are exempt. Medicaid doesn't cover all of those residents... medicaid sourced revenues are reduced by what is called "participation"... like any pensions or social security the resident receives... which IS taxable... ... but just like any other tax law, skillful AFH providers are good at fine-tuning medicaid revenues to maximize their earnings and eliminate their taxes. We found out the same with the Earned Income Tax Credit... there are many who earn enough "above board" to maximize the credit... then do other work for cash to keep it at it's highest payout level. Of course, the EITC isn't a "tax credit" at all... but actually a "transfer payment" to the working poor that was created by Reagan to compel the poor to work, then ramped up by Clinton to make it into a defacto government entitlement. The least understood tax issue among American voters today is that dividend income is taxed at a maximum of 15% because it is "double taxed" at the corporate level before it's distributed... ... If corporations could "deduct" dividend distributions, I would be the FIRST ONE to agree that dividend's should be taxed as ordinary income at the personal level... but Obama isn't proposing that because Obama hates corporations even more than he hates Captialism. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348507290688</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348507971847-26</Id><Title>Obamacare... the "anti-jobs" entitlement</Title><Msg>Of course, ALL entitlements eliminate jobs in America because all entitlements have to tax earnings and/or investment captial to pay for them. And the hits just keep coming... look at the "FICA" tax break currently in place... it reduces the rate the "employee" pays so he has more money to stimulate the economy by going down to WalMart and using it to buy Chinese stuff.... but it DOESN'T reduce the "employers" portion, which the employer might otherwise use to justify adding employees. Heck, 60% of voters polled don't even KNOW that the employer pays FICA taxes and contributes to their future social security payments. But, back to Obamacare. Simply put, if you're an employer of 50 or more employees, Obamacare MANDATES that you provide expensive health insurance... but if you employ 49 or fewer employees, you're exempt from providing them. I recently went to a Chamber of Comerce meeting and talked to as many employers as I could who might be impacted by Obamacare's mandate. TO THE LETTER, every one of them was aware of it and every one of them that employed 50 to 80 employees was looking at ways to pare it to 49... either by laying off employees or splitting operations into separate businesses. Bottom line: Laws have consequences. Exempt mortgage interest and capital gains from the sale of a house from taxes... and America will put all their capital into huge houses instead of the stock of corporations that hire people and make things... ... similarly, Obamacare is resulting in planned layoffs among companies trying to cope in an increasingly socialist America. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348507971847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348509065261-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama describes murder of U.S. ambassador to Libya and Mid East violence as 'bumps in the road' PUBLISHED: 08:55 EST, 24 September 2012 | UPDATED: 09:59 EST, 24 September 2012</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348509065261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348510208604-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The 6 resident limit is a "state" law." good grief, i just cited the IRS rule. it is an IRS rule. and fyi Romney is a LIAR about the 47% being moochers. MOST of them are working families, or seniors who worked all their life and only have meager savings and social security and no taxable income... the troops that Romney never mentioned at the RNC would also be romney moochers since many of them are e-4 or below 5 years or less and if they have a wife and and child.... no income taxes....... typical gop hypocriscy too, many of those working families previously paid taxes , but the bush tax cut doubled the child credit and add to the rolls of Romney's moocher class.....; nice how the gop bums create a problem they later whine and lie about ...... and sure the guy who saved the USA from another great depression "hates capitalism" which must be why pubs also accuse him of being in bed with wall street and why corporate profits have hit record highs , ceo pay at record highs and the stock market making the biggest gains in years.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348510208604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348510450078-29</Id><Title>Romney is just a bush rerun</Title><Msg>Bush : trust me on the WMD and the tax cuts ,we're on the road to riches! details later, trust me! Romney: trust me on the tax cuts on top of the Bush tax cuts and on the increased military spending, i call all this deficit reduction..... trust me...... specifics later!!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348510450078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348511465082-30</Id><Title>Obama is a Bush Rerun</Title><Msg>The only difference is Obama golfs alot more and caters to the 1% WS cronies.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348511465082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348513532560-31</Id><Title>NO! NO! NO!....those demrats shouted it out three times</Title><Msg>Those poor losers don't want the name of GOD on their platform or in their lives. Of course the guy behind the microphone had wax in his ears and obama was braindead on the subject (yea sure). If you don't want GOD in your Life, vote obama and face the consequences....</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1348513532560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348514168876-32</Id><Title>Last year it was Palin, this year it's......</Title><Msg>clint eastwood? lmfao - you jokers think you're fit to run the place?</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1348514168876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348514434751-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt Romney makes millions borrowing huge sums of debt to buy out strugling companies. He then sells off the profitable parts, saddles that company with the loans he borrowed, lays off most of the employees and sets up million $$ "consulting fees" before walking away. Then he shelters the gains offshore and tells the nation it's all fair and he's going to make everyone else better off. paleeeze</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1348514434751</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348515883137-34</Id><Title>Obama promises TAXES ARE GOING UP for everyone</Title><Msg>For everyone who pays taxes, the Bush tax cuts expire and Obama promises not to extend them any further. If Obama is re-elected, taxes are going up. If Romney gets in, Bush tax cuts will be extended. That's why Romney really only matters to the 53% of people who actually pay taxes instead of the 47% living on gubment handouts.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348515883137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348517978733-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama promises TAXES ARE GOING UP for everyone</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348515883137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'60 Minutes' explains 'overboard' omission 8 Comments (105) By DYLAN BYERS | 9/24/12 11:29 AM EDT One day after the '60 Minutes' interviews with President Barack Obama and former Gov. Mitt Romney, one of the most talked-about quote is from an excerpt that wasn't even included in last night's broadcast. In a portion of the interview posted online, the president told CBS's Steve Kroft that his campaign's ads sometimes went "overboard" and that the campaign sometimes made"mistakes" -- an admission the Romney campaign jumped on immediately late Sunday night, issuing a statement saying the president had "repeatedly shown a reckless disregard for the truth." The press -- from the Washington Post to the Wall Street Journal to CNN -- also jumped on the comment, while conservative outlets like The Weekly Standard knocked CBS for not airing the clip. "[C]uriously enough, the news magazine show did not air a clip of Obama admitting to interviewer Steve Kroft that some of his campaign ads contain mistakes and that some even 'go overboard,' the Standard's Daniel Halper wrote. The decision is not curious, according to the network, which filled the hour with excerpts from the two interviews and was happy to promote content online. "We covered a lot of ground with both men and we're happy to be able to put some of that material on our popular Web cast 60MinutesOvertime," Kevin Tedesco, a spokesperson for '60 Minutes' and CBS News told POLITICO.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348517978733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348518228622-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare... the "anti-jobs" entitlement</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348507971847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'it DOESN'T reduce the "employers" portion, which the employer might otherwise use to justify adding ====================================================================== employees.' An employer doesn't use spare cash on hand to add employees!!! He puts it in his pocket. The only time he adds employees is when he thinks he can increase production (and hence profits) by hiring. The reason trickle down doesn't work is because give the "job creators" tax cuts and they put the money in their pockets (or send it to an non-taxable off shore bank). The sad thing is, as you say, that improving the lot of the poor is not as stimulative as it once was. If they were to spend it on food, clothing and shelter, it would be stimulative. But to the extent that it instead goes for big screens TV's and Smart phones, etc., it stimulates the economy of China.</Msg><Username>economist_too</Username><Timestamp>1348518228622</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348519455545-37</Id><Topic><Title>Last year it was Palin, this year it's......</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1348514168876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Either one of those patriots would be infinitely better than the lying radical POS Pig sitting in the White House today, f'ing over the Country and conning the stupid gullible Mice of America!! Nonetheless, when Pigs are jumping from their Park Ave and Knob Hill windows after an Obama win and the rest of his stupid swine are in soup lines begging for a chicken wing and a cup of broth, you won't be laughing face down in a ditch for very long!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1348519455545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348519605814-38</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare... the "anti-jobs" entitlement</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348507971847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Socialists coined the term "trickle down" as a derogatory term to justify the notion that someone who builds a profitable business just takes the money and hoards it... ... rather than doing what allowed him to build a profitable business in the first place... which was to deploy the capital into financial and human (eg: employees) leverage to magnify his efforts. When socialists such as yourself argue that "they're going to take it and hoarde it anyway so we may as well tax the cr@p out of them"... you're arguing that if the average entrapreneur or corporation was taxed less, that they wouldn't view that as an incentive to build their business further and employ people along the way. Bottom line: Low taxes and rewarding the deployment of risk capital builds successful economies and high taxes and the punishment of risk capital (eg: Obama's approach) tears down otherwise successful economies... ... to suggest otherwise is to ignore the thousands of lessons that 100 years of economic history has taught us... right down to the low U.S. taxes 100 years ago that built our country's wealth... to the ocean of entitlements and historically ominous taxes of today that have given us no jobs, massive deficits and a capital base that is fleeing offshore to escape them. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348519605814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348519744157-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare... the "anti-jobs" entitlement</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348507971847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sure are stupid. FYI the gop tax plan wants to eliminate the home mortgage tax deduction.., you know ,stupid, for what you call broadening the tax base.......... and fyi , you stupid liar, most capital gains on the sale of a house are already exempt from income taxes... $500K profit on the sale of a home for a couple is exempt from taxation now..... jeez...</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348519744157</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348519965049-40</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is just a bush rerun</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348510450078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:14:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who would trust Romney who does not do as he preaches and show ten years of tax returns? Or who banks in tax evasion Cayman islands.? Or who obviously window dressed his 2011 tax return......</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348519965049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348520355049-41</Id><Topic><Title>republicans kill veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348146674466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:11:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McConnell: No jobs for vets. Senate Republicans decided to give the finger to veterans, using a procedural vote to kill the Veterans Jobs Corp Act, Typical gop 100% for sending the troop into iraq a $trillion paid for with tax cuts for the rich. but only 1% of them for a veterans jobs bill to help vets when they get home, a bill costing 1 billion a year for five years and paid for............. gop kills jobs for vets to get romney elected,,, what a disgrace</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348520355049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348520465088-42</Id><Title>Romney the tax preacher ( who offshores jobs and offshores his money)</Title><Msg>who would listen to a preacher that does not do as he preaches and show ten years of tax returns? Or who banks in tax evasion Cayman islands.? Or who obviously window dressed his 2011 tax return...... Kinda like listening to the preacher in church that everyone knows is a drunk and diddling some of the gals in the choir</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348520465088</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:01:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348524427814-43</Id><Topic><Title>Last year it was Palin, this year it's......</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1348514168876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take Hemlock Pig!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1348524427814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348525253536-44</Id><Topic><Title>Last year it was Palin, this year it's......</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1348514168876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is ANOTHER corpiss id......I can SMELL them.</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348525253536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348525450547-45</Id><Topic><Title>Last year it was Palin, this year it's......</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1348514168876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Signed corpisss one of many id's</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348525450547</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348525844854-46</Id><Topic><Title>Obama promises TAXES ARE GOING UP for everyone</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348515883137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You stinking dummy! Reagan, as he tripled debt and bg#$%$group as they doubled debt guaranteed TAXES went UP for everyone you dumb F! Repubs don't quite understand that debt must be paid off because they're all soooooooo used to declaring bankruptcy. F runners. f that other old dead repub here(pauper #$%$ buffoon) and f all repubs.</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348525844854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348528793626-47</Id><Title>Bumps In The Road</Title><Msg>That's what 4 American lives means to Obama. You can take Obama out of Chicago but you can't take Chicago out of Obama. Shootings and bodies laying all over Chicago, just bumps in the road, literally.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348528793626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529830947-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama promises TAXES ARE GOING UP for everyone</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348515883137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i do you figure? I pay taxes, and will not vote for that #$%$ Romney</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1348529830947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529960285-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama promises TAXES ARE GOING UP for everyone</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348515883137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what struct me in the interviews is that Romney can't run a campaign on ideas - just bashes Obama. He wasn't pressed very hard when asked for what programs he would make cuts to. just allot of fluff.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1348529960285</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:39:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530145739-50</Id><Topic><Title>Last year it was Palin, this year it's......</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1348514168876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clinton delivered big time for Obama - totally nailed it while Clint Eastwood......spoke to an empty chair?? and the gop would have you believe it's one of their finer moments and after getting caught on tape dissing 47% of the country - maybe it was.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1348530145739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348532224327-51</Id><Topic><Title>Romney the tax preacher ( who offshores jobs and offshores his money)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348520465088</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:01:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read an interesting article about the only sport shoe company that still makes it's shoes wholly in the U. S. New Balance. They were worried about the Kenyan's plan to reward the Viet Cong for killing American service men and keeping several thousand as prisoners after the shooting stopped by letting them import these types of shoes duty free into the U.S. They said that if he did they would probably go out of business. He's so great at issuing "Executive Orders" why doesn't he issue one placing a large tariff on slave labor goods made in foreign countries that compete with the American workers goods. You and I both know why. The Kenyan is in bed with those that make huge profits from slave labor. His buddies such as George Soros have boasted that they will "Bring America Down".</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348532224327</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:17:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348533005764-52</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... and the only way Romney and Bain capital could profit by their efforts to buy them and turn them around is if he increased their value. If Romney weren't able to increase their value, both Romney and Bain capital would not have done as well as they did. In many cases, Bain laid off employees... but in those cases, all of the employees of those companies were at risk if the company were to fail and it was better for those that remained to be a part of a company that was viable. I have worked for and invested in private equity... you are completely wrong about the impact of private equity firms on the companies they buy and usually improve on (there are exceptions like there is in any such venture). America is deep in debt, spending like a drunken sailor, and facing a fiscal cliff... ... just like the companies that Romney was so succesful in working to fix... just like every Olympics before Romney ran one. No presidential candidate in American history is more vocationally qualified to fix EXACTLY the impending bankruptcy our nation now faces (remember, in 3 years, our debt-to-GDP ratio will equal Greece's). For 4 years, all Obama has done in pile on entitlements and kick the can down the road... ... 4 more years of that, and we're Greece. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348533005764</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 20:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348536292806-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama: I'm 'eye candy' for women of 'The View' 23 Comments (155) By JOSH GERSTEIN | 9/24/12 7:00 PM EDT NEW YORK—President Barack Obama and First Lady Michelle Obama bantered playfully and held hands Monday during a taping of the female-oriented talk show, "The View," giving no indication of second thoughts about the appearance despite criticism that the president was blowing off international diplomacy in order to take part in the often-fluffy daytime gabfest. "I told folks I'm just supposed to be eye candy here for you guys," President Obama said during a back-and-forth about him being the only man on the program. The show's five co-hosts are women.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1348536292806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348539237998-54</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(CNN) -- Nearly half of the nation's states have new voting measures that could stop some Illegals from heading to the polls in November, a civil rights group said Monday. "This year, an unprecedented number of voting restrictions impose barriers to voting that disproportionately affect the illegal community," said a report from Advancement Project, which has also sued to block such voting measures in a number of states. Monday's report from the organization, which pushes to protect voting rights, was the latest volley in a national battle over such measures that splits largely along party lines. Advancement Project's report points to three different types of efforts in 23 states that it says will impact illegal voters: efforts to purge rolls of non-citizen voters, proof of citizenship requirements for voter registration and photo ID laws. Campaigns battle over narrow groups of voters It is difficult to calculate exactly how many illegals could be affected, Katherine Culliton-Gonzalez, director of voter protection for Advancement Project, told reporters in a conference call Monday.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1348539237998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348539281405-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>September 24, 2012 7:32 PM Print Text For Obama, diplomacy gets back seat to campaign comments 119 inShare More By Nancy Cordes Play CBS News Video (CBS News) UNITED NATIONS HEADQUATERS, New York - President Obama arrived in New York Monday afternoon for the United Nations General Assembly. One of the main topics of discussion at this annual meeting will be the recent unrest outside U.S. embassies in the Muslim world, including an attack in Benghazi, Libya, which claimed the lives of four Americans. But unlike years past, the president will not be sitting down with any of the more than 120 world leaders who are here in New York. Simply put, the White House is prioritizing the president's reelection effort. Most heads of state will be here all week, but the president will be in New York less than 24 hours, and even then will spend most of his time away from this conference. After landing in New York Monday afternoon, the president headed straight for a sit-down -- not with visiting leaders, but with the ladies of "The View," for an interview to air tomorrow. Last year at the U.N. General Assembly, President Obama held 13 one-on-one meetings with major leaders. Obama quips on The View: I'm just "eye candy" U.N. envoy sounds regional alarm over Syria war Obama has no meetings scheduled with foreign leaders at U.N. General Assembly Turmoil looms over U.N. meeting of world leaders But this year diplomacy is taking a back seat to campaigning, despite a worsening civil war in Syria, rising tensions between Israel and Iran, and the recent attack in Libya.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348539281405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348542620538-56</Id><Title>Republicans look for voter fraud, find little</Title><Msg>Repubs!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! For years right here you #$%$ claimed there was all sorts of voter fraud and that's why you wanted to prevent people from voting. I always knew you just wanted less voting. You stink on ice and have never actually believed in American values..you're fakes.</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348542620538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348542830404-57</Id><Title>Morning-after pills available at 13 NYC schools</Title><Msg>GREAT IDEA!!!!!!!!....whatever it takes.... you db's!</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348542830404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348543012964-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You gd lying #$%$ republican pos.</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348543012964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348544165786-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Taxing the Rich VS Broadening the Base</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348243347087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The way Mitt "saved" the Salt Lake Olympics, was by getting the biggest "donation" ever from the Feds. If he were Pres. from whom could he get a "donation" to save the Country???</Msg><Username>dumb_quest</Username><Timestamp>1348544165786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>