<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-02"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346590378910-1</Id><Title>Romney fails the Commander in Chief Test</Title><Msg>Ret. USAF Col. Klass: Romney Failing the Commander in Chief Test Now some of this is perfectly rational. Why mention the war in Iraq when the president who started it is also unmentionable. And, if mentioned, it would have to be acknowledged that President Barack Obama ended that war. And worse, in a torrent of claims of Obama's broken promises, it would not do to highlight that he kept his promise to end that war. But you would think that Mr. Romney might acknowledge that we still have a war going on in Afghanistan and that young Americans are still dying there. But then he might have to mention President Obama's decisions to increase troop strength and his strategy to wind down that too long conflict, while he has criticism but no alternative. The promise thing also nixes mentioning alQaeda or, quiet now, Bin Laden. People might remember that Mr. Romney said that it did not make sense to spend millions to get "one man" or, worse, that the President kept his promise and did it. Failure to acknowledge this nation's debt to veterans also raises awkward questions about promises kept. President Obama pledged to fulfill the "sacred trust" between the nation and our veterans. It would not be helpful to mention that promise was kept by the largest increases in the Department of Veterans' Affairs budgets in years, appropriations Congressman Ryan voted against. And someone might notice that Mr. Ryan also voted against the New GI Bill of Rights that is honoring today's veterans with educational opportunities akin to those that sent their grandfathers to college after WWII. It would also not do for someone to mention that the word "veteran" does not appear in Mr. Ryan's budget that is supposed to outline a future for America. I suppose it is possible for Mr. Ryan to imagine an American future without veterans. I cannot. And, though a mumbling Clint Eastwood could be tolerated, mentioning ending "don't ask, don't tell" would get you booed off the stage. So Mr. Romney and Mr. Ryan, when you are asking whether we are better off today than four years ago, I have some suggestions of some people to ask. Ask military members and their families if they are better off without multiple tours to Iraq and painful family separations. Ask veterans if they are better off with the educational opportunities offered by the New GI bill of Rights. Ask the vets who were excluded from earned veterans' care by the policies of the unmentionable previous president. Ask the spouses who have found it easier to transfer professional credentials to new duty station states due to the work of Michelle Obama and Dr. Jill Biden. Ask the formerly homeless vets who have been the beneficiaries of another Obama promise kept. And, stealthily of course, no sense stirring up the bigots, ask the thousands of gay and lesbian servicemen if they are better off not having to live a lie."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346590378910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346592170979-2</Id><Title>sleazebag Ralph Reed and sleazy item in the GOP platform</Title><Msg>Ralph Reed in the Marianas Trenches Bill Moyers and Michael Winship from the official GOP platform : "No minimum wage for the Mariana Islands. “The Pacific territories should have flexibility to determine the minimum wage, which has seriously restricted progress in the private sector.” ..........Which brings us to that curious Mariana Islands minimum wage plank in the Republican platform. Some years ago, our government made an effort to clean up sweatshops on the islands — including Saipan — that have been under the control of the United States since the end of World War II. Chinese women were brought over to the islands to work under awful conditions — subject to forced abortions and prostitution and paid pennies for producing garments labeled “Made in the USA.” Corrupt local officials hired the firm of infamous lobbyist Jack Abramoff — for more than four million dollars — to try to stop the reforms proposed back in Washington. Abramoff, in turn, hired Ralph Reed and his political direct mail company, Millennium Marketing, to conduct a phony grass roots campaign urging Alabama Christians to write their local congressman to oppose the reforms. Of course, Reed didn’t tell those Christians he was being paid to help keep running sweatshops that exploited women. Instead, he told them the reforms were a trick orchestrated by the left and organized labor. Limits on Chinese workers would keep them from being “exposed to the teachings of Jesus Christ.” His company explained it was just trying to encourage “grass roots citizens to promote the propagation of the Gospel”..............................................</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346592170979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 09:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346594261885-3</Id><Title>Ryan is such a liar</Title><Msg>"Another supremely dishonest moment was Ryan’s criticism of how Obama dealt with the Simpson-Bowles debt panel: “He created a bipartisan debt commission. They came back with an urgent report. He thanked them, sent them on their way, and then did exactly nothing.” Lordy. Ryan failed to mention that he was a member of the Simpson-Bowles commission. He also failed to mention that he was part of a minority of panel members who flatly rejected the “urgent report” he now blasts Obama for ignoring. That report, you see, endorsed a balanced approach including not only budget cuts but also revenue increases. Can’t have that."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346594261885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 09:57:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599928000-4</Id><Topic><Title>If The Media Freaks Of MSNBC, CNN, ABC, CBS &amp; The NY Times Say!!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346445236000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i heard it was good, bad and ugly that kind of speech works well at the Academy Awards, but when you represent someone trying to become President, it's risky business</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1346599928000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346599989000-5</Id><Topic><Title>If The Media Freaks Of MSNBC, CNN, ABC, CBS &amp; The NY Times Say!!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346445236000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"These sons of beetches have ZERO connection to real hard-working decent Americans" you're referring to the Romney family....right?</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1346599989000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 11:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346610731228-6</Id><Title>The Obama's are planning to move to Hawaii in January</Title><Msg>Barack and Michelle Obama will be moving to Hawaii in January of 2013 and preparations are now being made to purchase an estate in close proximity to land owned by the University of Hawaii, where the Obama presidential library and “political center” will be located. Here in Chicago, it’s pretty obvious that Michelle does not want to move back to this city and its winters (for any reason) and Michelle’s mother, who’s been living in the White House with her daughter and her family, will be happily making the move to Hawaii as well. ******* With what earned income are the Obama's buying a Hawaiian estate?</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346610731228</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346613033000-7</Id><Topic><Title>If The Media Freaks Of MSNBC, CNN, ABC, CBS &amp; The NY Times Say!!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346445236000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney has created and employed TENS of thousands of hard working men and women in good jobs! Your boy Obama, a half-baked law professor and mob organizer, has employed no one but Jackshyt!! Indeed, he told us that his Big Spending Stimulus would cut Unemployment to well under 6% by now!! It's well over 8% and climbing HIGHER!!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346613033000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346621778126-8</Id><Title>Bill Maher rips on the gop conveniently forgetting most of the entire Bush presidency</Title><Msg>"On Friday night, while you may have heard about Bill Maher ripping into the many, many lies of Dinesh D'Souza to his face, his final New Rule ripped the Republican Party for holding a convention and conveniently forgetting just about the entire Bush presidency. Here's the full transcript of that rule. And finally, New Rule: Republicans don't have to accept evolution, economics, climatology, or human sexuality, but I just watched a week of their national convention, and I need them to admit the historical existence of George W. Bush. (audience applause) If your party can run the nation for eight years, and then have a national convention and not invite Bush, Cheney, Rumsfeld, Colin Powell, Karl Rove, or Tom DeLay... (audience applause) you're not a political movement, you're the witness protection program. In fact, Republicans, next time, instead of holding a convention without your most recent President, your most recent Vice-President, your most recent Vice-Presidential nominee, and most of the runners-up from your most recent primary, why not just wave one of those Men in Black memory eraser wands in our face, and make us forget everything we know about you? (audience applause)</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346621778126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346625782143-9</Id><Title>Avatars seem to be all gone</Title><Msg>Big thing a few years ago.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346625782143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346630606000-10</Id><Title>Obama Not Up To The Job</Title><Msg>In all his time, he has not improved a thing. He is done. We have to let him go. On the golf circuit. LOL</Msg><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1346630606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346635101063-11</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Maher rips on the gop conveniently forgetting most of the entire Bush presidency</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346621778126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:36:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton on Obama: 'A Few Years Ago, This Guy Would Have Been Carrying Our Bags' 5:51 PM, Sep 2, 2012 • By DANIEL HALPER Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts Former President Bill Clinton tried to get former senator Ted Kennedy to endorse Hillay Clinton for president in the 2008 election by describing Barack Obama this way: "A few years ago, this guy would have been carrying our bags." This anecdote is revealed in a New Yorker article on the relationship between Bill Clinton and Obama: Tim Russert told me that, according to his sources, Bill Clinton, in an effort to secure an endorsement for Hillary from Ted Kennedy, said to Kennedy, “A few years ago, this guy would have been carrying our bags.” Clinton is giving a keynote address at the Democratic convention this week in Charlotte, North Carolina.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346635101063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:18:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346638394141-12</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Maher rips on the gop conveniently forgetting most of the entire Bush presidency</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346621778126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:36:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still expect Biden to step down as VP and Hillary to get drafted in as VP. More "diversity" for the ticket and fits Obama's "GOPs War on Women" theme.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346638394141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346638732532-13</Id><Topic><Title>oh, and comrades, they did this before, same format!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1346535234193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:33:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am VERY suspicious that this change was made about 66 days before election day. Right now it just by chance happens to suppress political activity on this (and a few other) message boards. WHAT A COINCIDENCE!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346638732532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:18:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346643460638-14</Id><Topic><Title>Romney fails the Commander in Chief Test</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346590378910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:52:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you type all this Obamanure by yourself?</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346643460638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346643615662-15</Id><Title>Another Obamanure Board!!!!!</Title><Msg>Nice!!!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346643615662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346643700920-16</Id><Title>Obamanure fails the Commander in Chief Test</Title><Msg>Too much to shovel in so little time!!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346643700920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346643961597-17</Id><Title>How much Obamanure this week?</Title><Msg>?????????</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346643961597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>