<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350641727344-1</Id><Title>not optimal</Title><Msg>Obama on Libya: 4 Americans killed is not optimal. Rather anti-septic. And the libs want us to be upset over "binders."</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1350641727344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 06:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350647252369-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why did Candy crowley have a transcript of Obamas Rose Gaerden Speech?</Title><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1350528764860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 22:52:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Candy Crowley’s Debate Moderation Exemplifies Why Americans Do Not Trust Their Media video by Noah Rothman | 8:42 am, October 17th, 2012 » 697 comments On Monday, I wrote that it would be wrong to prejudge CNN host Candy Crowley before she turned in her performance as a debate moderator. Just the week prior, ABC reporter Martha Raddatz was preemptively criticized for inviting President Barack Obama to attend her wedding in the 1990s, but she ended up being a straight moderator who advanced the vice presidential debate admirably. I wanted to extend the benefit of the doubt to Crowley, to not preemptively criticize her before she was worthy of criticism. Well, the verdict is in and criticism is entirely warranted. My singular take away moment of last night’s debate was one that elevated Crowley from moderator to debate participant. Crowley shot from the hip and echoed a talking point from the Obama campaign regarding their handling of the Libya attack to criticize Mitt Romney mid-debate. What’s more? She was wrong. Crowley did her profession a disservice last night and confirmed many Americans deepest suspicions about the media in the process. RELATED: Candy Crowley: Romney ‘Right’ That Obama Didn’t Call Libya Terror, But Thought ‘He Picked The Wrong Word’ During the debate, when President Obama was challenged – as his administration has been for weeks – about the White House’s handling of the attacks in Libya, he bristled with indignation over the suggestion that he was taking this attack with anything but the utmost seriousness. Romney responded by criticizing the president for his administration’s efforts to create the public impression that the attacks in Libya arose from a series of demonstrations against an offensive YouTube video. He accused the president and his administration of refusing to call the attack in Libya an act of terrorism for nearly two weeks. Obama objected and told him to look at the transcript. Crowley, rather than moderate the exchange, jumped into the fray and said that Obama had, in fact, called the incident terrorism. The timeline of events regarding Libya is clear. After weeks of the president’s surrogates, and the president himself on programs like Late Night with David Letterman and at the United Nations, saying the Libya attack resulted from a spontaneous demonstration, the story began to unravel. Drip by drip, it became clear that security at the consulate was lax, the station had come under attack before and there was never any demonstration outside the Benghazi consulate. Knowing they were caught in a distortion of the truth, the Obama campaign began pointing to the president’s Rose Garden address on the day after the 9/11/12 attacks to show that his administration had always referred unambiguously to Libya as an act of terrorism. “No acts of terror will ever shake the resolve of this great nation, alter that character or eclipse the light of the values that we stand for,” said Obama in the Rose Garden on September 12, after two paragraphs of recounting how Americans responded to the attacks of September 11, 2001. The Obama campaign, knowing that they had advanced a false narrative for weeks and were being called on it, found the word “terror” in his initial response and relied on that speech to show that the president had known the Libya attack was terror all along. This is wildly offensive to everyone who followed the story closely. The president seemed to think that he could perhaps get away with it if he had the assistance of complicit journalists who would not fact check that hard. He could not have known the kind of gift he would receive from Candy Crowley — amid a presidential debate, no less. Following the debate, Crowley appeared on her network where she shrugged and half-heartedly admitted that Romney was correct – that the Obama administration never described the Libya attack as a terrorist act and that they spent the better part of a month trying to convince the nation that what happened in Benghazi was anything but a premeditated assault. Crowley’s instincts in the moment led her to chastise Romney because she felt “he used the wrong word.” It was a shameful display and an indictment of so much of what is wrong with the media today. Broadly, it is also the reason why so few Americans trust the fourth estate –reporting means never having to say you’re sorry. Sometimes engaging in inaccurate opinion journalism does require a correction.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1350647252369</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 07:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350648143259-3</Id><Topic><Title>not optimal</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1350641727344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 06:15:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right.... getting assassinated due to unconscionable decisions by fools in the Obama Regime, followed by a massive cover-up... is never "Optimal"! But for Obama... it is Normal!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1350648143259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350648476489-4</Id><Title>The Country Is F'ing Nuts!</Title><Msg>Our clueless useless Justice System screwing around with some butchering Islamic Pig's (Nadal Hassan) hairdo is incredible! Put a bullet in his GD head and throw him to the fish!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1350648476489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350648959708-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Country Is F'ing Nuts!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1350648476489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:07:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kumbaya libs ain't gonna like you.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350648959708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350649283076-6</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt: promise to keep your promises</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350597956365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 18:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just read it again. You'll get it.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350649283076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350649521759-7</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt: promise to keep your promises</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350597956365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 18:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Romney’s Go-To Economist” .....was known as the principal architect of the Bush tax cuts.” In that capacity, and after returning to Columbia, Hubbard was also the chief cheerleader for a runaway derivatives market that spiraled out of control and left the Great Recession in its wake......... ......</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350649521759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350649736910-8</Id><Title>Mitt's economic guru was a principal architect of the Bush tax cuts</Title><Msg>(the tax cuts that turned a projected $6 trillion surplus into a $5.6 trillion deficit. I told you Romney is just a rerun of Bush) “Romney’s Go-To Economist” read the headline on a New York Times profile of the dean of Columbia University’s Business School, which notes that “During a stint as chairman of the Council of Economic Advisers for President George W. Bush, from 2001 to 2003, Mr. Hubbard was known as the principal architect of the Bush tax cuts.” In that capacity, and after returning to Columbia, Hubbard was also the chief cheerleader for a runaway derivatives market that spiraled out of control and left the Great Recession in its wake. While pocketing millions in fees from the financial industry that he was ostensibly studying as a neutral academic, Hubbard was an enthusiastic backer of the virtues of a burgeoning unregulated capital market that sold toxic derivatives to the world. In a landmark paper that he co-wrote in November 2004 with William C. Dudley, at the time the chief U.S. economist at Goldman Sachs, it was asserted, “The capital markets have helped facilitate a major transformation of the U.S. mortgage financing system over the past 25 years. … The result has been a dramatic decline in the cyclical volatility of housing activity.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350649736910</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350651189580-9</Id><Topic><Title>Rommitt says he will close the deficit and give tax breaks</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1350606983490</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 20:36:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mittens is going it increase spending too, or hadn't you heard him speak from both his faces, one saying the government doesn't create jobs, the other saying that the military can't be cut because that will cost jobs........also no cuts to medicare..... so there you go, two of the biggest budget items no cuts.......... If mitt wins i will just have to lump it and take my new tax cuts plus the mitt promises full as is, no cuts to medicare and social security..........all that .. plus increased military spending......sure doesn't sound like deficit reduction to me.......... are you sure it adds up?......... what are the details of his spending cuts again?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350651189580</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:53:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350652744304-10</Id><Title>demand creates jobs</Title><Msg>the many are poorer , the few got richer............ the many are broke and can't buy more ....so there is no demand and no new jobs created......... Will mitt make them poorer by cutting food stamps and UE insurance? Then there will be even less demand and jobs will be lost. sure mitt is going to build submarines and that government spending will create some jobs, but it will be paid for with tax cuts so the deficit will go up.</Msg><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1350652744304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350652751199-11</Id><Title>demand creates jobs</Title><Msg>the many are poorer , the few got richer............ the many are broke and can't buy more ....so there is no demand and no new jobs created......... Will mitt make them poorer by cutting food stamps and UE insurance? Then there will be even less demand and jobs will be lost. sure mitt is going to build submarines and that government spending will create some jobs, but it will be paid for with tax cuts so the deficit will go up.</Msg><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1350652751199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350653095738-12</Id><Topic><Title>demand creates jobs</Title><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1350652751199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Government creates an environment that encourages job creation. Obama has created an environment that obstructs job creation through high taxes and threats of higher taxes, excessive regulation and threats of more regulation and lawsuits, FDA and EPA red tape and obstructionism, high deficit spending, excessive government overhead -- he's created the Greek and Spanish economy in the USA. Throw the bas*tud out! And... IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350653095738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:24:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350654911485-13</Id><Topic><Title>not optimal</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1350641727344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 06:15:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This statement can only leave you speechless unless of course someone like Bush had said it... then libs would be pointing out how completely asinine and out of touch with reality it is. (personally it is obscene... completely offensive) But Obumbler said it... so libs wont comment... how did Stewart even let it go? It just becomes another bullet (thanks Joe Biden) that Romney has for his gun next week The only reply the Obama should have had to the question was to hang his head in shame... kinda like he looked like at the first debate</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1350654911485</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350655584948-14</Id><Topic><Title>demand creates jobs</Title><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1350652751199</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the threats of higher taxation over 4 years has influenced every business owner I know.</Msg><Username>simms7292</Username><Timestamp>1350655584948</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350656284451-15</Id><Title>Romney ahead 52 to 45 in newest poll!</Title><Msg>Real Clear Politics has Romney ahead in the Electoral College! Meanwhile, Obama says that having our ambassador murdered in a terrorist attack, "is not optimal." It's all over but the voting on Nov 6!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350656284451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350656297277-16</Id><Title>Fidel Castro is dead</Title><Msg>Fidel Castro Reportedly Close to ‘Neurovegetative State’ After Stroke, But Not Dead Yet Fidel Castro death rumors are like the Nigerian e-mail scam of the news cycle — they've been around forever and are never going away. This time it's really close. He's a vegetable. According to the Miami Herald, Castro is in a "neurovegetative state" — not quite dead, but close. Former Cuban leader Fidel Castro suffered a cerebral hemorrhage and his state of health is so precarious that he has trouble feeding, speaking and recognizing people, said a Venezuelan physician who assured El Nuevo Herald that he has access to firsthand sources and information. "He suffered an embolic stroke and recognizes absolutely no one," said José Marquina, a respected doctor who in the past has claimed to have direct information about the illness affecting President Hugo Chávez of Venezuela. "The people with a condition of this nature have difficulty eating and, of course, they end up with total deficit in their neurologic capacities." The Herald also reported that Hugo Chávez flew to Castro's home this week to check on his health, but he's probably there because his cancer as entered the final stage. Also just in, breaking news, Generalissimo Francisco Franco IS STILL DEAD!. Things are looking up!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350656297277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:18:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350656700035-17</Id><Topic><Title>Romney ahead 52 to 45 in newest poll!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350656284451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama says that having our ambassador murdered in a terrorist attack, "is not optimal." *** He didn't want to call the Fort Hood shooting a terrorist attack either. That was hushed up. The North Korean lib media also hushed up the daily body count for Obama. More American troops have died under 3 1/2 years of Obama dictatorship than under 8 years of Bush. It's now referred to as the Bush-Obama doctrine. How many Americans have died due to terrorist attacks on American soil under the Obama regime. The Lib media won't tell you. Obama has failed to keep Americans safe. Now, he wants to cut the military budget and let al Queda re-establish. Great idea bozo. You're going the wrong way. The Mooslim Brotherhood took over in Egypt replacing our corrupt ally Mubarak. He's following Helen Thomas' last wish: Just let the Mooslims win.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350656700035</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350657197755-18</Id><Title>Having Barack Obama as President is *not optimal* for America!</Title><Msg>Not optimal for our economy! Not optimal for our military! Not optimal for our foreign policy! Not optimal for our people (rich, middle class or poor)! Not optimal for America!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350657197755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350657307508-19</Id><Topic><Title>Fidel Castro is dead</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350656297277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:18:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barack Obama and the Left will fly our flag at half-mast and have three days of mourning.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350657307508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350657529411-20</Id><Topic><Title>not optimal</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1350641727344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 06:15:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our First Affirmative Action President is not optimal for the USA. Mitt Romney is a successful man with unique talents and skills to lead us in these difficult times!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350657529411</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350657689296-21</Id><Topic><Title>Romney ahead 52 to 45 in newest poll!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350656284451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, yes &amp; Yes!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350657689296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350658127047-22</Id><Title>'He didn't want to call the Fort Hood shooting a terrorist attack either'.......</Title><Msg>It looks like Yoho hit the nail on the head with that observation</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1350658127047</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:48:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350659623196-23</Id><Topic><Title>Romney ahead 52 to 45 in newest poll!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350656284451</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Election 2012: Virginia President Virginia: Romney 50%, Obama 47% Sign up for free daily updates Friday, October 19, 2012 Mitt Romney has now hit the 50% mark in Virginia. The latest Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of Likely Virginia Voters, taken two nights after the second presidential debate, shows Romney with 50% support to President Obama’s 47%. Two percent (2%) remain undecided. (To see survey question wording, click here.)</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1350659623196</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350659626178-24</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>robertkozak267</Username><Timestamp>1350581106481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 13:25:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you been to Monte Carlo? Have you played roulette?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350659626178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350660866066-25</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt: promise to keep your promises</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350597956365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 18:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama doesn't know how to balance a budget. He won't make the tough choices. He just wants to be popular and fly around on Air Force One and make speeches. He's good at that. Nancy can write pork barrel spending bills and I'll sell it to the lemmings.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350660866066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350664519501-26</Id><Topic><Title>demand creates jobs</Title><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1350652744304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mitts tax plan and job plan are total horse manure</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1350664519501</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350664578531-27</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's economic guru was a principal architect of the Bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350649736910</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, Mitt is Bush all over again</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1350664578531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350665086100-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's economic guru was a principal architect of the Bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350649736910</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A top liberal commentator called for Eva Longoria's resignation from President Obama's reelection campaign following her retweet of a vulgar message aimed at Mitt Romney. "I think she should resign from the campaign or be asked to resign as co-chair because I don't think it reflects well on the campaign," Alan Colmes said Thursday on Fox News Channel's 'American Live.' Colmes gave his opinion after Eva Longoria retweeted a follower on Wednesday who called the GOP presidential candidate a #$%$" (And not the word that rhymes with "Mitt," the word that rhymes with "swat.") “I have no idea why any woman/minority can vote for Romney. You have to be stupid to vote for such a racist/misogynistic #$%$” the tweet, which Longoria retweeted, read. After sending the nasty message to her 4,462,095 followers, Longoria took some heat, and took to Twitter on Thursday morning to explain. "Is anyone else's twitter bugging out? There are things in my timeline I didn't retweet today. Hmmm? Standby trying to fix!" she tweeted. But later on Thursday, Longoria appeared to come clean and take responsibility. "I use Twitter as a platform for all Americans and their opinions. Sorry if people were offended by retweet," she wrote. "Obviously not my words or my personal view. I respect all Americans #FreedomOfSpeech."</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1350665086100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350665446392-29</Id><Title>big fat lying liar O'Reilly lie about PBS and Bill Moyers</Title><Msg>O'Reilly caught lying as ususal: "O'Reilly bashed PBS for funding lefty agitators like Bill Moyers. "Here's what we get – a $16 trillion debt, and we've gotta pay for Bill Moyers," O'Reilly boomed. He also held up a flash card with a picture of Moyers and the headline, "Why is NPR getting our money?" There are only two problems with O'Reilly's argument: 1. Bill Moyers doesn't work for NPR, and never did. 2. Moyers doesn't get any money from PBS. His show is entirely self-supported by donors. If anything, he supports public television. -Matt Taibbi</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350665446392</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350665605406-30</Id><Topic><Title>I See Blue Skys</Title><Username>margarette_alisa77</Username><Timestamp>1346505181000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:13:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for resurrecting this dead thread. Cuban cigars for everyone! Aren't you glad Obama didn't send a Gitmo terrorist to each state like he planned because 9/11 was really a fake inside job by you know who.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350665605406</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350665767780-31</Id><Topic><Title>Fidel Castro is dead</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350656297277</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:18:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you Geezers whining about, Castro is not Obama and therefore, it is no good for You if Castro lives or dies, #$%$!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350665767780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350665848469-32</Id><Topic><Title>Having Barack Obama as President is *not optimal* for America!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1350657197755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 10:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These last 4 years under the Obama regime have really been "not optimal." To say the least. Obama got dressed up in white tie last night. Romney told him that's how we dress when we sit around the house all day :)</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350665848469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350665851811-33</Id><Title>WHERE IS DB, DROPKICK?</Title><Msg>HE must of got Dropkicked one too many times.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350665851811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350665966622-34</Id><Title>They are still finding oil at BPs Well. Who Would have thought?</Title><Msg>The markets are still rigged. Fukushima is still polluting the Earth … “EAT THE FISH.” AND, KATLA WILL BLOW!!!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350665966622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350666070110-35</Id><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Msg>A war criminal, a financial criminal, as he is the lawless one!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666088305-36</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE IS DB, DROPKICK?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350665851811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Carl... you're back? What happened? Did some sushi put you under the weather or did the new format cause you to leave? I don't like it either but at least it appears Marissa must have fired or re-assigned the censors. Let's see what they do to this post. Have you read Yahoo's handy tips for posting?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350666088305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666401181-37</Id><Topic><Title>They are still finding oil at BPs Well. Who Would have thought?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350665966622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:59:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The markets are still rigged. Fukushima is still polluting the Earth … “EAT THE FISH.” AND, KATLA WILL BLOW!!! *** You are right Carl. Katla is rumbling. 3.2 magnitude earthquake rattles Katla volcano. Could blow any day now. Cracks are showing everywhere. Greece could exit the Euro this weekend. They ran out of the money that was supposed to get them to November after Obama's re-coronation. Spain is trying to hold on just a little bit longer. No one wants to be the pin prick.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350666401181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666406912-38</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you want less of the US involved in the middle east then I suggest you place Obama signs all over your front lawn and put a couple bumper stickers on the old honda you drive cause Romney isn't exactly pumping diplomacy for the middle east with his rhetoric.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1350666406912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666476720-39</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE IS DB, DROPKICK?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350665851811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fidel Castro had a stroke. That silenced him.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350666476720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666615427-40</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE IS DB, DROPKICK?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350665851811</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my guess is that yahoo is losing a bundle on this format change. the bulk of the posts now are spamers pumping stock advice.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1350666615427</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666950562-41</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Florida: Romney 51%, Obama 46% Mitt Romney has taken his biggest lead of the year in Florida and now outpaces President Obama by five points in the key swing state following Tuesday night's debate. The latest Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of Likely Florida Voters finds Romney with 51% support to Obama’s 46%. One percent (1%) prefers some other candidate, and two percent (2%) remain undecided. (To see survey question wording, click here.) Florida now moves from a Toss-Up to Leans Romney in the Rasmussen Reports Electoral College Projections. Last week, Romney held a slightly narrower 51% to 47% lead. Prior to that time, the candidates have been within two points of each other in Florida in every survey since April. Ninety-five percent (95%) of likely voters in the Sunshine State say they are certain to vote in this year’s election. Among these voters, it’s Romney 51%, Obama 47%. Florida allows early voting, and among voters who have already voted, Romney's ahead 51% to 45%. Among those who have yet to vote, 88% say they have already made up their minds which candidate they will vote for. Romney leads 54% to 45% among these voters.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1350666950562</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666972096-42</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'My son is not very optimal - he is very dead': Mother of diplomat killed in Benghazi attack slams Obama's comment on raid President told Jon Stewart, 'If four Americans get killed, it's not optimal' Remarks sparked massive backlash from conservatives on social media Mother of slain diplomat Sean Smith says Obama was 'disrespectful' By Toby Harnden In Washington and Daniel Bates PUBLISHED: 10:49 EST, 19 October 2012 | UPDATED: 11:22 EST, 19 October 2012 Comments (0) Share The mother of an American diplomat killed during a terrorist raid on the U.S. consulate in Benghazi has hit out at Barack Obama for describing the attack as 'not optimal', saying: 'My son is not very optimal - he is also very dead.' During an interview shown on Comedy Central, Obama responded to a question about his administration's confused communication after the assault by saying: 'If four Americans get killed, it’s not optimal.' Speaking exclusively to MailOnline today, Pat Smith, whose son Sean died in the raid, said: 'It was a disrespectful thing to say and I don't think it's right. 'How can you say somebody being killed is not very optimal? I don't think the President has the right idea of the English language.' Read more: http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2220241/Barack-Obama-Benghazi-attack-Mother-diplomat-criticises-Presidents-optimal-comment.html#ixzz29lZ7QWKX Follow us: @MailOnline on Twitter | DailyMail on Facebook</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1350666972096</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666996743-43</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'My son is not very optimal - he is very dead': Mother of diplomat killed in Benghazi attack slams Obama's comment on raid By Toby Harnden In Washington and Daniel Bates PUBLISHED: 10:49 EST, 19 October 2012 | UPDATED: 11:22 EST, 19 October 2012 The mother of an American diplomat killed during a terrorist raid on the U.S. consulate in Benghazi has hit out at Barack Obama for describing the attack as 'not optimal', saying: 'My son is not very optimal - he is also very dead.' During an interview shown on Comedy Central, Obama responded to a question about his administration's confused communication after the assault by saying: 'If four Americans get killed, it’s not optimal.' Speaking exclusively to MailOnline today, Pat Smith, whose son Sean died in the raid, said: 'It was a disrespectful thing to say and I don't think it's right. 'How can you say somebody being killed is not very optimal? I don't think the President has the right idea of the English language.'</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1350666996743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350667154773-44</Id><Topic><Title>Gop can preach about science and tax cuts at the same time, and send you to afghanistan forever and a day</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350423045547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 17:30:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earth is 9,000 years old, says Rep. Paul Broun, who sits on House Science Committee. fellow gop science committee member Aikin agreed and also says women have a miraculous power to fight off a rapist's sperm ..... legitimate rape, the female body has ways to try to shut the whole thing down.......</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350667154773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350667202437-45</Id><Title>the promise bushy and the gop did keep</Title><Msg>they sure got rid of the projected $6trillion surplus...........did their thing and wham a $5 trillion debt is added to the previous $5 trillion. 24 February 2001 "President Bush said Saturday that the most important number in the budget he sends to Congress next week is the $5.6 trillion surplus it projects over the next 10 years. That huge projected surplus provides the underpinning of all the administration's tax-cut and spending plans, Mr. Bush said in his recorded weekly radio address."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350667202437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350667311275-46</Id><Topic><Title>China bosses send letter to employees demading loyalty and full rear end kissing</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350582251109</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 13:44:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>china bosses are like some USA bosses who also sent letters to employees demading loyalty and full rear end kissing</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350667311275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:21:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350667405564-47</Id><Topic><Title>gop to offer cans of 'Aikins' sperm killer as acceptable birth control</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350587354391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:09:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop science is incredible!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350667405564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350668129279-48</Id><Title>will gop throw a tantrum over a Mitten's debt ceiling hike?</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — Mitt Romney's transition team is quietly talking with government officials and "Capitol Hill to develop a plan, if he's elected, to prevent massive cuts to the defense budget and extend tax cuts first passed under President George W. Bush.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350668129279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350668240338-49</Id><Topic><Title>gop to offer cans of 'Aikins' sperm killer as acceptable birth control</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350587354391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:09:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He really meant... just wash it out with a bottle of Coke.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350668240338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350668433790-50</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Carl, This might me Obama and Hillary's or Biden's Iran Contra. Gaddaffi's stockpile of missiles is being shipped Syria. In March 2011 Stevens became the official U.S. liaison to the al-Qaeda-linked Libyan opposition, working directly with Abdelhakim Belhadj of the Libyan Islamic Fighting Group—a group that has now disbanded, with some fighters reportedly participating in the attack that took Stevens' life. In November 2011 The Telegraph reported that Belhadj, acting as head of the Tripoli Military Council, "met with Free Syrian Army [FSA] leaders in Istanbul and on the border with Turkey" in an effort by the new Libyan government to provide money and weapons to the growing insurgency in Syria. Last month The Times of London reported that a Libyan ship "carrying the largest consignment of weapons for Syria … has docked in Turkey." The shipment reportedly weighed 400 tons and included SA-7 surface-to-air anti-craft missiles and rocket-propelled grenades.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350668433790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:40:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350668495217-51</Id><Title>Last 4 years have been "not optimal"</Title><Msg>Prolong the misery. 4 more years. You deserve it.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350668495217</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350668644599-52</Id><Topic><Title>will gop throw a tantrum over a Mitten's debt ceiling hike?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350668129279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:35:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's not doing anything. He's already said, he will veto any attempt to fix the fiscal cliff. And we hit the debt ceiling again right after the election. Here we go again.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350668644599</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350669072550-53</Id><Title>US Weapons Are Going To Hard-Line Jihadists To Syria</Title><Msg>Obama's secret war Last month The Times of London reported that a Libyan ship "carrying the largest consignment of weapons for Syria … has docked in Turkey." The shipment reportedly weighed 400 tons and included SA-7 surface-to-air anti-craft missiles and rocket-propelled grenades. Those heavy weapons are most likely from Muammar Gaddafi's stock of about 20,000 portable heat-seeking missiles—the bulk of them SA-7s—that the Libyan leader obtained from the former Eastern bloc. Reuters reports that Syrian rebels have been using those heavy weapons to shoot down Syrian helicopters and fighter jets. The ship's captain was "a Libyan from Benghazi and the head of an organization called the Libyan National Council for Relief and Support," which was presumably established by the new government. That means that Ambassador Stevens had only one person—Belhadj—between himself and the Benghazi man who brought heavy weapons to Syria. Furthermore, we know that jihadists are the best fighters in the Syrian opposition, but where did they come from? The North Korean Lib media has to keep a lid on this. Katla will blow!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350669072550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350670082014-54</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Carmona apologizes for calling male debate moderator 'prettier' than Crowley 9 Comments (18) By SCOTT WONG | 10/19/12 11:46 AM EDT Arizona Senate candidate Richard Carmona apologized Friday for joking at a debate that the male moderator was “prettier” than Candy Crowley, the veteran female CNN journalist who moderated the presidential debate earlier this week. "I tried to tell a joke to lighten the mood in a debate. I shouldn't have, and I'm sorry,” Carmona, the Democratic nominee, said in a brief statement to POLITICO.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1350670082014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350671825552-55</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL price per share could probably blast off! View why!</Title><Username>robertkozak267</Username><Timestamp>1350581106481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 13:25:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>done well *** Oh no, my friend. Well done. Toasted.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350671825552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350672171319-56</Id><Title>Obama's Libyan Missile Crisis -- Libyan missiles sent to Syria</Title><Msg>More questions on Libya: Three days until the final Obama-vs.-Romney debate -- on the topic of foreign policy -- don’t be surprised if this story gets raised. The AP: “The CIA station chief in Libya reported to Washington within 24 hours of last month's deadly attack on the U.S. Consulate that there was evidence it was carried out by militants, not a spontaneous mob upset about an American-made video ridiculing Islam's Prophet Muhammad, U.S. officials have told The Associated Press. *** BBC reports Libyan ships in Syria unloading dead Gaddaffi's missiles. Was Chris Stevens middle man in deal to send missiles from Libya to Syria? Obama must have been involved. Obama said he alone takes responsibility. Did everyone wake up today and realize that the global recession started back in March?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350672171319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350672415880-57</Id><Title>Tech Wreck</Title><Msg>iPads and iPhones sales have topped out. Global Recession means Tech is Dead. It's discressionary spending. The Web 2.0 Tech Wreck has begun. Short Groupon to zero. Short Zynga and FB to zero. Great ideas in the newsletter.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350672415880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350672531689-58</Id><Title>End of 5th Wave within the 3rd Wave</Title><Msg>Setting up for a 22% drop on Monday -- that would be 3,000 points. Thanks for the hot tip baby.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350672531689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350672605416-59</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the Al Smith hangover. They are shooting the generals. Can you hold this bag for me?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1350672605416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350673656858-60</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why I Am Voting for Mitt Romney Oct 19, 2012 by DORIAN DE WIND, Military Affairs Columnist I am a Democrat. I voted for Barack Obama in 2008. However, this time — after a lot of soul searching and closely examining both candidates and the issues — I have decided to vote for Mitt Romney. Here is why. Because of Romney’s strong support for every Obama administration proposal designed to lift our country from the deep economic and financial crisis it has found itself in during the past four years. Because I know exactly where Romney stands on important issues. For example, his steadfast position on abortion and other women’s issues, his gracious acceptance of an offered binder full of women and his promise to get back with us on the Lilly Ledbetter Fair Pay Act. His principled, rock-solid, unchanging positions on immigration and path to citizenship, gun policy, embryonic stem cell research, his no-tax pledge and so many other important issues. I respect how quickly and fully he shared with the American people every aspect of his personal finances for the past decade, his openness and transparency on all his tax, financial and investment matters. I admire his stated commitment to 100 percent of Americans, including the 47 percent — retirees, veterans, the disabled and the working poor — who have a hard time making ends meet and, therefore, cannot pay their share of taxes. I admire his record of acquiring companies, turning a profit, discarding those companies and giving their employees the opportunity to find even better career opportunities elsewhere. I was especially taken by how Romney immediately came to the support of the President after — even during — a recent national tragedy and how he set politics aside for a while. I found it thoughtful and compassionate of the former governor of Massachusetts to want to share with all Americans a health care plan that worked so well for the people in the state of Massachusetts. While our nation was in the depths of an economic and financial crisis, Romney had the clairvoyance and business instinct to support saving the auto industry and to oppose the Wall Street bailouts. For his solid performance on international issues and the favorable impression he has made on our allies — on the world — during his foreign excursions. For his sound, specific proposals on how to intervene in Syria, prevent Iran from acquiring nuclear weapons and for taking action in other hot spots and crises around the world and for his fresh ideas for ending the Afghanistan War in ways so different and so much more effective from what the present administration is pursuing. I have studied and I believe in his detailed, crystal clear plans to rebound our economy, to cut taxes by $5 trillion, increase our defense budget, create 12 million jobs over the next four years without adding to the deficit. (How can anyone not vote for this man?) I admire Mr. Romney’s patriotism evidenced by his rejoicing every time the unemployment figures have come down, when gas prices came down and every time an economic indicator improved. Also, his obvious disappointment and constructive comments when things went the other way. I am excited about how Romney will protect, preserve and conserve our precious environment and invest in clean, renewable energy. As a retired military, I was touched by his laser-like focus during the Republican National Convention on our military and on the Afghanistan war — a conflict where our troops continue to fight and die in. Finally, having seen Mitt Romney stand firm on his core beliefs, his principles — never wavering, never changing, never hesitating throughout the Republican primaries and now during the last weeks of campaigning and debating — whether his audiences consist of right wing Evangelicals, Tea Party members, Latinos, moderates and independents or just a roomful of wealthy Boca Raton donors, I am convinced that what I see in Mitt Romney the candidate is what I’ll get in Mitt Romney the President.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1350673656858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350674006551-61</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt: promise to keep your promises</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350597956365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 18:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obummer go to economist : Bozo the clown</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350674006551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350674011132-62</Id><Title>if we are in a real indices correction</Title><Msg>then the 30 year chart shows 27 is coming</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1350674011132</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350674165909-63</Id><Topic><Title>will gop throw a tantrum over a Mitten's debt ceiling hike?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350668129279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:35:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is doing nothing and is a nothing. Wait....check that.....he's a community organizer.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350674165909</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350674256814-64</Id><Topic><Title>gop to offer cans of 'Aikins' sperm killer as acceptable birth control</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350587354391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 15:09:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And he's gonna beat the clueless one McCaskill.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350674256814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350674451139-65</Id><Topic><Title>the promise bushy and the gop did keep</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350667202437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:20:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still Bush's fault. Libiots are idiots by nature.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1350674451139</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350680861829-66</Id><Title>turns out mr 'i love ayn rand' paul ryans brother is a cargill executive in china....working with collectivists</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan's Brother is a Cargill Exec in China "Given that Paul Ryan is an acolyte of Ayn Rand, who thundered against "collectivism" and government control, Ryan family events must get tense when Stan Ryan begins extolling the virtues of Chinese agricultural planning"—</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350680861829</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350681161760-67</Id><Title>Earnigs, Revenues and Jobs Falling!!</Title><Msg>Obama's weakest ever Recovery turning into another Great Recession! Democrats are good at making Recessions and Depressions "Great"! America is the only nation to have called the 1930's Depression "Great"... why... because Roosevelt make it Great!! For all the others, it was just another Depression... which they came out of well ahead of America, and America... thanks only to the Germany &amp; Japan!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1350681161760</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350681653612-68</Id><Topic><Title>Earnigs, Revenues and Jobs Falling!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1350681161760</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:12:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree 100% econ_meister. Everything is going down faster than bigpopcomingsoon in a Turkish bathhouse!</Msg><Username>whojadaddy</Username><Timestamp>1350681653612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350682275722-69</Id><Topic><Title>Markets In Panic! Google!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1350580231430</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 13:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We should know we're in trouble when the burrito is a leading economic indicator...</Msg><Username>whojadaddy</Username><Timestamp>1350682275722</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350683983167-70</Id><Title>ugly repubs</Title><Msg>why not just wait a few weeks and see who wins and just #$%$ until.............btw,..I would like to see romn win pop vote and lose EC... that'd be perfect an exatly what you #$%$ deserve..surely then you'd change your minds about ec. f off.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1350683983167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350686376317-71</Id><Title>It's Bush's Fault! It's Clapper's Fault! The CIA Did It! Hillary Made Me Do It!</Title><Msg>Obama... the complete Loser, Liar &amp; Incompetent Fool!!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1350686376317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350686859750-72</Id><Title>reagon "recovery" no better than Obamas in first term you f's</Title><Msg>Repubs are nothing but #$%$ liars.,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1350686859750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350686946735-73</Id><Title>raygon "recovery" no better</Title><Msg>than this one in Obama first term.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1350686946735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350692255038-74</Id><Topic><Title>turns out mr 'i love ayn rand' paul ryans brother is a cargill executive in china....working with collectivists</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350680861829</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:07:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, the great "liberal" Diane Feinstein, Senator from California, owns FOUR corporations in China. She and her husband Berg are billionaires from selling you and I to the Chi-Coms and helping them build trheir military for future war against us. There is a word for that. It starts with T.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1350692255038</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 20:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350693191312-75</Id><Topic><Title>Barrat OBAMA IS A CRIMINAL!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1350666070110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Obama Buying the Election With His Welfare Explosion? Published: Friday, 19 Oct 2012 | 3:36 PM ET Text Size By: Larry Kudlow CNBC Anchor With the unprecedented budget explosion of means-tested, welfare-related entitlements, does Team Obama think it can buy the election? Remember Harry Hopkins, Franklin Roosevelt’s close aid? It was Hopkins who argued tax and tax, spend and spend, elect and elect. Sound familiar? And if I’m not mistaken, the high-tax, anti-rich, big-spending, redistributionist FDR is one of President Barack Obama’s idols. So let’s take a look at some of the recent budget-explosion data points: According to Jeff Sessions, the ranking Republican on the Senate Budget Committee, means-tested welfare programs soared to over $1 trillion last year. The federal government accounted for $750 billion of that, while $250 billion came from the states, which leveraged federal payments into even larger expenses. Between 2008 and 2011, federal welfare payments have jumped 32 percent. Food stamps have surged, with 71 percent more spending on the program in 2011 compared with 2008. Health payments, principally Medicaid, have climbed 37 percent. By the way, it’s not just the deep recession and weak recovery that’s driving up these programs. It’s a substantial eligibility expansion, which started under George W. Bush, but has gone much further under President Obama. (Read More: Kudlow: Romney Trouncing Obama in 'This' Critical Area.) In a larger budget context, reporter Jeffrey H. Anderson uses a Treasury Department study to chronicle the 7-Eleven presidency. In fiscal year 2012, ending Sept. 30, the government spent nearly $11 for every $7 of revenues taken in. The exact figures are $2.5 trillion in tax revenues and $3.5 trillion in spending. In other words, it spent 44 percent more than it had coming in. Previous fiscal years look even worse: The government spent 56 percent more than revenues in fiscal year 2011 and 60 percent more in fiscal year 2010. Your Money Your Vote - A CNBC Special Report All in all, according to Anderson, the government under the Obama administration received $6.8 trillion in taxes and spent $10.7 trillion — 56 percent more than it had available. What’s going on here is fiscal profligacy on the grandest scale in American history. And there are consequences. Massive amounts of capital are being drained from the private sector and transferred to the government. This is one reason why American businesses have gone on a virtual capital-investment strike. Small businesses, in particular, can’t get the capital being drained by Uncle Sam. (Read More: Did Obama Really Cut Small Business Taxes 18 Times?) After four years of trillion-dollar deficits, both businesses and individuals have held back investment because they fear massive tax increases are on the way. That’s a big reason why the so-called recovery has been so weak. In addition, in our new entitlement nation, growing government dependency is ruining the very moral fiber and backbone of America’s traditional work ethic. Increasingly, the feds are paying more to not work, rather than providing after-tax incentives to go back to work. Mitt Romney has taken a lot of flak for raising the issue of growing government dependency. But however inartfully he may have expressed his view, his basic story is correct. The sheer volume of spending going on in this country is bringing us ever closer to bankruptcy. (Read More: Romney on '47 Percent': I Was 'Completely Wrong'.) And consider this: The spending explosion for means-tested welfare programs is outpacing spending on Social Security and Medicare, which are themselves veering toward bankruptcy. I may be too cynical about Obama trying to buy the election with this entitlement explosion. Perhaps. But Obama wants to raise taxes in order to spend more on government unions and entitlement programs. It is redistribution, but it could be vote-buying, too.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1350693191312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 20:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350697922644-76</Id><Title>let Margaret &amp; Helen tell you about Mittens</Title><Msg>From the GREAT STATE OF MAINE… Margaret &amp; Helen Blogging The intertubes' feistiest 80-somethings weigh in from their undisclosed binder: Two broads Mitt ain't foolin' The Mitt who showed up to the debate this week is the same one who has been showing up in politics for years---the one who will say anything to get elected. Well. I’m done. I’ve seen and heard quite enough and I am voting for President Obama. ... The Republicans say that Obama can’t run on his record. Really? You want to talk about records? Mitt Romney was born wealthy, married wealthy and will most likely die wealthy. Bully for him. The other guy is [a] black man born in America in 1961 to a single white woman. He went on to become President of the United States. I’d say there’s no contest. Thanks to Republicans, Obama inherited the biggest mess since the great depression and in his first year in office prevented a total economic meltdown. As for Mitt’s record---he was a bully in high school and got pretty upset when his father wasn’t elected President. At the age of 46 he was bored with making more money so he decided to become a Republican simply to challenge Ted Kennedy for the Senate. By the way, he claimed that he was more Pro-Choice than Teddy. He lost. Then he spent millions of his own fortune to get himself elected Governor of Massachusetts in 2002. Four years later he left with an approval rating so low he ranked 48 out of the 50 Governors. Most of the middle class in Massachusetts got frustrated with his taxes which Mitt called fees---license fees, gun fees, gas fees, college fees… He left with a 38% approval rating. … I know no one wants to drag up George Bush’s name because what’s done is done. Lord knows I would like to forget him. But I take issue when Mitt and the Republicans try to blame all of Bush’s problems on the black guy who moved into the neighborhood. I say #$%$. Mitt Romney is George Bush all over again---same song, second verse.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350697922644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350698140011-77</Id><Title>they were glad when Mitt left Ma... he had a 38% approval rating</Title><Msg>"As for Mitt’s record---he was a bully in high school and got pretty upset when his father wasn’t elected President. At the age of 46 he was bored with making more money so he decided to become a Republican simply to challenge Ted Kennedy for the Senate. By the way, he claimed that he was more Pro-Choice than Teddy. He lost. Then he spent millions of his own fortune to get himself elected Governor of Massachusetts in 2002. Four years later he left with an approval rating so low he ranked 48 out of the 50 Governors. Most of the middle class in Massachusetts got frustrated with his taxes which Mitt called fees---license fees, gun fees, gas fees, college fees… He left with a 38% approval rating. …"</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350698140011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:55:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350698592750-78</Id><Title>Mitt revises to caring for 125% of Americans</Title><Msg>up from 100% , and up from 47% other revisions: tax cuts for the rich are off, or on or maybe, no details. and the government DOES created jobs says mittens now as a reason for not cutting military spending, to save jobs...... and by INCREASING military spending more jobs will be created! amazingly enough.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1350698592750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350700154442-79</Id><Title>How do you get updates for the oracel products</Title><Msg>i have never seen anything like this</Msg><Username>farml1234</Username><Timestamp>1350700154442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 22:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>