<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346151771000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Is Losing A Stunning Amount Of African-American Support In North Carolina</Title><Username>orsa_novus</Username><Timestamp>1346119016000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't imagine that happening, orsa! 94% likely Obama's worst case! Blacks have been raised for the last 50 years betting on Government and their race-baiting Pimps, like Jackson and Sharpton, to steel money from taxpayers and shove it in their pockets!! The Shelby Steele's, Thomas Sowell's, Allen West's, and those that admire them, are 5%'ers!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346151771000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 07:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346155153000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Is Losing A Stunning Amount Of African-American Support In North Carolina</Title><Username>orsa_novus</Username><Timestamp>1346119016000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20% of NC black vote would go to Romney? That seems pretty unbelievable. So unbelieveble that I don't believe it. On the other hand, what if it's true? What if it's true not only in NC but all over?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346155153000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 07:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346156534000-3</Id><Topic><Title>idiot ortho novus says it didn't double,.bush jobless ONLY increased 85%</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346153138000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 07:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the increase is CLEARLY linked to his bad policies as president. The U/E rate increase in the last month of the Bush admin is clearly NOT linked to any policy of Bush, but clearly IS linked to economic incompetence &amp; sabotage 0i.e. TREASON!) of the Democrats &amp; radicals who destroyed our economy to get Obama elected. We need to end a bunch of Democrat careers in November!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346156534000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346156701000-4</Id><Title>DEMOCRATS COMMITTED TREASON IN 2008!</Title><Msg>The Destroyed our economy to get Obama elected. Still they want to blame Bush. VOTE ALL THE DEMOCRAT SCUM OUT OF OFFICE IN NOVEMBER! To quote a phrase: "DRAIN THE SWAMP!" --- Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) circa 2006</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346156701000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346156769000-5</Id><Title>A Joke about Golf</Title><Msg>A woman was playing golf when she took a big swing and fell. The party waiting behind her was a group from the White House that included Obama. Obama quickly stepped forward and helped her to her feet. She thanked him and started to leave, when he said, "I'm President Obama and I hope you'll vote for me this November." She laughed and quickly said, "I fell on my butt, not my head!"</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346156769000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346156990405-6</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DNC Proceeds With 2-Hour Islamic ‘Jumah’ Prayers After Rejecting Cardinal’s Blessing (And You Won‘t Believe Who’s Invited) Posted on August 27, 2012 at 8:25pm by Erica Ritz Erica Ritz Print » Email » Comments (359) The Democratic National Committee is raising a number of eyebrows after choosing to proceed with hosting Islamic “Jumah” prayers for two hours on the Friday of its convention, though it denied a Catholic cardinal’s request to say a prayer at the same event. Watch the promotional video, via the Bureau of Muslim Affairs, which is partnering with the DNC for the event. The first two minutes are rather dry, but around 2:04 a muezzin sings the call to prayer with an American flag background, and the video “picks up” considerably: Up to 20,000 people are expected to attend the Friday prayers and Jibril Hough, a spokesman for the Bureau of Indigenous Muslim Affairs (BIMA), said the purpose of the event is to hold political parties accountable for the issues faced by Muslim-Americans. In particular, the event will target the Patriot Act, the NYPD, the National Defense Authorization Act, and anti-Shariah sentiment. Democratic National Convention to Host Islamic Jumah Prayers with Jibril Hough, Siraj Wahhaj (Photo: Bureau of Indigenous Muslim Affairs) And while Muslim-Americans undeniably face distinct challenges, those who are well-informed on the dangers of radical Islam are expressing their doubts about the event. Dr. Zuhdi Jasser, a devout Muslim and the Founder and President of the American Islamic Forum for Democracy, wrote: The leaders of this event – Jibril Hough and Imam Siraj Wahhaj [are not] moderates. They are radicals. These individuals embrace Islamist supremacy and have demonstrated support for radical ideologies. A quick Google search by the DNC would have shown them that Hough and Wahhaj are leaders in the separatist American Islamist movement. While they may be able to get a few thousand Muslims to attend the event, they are NOT going to be mainstream Muslims. Most will likely come from Hough and Wahhaj’s radical networks that have long been entrenched in the Charlotte area. Make no mistake they are part of the Islamist movement.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346156990405</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:29:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346157658000-7</Id><Title>Fairness in Income Taxes</Title><Msg>46% of household pay no federal income tax. 12% of households earn between $59,000 and $75,000 and pay 8% of federal income tax. 0.3% of households earn $1,000,000 or more and pay 20% of federal income tax. How "fair" is that?</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346157658000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346157758000-8</Id><Topic><Title>idiot ortho novus says it didn't double,.bush jobless ONLY increased 85%</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346153138000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 07:25:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BECAUSE OBAMA IS A FAILURE! He is an arrogant, elitist, Democrat FRAUD!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346157758000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346157833000-9</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS COMMITTED TREASON IN 2008!</Title><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346156701000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats ruined our economy, doubled the unemployment rate and still want to blame bush!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346157833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346157912000-10</Id><Title>Obama Conning White Americans - Whispering Truth To Russian Fascists!</Title><Msg>"I can be much more flexible (to F'over stupid White gullible Americans) after the election!!" YeeeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa! Hope &amp; Change We Can Believe In... best Con &amp; Liar ever in American history!! The American Presidency has never been deeper... in the Sewer!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1346157912000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346158047000-11</Id><Topic><Title>IMAGINE ortho novus quibbling over 85% or 100% increase of bgroup JOBLESS!</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346156467000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney still paid $3 million in taxes. Much more than messybrains or droopydork pays!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346158047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346158155000-12</Id><Title>IF 85% == 100% THEN</Title><Msg>PRINT "NEW MATH FROM DROPKICK!" ELSE PRINT "DROPKICK IS A MORON!" ENDIF</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346158155000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346158246000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Conning White Americans - Whispering Truth To Russian Fascists!</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1346157912000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:45:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama bowed to Vladimir Putin while saying that!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346158246000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346158333755-14</Id><Title>New boards</Title><Msg>You can click the banner on the bottom and tell Yahoo how much you dislike the new format</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1346158333755</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346158355000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Watch For Potential Topping</Title><Username>anniejoshep503</Username><Timestamp>1346156560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republican President! Republican majority in House! Republican super majority in Senate! Republican governors! Republican state legislatures! Now THAT would be a "Topping"!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346158355000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346158375000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Watch For Potential Topping</Title><Username>anniejoshep503</Username><Timestamp>1346156560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DRAIN THE SWAMP!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346158375000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346158946000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Is Losing A Stunning Amount Of African-American Support In North Carolina</Title><Username>orsa_novus</Username><Timestamp>1346119016000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Onama is destroying black peoples lives. U/E rate among blacks averages 15%. Among black youth almost 40% About 1 in every 6 or 7 black persons is unemployed. About 1 in every 2.5 black youth are unemployed. Obama is a DISASTER for black Americans. As Reagan use to say; "Rising tides lift all boats!" But Obama and the democrats prove; Ebbing tides strands all boats!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346158946000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346159087000-18</Id><Title>Tropical Storm Isaac may still become a hurricane</Title><Msg>It may still make landfall near New Orleans. Then again, it might not. Meanwhile, all Liberal News ignores the Republican Convention to focus on this "horrible" tropical storm.</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346159087000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346159469000-19</Id><Title>if ( 0.85 == 1.00 ) {</Title><Msg>cout "New math from Dropkick!"; } else { cout "Dropkick is a MORON!"; }</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346159469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346159569041-20</Id><Title>Romney caved in to extremist loons when he picked Ryan in a hail mary pass</Title><Msg>Romney desperately chose Ryan the extremist lunatic .. The USA needs compromise and not more of the extremist ideologues like Ryan who agrees with the creep Grover Norquist that "compromise is like date rape"...... just what the nation needs, right? We would already have a decent by partisan debt deal were it not for the extremist mullahs like Ryan:"Ryan helped scuttle three deals on the budget. He had served on the Simpson-Bowles deficit commission but refused to endorse its final proposal, in December, 2010. When deficit negotiations moved from the failed commission to Congress, Ryan stuck with the extreme faction of the G.O.P. caucus, which withheld support from any of the leading bipartisan plans. In the summer of 2011, when a group of Democratic and Republican senators, known as the Gang of Six, produced their own agreement, Ryan’s detailed criticism helped sink it. And, also that summer, during high-level talks between the White House and Republican leaders, Cantor and Ryan reportedly pressured Boehner to reject a potential deal with President Obama."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346159569041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:12:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346161007000-21</Id><Title>'Example of an infinite loop in VBA</Title><Msg>DO WHILE DROPKICK = MORON PRINT "DROPKICK IS A MORON!" EXIT DO ' Dropkick will NEVER not be a moron so this code will loop forever! ' Press Esc or CTRL+BREAK to end</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346161007000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346161358000-22</Id><Title>Democraps upset because Ryan is Roman Catholic, BUT:</Title><Msg>Six of our nine Supreme Court Justices are already Roman Catholic. The other three are Je wish. Thus the government body who really COULD change "a woman's reproductive rights" on a whim is already predominated by Roman Catholics! Maybe Romney-Ryan will create "diversity" and nominate a Mormon, or a Protestant! FYI Link: http://wiki.answers.com/Q/What_is_the_religion_of_each_US_Supreme_Court_Justice</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346161358000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346161969000-23</Id><Title>Democrat Tax Cheat Exposed!</Title><Msg>Along with phonieness of Obama Admin! DRAIN THE SWAMP! by Tony Lee 27 Aug 2012, 9:23 AM PDT Illinois congressional candidate Tammy Duckworth, a Democrat and a candidate the Obama campaign likes to tout, has been accused of being a tax cheat after a Chicago newspaper suggested she illegally claimed homestead exemptions on two properties from 2007 to 2010. Illinois state law allows for taxpayers to claim only one such exemption, on the property that is their primary residence. The Daily Herald discovered records that showed Duckworth claimed homestead exemptions in both DeKalb and Cook counties from 2007 to 2010. The homestead exemptions reduced the assessed values of both properties, lowering the amount of property taxes owed on them. Even worse, during those years, Duckworth was actually living in Washington, D.C. and not in Illinois. Duckworth is in a competitive race against Republican Rep. Joe Walsh in Illinois' eighth congressional district. President Barack Obama’s chief strategist David Axelrod, who has relentlessly accused Mitt Romney of being a tax cheat and has called on him to release his tax returns, has hosted fundraisers for Duckworth and has been one of her strongest supporters. Duckworth is also a candidate the Obama campaign likes to talk up at events on the campaign trail. Democrats and mainstream media networks have touted her as one of the party’s next stars. In light of all this, these revelations make Democrats seem even more hypocritical when it comes to taxes. &gt;&gt;</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346161969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346162009000-24</Id><Title>GM Outsourcing Jobs!</Title><Msg>Yes and we bailed them out and they are floundering again. 70% of GM autos are built outside if USA. GM CEO recently visited China and talked about expanding manufacturing there. Meanwhile, GM has labor union strikes in Canada and Brazil. Buy American! Buy Toyota!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346162009000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346162066000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Watch For Potential Topping</Title><Username>anniejoshep503</Username><Timestamp>1346156560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will take a look at this.</Msg><Username>peterloius901</Username><Timestamp>1346162066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346163530206-26</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The pathetic last gasp for a failed ideology is to resort to the false canard of racism.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1346163530206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346163624776-27</Id><Topic><Title>romknee unsuccessfull getting Akin to quit</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346041265000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:21:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama would have sent the New Black Panthers, have Holder's DOJ shake down the entire family. The Chicago way.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1346163624776</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346163977000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Tax Cheat Exposed!</Title><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346161969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if paying taxes is a big deal to you , then there's no way you can support a guy like Romney.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1346163977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346164132000-29</Id><Topic><Title>No stinking republican(that'd be all of them except seebe, ha) has ANY right</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346149685000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 06:28:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this board is dead it's been hyjacked by spamers and one star monkey</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1346164132000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346166288000-30</Id><Title>Stutistics on the Annual Deficit</Title><Msg>GW Bush’s deficit (including 2009 budget which Obama liberally added to) was about 2.7% of GDP. This is only slightly higher than most presidents deficits of about 2.6%. According to the budget that Barack Obama proposed (but never passed in Congress) his deficits are about 6.1% of GDP. But his budget includes many fanciful savings that will never occur and new taxes that will never occur. Correcting for these leaves a deficit of 7.5% of GDP, amost triple of GW Bush’s. OBAMA IS A FAILURE FOR AMERICA! See GBTV/BlazeTV for details.</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1346166288000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346166497000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat Tax Cheat Exposed!</Title><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346161969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:52:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has 36 tax cheats who work in high places in his administration, including Tim Geithner, Secretary of Treasury, whose job is to enforce the tax code, Also, since Obama took office, tax compliance has declined among federal union workers. Democrats complain about Romney's tax rate but bo one has shown that he cheated in his taxes.</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1346166497000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:08:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346166534000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Fairness in Income Taxes</Title><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346157658000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:40:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B U M P !!!</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1346166534000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346166714000-33</Id><Topic><Title>CHELSEA: MOM THINKS HE*S A CRACK HEAD AND A PHONY!</Title><Username>orsa_novus</Username><Timestamp>1346119645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:07:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Inside info!</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1346166714000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346167503000-34</Id><Title>Armstrong was 1st on the Moon -- make Obama the 1st coconut from Mars!!!</Title><Msg>To Honor Neil Armstrong, Obama Posts Photo of Himself The thing that most bothers me about Barack Obama is his unearned narcissism. His smugness and arrogance are beyond the ability of science to measure. I don't mind someone being a bit cocky or even arrogant, IF they have the accomplishments and achievements to back up the attitude. Obama's greatest achievement, though, is creating his own personal narrative. He is his own personal touchstone. Even when honoring a great American hero, Obama can't help but thrust himself into the event. On Friday, America and the world lost a true hero. Neil Armstrong, who died of heart complications at the age of 82, was the first human to walk on the moon. His steps onto the lunar surface were watched by the largest television audience in history. His statement "one giant leap for mankind" echoed throughout the world, allowing people everywhere to step back from the clutter of their daily lives and pause to dream big things. People who witnessed it will never forget it. Armstrong's heroism wasn't the lunar walk, though. It was how he comported himself afterwards that showed the true measure of the man. He was among the more famous human beings in history. Yet he retired to a quiet and private life teaching aeronautical engineering and tending to his farm. His walk on the moon wasn't a personal achievement, per se, but an accomplishment for all of humanity. Obama took to his tumblr page to offer a tribute to Neil Armstrong. The words--two sentences--are fine in a generic politician way. But, Obama being Obama, he injected himself into the tribute. He included a photo, not of Armstrong or the iconic step onto the lunar surface, but of himself, gazing up at the moon. Obama is a literary construct. It's as if Zelig jumped off the movie screen and took up residence in the Oval Office. He puts himself in the frame of historical events, even if he has only the smallest cameo. He let Democrats in Congress construct the stimulus package, as well as his signature legislation, Obamacare. He comes on the scene just in time for the photo-op, after others have done the heavy lifting. Neil Armstrong did the heavy lifting. Even a tribute to his death is just another photo-op for Obama. http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/08/26/to-honor-neil-armstrong-obama-posts-a-picture-of-himself</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1346167503000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346167805000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Fairness in Income Taxes</Title><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346157658000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:40:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How's about Whites &amp; Asians paying over 90% of all Federal Income Taxes while Blacks &amp; Hispanics soak up 90% of the 'Welfare' Payments! Obama just loves "Spreadin' The Wealth"!!! I bet I'm not off by much... because the stinking Government, Pig Press and University whores don't want to share the data by RACE! They love Scamming the Mice and it just might wake up a few million stupid White Mice Democrats and bubblehead Moderates!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346167805000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:30:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346168500000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Watch For Potential Topping</Title><Username>anniejoshep503</Username><Timestamp>1346156560000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares?</Msg><Username>goodgal000000001</Username><Timestamp>1346168500000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346169462683-37</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Robertson is a far right goof. LOVED by repubs</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346018763000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:06:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever read who financed and started Pat Robertson off on his career? I know you didn't. Most never have. It came from a virulently anti-Christan source. This same source finances both "left" AND "right" entities. Do some research. You and others may eventually wake up to who and what REALLY runs things here and abroad.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1346169462683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 11:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346169600000-38</Id><Topic><Title>broke 50 DAY MA strong buy</Title><Username>farvergcin7447</Username><Timestamp>1346164409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberate America from statist tyranny!</Msg><Username>lord_snivel_drivel_project</Username><Timestamp>1346169600000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:00:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346170015000-39</Id><Topic><Title>New Analysis on Oracle CorporationSuggests Drop</Title><Username>marylouamtower</Username><Timestamp>1346165688000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:54:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote Republican in November!</Msg><Username>lord_snivel_drivel_project</Username><Timestamp>1346170015000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346170073000-40</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS COMMITTED TREASON IN 2008!</Title><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1346156701000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 08:25:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VOTE REPUBLICAN IN NOVEMBER!</Msg><Username>lord_snivel_drivel_project</Username><Timestamp>1346170073000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346170142232-41</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know E3, I always thought of you as at least having the capacity to think for yourself. However, you've proven your self to be nothing more than another lib kool-aid drinker.</Msg><Username>uguyssuk</Username><Timestamp>1346170142232</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346170227210-42</Id><Topic><Title>Right, that hurricane would have never happened if the Repubs weren't there.</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345974605000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 05:50:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot alert- chipsdork is phyllis. Bad puncuations and she calls me professor, I wonder if she and buckwheat have figured out the new format. buckwheat hasn't been on his daily hoot since it changed. Good!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346170227210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346170298984-43</Id><Topic><Title>Romney caved in to extremist loons when he picked Ryan in a hail mary pass</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346159569041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:12:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When you have no record to run on, then you characterize your opponent as someone you should run away from." Barack Obama 2008. Guess he was pretty prescient.</Msg><Username>e3_dsb_enki_messy_hater</Username><Timestamp>1346170298984</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:11:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346171706617-44</Id><Topic><Title>Romney caved in to extremist loons when he picked Ryan in a hail mary pass</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346159569041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:12:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kenyan's buddies that planted bombs , of course, aren't extremists. The same goes for the Kenyan's "Father Figure" Frank Davis, card carrying commie, bi-sexual cocaine dealer and quite possibly his real father. Knowing what I know of who really runs this country you will really be given NO choice, just rhetoric to incite fools into taking "sides" when there is only one "side". The side that runs the corrupt money system.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1346171706617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346173012424-45</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes me a "lib" doofus? I support Simpson-Bowles and balanced budgets and smart/lean govt But I don't like bullshltters/liars and those who have sold out, whether it be to special interests or capitalists shipping jobs overseas for strictly their own enrichment. And I support protection of the environment as much as is feasible. Call me a weirdo.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346173012424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346173094726-46</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody claiming Obama is a Mzzlm or is secretly trying to push their influence is a bullshltter</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346173094726</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 12:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346173546112-47</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know a fair number of these people (I'm related to a few). I speak to what I see.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346173546112</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:05:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346173549903-48</Id><Topic><Title>Romney caved in to extremist loons when he picked Ryan in a hail mary pass</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346159569041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:12:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny how all pubs can do lie, lie , lie. and sure romneyann are going to fix everything by giving more tax cuts to the rich, full AS IS medicare and social security to most boomers and plus increased military spending for the neo cons all that they call "deficit reduction",, the last time the lying gop did tax cuts it was for surplus reduction... jeez.... all pubs do is lie lie lie.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346173549903</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346173659016-49</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah I forgot to mention: I believe in evolution and the scientific method. I spose that makes me a "lib" in your book.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346173659016</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346174291691-50</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I support Simpson-Bowles and balanced budgets " yep, a good bipartisan compromise which the lunatic extreme ideologue Ryan helped kill..... Ryan is a grover norquist type of #$%$ who says "compromise is like date rape" and "drown the government in a bathtub" and etc.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346174291691</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346174450525-51</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you support all those things then how can you support the lying, deceitful, hypocritical, losers that are the current administration? You take the pablum they serve up and buy it as gospel, yet you claim to think for yourself. Do you realize that jobs are sent overseas because that's where the greatest growth is for American companies' products? Local's want to buy products from companies doing business locally. Why do you think foreign car manufacturers build plants in the US? Are they also guilty of "shipping jobs overseas" to their countrymen? Stop drinking and start thinking, because you clearly haven't up until now.</Msg><Username>uguyssuk</Username><Timestamp>1346174450525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346174537490-52</Id><Title>what do professional meteorologists say?</Title><Msg>American Meteorological Society (AMS), has now stated plainly that the warming world is a fact beyond reproach and that human activity—despite some natural variability—is the main force behind such changes. "Warming of the climate system now is unequivocal," the group said in a statement on Monday. "Observations show increases in globally averaged air and ocean temperatures, as well as widespread melting of snow and ice and rising globally averaged sea level." The dominant cause of the warming since the 1950s is human activities, they said, adding that their scientific finding is based on "a large and persuasive body of research." "Due to natural variability," the statement noted, "not every year is warmer than the preceding year globally. Nevertheless, all of the 10 warmest years in the global temperature records up to 2011 have occurred since 1997, with 2005 and 2010 being the warmest two years in more than a century of global records."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346174537490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346174574883-53</Id><Topic><Title>rape &amp; tax cuts for the rich gop convention</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346028253000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:44:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing but liar's talking points. However, your brain is too dysfunctional to comprehend the truth, so I won't bother. Your diaper needs changing messypants.</Msg><Username>uguyssuk</Username><Timestamp>1346174574883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346174632881-54</Id><Topic><Title>GOP party of morons and aholes</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346115126306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hosting Islamic prayers. The complying party, the bowing party, the rank and file liberal goons will do anything for votes. Since when does any race or nationality get special publicity for their beliefs? Hindus, Buddists, Shintos? You think Americans would have the privilege of hosting Christian prayers in Lebanon or Syrian elections? The Democrats are slowly giving way to foreign ideology. We have to stop them.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346174632881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346174742142-55</Id><Topic><Title>what do professional meteorologists say?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346174537490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...more than a century of global records." ----------------------------------- The earth has been around for billions of years and we're using 100 years worth of data to make conclusions. That's like determining a baseball players career batting average by a single at bat.</Msg><Username>e3_dsb_enki_messy_hater</Username><Timestamp>1346174742142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346174805269-56</Id><Topic><Title>rape &amp; tax cuts for the rich gop convention</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346028253000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:44:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nothing but liar's talking points" are you saying the stated purpose of the bush tax cuts wasn't to reduce the $5.6 trillion in budget surpluses they projected? YOU are the LIAR, AS ALWAYS.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346174805269</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346175101058-57</Id><Topic><Title>what do professional meteorologists say?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346174537490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only a stupid person like you would spout off uneducated and childish nonsense to counter the work of professional meteoroligists, who are certainly aware of the age of the earth you #$%$ "Warming of the climate system now is unequivocal," the group said in a statement on Monday. "Observations show increases in globally averaged air and ocean temperatures, as well as widespread melting of snow and ice and rising globally averaged sea level." The dominant cause of the warming since the 1950s is human activities, they said, adding that their scientific finding is based on "a large and persuasive body of research." no doubt you offer your idiot opinion to your relatives in lieu of professional medical advice too, right?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346175101058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346175747738-58</Id><Title>Democrats, party of terrorist sympathizers</Title><Msg>I decided to re-post this with a subject line. Hosting Islamic prayers? The complying party, the bowing party, the rank and file liberal goons will do anything for votes. Since when does any religion get special publicity for their beliefs, Hindus, Buddhists, Shintos? Would Americans have the privilege of hosting Christian prayers in Lebanon or Syrian elections? Dems are slowly giving way to foreign ideology, one that is against all others. We have to stop them.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346175747738</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:42:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346176571243-59</Id><Title>Obama: High Un-employment, No Growth, Massive Deficits</Title><Msg>... our debt-to-GDP ratio is already 104... worse than all but 5 European countries. Obama hasn't proposed ANY solutions... only a proposal to jack up taxes on the wealthy, and the CBO says that would only cover 1/16 of the deficit. Who in their right mind would vote for 4 more years like the LAST 4 years... ... the fact that this election is so close scares the he11 out of me!</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1346176571243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346179675233-60</Id><Title>What happened to buckwheat?</Title><Msg>Re-new boards. If this format gets rid of him, I like it.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346179675233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 14:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346181001747-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: High Un-employment, No Growth, Massive Deficits</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1346176571243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... our debt-to-GDP ratio is already 104... worse than all but 5 European countries. Obama hasn't proposed ANY solutions... only a proposal to jack up taxes on the wealthy, and the CBO says that would only cover 1/16 of the deficit. --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Of course Obama has proposed a solution: raise the debt to 104% of GDP.... And yes... it's worse than Europe and it's why the US is doing better than Europe... Funny to see stupid republicans who can't see how we got there (through a huge housing bubble supported by massive credit fraud with the complicity of BUSH), and how the different issues (insolvent banks, large debt and unemployment) depend of each other. Lol.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1346181001747</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 15:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346181118631-62</Id><Topic><Title>what do professional meteorologists say?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346174537490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>professional meteoroligists ------------------------------------------------------ They are not climatologists and have no particular credibility on that subject.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1346181118631</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 15:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346182192000-63</Id><Topic><Title>broke 50 DAY MA strong buy</Title><Username>farvergcin7447</Username><Timestamp>1346164409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love your videos.</Msg><Username>raygosaspoy47446</Username><Timestamp>1346182192000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 15:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346184208000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Bear Market</Title><Username>koelschspwd2573</Username><Timestamp>1346178161000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 14:22:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking cool.</Msg><Username>muscenteden6019</Username><Timestamp>1346184208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 16:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346185046510-65</Id><Topic><Title>what do professional meteorologists say?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346174537490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They are not climatologists and have no particular credibility on that subject." Nope, you are mostly wrong, AMS members are degreed scientists who study the atmoshpere. Climatology is the study of climate, scientifically defined as weather conditions averaged over a period of time. and fyi the best evidence of climate change is seen in the temperature data gathered daily for over a hundred years and also in more recent satellite data.Meteorology, climatology, atmospheric physics, and atmospheric chemistry are sub-disciplines of the atmospheric sciences.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346185046510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 16:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346185696787-66</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: High Un-employment, No Growth, Massive Deficits</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1346176571243</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:56:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's Voltwagen = Solyndra 2.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1346185696787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 16:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346185956000-67</Id><Topic><Title>broke 50 DAY MA strong buy</Title><Username>farvergcin7447</Username><Timestamp>1346164409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow!!!</Msg><Username>aycoxeux0990</Username><Timestamp>1346185956000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 16:32:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346188098000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Bear Market</Title><Username>koelschspwd2573</Username><Timestamp>1346178161000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 14:22:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Promised Profit</Msg><Username>monfordfcbx59075</Username><Timestamp>1346188098000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 17:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346196117000-69</Id><Title>The GM Volt! Corvair Deja Vu All Over Again!</Title><Msg>Where the hell is Ralph Nader!?? I guess if it's Green and Sucks it's OK!!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346196117000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 19:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346198300679-70</Id><Topic><Title>what do professional meteorologists say?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346174537490</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 13:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They are not climatologists and have no particular credibility on that subject." Nope, you are mostly wrong, AMS members are degreed scientists who study the atmoshpere. ------------------------------------------------------------------- #$%$ They study in part the atmosphere and that's the only common point. They are working with sets of measures that are totally different, and equations and models that are totally different. Meteorology studies for example current winds, humidity, pressure conditions and the uses fluid mechanics to predict movements to project future conditions. Climatology study a complex system, uses mostly thermodynamics and chemistry, while it considers and tries to model a wide variety of sub-systems (oceans, permafrost, polar ice etc...). Measures could be tree rings and ocean floor mud deposits to understand past temperatures. Therefore meteorologists have no particular credibility talking of climatology.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1346198300679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 19:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346207319357-71</Id><Title>Obama took Home Ec. for His Science Requirement</Title><Msg>He has an effeminate brain. Math and science make him ovulate. That is why he went for a lawyer degree. That is also why he squeezes a tampon between his legs every time Romney speaks.</Msg><Username>i_got_yer_big_finger_right_here</Username><Timestamp>1346207319357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346207761000-72</Id><Title>Anne Romney hits a grand slam!</Title><Msg>She loves America. Mitt loves America. Mitt is a hard worker and a success! Mitt will fix America! GOD BLESS AMERICA!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346207761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346209320000-73</Id><Topic><Title>broke 50 DAY MA strong buy</Title><Username>farvergcin7447</Username><Timestamp>1346164409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job man!</Msg><Username>duggerlscm05555</Username><Timestamp>1346209320000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346209821000-74</Id><Title>Chris Christie made a great speach!</Title><Msg>God Bless Mitt Romney! God Bless America!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346209821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346209984000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Bear Market</Title><Username>koelschspwd2573</Username><Timestamp>1346178161000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 14:22:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will take a look at this.</Msg><Username>lapeteqcwp95890</Username><Timestamp>1346209984000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346210463000-76</Id><Topic><Title>broke 50 DAY MA strong buy</Title><Username>farvergcin7447</Username><Timestamp>1346164409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 10:33:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great site!</Msg><Username>kassulkexvz8743</Username><Timestamp>1346210463000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 23:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>