<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342953503000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Where does an unemployed student get money for all that equipment?</Title><Username>wournos.aileen</Username><Timestamp>1342926248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe an Obama Executive Order is in the immediate future. The stroke of his pen and voila...guns done. If so, what then? How would they round all the guns? Would local law enforcement actually enforce such a thing?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342953503000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 06:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342956088000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Where does an unemployed student get money for all that equipment?</Title><Username>wournos.aileen</Username><Timestamp>1342926248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>credit cards. You don't think he intended to pay it off, do you?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342956088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 07:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342957930000-3</Id><Title>enter the lawyers</Title><Msg>since you can't get blood from a turnip, sue the movie theater company. Sounds about right for our times. http://www.reuters.com/article/2012/07/20/tagblogsfindlawcom2012-injured-idUS387141306620120720</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342957930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 07:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342959830000-4</Id><Topic><Title>enter the lawyers</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342957930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 07:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>businesss do have responsibilities,,,how'd the guy get those guns in there again&gt; .................................................................. see where we're going with this? Plenty of people out there, you're one apparently, who think someone other than the perp should pay. Following your line of thinking, every business out there (because they're the ones with money) has to plan for and defend against all weird things all the time. Planning for normal living can't be done anymore. Having said that, there is no doubt in my mind the biz will be held liable. All it takes is a sympathetic jury. And they are easy to find. John Edwards got wealthy by finding sympathetic juries.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342959830000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:23:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342960106000-5</Id><Title>CO Shooting! Obama Regime Passes "Stupid Test" Yet Again!</Title><Msg>Within a matter of TWO months, one guy goes on the Internet and into gun stores and buys a top of the line S&amp;W AR-15 .223 assault rifle, a 100 round 'drum' magazine, 6000 rounds of ammunition, a 12ga shotgun, a Glock 40 semi-auto pistol, even more ammunition and a full set of body armor, and no one at the GD ATF/FBI notices! WTF!! One guy with ONE Name, One Address, ONE Social Security number and ONE Driver's license number buys an arsenal of weapons in matter of days and the F'ing ATF &amp; FBI, whose computers get all this information, can't add 2+2 and send someone out to talk with this POS!! The Government is at best stupid and USELESS, and at worst, calculating and COMPLICIT!! It's so GD stupid one must can only assume that they were hoping, even encouraging, a whackjob massacre to happen!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1342960106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342960472000-6</Id><Topic><Title>enter the lawyers</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342957930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 07:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>moron seaburgc is in a tizzie over the mention of "potential" targets for a law suit. Nothing ACTUAL, mind you. He adds that lawsuits "Sounds about right for our times" but of course law suits have been going on for centuries. Mass murder with NRA pumped assault rifles are recent and a sign of the time; and the gop in 2004 made 100 round machine gun style magazines legal .... they had been outlawed. Isn't that a sign of the times?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342960472000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342960845000-7</Id><Topic><Title>enter the lawyers</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342957930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 07:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>potential" targets for a law suit. Nothing ACTUAL, mind you.&gt; .................................................................. nothing actual? Well not yet. What do you think will happen? Of course there will be lawsuits. And of course the theater company will be held liable by a sympathetic jury. Virginia Tech had to pay because amongst all the chaos when no one there was fully aware of what was happening, they didn't warn the students fast enough.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342960845000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342960981000-8</Id><Topic><Title>NRA are crazy people&amp;gun dealer pimps</Title><Username>doodlersdoodledo</Username><Timestamp>1342876687000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 09:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lame and liar vansniff. looks to me most mass shooting are done by lunatic NRA armed white dudes in the stars &amp; bars states, for example: March 10, 2009 -- In Alabama, 28-year-old Michael McLendon of Kinston kills 10 and himself. The dead include his mother, grandparents, aunt and uncle. Killeen, Texas, tragedy after a 1991 restaurant shooting left 24 people dead. CHARLES WHITMAN: THE TEXAS TOWER SNIPER</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342960981000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342961100000-9</Id><Topic><Title>enter the lawyers</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342957930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 07:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop and NRA should be sued. lol Mass murder with NRA pumped assault rifles are recent and a sign of the time; and the gop in 2004 made 100 round machine gun style magazines legal .... they had been outlawed. Isn't that a sign of the times?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342961100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342961200000-10</Id><Topic><Title>enter the lawyers</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342957930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 07:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa,a question for you. Do you get out of bed in the morning and wonder which screen name will I be today? And do you spend a lot of time thinking up future screen names. Apparently you do.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342961200000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342961399000-11</Id><Topic><Title>enter the lawyers</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342957930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 07:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you obviously get up everyday and don't think at all, you are in perpetual kneejerk mode.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342961399000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342961622000-12</Id><Title>I agree with Fox on this one</Title><Msg>Even Murdoch has had enough of right wing gun nut morons. "Media baron Rupert Murdoch took to Twitter Saturday evening to express his support for gun-control measures in the wake of the Aurora, CO shooting that killed 12 people on Friday: Rupert Murdoch We have to do something about gun controls. Police license okay for hunting rifle or pistol for anyone without crim or pscho record. No more ( personally anyone who has military style weapons at home is a lunatic, and especially those who buy 100 round magazines, that the gop made legal in 2004, being the money suking evil ajoles they are)</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342961622000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342962013000-13</Id><Topic><Title>CO Shooting! Obama Regime Passes "Stupid Test" Yet Again!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1342960106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This has nothing to do with 'Gun Control' you Clown! It has everything to do with normal, reasonable, expected monitoring of weapons purchase!! Why the F are we required to provide all kinds of information to purchase a weapon?? Answer... so the Government can track purchases and take action when Red Flags are raised! This event had Red Flags in spades... yet the Government did Jackshyt! It's negligence was so horrific it has to be criminal!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1342962013000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:00:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342962114000-14</Id><Topic><Title>romeny must be a crook to hide his tax data</Title><Username>softwaretroubleshooter73</Username><Timestamp>1342718859000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-19 13:27:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama didn't hide his tax info, and obama , btw, not being as rich as Romney, paid a HIGHER % of his income than Mittens. Even the avg USA household paid several percent MORE of their income in fed income tax that did Mr. Cayman Islands.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342962114000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342962239000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so much for the myth of the "self made" man: But in an interview with Boston-based reporter Jon Keller of WBZ-TV, Maloney acknowledged that his business received some government help" yep, and ntm, there are roads and schools and a justice system and the elderly are not in poverty and etc....all the kind of stuff the "self made" pub business men take for granted even though there would be no business at all without it.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342962239000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342962391000-16</Id><Topic><Title>I agree with Fox on this one</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342961622000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt! Gun Control my azzs!! This is little more than Government Criminal Negligence! Within a matter of TWO months, one guy goes on the Internet and into gun stores and buys a top of the line S&amp;W AR-15 .223 assault rifle, a 100 round 'drum' magazine, 6000 rounds of ammunition, a 12ga shotgun, a Glock 40 semi-auto pistol, even more ammunition and a full set of body armor, and no one at the GD ATF/FBI notices! WTF!! One guy with ONE Name, ONE Address, ONE Social Security number and ONE Driver's license number buys an arsenal of weapons in matter of days and the F'ing ATF &amp; FBI, whose computers get ALL this information, can't add 2+2 and send someone out to talk with this POS!! A 12 year old would have programed the Govt computers to do this, at the very least! The Government is at best stupid and USELESS, and at worst, calculating and COMPLICIT!! Indeed, it's so GD stupid that one can only assume that they were hoping, even encouraging, a whackjob massacre to happen... so they and stupid shytheads like yourself can scream Gun Control!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1342962391000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342962975000-17</Id><Topic><Title>NRA are crazy people&amp;gun dealer pimps</Title><Username>doodlersdoodledo</Username><Timestamp>1342876687000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 09:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure Pigshyt! Gun Control my azzs!! This is little more than Government Criminal Negligence by the Obama Regime!! Within a matter of TWO months, one guy goes on the Internet and into gun stores and buys a top of the line S&amp;W AR-15 .223 assault rifle, a 100 round 'drum' magazine, 6000 rounds of ammunition, a 12ga shotgun, a Glock 40 semi-auto pistol, even more ammunition and a full set of body armor, and no one at the GD ATF/FBI notices! WTF!! How can that be! It's impossible! One guy with ONE Name, ONE Address, ONE Social Security number and ONE Driver's license number buys an arsenal of weapons in matter of days and the F'ing ATF &amp; FBI, whose computers get ALL this information, can't add 2+2 and send someone out to talk with this POS!! A 12 year old would have programed the Govt computers to do this, at the very least! Your Government is at best stupid and USELESS, and at worst, calculating and COMPLICIT!! Indeed, it's so GD stupid that one can only assume that Government Pigs were hoping, even encouraging, a whackjob massacre to happen... so they and stupid shytheads like yourself could scream 'Gun Control'!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1342962975000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963021000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there are roads and schools and a justice system and the elderly are not in poverty .................................................................. that is a loser of an argument. Keep on doing it though. The people don't buy it.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342963021000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342963063000-19</Id><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Msg>Mittens is hiding something..... how can anyone trust a bum who says this in essence: -- I-was-CEO-I-wasn't-in-charge-I-retired-retroactively-but-I-still-got-paid a huge bundle-- and he HAS to hide his taxes from public scrutiny????</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963164000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>people aren't buying that lame argument either. But it's all you got, right. It's all Obama's got.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342963164000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963385000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the loser is Mittens, he cited a "self made" pub businessman, who practically sang " I did it my way.... all on my own"........until later when he had to admit he did take a government loan and couldn't have gotten started without it. and all know how Romney's family was bailed out by tax dollars when they arrived destitute in El Paso having fled their COMMUNE in Mexico. (Romney endorsed TARP, btw)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963385000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963555000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and all know how Romney's family was bailed out by tax dollars when they arrived destitute in El Paso having fled their COMMUNE in Mexico.&gt; .................................................................. and from that you'd like us to conclude what?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342963555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963680000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>later when he had to admit he did take a government loan&gt; ................................................................. if true, did he pay back the loan? Or was he like Solyndra that just took the money w/o a viable business model?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342963680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:28:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963707000-24</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are a laugh, quite a few prominent pubs are also demanding Mittens show more tax data. this issue isn't going away, and the nation can't wait to find out what disgrace Mittens is hiding. My theory is that there are years in which he paid ZERO income taxes. It's bad enough that he had to show that he pays 3% LESS of his income than the avg household pays of theirs. but we know how the super rich are very special and their money is more important to them than the money of the avg household.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963707000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342963794000-25</Id><Topic><Title>CO Shooting! Obama Regime Passes "Stupid Test" Yet Again!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1342960106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a lying Piece of PC Pig Trash! Not only CAN your GD Obama Government do what I'm saying... that is exactly what it must and should be doing! That it did not is Criminal Negligence!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1342963794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342964032000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>naturally you discount the millions he's given in charity. But that's charity and it means nothing to you. Means nothing to Biden or Alfore either since they don't do charitable giving. Taxes is the only charity you value.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342964032000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342964178000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure, ignore the point that Mitt and his example of a "self-made" business man were caught in a lie. and that in fact, the businessman got his start with a government loan. the link to the story is in the first post. funny how you also ignore that Mitten's family has also received government help, tax dollars. The typical pub blindness to the real world and the facts, i guess. (&amp; don't forget Mittens endorsed TARP, you know as in Bush demanding government money: "unless money is loosened up, the sucker could go down"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342964178000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342964503000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ignore that Mitten's family has also received government help, tax dollars.&gt; .................................................................. meaning welfare in 1912 or sometime around then. I asked you before, what should be concluded from that? I'll wait for your answer.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342964503000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342964630000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My theory is that there are years in which he paid ZERO income taxes.&gt; .................................................................. it's a theory, nothing more.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342964630000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342964823000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there you go changing the subject which is taxes and the fact that Mittens paid LESS % than the avg USA household. Why should Mittens pay LESS for the enormous military budget, that he wants to increase, for example, than the avg household who paid 3% MORE of their income than Mittens did toward that? aside from taxes, i could not care less if mittens spends more on his horses than most Americans earn for a living , or if he buys car elevators and mansions and gives a bundle to the Mormons or whatever.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342964823000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342965150000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i could not care less if mittens spends more on his horses than most Americans earn for a living , or if he buys car elevators and mansions&gt; .................................................................. You do care. Otherwise you wouldn't mention it in a snide sort of way. You are envious. I've known your type all my life. The left is comprised of many many people like you. It's a personality disorder. You're only happy when cra*ping on someone with more than you.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342965150000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342965171000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sure are in denial. 1. mittens and his "self made" businessman, were wrong, he admited a government loan got him started. 2. it's a fact that mitten's family got US tax dollar relief in el paso 3. Mittens endorsed a government bail : TARP.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342965171000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342965262000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's a fact that mitten's family got US tax dollar relief in el paso&gt; .................................................................. so far, Mesa, you have not answered what we should conclude from that? I'm waiting.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342965262000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342965448000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you are on record as approving that the rich pay less a % in taxes than the middleclass? You keep ignoring the point: Why should Mittens pay LESS for the enormous military budget, that he wants to increase, for example, than the avg household who paid 3% MORE of their income than Mittens did toward that? seaburgc is offically a leona Helmsian and agrees with her and thinks it is right that " WE {the rich} don't pay taxes, the little people pay taxes"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342965448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342965737000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the fact is Mittens family was on government relief. doesn't matter that you want to spin it, it is a fact. not "self made" is it ? doesn't fit into the pub lie of the "self made" neither did Mittens businessman example who admitted his start was a government loan. neither does Mittens endorsement of TARP but sure be a weasel and try to ignore , spin and deny the facts</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342965737000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342966057000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm one of those "little" people that you refer to. I do not have an envious bone in my body, unlike you. And unlike you, I do not begrudge wealth achieved by others via their own smarts, wits, luck, or whatever thru legitimate means persuing whatever it is they are passionate to persue. Envy is very bad for you. eats you up like a cancer.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342966057000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342966341000-37</Id><Title>zimmerman still a rightwing hero?</Title><Msg>maybe the rightwing finally dropped him. His blaming god for the killing may have lost right wing support. they didn't care about his violent record, his arrest record, his abuse of women, his mental problems and use of psych drugs, or his hatred for authority, he had assualted a cop, lied to a judge, ignored police instructions and neighborhood watch rule...... no the gop were OK with that, after all shooting a black they like... but they many balk at blaming it on god.... they like their heroes "self-made"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342966341000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342966409000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doesn't matter that you want to spin it, it is a fact.&gt; .................................................................. I didn't spin anything. I did not dispute your fact on the matter. I did ask you what we should concluded from that. And you haven't answered. Then I'll answer it for you, you envious clown. With respect to Romney's candidacy for president, nothing at all can be concluded from it. Right Mesa?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342966409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:13:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342966506000-39</Id><Topic><Title>corpiss says,..Co. shooting is the fault of Obama govt BUT 9/11/01</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342965379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:56:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, Govt negligence and stupidity permitted, even encouraged, "911"... but most of it proceeded Bush! The F'ing Clinton Pigs prevented the FBI and CIA from talking about potential terrorists, allowed Islamic Scum to get flying lessons on multi engine aircraft, and never required locks on cockpit doors... all being AS STUPID AS IT GETS! The Clinton and Bush regimes even knew this type of attack was a real probability!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1342966506000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342966773000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still, you think it is OK that the rich pay less a % in taxes than the average household. why is that, and what does it have to do with envy? You are just doing the weasel change of subject. Why should Mittens pay LESS for the enormous military budget, that he wants to increase, for example, than the avg household who paid 3% MORE of their income than Mittens did toward that? and ntm that Mittens is hiding his tax info and has to make bizzare dishonest statments in essence like: -- I-was-CEO-I-wasn't-in-charge-I-retired-retroactively-but-I-still-got-paid a huge bundle--</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342966773000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342966952000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what do YOU conclude about the gop myth of the "self made" man, the topic of this thread given that: 1. mittens and his "self made" businessman, were wrong, he admitted a government loan got him started. 2. it's a fact that mitten's family got US tax dollar relief in el paso 3. Mittens endorsed a government bail : TARP.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342966952000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342967018000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why should I bother to answer your question when you haven't ventured a response to mine, even though you have mentioned countless times that Romney's grandfather received some form of welfare from the government in 1912. And yes, you have brought it up multiple multiple times. All I ask is what conclusion should be drawn. You don't conclude anything either,do you? You just throw it out there. You envious government-monger.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342967018000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342967267000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mittens endorsed a government bail : TARP. &gt; .................................................................. thanks for bringing that up. Unlike you, I won't duck the question. I hate TARP. The repubs who supported it are RINOs basically. And I've little respect for their votes on that. I have very little respect for Bush who said "I sacrificed my free-market principles to support TARP." It means Bush had no free-market principles to begin with. Is Romney a RINO? I think he is. Will I vote him? Of course I will.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342967267000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342968284000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>congratulations, you adressed 1 of the 3 items, but still, MITT endorsed TARP and yet he also blathers about "self-made"? what do YOU conclude about the gop myth of the "self made" man, the topic of this thread given that: 1. mittens and his "self made" businessman, were wrong, he admitted a government loan got him started. 2. it's a fact that mitten's family got US tax dollar relief in el paso 3. Mittens endorsed a government bail : TARP.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342968284000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342968622000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you agree that it's OK for Mittens to pay LESS for the enormous military budget, that he wants to increase, for example, than the avg household who paid 3% MORE of their income than Mittens did toward that..... it just means that you are crazy, which isn't a surprise.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342968622000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342968646000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. mittens and his "self made" businessman, were wrong, he admitted a government loan got him started. 2. it's a fact that mitten's family got US tax dollar relief in el paso 3. Mittens endorsed a government bail : TARP. &gt; .................................................................. In fact, I've address all three of your inanities. 1) Gov loan. If true, did he pay it back? Why would I think that he did. 2) Gov welfare in 1912? You know I addressed it. But you haven't even though you throw it out there. Now, Mesa, let's address your envious nature. When did you first notice your personality disorder? When did you first denigrating thsoe with more than you? Did you have any friends growing up? Do you have any friends now?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342968646000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342969848000-47</Id><Topic><Title>I can't lose Time to turn</Title><Username>sansonveq741</Username><Timestamp>1342962579000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:09:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expecting more news</Msg><Username>nicoladde909</Username><Timestamp>1342969848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 11:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342975325000-48</Id><Title>LIBOR a perfect example of GOP ideals</Title><Msg>the LIBOR fraud is the way of the gop: all unregulated ,a few rich men fixing prices. Same with the mortgage meltdown. No coincidence that investment banks were deregulated and allowed to get into home mortgages first time since FDR new deal laws had outlawed their fraudulent ways. ditto for the Reagan era deregulation of the S&amp;L, and 1st thing the fraudsters go to town even including the Bush boys, Neil at Silverado and Jeb at Broward county S &amp; L. ditto for another fdr new deal law that got undone and the utes get deregulated, and what do you know, 1st thing Enron and others are committing fraud right and left.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342975325000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342975796000-49</Id><Title>class war to Romney</Title><Msg>class war to Romney means some one asking about the tax returns he hides or his questionable record at bain or his cayman island bank accounts. and of course if someone points out that Romney pays less % in come tax than the average family, pay no attention to THAT fact, since people are just envious of how special the rich are that they get to pay LESS of their income than the middleclass for the nation's defense, for example. Why shouldn't the Romneys and the Leona Helmsleys pays less a percent of their millions of income than the avg USA household does on their $50K income or whatever?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342975796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342976196000-50</Id><Topic><Title>class war to Romney</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342975796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:49:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is fighting the wrong war. Internal class warfare is negative and divisive. Divisive, Negative, Bashing, Bas*tud. That's how Obama will be remembered. Aileen is onto something. They only way out of this Obama-created Depression is a big war. Germany is slowly taking over Europe by legally owning all the debts of the weak countries. Iran and the Persian hordes want a showdown. Obama is not the man. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1342976196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342976711000-51</Id><Topic><Title>class war to Romney</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342975796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:49:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you say, but you are another Leona Helmsleyian who is OK with the rich paying less a % income tax than the middleclass. You must think you are as fluffy and special as Leona. You are also OK with the hypocrisy of Mittens offshoring his money in countries that have universal healthcare such as Switzerland and Bermuda. Even the Cayman Islands require all employers to provide health insurance. That was something nixon proposed for the UDA. Mitt is just a shyster who hide behind cayman island incorporations and bank accounts, refuses to show his taxes and has lied about his Bain connections... although he tried to "retroactively" correct that.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342976711000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342977179000-52</Id><Topic><Title>class war to Romney</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342975796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:49:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are free. Free abortion, free sterilization, free healthcare. *** An interesting insight.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1342977179000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342977264000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Gov loan. If true, did he pay it back? Why would I think that he did." it is true, the link is in the fist post. the businessman admitted he got his start with a GOVERNMENT LOAN. I guess you think "self made" includes using a GOVERNMENT LOAN. and weren't YOU one those liars and idiots who like Romney and the pub businessman were saying OBAMA was WRONG to say the "self-made" man is an illusion? HELLO..... the guy got his start with a GOVERNMENT LOAN, does that mean self made to YOU? He obviously got help from the government. and so did Romney's family and so did the entire USA economy thru the TARP that Romney endorsed.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342977264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342977640000-54</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: the CEO who wasn't</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342963063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Sunday shows Mitt Romney attracting 46% of the vote, while President Obama earns support from 44%. Romney has a 24-point lead among military veterans. Scott Rasmussen’s weekly newspaper column notes that the Obama campaign attacks on Bain Capital have failed to shake up the presidential race. In fact, they are helping Romney. $5 Gasoline = BYE BYE OBAMA.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1342977640000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342977647000-55</Id><Topic><Title>class war to Romney</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342975796000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 12:49:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop prefers bushcare at the ER since it is paid for in the form of increased premiums for all who do buy health insurance, about $1500 more a year for a family premium. so again, the avg family pay 4% of their income for the gop tax to pay for Bushcare at the ER, but that is about .003% for the Romney family. easy to see what the gop stands for: Leona Helmsley, cayman island tax scams, and the rich paying less a burden than everyone else even for the increased military welfare spending the gop pushes.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342977647000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342978136000-56</Id><Title>Here We Go, Obama</Title><Msg>Ready, Fire, Aim! Oh no! The smartest man in the world shot his foot off again.</Msg><Username>spam_buster_ir</Username><Timestamp>1342978136000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342978157000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Where does an unemployed student get money for all that equipment?</Title><Username>wournos.aileen</Username><Timestamp>1342926248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Silly, You are dealing with medical school. Many Parent “second” home mortgages and loans are involved. Only the wealthiest families can afford it. How do you know he was unemployed, for how long, because with his level education he could have been working at a decent rate; and therefore, easily able to afford these items. You republicans want everyone “except you” to be poor. Shame on you all. Oh, and if He could not find decent employment, then there you have his motive. You load children up with debt to levels that they feel trapped, then they cant find work, BOOM comrade! And, Your Nation Deserves it! I am shocked that it does not happen more often. This could all be the result of a BK. He did not get bailedout but BILLIONAIRE BANKER DID!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1342978157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342978282000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many are too embarrassed that they voted for Obama three times. They won't do that again. It's a secret ballot but everyone knows people who wear Crocs voted for John Kerry.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1342978282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342978371000-59</Id><Topic><Title>carl,..you're a far bigger db than I am</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342906066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 17:27:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If putin had a brain he would nuke Washington and send obama to the underworld! He would do humanity a favor! OBAMA IS A MASS MURDERER!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1342978371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342978443000-60</Id><Topic><Title>Where does an unemployed student get money for all that equipment?</Title><Username>wournos.aileen</Username><Timestamp>1342926248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 23:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he got it Fast &amp; Furiously! *** IMPEACH HOLDER NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1342978443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342978708000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you think "self made" includes using a GOVERNMENT LOAN.&gt; .................................................................. Mesa, you have bought into Obama's BS. That someone else made his business happen. (BTW, Obama will eat those words. People won't forget that remark.) What diff does it make? And what should we conclude from your continued inanity and insanity? That anyone who has ever received a buck from the gov is somehow a hypocrite if he doesn't then embrace liberalism? See that's the insidiousness of it. You receive a buck from the gov then you and the left forever hold it over one's head..unless he/she embraces your crap line of thinking. Forget that crap. Romney still made his business come true. The people are coming, Mesa.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342978708000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342978709000-62</Id><Title>you drunk Russkie taxi-dirver</Title><Msg>You can hug my root.</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer11</Username><Timestamp>1342978709000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342978717000-63</Id><Title>gallup has Obama leading</Title><Msg>Pubs like the cite Rasmussen, but that is the fox news of polling of course. They filter some of their polls using what they call "likely voters" which is code for geezer pubs just like they are. Heck, Rasmusssin has been a paid gop hack at times. an honest poll like gallup shows obama with a slight lead http://www.gallup.com/poll/150743/Obama-Romney.aspx</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342978717000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342979295000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the FACT IS, that businessman IS NOT self-made. he says he got his start with a government loan. He said, "The only way " he got his business started was because he got a GOVERNMENT LOAN. GET IT????? the "ONLY WAY" quote. A self made man would not have taken a government loan , (Or any loan i suppose) i guess all you can do now is weasel about how your and romney and the gop definition of "self-made" includes using government loans. which means Romney and the gop and your defintion of self- make is the same as Obama's, because all of us have benefited from our government one way or another, even relied on it to survive as did the Romney family in El Paso when they were destitute.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342979295000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:48:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342979566000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Still Blame Bush More Than Obama for Bad EconomyJune 14, 2012</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342979299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:48:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, you got it. here is an accurate account of the mess the gop made: "In 2000, incoming President George Bush took over a booming economy. He inherited a federal budget surplus of $236 billion, an unemployment rate of 4 percent and an average GDP growth rate for the previous four years of 4.4 percent. And the Dow was at 11,250. The economy was as good as it gets. Bush should have dampened the economy with increased taxes. Instead, like most Republicans, he ignored the Keynesian lessons of the Great Depression. He stimulated a bubble economy by cutting taxes and giving away the surplus. Romney's proposals to balance the budget in the midst of a weak economy reflect the same kind of perversity and refusal to learn from history. The Keynesianism that the Republicans reject is straightforward logic. A recession is by definition the existence of idle resources. So you put those resources to work by cutting taxes and increasing spending. Is that so hard to understand? " above from: Romney using Bush's failed playbook By PAUL HEISE Mitt Romney has clinched the Republican nomination, so it's time to ask what a Romney administration would be like. Since everyone agrees that the election will be about the economy, it makes sense to start the campaign off with that. Well, we have a model for what Republican economic policy is like: It is the George W. Bush administration. Bush was elected on the same platform Romney advocates: globalization, deregulation, privatization, and cuts in taxes and government spending."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342979566000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342979671000-66</Id><Topic><Title>US man with huge penis stopped at airport</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342979150000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>was he toe-tapping in a bathroom stall, again?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342979671000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342980719000-67</Id><Title>Netanyahu to meet like minded Romney</Title><Msg>I..sr.a.eli sets self on fire "In a letter he read out before setting himself alight, he accused the I.s.r.ae..li establishment of "taking from the poor and giving to the rich." yahoo news</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342980719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342980970000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A self made man would not have taken a government loan , (Or any loan i suppose)&gt; .................................................................. baloney! So anyone that did owes the government...with votes for government? Hah! Changing the definition to suit your political agenda. You libs do that to a faretheewell. Did the gov develop an idea? Put it into action? Did the gov put in all the hours it takes for success? BTW, Obama has never received a paycheck from a real biz so he knows nothing about it. Foreign concept to him.)</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342980970000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342981543000-69</Id><Title>NCAA to mete out Penn State punishment</Title><Msg>tomorrow from what I hear. Source says unprecedented punishment. I suppose that means cancelling at least 1 season. Very unfortunate if true. All those involved/aware/responsible are gone. They tore down Paterno's statue this morning. That's appropriate. I never liked building monuments to people who were alive when built. Anyway, if season is cancelled NCAA punishes many many people who were not involved. Hotels, restaurants, and other businesses. Mesa won't give a crap since they likely got a gov loan of some sort to start their biz.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342981543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342982421000-70</Id><Topic><Title>All those involved/aware/responsible are gone.</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342981797000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you must think PSU took no responsibility. Will cancelling a season (if that's all it is) make things right? Tellyawhat. PSU should never ever be permitted to field a football team again. Make you feel better?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342982421000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342982710000-71</Id><Topic><Title>All those involved/aware/responsible are gone.</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342981797000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Further, PSU is as liberal as almost every other college. Receipt from football funds a whole host of other sports, women's teams included. Without that funding they won't be able to fund women's softball or volleyball, for example. (Aside note: My daughter attended PSU and I once watched a women's softball game against Michigan State. Gads, to see those girls, if they were really girls. Thighs the size of tree trunks. I was frightened.)</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342982710000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342983326000-72</Id><Topic><Title>US man with huge penis stopped at airport</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342979150000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>white. that white/black thing is all bs. its all genetic.</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1342983326000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342983593000-73</Id><Topic><Title>That someone else made his business happen.</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342978817000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:40:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not just that, these idiots "could they do without their employees/managers? HELL NO! And,I thought I had a god ( thats lowercase) complex, these republicans are blasphemers!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1342983593000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342983688000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Still Blame Bush More Than Obama for Bad EconomyJune 14, 2012</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342979299000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:48:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Americans are you talking about, blacks, gays and goons? The Americans that count have seen what 4 years of Obama has done to the economy. And before that it was the Dem controlled HFC that lit the fuse and by 2007 the results were obvious and are still beech slapping us. Obama will be lucky to get a job as a bellhop at the Trump Hotel after Nov.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1342983688000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342983692000-75</Id><Topic><Title>All those involved/aware/responsible are gone.</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342981797000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There shouldn't even BE a statue of the wop to begin with.&gt; .................................................................. ooohh, that's racist drop. But I won't hold it against you the way you'd hold it against me. Agree about statue. Statues and monuments shouldn't be built when subject is alive.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342983692000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342983733000-76</Id><Topic><Title>US man with huge penis stopped at airport</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342979150000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope, I am bigger!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1342983733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342983782000-77</Id><Topic><Title>US man with huge penis stopped at airport</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342979150000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as a medical professional, i had to learn it.</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1342983782000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342983886000-78</Id><Topic><Title>what 4 years of Obama has done</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342983790000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:03:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>comrade, when are you going to learn, obama, bush and the tooth fairy all have one thing in common. They dont exist. In reality, a bunch of rich, angry white men control everything, including: OBAMA!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1342983886000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:04:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342983982000-79</Id><Topic><Title>All those involved/aware/responsible are gone.</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342981797000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DROPDORK claims to be a WOP?</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1342983982000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342984112000-80</Id><Topic><Title>All those involved/aware/responsible are gone.</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342981797000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A DA wop calling Paterno a wop. Watch out buckwheat, the commission might put a hit on you.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1342984112000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:08:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342984669000-81</Id><Topic><Title>look at all the 1 stars! Starting to be funny</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342984173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This one star loser can only be defeated if every one of us cooperate and 5-star all posts. This one star is the biggest loser here! I swear the pervert lives on this board!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1342984669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342985161000-82</Id><Topic><Title>NCAA to mete out Penn State punishment</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342981543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:25:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical American university PC Pigshyt! Only one person was responsible for the sexual abuse, to say nothing of F'ing over his best friends, and that was Sandusky... and to the extent that a handful of others (maybe 4) did not do everything they possibly could have to bring this to an end, it was not "institutional abuse" by any stretch... unless you bathe in the American PC Sewer... in which a society of gullible Fools get to feel all warm and fuzzy for a few moments as Pigs, including a bunch of scum-sucking lawyers, try to assert Common Guilt, Cash in for Millions, and take-down a great institution!! Why... because in a Pigshyt driven Society like America, a few million bucks seems to make everyone get over their "Inconsolable Pain &amp; Suffering", which explodes like Dandelions in Spring as the sweet smell of GreenBacks grows ever stronger!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1342985161000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342985256000-83</Id><Topic><Title>assbuckeroo, leading candidate for one stars</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342984682000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:18:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have never, nor will I ever give you one star, half a star or any star. You're a DA goon. I'm very selective who I rate. To tell you the truth I think it's carl. He likes the drama.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1342985256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342985460000-84</Id><Title>shrimp salad</Title><Msg>relaxing on a lazy Sunday afternoon and just finished making a delectable shrimp salad. Slight bite to it due to horseradish and a dash of tabasco. Oh, I'm good.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342985460000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342985993000-85</Id><Title>Perry urges Mitt to come clean on taxes</Title><Msg>"Gov. Rick Perry Texas Governor and former Republican Presidential candidate Rick Perry (R) has come out and urged Romney to release his returns. According to the AP, “Perry said that anyone running for office should give people what he called ‘backgrounds,’ including tax returns, if asked and if the requests are within reason.” When Perry was running for President, he released 10 years of returns. " OOPS!!!! Perry must be envious</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342985993000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342986142000-86</Id><Topic><Title>shrimp salad</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342985460000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>conch? No never. I'd try it given the opportunity. Hell,I'll try anything.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342986142000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342986275000-87</Id><Topic><Title>shrimp salad</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342985460000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my eggplant parm will buckle your knees.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342986275000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342987298000-88</Id><Topic><Title>shrimp salad</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342985460000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yay, seebes a wop too&gt; .................................................................. yeah, part. Grandmother's name was DeNessi (DiNessi, DaNessi..not sure which.) Wife is half italian. Her family's original name was DiGenaro shortened to Genaro.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342987298000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342987575000-89</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>/ why are the gop such hypocrites on the myth of the self made man? SELF MADE to most people means.......ON ONE'S OWN........ NO HELP........ and they especially mean it to mean without GOVERNMENT HELP, they hate the government and insist they don't need it and want ot drown it in the bathtub. Which goes to show how if facts don't suit some, they then redefine words to suit the facts, in this case seaburgc redfines "self-made" to mean "went and got government HELP" It's a good thing they hadn't drowned it in a tub before that businessman got it to help him.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342987575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342987749000-90</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO HELP........ and they especially mean it to mean without GOVERNMENT HELP, they hate the government and insist they don't need it&gt; ..................................................................loans repaid with interest. Would you prefer the Solyndra model? I'm sure you would. That way the biz is in the gov's pocket forever.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342987749000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342987814000-91</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, I'd love to serve you some of my homemade shrimp salad and maybe some eggplant parm. Gee, maybe then you'd like me.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342987814000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342988376000-92</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you're the weasel who if facts don't suit you, will redefine words to suit the facts, in this case seaburgc redfines "self-made" to mean "went and got government HELP" as i describe here: http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_O/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=13520&amp;tid=1061963&amp;mid=1062235&amp;tof=1&amp;rt=1&amp;frt=1&amp;off=1&amp;p=69oMj4TAWsR2mzyl1WlvEMhxjWMjH5FVjt1YK32ghLzpuIwaYjFhPzc-</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342988376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342988585000-93</Id><Title>Sen. Grassley urges Mitt to come clean on taxes</Title><Msg>Sen. Chuck Grassley The Iowa Republican joins the fray, The Hill reports: “”I don’t think he should be called on to do anything extraordinary other than what other presidential candidates have done.’ When asked if he thought Romney should do as much as prior presidential nominees have, meaning release more returns, Grassley said, ‘based upon my comment, I’d have to say yes.’</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342988585000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342988752000-94</Id><Title>fmr head of GOP: come clean on taxes Mitt</Title><Msg>"Michael Steele. The former chair of the Republican National Committee is pushing for release. He claims it will help voters trust Romney, especially since he claims there is nothing to see in the returns: “If there’s nothing there, there’s no ‘there’ there, don’t create a ‘there.’ Put out as much information as you can. Even if you don’t release 12 years worth of tax returns, at least three, four, five.”</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342988752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 16:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342993501000-95</Id><Title>Climate change affecting communities</Title><Msg>Leaders say climate is changing Native way of life Jul 19, 2012.. . WASHINGTON (AP) — Native American and Alaska Native leaders told of their villages being under water because of coastal erosion, droughts and more ..... ..+++++++++ recently , the ceo of exxon, rex tillerson agreed that human fossil fuel burning is causing global warming but said we can just adapt, no problem! "In a speech on Wednesday, Tillerson acknowledged that burning of fossil fuels is warming the planet, but said society will be able to adapt"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342993501000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342998718000-96</Id><Topic><Title>I have never, nor will I ever give you one star</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342986004000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You whiny wop. You think I care if you believe me. Things like multiple IDs and 1 star rates are childish. Do those stars define your importance in the world? They must, you're obsessed. It says something about your maturity, grow up. This is a note to the one star poster, pleeeease give buckwheat more than one, he's having a breakdown. GO PLAY OLD MAID, (for ages 4 to 8)</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1342998718000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 19:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342998720000-97</Id><Topic><Title>CO Shooting! Obama Regime Passes "Stupid Test" Yet Again!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1342960106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will the endless F'ups of the Obama Regime ever end!??? Yes... but only when they are totally destroyed! When they can't see an obsessive whack-job gun-ammo-weapons BUYER over a 60 day period, with gun shops feeding them streams of real-time data day after day... it is nothing short of Total Failure!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1342998720000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 19:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343001372000-98</Id><Topic><Title>I am questioning.why is Obama going again to Co?</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342959675000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:21:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a swing state, he's going to campaign and blame Rublicans for what happened.</Msg><Username>rojolacr</Username><Timestamp>1343001372000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 19:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343001377000-99</Id><Topic><Title>Climate change affecting communities</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342993501000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 17:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>El Nino is forming. Weather pattern will change. Stupid lemming's still believe in global warming. They believe in black mold too!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1343001377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 19:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343001579000-100</Id><Topic><Title>I am questioning.why is Obama going again to Co?</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342959675000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:21:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Campaign trip with veiled appearance of caring. He still hasn't done jack about the Ft. Hood shooter.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1343001579000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 19:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343001665000-101</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "self-made" pub caught lying</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342886930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 12:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now another massacre in Colorado and Obama shows up because he's trying to get elected and the shooter is no Mooslim.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1343001665000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 20:01:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343001757000-102</Id><Topic><Title>look at all the 1 stars! Starting to be funny</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342984173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for a change of leadership.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1343001757000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 20:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343002182000-103</Id><Topic><Title>gallup has Obama leading</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342978717000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen was most accurate poll last few elections. *** CO IA WI IN OH FL Go Romney. ORCL going to $40.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1343002182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 20:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343004387000-104</Id><Topic><Title>CO Shooting! Obama Regime Passes "Stupid Test" Yet Again!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1342960106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've wondered the same thing too. Aren't they supposed to have sophisticated data mining (maybe from Oracle?) that should have turned that slug out from under his rock. Remember, these are the same turkeys that want 100% control over your personal health care!</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1343004387000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 20:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343004752000-105</Id><Topic><Title>I am questioning.why is Obama going again to Co?</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1342959675000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:21:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt; If this was Bush,..I'd say stop the fakeness. It is all granstanding for reelection. Obama doens't give a crap about anybody. We are all "the masses." No individuals.</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1343004752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 20:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343004974000-106</Id><Topic><Title>shrimp salad</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1342985460000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"DeNessi" as in "Loch DeNessi"???</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1343004974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 20:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343005135000-107</Id><Topic><Title>NRA are crazy people&amp;gun dealer pimps</Title><Username>doodlersdoodledo</Username><Timestamp>1342876687000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 09:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the ATF/FBI or other Feds did what you suggest they should, you nuts would scream that the Constitution doesn't give them that right. How can buying "perfectly legal" firearms and legal 100 round clips and ammo call someone's intents into question??? Perhaps like Mitt, he just wanted to hunt varmints.</Msg><Username>dumb_quest</Username><Timestamp>1343005135000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 20:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343005794000-108</Id><Title>OBAMA FAILS AMERICA - AGAIN!</Title><Msg>Just in time for his reelection too! US poverty on track to rise to highest since 1960s WASHINGTON (AP) — The ranks of America's poor are on track to climb to levels unseen in nearly half a century, erasing gains from the war on poverty in the 1960s amid a weak economy and fraying government safety net.</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1343005794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 21:09:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343006121000-109</Id><Topic><Title>NRA are crazy people&amp;gun dealer pimps</Title><Username>doodlersdoodledo</Username><Timestamp>1342876687000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 09:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt! They are suppose to be doing EXACTLY what I said! The applications and background checks required for weapons purchases of 'perfectly legal firearms' were intended to identify who is buying what, when and where... and when there are UNUSUAL patterns, to immediately investigate!! It's not a matter of Gun Rights, it's a matter of potentially dangerous Red Flag multiple purchases of certain types of weapons, like assault rifles and semi-automatic pistols, over a short period of time... which even the NRA supports!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1343006121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 21:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343006282000-110</Id><Topic><Title>CO Shooting! Obama Regime Passes "Stupid Test" Yet Again!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1342960106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly!! That's why they require full details of the weapon and purchaser on every sale, which is immediatlly sent up to ATF/FBI computers!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1343006282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 21:18:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343007596000-111</Id><Topic><Title>CO Shooting! Obama Regime Passes "Stupid Test" Yet Again!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1342960106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:28:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And if those ATF/FBI computer systems can't Red Flag UNUSUAL patterns... like one guy, within a matter of TWO months, suddenly buys a top of the line S&amp;W AR-15 .223 assault rifle, a 100 round 'drum' magazine, 6000 rounds of .223 ammunition, a 12 ga semi-auto shotgun, TWO Glock 40 semi-auto pistols, even more ammunition, dozens of boxes of 40s' and 12's, and a full set of body armor, the entire system and laws are a GD Waste!! But they CAN... so why the F wasn't something done... like a visit to his apartment by a couple of cops! ONE guy with ONE Name, ONE Address, ONE Social Security Number and ONE Driver's License number buys an arsenal of weapons in matter of days and the F'ing ATF &amp; FBI, whose computers get all this information, can't add 2+2 and send someone out to talk with this POS is total Bullshyt!!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1343007596000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 21:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343009143000-112</Id><Title>Obama is an example of nature versus nurture</Title><Msg>Bad Breeding and Bad Up Bringing!</Msg><Username>wearelegion100000</Username><Timestamp>1343009143000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343009960000-113</Id><Title>3.8% Unemployment in Midland Texas!</Title><Msg>That's where George W. &amp; Laura Bush are from! Fracking oil boom!</Msg><Username>newchimpagainagain</Username><Timestamp>1343009960000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343010287000-114</Id><Topic><Title>3.8% Unemployment in Midland Texas!</Title><Username>newchimpagainagain</Username><Timestamp>1343009960000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:19:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drill Here! Drill Now! Make Jobs Here! Pay Less!</Msg><Username>newprimateagainagain</Username><Timestamp>1343010287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343010414000-115</Id><Topic><Title>3.8% Unemployment in Midland Texas!</Title><Username>newchimpagainagain</Username><Timestamp>1343009960000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:19:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>G W Bush was the GREATEST!</Msg><Username>nudeprimateagainagain</Username><Timestamp>1343010414000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343010869000-116</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA FAILS AMERICA - AGAIN!</Title><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1343005794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 21:09:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>41 Months of unemployment over 8%! FORTY-ONE MONTHS!</Msg><Username>zuccotti_park</Username><Timestamp>1343010869000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343012429000-117</Id><Topic><Title>NRA are crazy people&amp;gun dealer pimps</Title><Username>doodlersdoodledo</Username><Timestamp>1342876687000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 09:18:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't if you're a gun nut or not but ---- If you're not, how do you defend buying even one gun that would fire 100 rounds in under 2 minutes, if it didn't jam. If you are, you're whole argument is being blown out of you a.</Msg><Username>spam_buster_jr</Username><Timestamp>1343012429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343013125000-118</Id><Topic><Title>I agree with Fox on this one</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342961622000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The NRA says it's all about freedom when it comes to stock piling ammo and automatic weapons. mean while marijuana is dangerous and illegal</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1343013125000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343013260000-119</Id><Title>Penn State lucky they aren't getting the death penalty</Title><Msg>for ncaa div. 1 football they will more than deserve what ever punishment the NCAA throws at them for the negligence and crimes committed by the leaders of Happy Valley</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1343013260000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343013348000-120</Id><Topic><Title>gallup has Obama leading</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342978717000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>poll taken at NRA coventions</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1343013348000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343015279000-121</Id><Topic><Title>gallup has Obama leading</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1342978717000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>46% to 45% with 9% undecided is not a convincing lead. Looks to me like Obama is on the ropes to a man who hasn't become the Republican nominee yet.</Msg><Username>goodgal000000001</Username><Timestamp>1343015279000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:47:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343015700000-122</Id><Topic><Title>I agree with Fox on this one</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1342961622000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&gt;&gt;&gt; anyone who has military style weapons at home is a lunatic, and especially those who buy 100 round magazine Why? We may need to defend our Republic against Communists, Islamofascists or the EPA!</Msg><Username>goodgal000000001</Username><Timestamp>1343015700000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 23:55:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>