<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346817905254-1</Id><Topic><Title>gop offshoring jobs</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346682198736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should be abolished! For a long while, maybe back to Reagan, Fed Min Wage was like $5.25. But here in NYC the "market based" minimum wage was more like $8 per hour. Democrats increased Fed Minimum wage in stages and employment has gone down and unemployment up, ever since.</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1346817905254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 00:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346846004405-2</Id><Title>All DNC Convention Speakers Share The Same Core!!</Title><Msg>Slicker than a greased Pig, character assassins, bombastic, sarcastic (albeit stupid!), desperately trying to be "cool" and twisted shameless liars! Not much new here!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346846004405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 07:53:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346847982222-3</Id><Topic><Title>gop created the debt, it's their mess, and it isn't spending it's the tax cuts for the rich</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346779910209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 13:31:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yep it's very clear: more taxes + spending cuts in the amount of the complete bush tax cut = austerity." you are just plain dense and dishonest. the rich can afford some tax hikes, their tax cuts are piled up in foreign bank accounts and not spent. Tax cuts for the middleclass are SPENT , which produces DEMAND and is a stimulus, SO RIGHT NOW much revenue can be raised and it is not AUSTERITY,,, AND OF COURSE, as the economy strengthens SPENDING CUTS CAN BE MADE, AND BTW SPENDING CUTS also be MADE AND AT NO LOSS TO THE ECONOMY. for instance if $200 billion was cut from defense, but 100billion of that spent in education and healthcare MORE JOBS would be CREATED than were lost in defense...... get the picture?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346847982222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346848092036-4</Id><Topic><Title>Forward Not Back!</Title><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1346815441332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:24:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forward to more debt, greater decrease in manufacturing jobs, higher unemployment numbers, more food stamp recipients, more gay marriages, more gays in the military, another killing of OBL ( oops, he's already dead ), Onward and upward.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346848092036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:28:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346848146214-5</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOPers ranted and raved about the need for tax cuts for “job creators” but when the time came for a renewal of a payroll tax cut – which helped the middle class enormously but did almost nothing for the rich – the GOP fought it. When Obama proposed allowing the Bush tax cuts for the middle class to be renewed, the GOP refused, instead taking the proposal hostage in an attempt to force through tax cuts for the rich." Kurt Eichenwald</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346848146214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:29:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346848306514-6</Id><Topic><Title>OK. Mitt gives himself a huge taxcut and sends more money to the Caymans and switzerland</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346791844399</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still wondering about that tax break that nobody else got. Really, need an explanation.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346848306514</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346848666915-7</Id><Topic><Title>scummy gop on debt limit</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346790061252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:21:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbocrapic logic. The Bummer set a record for largest debt increase in four year period. Did it all with help of fellow Dumbocraps in Congress. FORWARD. You libs have similar thinking to clueless European countries that are going broke, broke, broke.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346848666915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346848902290-8</Id><Topic><Title>let's return to Reagan tax rates!.....( about a 23% iincrease)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346789571753</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:12:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think that 47 percent of all taxpayers then paid no federal taxes. Everyone CONTRIBUTED then. More class warfare crap from the party of Dumbocraps.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346848902290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:41:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346849683346-9</Id><Title>Mouchelle, my gal</Title><Msg>Spoke about the Bummers struggles growing up and how different they were from Romney. Of course, Romney never crooned for years,never associated with communists, never was Muslim, and was born in America. But then the Bummer never built a successful business,never served his country without pay, nor saved an olympics, and probably took from charities rather than tithing to them.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346849683346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346850450345-10</Id><Title>New Message Format Sucks!</Title><Msg>Typical Yahoo!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346850450345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346850954183-11</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>History of writing for Dumbocrapic Journals like NYT's, VF, etc. A shill for the implosion of America. Another Paul Krugman, but as a role of investigative reporter. Paid for child porn with his wife in dubious deals. Not to be considered seriously.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346850954183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346851545704-12</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's Headlines: Dems Drop 'God' From Party Platform... Jerusalem: Pro-Israel Language Removed... Endorse taxpayer-funded abortions... DNC Video: 'The Government Is The Only Thing We All Belong To'... MSNBC Anchor: Michelle 'Best Speechmaker in History of First Ladies'. USA Slips Down the Ranks of Global Competitiveness... ABCNEWSWASHPOST POLL: Obama personal popularity fading... Women Turning... Street vendors' artwork portrays Obama as Jesus... Protesters shut down street... FOOD STAMP USE CLIMBS TO RECORD 46.7 MILLION... Where's Cuomo? Where's Al Gore? Dem circus comes to town, forces Charlotte's homeless onto streets... AP: Exaggerations, Embellishments Abound on Day 1 of Convention... CNN: 'About those 4.5 million jobs'... 'A media lovefest in Charlotte'... Islamists installed in Egypt state institutions...</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346851545704</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346851670463-13</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some Obama programs embellished by Democrats By TOM RAUM and RICARDO ALONSO-ZALDIVAR Associated Press US Video Latest News Democrats creating 2016 White House buzz Some Obama programs embellished by Democrats At Democratic convention, record presence for gays Democrats' Castro says Romney 'doesn't get it' Castro says GOP pushing trickle-down economic plan Buy AP Photo Reprints WASHINGTON (AP) -- Speakers at the Democratic National Convention portrayed President Barack Obama's presidency in glowing terms Tuesday evening, but sometimes left out important details or embellished his record. Others mischaracterized programs backed by Republican challenger Mitt Romney and GOP running mate Paul Ryan. Obama's landmark health care overhaul, which Republicans lacerated at their convention last week, and his job-creation performance were among the initiatives burnished the most. First Lady Michelle Obama was the main draw and San Antonio Mayor Julian Castro the keynoter, but more than four dozen other speakers made presentations.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1346851670463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346851933541-14</Id><Topic><Title>Mouchelle, my gal</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346849683346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we are to see that Barack O'Barry is just a regular sort of guy! HAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346851933541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852070584-15</Id><Topic><Title>Mouchelle, my gal</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346849683346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(CNN) -- Anyone watching the Democratic National Convention on Tuesday night heard the number 4.5 million several times. "Despite incredible odds and united Republican opposition, our president took action, and now we've seen 4.5 million new jobs," San Antonio Mayor Julian Castro, the party's keynote speaker, said. Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel, who served as President Barack Obama's chief of staff, and Massachusetts Gov. Deval Patrick, who followed Obama's November rival Mitt Romney as governor of Massachusetts, both cited the same number. It's a big-sounding number, given the still-sputtering job market. So we're giving it a close eyeballing. The facts: The number Castro cites is an accurate description of the growth of private-sector jobs since January 2010, when the long, steep slide in employment finally hit bottom. But while a total of 4.5 million jobs sounds great, it's not the whole picture. Watch full speech of Julian Castro Photos: Best of the DNC Photos: Best of the DNC Nonfarm private payrolls hit a post-recession low of 106.8 million that month, according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. The figure currently stands at 111.3 million as of July. While that is indeed a gain of 4.5 million, it's only a net gain of 300,000 over the course of the Obama administration to date. The private jobs figure stood at 111 million in January 2009, the month Obama took office. And total nonfarm payrolls, including government workers, are down from 133.6 million workers at the beginning of 2009 to 133.2 million in July 2012. There's been a net loss of nearly 1 million public-sector jobs since Obama took office, despite a surge in temporary hiring for the 2010 census. Meanwhile, the jobs that have come back aren't the same ones that were lost. According to a study released last week by the liberal-leaning National Employment Law Project, low-wage fields such as retail sales and food service are adding jobs nearly three times as fast as higher-paid occupations. Conclusion: The figure of 4.5 million jobs is accurate if you look at the most favorable period and category for the administration. But overall, there are still fewer people working now than when Obama took office at the height of the recession.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346852070584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852119158-16</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everything you write is hyperbol - just complete paranoia remeniscent of the McCarthy era. the GOP isn't the party of less government - they're affraid of long hair and nose piercings, pink shirts on men, pot and anyone who doesn't believe in their god. bunch of lunitics addicted to war.</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1346852119158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852317557-17</Id><Title>Likeability Polls</Title><Msg>The Liberal Propaganda Media insists on announcing that polls show that Barack O'Barry is "more likeable." "More likeable" than WHAT? A rattle snake? A cockroach? I am sorry but Barack O'Barry is just NOT a likeable person! Arrogant. Elitist. Phony. Fraud. And Radical Communist (oops! I'm sorry, "Progressive"!) who disdains America, American's and our American values! Give me Mitty Romney any day of the week!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346852317557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852378769-18</Id><Title>We are not allowed to post URLs anymore!</Title><Msg>Not in Yahoo's new format. Sheese!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346852378769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852732334-19</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The so called "pay roll tax cut" reduces the tax paid in to the Social Security system. Reducing it weakens a system already under challenge due to aging baby boomers and people retiring early or claiming disability because of Obama's crummy economy. It is a guarantee that we will have to print fiat dollars or borrow more money to pay out benefits due. In the long run, the "pay roll tax cut" robs from the elderly, poor and needy so Obama can engage in short term political pandering.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346852732334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852980294-20</Id><Topic><Title>New Message Format Sucks!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346850450345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your feedback. URLs have not been allowed under the SOS for years.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1346852980294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854722211-21</Id><Topic><Title>We are not allowed to post URLs anymore!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346852378769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:39:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is really ridiculous... I did't find any important info here</Msg><Username>paulosborne667</Username><Timestamp>1346854722211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:18:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346854752615-22</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporatio - The Valuable Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>wfederico38</Username><Timestamp>1345559784000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:36:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An investor without investment objectives is like a traveler without a destination. So do invest in the right way on the right time &amp; the right amount; Feel like free bird that was never felt before. Wishing you best of luck.</Msg><Username>paulmccarthy790</Username><Timestamp>1346854752615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346855666851-23</Id><Title>Right! We Can't Go Back To Four More Years Of Obama!!</Title><Msg>Talk about a Path Forward to Suicide! Obama is the Pied Piper of Destruction!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1346855666851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855765711-24</Id><Topic><Title>Right! We Can't Go Back To Four More Years Of Obama!!</Title><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1346855666851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:34:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obama is reelected will he complain about the bad economy he inherited from his predecessor?</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1346855765711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855978103-25</Id><Topic><Title>So Just What Did Obama "Inherit"!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346789782205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If what he inherited was so bad there should have been no where to go but up. Like you said the recession ended in June 2009 before stimulus money was spent. Obaama policies limited growth and harmed the economy along with the fed.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1346855978103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857232368-26</Id><Topic><Title>So Just What Did Obama "Inherit"!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346789782205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rivlin: Obama doesn't understand realities of the Mideast By LAHAV HARKOV 09/05/2012 15:34 Knesset speaker says Democrats' removal of Jerusalem as Israel's capital from platform is a bigger problem than disagreements on Iran, may have far-reaching consequences; Ariel: Obama's true face is revealed. Knesset Speaker Reuven Rivlin Photo: Marc Israel Sellem US President Barack Obama's administration does not understand the realities of the Middle East, Knesset Speaker Reuven Rivlin said Wednesday, amid ongoing speculation of a rift in US-Israel relations. "The fact that the Democrats removed a united Jerusalem as Israel's capital from their platform is more worrying than the argument over Iran," Rivlin told The Jerusalem Post. "The change may have far-reaching consequences." Related: Liberman praises Obama, talks tough on Iran Democrats reject Republican attacks on J'lem policy Published earlier this week, the new Democratic platform speaks of US President Barack Obama’s “unshakable commitment to Israel’s security” and describes the security assistance provided by Obama to Israel. It also emphasizes that “the president has made clear that there will be no lasting peace unless Israel’s security concerns are met” and that “President Obama will continue to press Arab states to reach out to Israel.” According to Rivlin, anyone who thinks that dividing Jerusalem will bring peace is mistaken, and does not understand the Middle East. "A united Jerusalem will help bring peace and stability," he stated. The Knesset Speaker added that "rumors of a rift between Israel and the US are wrong," and that the two countries have a "sharp, unambiguous understanding" on Iran, whose nuclear ambitions threaten not only Israel, but the whole free world. Rivlin plans to discuss the Iranian threat with Italian Foreign Minister Giulio Terzi later Wednesday. MK Uri Ariel (National Union), chairman of the Knesset Caucus for Jerusalem, said Wednesday that "finally, Obama's true face is revealed." According to Ariel, Obama previously acted against Jerusalem via surrogates and messengers, but now his actions show his intentions. "We must not worry. With or without Obama, Jerusalem will stay united under Israeli sovereignty forever," the National Union MK added. Jerusalem mayor Nir Barkat dismissed the political argument altogether. “The fact that Jerusalem is the capital of the State of Israel is not a subject for debate, and its status is not affected by foreign political platforms or elections,” he said.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346857232368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857664340-27</Id><Topic><Title>So Just What Did Obama "Inherit"!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346789782205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>since when is Israel more important than looking out for our own best interests? A guy like Romney sure as heck wouldn't send his own childrend to war on behalf of another country - Romney's the guy who went to prep school and then took 4 deferments to avoid Nam. He's quoted saying he really wanted to go to Nam to help out which is complete #$%$</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1346857664340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346859254240-28</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only tax increases I've ever had came from left wing Democrats. I worked for hourly wages all my life. I have made some extra by buying various stocks including AT&amp;T through an employee stock plan. The lefties have continually increased SS taxes due to the inflation they've created through deficit financing. LBJ started stealing money from SS to finance the endless Illegal and undeclared wars of the NWO and all others BOTH Dem and Rep continued to do so. All I can say is "A pox on both their houses" and on those that continue to support the massive theft going on through the corrupt privately operated money system.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1346859254240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346861107506-29</Id><Title>Clinton &amp; Obama Rival One Another In Critical Arena!</Title><Msg>Who is the Best CON-artist in American history! Sorry Bill.. you lose! And by a wide margin!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1346861107506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861417851-30</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michelle Says “I” or “Me” 83 times by Keith Koffler on September 5, 2012, 10:51 am In her address to the Democratic Convention Tuesday evening, First Lady Michelle Obama used the words “I” or “me” 83 times, an average of more than three self-references a minute during her 25 minute speech. The emphasis on herself is of note not only because of the strikingly personal nature of the speech, but because of the remarkable suggestion by the first lady that her political views and those of her husband arise much from their own experiences than a reasoned assessment of policies and facts. Time and again in her remarks, Michelle cites examples from her life and President Obama’s that lead to policies they have tried to implement during his presidency.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1346861417851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861536938-31</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen dude</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346861536938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861625189-32</Id><Topic><Title>Right! We Can't Go Back To Four More Years Of Obama!!</Title><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1346855666851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:34:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress is the real problem Completely sold-out to special interests</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346861625189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:13:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346861850058-33</Id><Title>GOP: party of aholes, #$%$ liars and warmongers</Title><Msg>Concerned about the welfare of the rich Not concerned about the welfare of the working class Easy example: why not tax the rich and spend the money on infrastructure improvements, or start to pay down the debt? #$%$ all I believe in limited govt, but I'm not into #$%$</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346861850058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346863290861-34</Id><Title>GOP created the mess in the middle east and the economy</Title><Msg>is there any doubt who created the mess in the middle east? the gop wastes Billions in the middle east while pretending to create "beacons of democracy" and stand for fiscal restraint. Is there any doubt who wants to take on Iran on behalf of Israel?</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1346863290861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346864575662-35</Id><Title>Obama's speech tomorrow moved indoors</Title><Msg>DNC claims that the weather forcast is the reason. Thunderstorms is what they're saying. Don't believe a word of it. The reason is because DNC can't fill the stadium. Can't give away tickets. People don't want to go. As I have said, this election won't be that close.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346864575662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346865199616-36</Id><Topic><Title>yoho, you turned traitor!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1346790280885</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:24:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Izreal may be a corruption, or at least partially; therefore, side with no nation, only GOD. The true Izreal will be revealed by GOD. If these are Gods people, then they will ACT with GOD, and not depend on America. I just want everything to conclude, I await the Creator. ALL THE NATIONS ARE CONTROLLED BY SATAN, THEREFORE, GOD WILL HAVE TO SEPARATE THE WHEAT FROM THE CHAFF.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1346865199616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346866992412-37</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A History Lesson on Your Social Security Card 1934 - 1980 With the elections just a little over 2 months away you'll soon be hearing some Democrats running for political office, warning how the Republicans want to take away the old people's Social Security. Just in case some of you young whippersnappers (&amp; some older ones) didn't know this it's easy to check out, if you don't believe it. Be sure and show it to your family and friends. They need a little history lesson on what's what and it doesn't matter whether you are Democrat or Republican. Facts are Facts: Social Security Cards, issued in 1934, and up until the 1980s expressly stated the number and that card were not to be used for identification purposes. Since nearly everyone in the United States now has a number, it became convenient to use it anyway and the message, NOT FOR IDENTIFICATION, was removed. When Franklin Roosevelt, a Democrat, introduced the Social Security (FICA) Program. He promised: 1.) That participation in the Program would be completely voluntary, No longer Voluntary 2.) That the participants would only have to pay 1% of the first $1,400 of their annual Incomes into the Program, Now 7.65% on the first $90,000 3.) That the money the participants elected to put into the Program would be deductible from their income for tax purposes each year, No longer tax deductible 4.) That the money the participants put into the independent 'Trust Fund' rather than into the general operating fund, and therefore, would only be used to fund the Social Security Retirement Program, and no other Government program. Under Johnson, another Democrat, the money was moved to The General Fund and Spent 5.) That the annuity payments to the retirees would never be taxed as income. Under Clinton &amp; Gore, Democrats, Up to 85% of your Social Security can be Taxed Since many of us have paid into FICA for years and are now receiving a Social Security check every month -- and then finding that we are getting taxed on 85% of the money we paid to the Federal government to 'put away'for us -- you may be interested in the following: Q: Which Political Party took Social Security from the independent 'Trust Fund' and put it into the general fund so that Congress could spend it? A: It was Lyndon Johnson and the Democratically controlled House and Senate. Q: Which Political Party eliminated the income tax deduction for Social Security (FICA) withholding? A: The Democratic Party. Q: Which Political Party started taxing Social Security annuities? A: The Democratic Party, with Al Gore casting the 'tie-breaking' deciding vote as President of the Senate, while he was Vice President of the US Q: Which Political Party decided to startgiving annuity payments to immigrants? AND MY FAVORITE: A: That's right! Jimmy Carter and the Democratic Party. Immigrants moved into this country, and at age 65, began to receive Social Security payments! The Democratic Party gave these payments to them, even though they never paid a dime into it! Then, after violating the original contract (FICA), the Democrats turn around and tell you that the Republicans want to take your Social Security away!</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1346866992412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346868648037-38</Id><Title>46 Million Americans on food Stamps</Title><Msg>Close to a 50% increase during the Obama administration Are those recipients better off than they were 4 years ago?</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1346868648037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346869745361-39</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes. we know Romeny and Ryanulus promise full as is social security and full as is medicare to all on them now , and all within 10 years of being on them, meaning most of the boomers....... all that PLUS tax cuts and increased military spending! So you certainly lie when you say "the Democrats turn around and tell you that the Republicans want to take your Social Security away".</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346869745361</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346870017932-40</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems. Ignore Gulf Storm Victims at Convention 1:46 PM, Sep 5, 2012 • By DANIEL HALPER Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts On Monday, President Obama traveled to Louisiana to tour flood damage after Hurricane Isaac hit the Gulf region last week. "As you can see, there has been enormous devastation in St. John’s Parish, and that’s not the only place that’s been hard hit," said Obama, speaking about 35 miles from New Orleans, a city that had been devastated in 2005 when Hurricane Katrina hit. "We’ve also seen enormous damage in Plaquemines Parish and in other parts of Louisiana and Mississippi." But the devastation--which includes loss of lives--went unmentioned last night by the three major prime time speakers at the Democratic convention in Charlotte, North Carolina. All three main speakers last night, Maryland governor Martin O'Malley, San Antonio mayor Julián Castro, and First Lady Michelle Obama, failed even to acknowledge that the storm had just recently hit the Gulf Coast, a review of their prepared remarks reveals. The same storm, Hurricane Isaac, caused the Republicans to cancel the first day of their convention last week in Tampa. Meanwhile, at least 8 Americans are dead as a result of Hurricane Isaac: Related Stories As if the battered survivors of hurricane Isaac haven't been through enough already what with massive flooding, raging wind and rain, power outages and many people losing their homes, Louisiana authorities Monday pegged an eighth death on the effects of last week's Hurricane Isaac. A 90-year-old man died in a sweltering hot and humid home without electricity in suburban New Orleans. According to Jefferson Parish Coroner Gerry Cvitanovich, the man “was found in his home by family, and the home had no power to it." Parish officials have advised everyone to check on family members and get them into air conditioning somewhere or get them to a shelter. Isaac killed six people in Louisiana and two in Mississippi, according to state authorities. And at least 13,000 are still without power in Louisiana, according to CNN. "Throughout the state, at least 13,000 homes were damaged, Christina Stephens, a spokeswoman for the Louisiana Office of Homeland Security and Emergency Preparedness, said Tuesday."</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1346870017932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346870824950-41</Id><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Msg>all reference to God has been removed from the dem platform. Who are the dems trying to please with this?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346871447912-42</Id><Topic><Title>gop "economics" has nothing to do with economics, it's all tax cuts for the rich, period</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346809296547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pubs in Louisiana are no longer talking austerity and cuts, they are asking for fed money, and the scummiest most hypocritical pubs are asking for the most. Gov Jindal isn't spouting the hate government line as usual, now he wants fed gov help. Funny how pubs are like that huh?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346871447912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346871713424-43</Id><Topic><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you just plain stupid or what? God talk belongs in your chruch or mosque or synagogue, OBVIOUSLY......... what kind of crap did the pubs put in their platform about "god" ? what a silly twit you are! I guess you want a government office or bureau of god or gods or whatever.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346871713424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346872262356-44</Id><Title>is the god the gop politicizes in their political manifesto the same god for everyone?</Title><Msg>as in there is no god but allah and moohamud is the profit, that god.? for one? you can leave it to pubs to wave their religion around like a flag in public, while in private they hate the other guys religion, and call each other "cults" and the one "true" religion...... and heck , not even in private, many are such religious bigots that they advocate burning down mosques and some go out and murder seikhs....jeez..... and seabugerc is such a #$%$ bigot he attacks people WHO DON'T politicize religion and don't put religious blather and litmus tests and loyalty oath crap in their platform.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346872262356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346873650080-45</Id><Topic><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to explain what God has to do with picking the head of a secular government.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1346873650080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:34:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346875109071-46</Id><Topic><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As He should be! The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1346875109071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346875416688-47</Id><Title>Obama Has Added 13,000,000 To Food Stamp Brigade!</Title><Msg>YeeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaaa!! Let's hear about that Great Achievement tonight! And if you want to throw another 13,000,000 on the barbie be sure and re-elect this Nanny State Loser!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346875416688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346876403890-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Added 13,000,000 To Food Stamp Brigade!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346875416688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who says it's Obama, doofus? Btw, tax cuts were extended to create jobs. If they aren't working, why not rescind them?</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346876403890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346876482620-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Added 13,000,000 To Food Stamp Brigade!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346875416688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Philadelphia Food Organization Says Hunger Is Hitting More Middle Class Families September 5, 2012 12:59 PM Share this 112 By Paul Kurtz PHILADELPHIA (CBS) — The anti-hunger organization Philabundance has kicked off its annual Hunger Action Month food drive with some sobering new statistics. The US Department Agriculture says 50 million people went hungry last year. “It confirms what we’ve been seeing, that the situation is not getting any better yet — in fact, it’s slowly decaying,” says Philabundance president Bill Clark (below). clark bill philabundance kurtz Philadelphia Food Organization Says Hunger Is Hitting More Middle Class Families Clark says that in Pennsylvania, one in nine households now suffers from food insecurity. In the Delaware Valley, he says, more than 900,000 people don’t get enough food. And Clark says it’s no longer just those living below the poverty line. “The bottom of the middle class is being forced to reach out and get assistance,” Clark tells KYW Newsradio. “Their income has not kept pace with inflation, and they’re being squeeze in a vise. They just cannot get through the month.” Philabundance is asking folks to help out in a number of ways: by donating money or food, organizing a community drive, or taking part in the “Fill A Plate, Give A Meal” campaign. “With 50 cents we can acquire a meal that we can provide people,” Clark says, “so for every dollar you get two meals.”</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346876482620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346876495229-50</Id><Topic><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Nobody even knows what "god" is, so why get so pissy about it?</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346876495229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346876648084-51</Id><Topic><Title>46 Million Americans on food Stamps</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1346868648037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:10:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who says it's Obama, doofus? More likely congress is the problem.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346876648084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346876891576-52</Id><Topic><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right Mesa. But you miss the point. No surprise there. Obama needs a majority. This is not smart politically. How many are offended by this? Who are the dems trying to please?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346876891576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346877428978-53</Id><Title>Ryan requested Obamacare funds</Title><Msg>"a stark reminder that even the most ardent opponents of Obamacare privately acknowledge many of the law’s benefits................" Exclusive: Paul Ryan Quietly Requested Obamacare Cash Lee Fang on September 5, 2012 - 1:35 PM ET Republican vice-presidential candidate Paul Ryan is barnstorming the country, promising to repeal every provision of the Affordable Care Act if the Romney-Ryan ticket is elected. But a letter he wrote to the Obama administration may undermine this message. On December 10, 2010, Ryan penned a letter to the Department of Health and Human Services to recommend a grant application for the Kenosha Community Health Center, Inc to develop a new facility in Racine, Wisconsin, an area within Ryan’s district. “The proposed new facility, the Belle City Neighborhood Health Center, will serve both the preventative and comprehensive primary healthcare needs of thousands of new patients of all ages who are currently without healthcare,” Ryan wrote. Paul Ryan's request for Obamacare funds The grant Ryan requested was funded directly by the Affordable Care Act, better known simply as healthcare reform or Obamacare. The letter, among several obtained by The Nation and The Investigative Fund through a Freedom of Information Act request, is a stark reminder that even the most ardent opponents of Obamacare privately acknowledge many of the law’s benefits................</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346877428978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346878100849-54</Id><Topic><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you hear Sen. Durbin get all defensive when asked about it? Talk about a guy who was uncomfortable dealing with the question. Clearly he was embarrassed. Is this the way to get a majority?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346878100849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346878344366-55</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Added 13,000,000 To Food Stamp Brigade!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346875416688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And all these millions and milliions of Food Stamp "newbies" in a Private Economy that is doing "just fine"! Isn't that amazing! I thought Food Stamp users actually dropped in a Recovery!! Guess this is just the new definition of an Obama Recovery!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346878344366</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346879467172-56</Id><Topic><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People offended by NOT TALKING ABOUT GOD in the context of secular election are too dumb to be even considered.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1346879467172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346880149303-57</Id><Title>Godless Commies take word *DEMOCRAT* out of their party platform!</Title><Msg>What were they thinking?</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1346880149303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346881210916-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Added 13,000,000 To Food Stamp Brigade!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346875416688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US Department Agriculture says 50 million people went hungry last year. Commie propaganda #$%$ 46.7 million are on Food Stamps program. So why are they hungry? Clark says that in Pennsylvania, one in nine households now suffers from food insecurity. Yet obesity is one of America's major health problems. How can starving people be obese? “With 50 cents we can acquire a meal that we can provide people,” Clark says, “so for every dollar you get two meals.” Just where and how are they going to get two meals for a dollar? This is more commie propaganda crap.</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1346881210916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346881482439-59</Id><Title>Debbie Wasserman Schultz caught in bald-faced lie</Title><Msg>Truth, reality and integrity eludes this woman.</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1346881482439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346883587944-60</Id><Topic><Title>Debbie Wasserman Schultz caught in bald-faced lie</Title><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1346881482439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:44:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's an easy catch!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1346883587944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346883612370-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Added 13,000,000 To Food Stamp Brigade!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346875416688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"President Bush 2001- 2008, increased use of food stamps by 63 percent...... and of course he should get credit for 2009 too since that was his budget as well. ....so did you YEEEEEE HAAAAA that too, a bigger % increase than currently..... what a dishonest goofball you are!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346883612370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346884152049-62</Id><Title>romknee says, climate change IS caused by PEOPLE!</Title><Msg>HOW the F can you vote for him you stinking lying hypocrites?</Msg><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346884152049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346884948382-63</Id><Topic><Title>God out of Dem platform</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346870824950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They read your posts: Embarrassed by Republicans, Democrats amended their convention platform Wednesday to add a mention of God and declare that Jerusalem is the capital of Israel. Many in the audience booed after the convention chairman, Los Angeles Mayor Antonio Villaraigosa, ruled that the amendments had been approved despite the fact that a large group of delegates had objected. Votes don't count. The ruler dictates. That's why Nancy nominated him by acclamation. Can't wait for Slick Willie tonight.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1346884948382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346885000556-64</Id><Topic><Title>46 Million Americans on food Stamps</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1346868648037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:10:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do I sign up?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1346885000556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346885530638-65</Id><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Msg>GODLESS PIGS??? Says corpiss. The fact is,..the pigs throughout history HAD GODS! The least bit of problems CAME FROM GODLESS PIGS!</Msg><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346885945888-66</Id><Title>Tax cuts for the middleclass</Title><Msg>helped people enjoy more of their own hard earned money. Most don't even have the extra to enjoy anymore due to the ever increasing jobless numbers. messy just comes up with these wild, ludicrous remarks and sounds like he just got off the turnip truck. How do you raise taxes on a segment of the population that can no longer afford to distribute their "wealth" and support the increasing size of government? Romney knows how to "manage" money, that is why he has lots of it. You think he wants to pay more taxes for government folly? We need someone who can make changes we need, the changes we got are killing us. Who cares if Romney sends money to the Cayman Islands, I would too. You think Democrats are above skimming the system? Rangel and Geithner come to mind. Get back on the turnip truck, you twit.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346885945888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346886194158-67</Id><Title>dems are scums for adding god</Title><Msg>What #$%$</Msg><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346886194158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346886244039-68</Id><Topic><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to read a little more history, Bagger! Try starting with Hitler, Stalin and Mao... you Godless Stupid Pig!!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346886244039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346886272261-69</Id><Topic><Title>dems are scums for adding god</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346886194158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the other hand,..fight #$%$ with #$%$.</Msg><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346886272261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346886488631-70</Id><Title>I'm just home from 3 nights in La. EVERYONE there wants fed help</Title><Msg>It's quite a place... got a question about the place ? ASK ME!</Msg><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346886488631</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346886537484-71</Id><Title>Democrats Clearly Vote "NO" for God &amp; Jerusalem!</Title><Msg>But the Party bosses overrule... and call it a YES! YeeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaaa! Nothing like Democrat democracy! Never trust a GD Democrat!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1346886537484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346886910991-72</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Added 13,000,000 To Food Stamp Brigade!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346875416688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee... the number is actually a 14,000,000 jump in less than 4 years! It took Bush 8 years to add the same amount!! Obama has doubled-up!! Figures! Just as he has done on the DEBT!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346886910991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346887114951-73</Id><Topic><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corpiss, You #$%$ Hitler was a roman catholic. He grew up in lintz Austria where he was a choir boy in a catholic church where the middle-age swastika relic (a symbol of the cross from crusades) adorned the crown moldings. Hitler served as witness ( best man) for the catholic wedding of Herman Goring. -Adolph Hitler, by John Toland. Stalin ? Russian Church bells rang during the Kursk offensive (Jul 5/43) to the end of the War. Moa … Ok.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1346887114951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346887530140-74</Id><Title>Re: Godless Pigs</Title><Msg>buckwheat knows Godless. Hitler, Stalin and Mao are good starters, what about serial killers and child molesters.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346887530140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:25:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346888436419-75</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Godless Pigs</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346887530140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok smartypants What's "God"? Do you even know? Can one believe in a relationship with "God" without going to a specific church? So you have to be a church-goer, is that it? Is "God" a man in the sky that cares about you and determines your moves? Or is it just a life-force that is not human and not so personal? Or is it just a voice in your head that you talk to? Is it just your conscience? Even non church-goers have a conscience. How can you make such judgments about people and God when o one really knows #$%$ they are even talking about?</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346888436419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346888511080-76</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Clearly Vote "NO" for God &amp; Jerusalem!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1346886537484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346888511080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346888856216-77</Id><Title>buckwheat back with his usual dose of DA</Title><Msg>You keep saying Repubs are fake Christians, but you think Stalin and Hitler weren't. How you can attach religion to those monsters shows what a feeble minded goon you are. It wasn't religion that inspired their atrocities. GO PLAY OLD MAID</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346888856216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346889202741-78</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Clearly Vote "NO" for God &amp; Jerusalem!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1346886537484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blahblahblah It's meaningless rhetoric anyway It's very American - symbols and fake outrage are more important than real issues</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346889202741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346889733858-79</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Godless Pigs</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346887530140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:25:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>egeek, this is why you liberals can't argue about God. You know nothing of him. Conscience is something you can attribute to the Golden Rule, do unto others. How can I make judgements about serial killers and child molesters? Why not? On the positive side, you've come up with dumber comments.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346889733858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346890649410-80</Id><Topic><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure Pighshyt! Who the F cares about Hitler's choir boy #$%$ Naz.ism was buried in the Occult! Stalin even memorized the New Testament! Both Hitler and Stalin were total Frauds and USED religion to CON the masses... not an ounce of Christianity in their F'ing souls... or their minds! And anyone who would even suggest they were Christians is a Godless Pig!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346890649410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346890755380-81</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Clearly Vote "NO" for God &amp; Jerusalem!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1346886537484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right... The Democrat Party is a CONjob top to bottom!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1346890755380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346891008304-82</Id><Topic><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure Pighshyt! Who the fvk cares about Hitler's choir boy #$%$ Na.zis were buried in the Occult across the Regime.... mostly at and near the top! Stalin even memorized the New Testament! Both Hitler and Stalin were total frauds and USED religion to CON the masses... not an ounce of Christianity in their f'ing souls... or their minds! And anyone who would even suggest they were Christians is a Godless Pig!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346891008304</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346891008490-83</Id><Topic><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure Pighshyt! Who the fvk cares about Hitler's choir boy #$%$ Na.zis were buried in the Occult across the Regime.... mostly at and near the top! Stalin even memorized the New Testament! Both Hitler and Stalin were total frauds and USED religion to CON the masses... not an ounce of Christianity in their f'ing souls... or their minds! And anyone who would even suggest they were Christians is a Godless Pig!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346891008490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346891350933-84</Id><Topic><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This new format is pure crap! Only 3 replies show unless you click their little arrow!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1346891350933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346891486637-85</Id><Topic><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welll... it seems to depend on the length of the replies! Generally 3-6 will show up!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1346891486637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346894669586-86</Id><Topic><Title>The Party leadership is awash in Godless Pigs! Says corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346885530638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats reinstate ‘God-given’ and Jerusalem as Israel’s capital to party platform By Olivier Knox, Yahoo! News | The Ticket – 2 hrs 43 mins ago 6 Email Print CHARLOTTE, N.C.—Facing unhappy pro-Israel groups amid a Republican-led outcry, Democrats gathered Wednesday at their presidential nominating convention made 11th-hour changes to the party platform to reinstate a reference to God and a declaration that "undivided" Jerusalem is Israel's capital. There was widespread booing on the floor of the Time Warner Cable Arena in Charlotte as Los Angeles Mayor Antonio Villaraigosa led delegates in three voice votes that sounded, at best, equally divided on whether to restore language from the party's 2008 document. Observers said the boos were directed at Villaraigosa's decision to skip a formal ballot and declare the platform amended. "Jerusalem is and will remain the capital of Israel. The parties have agreed that Jerusalem is a matter for final status negotiations. It should remain an undivided city accessible to people of all faiths," the amended document read. The vote also returned this language to the platform: "We need a government that stands up for the hopes, values, and interests of working people, and gives everyone willing to work hard the chance to make the most of their God-given potential." Republicans raised a hue and cry over the Democrats' decision to no longer include the words "God-given" after David Brody of CBN News reported its absence (while also noting that the platform included a section on the importance of faith).</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1346894669586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346897828599-87</Id><Title>Interesting that Sandra the #$%$ will speak</Title><Msg>Followed by President Bill, the Molester-Rapist. Remind me who has a "War on Women"?</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1346897828599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346897927499-88</Id><Title>Elizabeth Warren - is speaking now.</Title><Msg>Admits she's the "warm up" act for Bill Clinton.</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1346897927499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898024515-89</Id><Topic><Title>Elizabeth Warren - is speaking now.</Title><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1346897927499</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:18:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She have powwow with Dumbos in Charlotte.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346898024515</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898477649-90</Id><Topic><Title>Debbie Wasserman Schultz caught in bald-faced lie</Title><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1346881482439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 17:44:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Her whole life has been a lie. We have three or four women who write editorials in our local newspaper here just like her, liberal minded fools. But they are somewhat entertaining even though they are clueless idiots.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346898477649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:27:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898611305-91</Id><Topic><Title>I'm just home from 3 nights in La. EVERYONE there wants fed help</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346886488631</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:08:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm just back from Colorado. Everyone here wants help too in spite of the great economy and employment opportunities. NOT!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346898611305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346898760779-92</Id><Topic><Title>I'm just home from 3 nights in La. EVERYONE there wants fed help</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346886488631</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:08:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad to be back from Colorado. But in Florida, there are more people here needing help than in Colorado. Guess it's the same everywhere. Go Bummer.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346898760779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 22:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>