<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349089471822-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's illegal war in Iraq wages on.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1349028689839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:11:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A new report claims previously unreported weapons can be linked to the botched Operation "Fast and the Furious," and that the U.S. supplied some of the weapons used in a massacre of young men in Mexico in 2009. The report by Spanish-language news network Univision aired on the channel Sunday night in Spanish and a partial transcript was obtained by Fox News. In the report, Univision identifies a total of 57 more previously unreported firearms that were bought by straw purchasers monitored by ATF during Operation "Fast and Furious," and then recovered in Mexico in sites related to murders, kidnappings and other actions by Mexican hit men and drug cartels. The report also reveals that the Obama administration may have indirectly played a role in the 2009 massacre, where 18 young men were killed at a rehabilitation center in the violent border city of Ciudad Juarez. The massacre was reportedly ordered and carried out by Mexican hit men. According to a Mexican army document obtained by Univision, three of the high caliber weapons used in the attack were linked to a gun tracing operation run by the ATF. The partial transcript obtained by Fox News did not specify whether this was Operation "Fast and Furious," or another similar ATF operation. The "Fast and Furious" program caught the attention of Congress and the rest of the country after weapons from "Fast and Furious" were found at the crime scene of murdered U.S. Border Patrol agent Brian Terry. One Justice Department official resigned and another retired after an inspector general report on the probe faulted multiple agencies for letting it get out of hand. Another 14 officials were forwarded for possible disciplinary action.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349089471822</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 07:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349094072026-2</Id><Title>For all you global warming wackos</Title><Msg>Antartica has set a new record for the greatest sea ice extent ever measured at either pole. Artic ice represents only 1 percent of Earths ice while Anartica represents about 90 percent of Earths ice. But the GW nuts only want to look at Artic ice cause it suits their wacko beliefs. Thank the Lord Algore lost in 2000. Now we have just one more hurtle to sanity in Nov.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349094072026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 08:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349094181828-3</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's illegal war in Iraq wages on.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1349028689839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:11:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surely you mean the war all those Dumbocraps supported after the 9/11 attacks by the Bummers good friends from the Middle East.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349094181828</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 08:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349094314736-4</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan says you're too stupid to understand his tax plan and he doesn't have time to explain it, unless you are a billionaire</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349031784672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, he said Donkeys would not understand it. They have heart but no brains.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349094314736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 08:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349096517842-5</Id><Topic><Title>As race stands, Obama within reach of second term</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1349027522824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:52:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As race stands, America in reach of total disaster. Executive orders by presidents up to Obama realm - about 150. In four years under the Bummer - 932. Pretty soon, Congress will become irrelevant.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349096517842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349096674200-6</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's jobs plan.........for china</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349015471545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bummers jobs plan for America after four years? 5 trillion additional debt.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349096674200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349096786974-7</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's jobs plan.........for china</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349015471545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 10:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solyndra! Shovel ready! Green jobs! China may be a better alternative.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349096786974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349097066368-8</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens wants YOU to pay for increased defense spending</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349013136273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax cuts to rich would run this govt for an additional five days. Only 360 more days in the year to worry about. But growing our economy is certainly not a solution. Just print more money like the Weimer Republic did in the 1930's. That produced massive inflation and Hitler. Let's see, Hitler/Obama.....Hitler/Obama. See a pattern here. Why are libiots such idiots?</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349097066368</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349097429691-9</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens wants YOU to pay for increased defense spending</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349013136273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U.S. MILITARY DEATHS IN AFGHANISTAN HIT 2,000.... AFGHAN SOLDIER KILLS 2 MORE AMERICAN TROOPS... 3 US SOLDIERS KILLED BY MOTORCYCLE BOMBER... Biden Misstates Number Of Fallen Heroes... Military absentee ballots going AWOL in 2012... PEROT: FISCAL NIGHTMARE MEANS USA COULD BE TAKEN OVER</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349097429691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349097434010-10</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens wants YOU to pay for increased defense spending</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349013136273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually W's tac cuts to the rich cost a couple trillion. and now Mittens whines about little the poor did get. Prior W many poor families paid a little income tax, but after W doubled the child tax credit they became moochers that Mittens whines about while riding a dressage horse ,sipping champagne and bragging about how stinking rich he is. "taxes are for the little people" he says.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349097434010</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:17:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349097514989-11</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens wants YOU to pay for increased defense spending</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349013136273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sunday, September 30, 2012 Univision Video: Fast and Furious Scandal Univision explores how US Weapons, given to Mexican Drug Cartels have now been traced to numerous murders in Mexico via the gunrunning program known as "Fast and Furious" Fast and Furious Scandal: New D</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1349097514989</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349097623365-12</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens wants YOU to pay for increased defense spending</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349013136273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHAVEZ TO OBAMA: I'D VOTE FOR YOU, AND YOU FOR ME... MUSLIM BROTHERHOOD: OBAMA PLANS $450 MILLION CASH FOR EGYPT... CADDELL: Mainstream Media Threatening Our Country's Future... POLL: 43% of voters certain they will vote for Romney. 42% certain they will vote for Obama. Remaining 15% either uncommitted or open to changing mind.... MORE...</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1349097623365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349097641228-13</Id><Topic><Title>why wouldn't they hate USA “imperialism,” as it used to be called?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348932118550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The US tried to prevent the spread of communism globally. It is a failed system of govt that the Bummer would like to foist on America to precipitate our failure. If you think the ME will be a better place to live under Mooslim rule, think about this. Where are Mooslims most happy? America, Canada, France, Great Britain, Italy, Belgium, Netherland, and other free countries. Where are they most miserable? Iran, Iraq, Yemen, Afganistan, Syria, Lebanon, Libya, and other countries they rule. It is a hopelessly lost people with no morals, no intelligence, no desire to be free, no desire for independence. Lost souls of the world.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349097641228</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349097779914-14</Id><Topic><Title>Romney: ‘My heart aches’ for struggling Americans</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348714581626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the Bummer and Mrs. bummer care. That's why she takes those million dollar vacations.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349097779914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349097844625-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney: ‘My heart aches’ for struggling Americans</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348714581626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder who gives more money to charity? Wonder who tithes 10 percent to hose church? Wonder who even goes to his church?</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349097844625</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349099241665-16</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this article.</Msg><Username>elodiafgo02646</Username><Timestamp>1349099241665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349101748672-17</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>hildapyi67500</Username><Timestamp>1349101748672</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349102317479-18</Id><Topic><Title>why wouldn't they hate USA “imperialism,” as it used to be called?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348932118550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure #$%$ the French and the USA left vietnam and the dominoes didn't fall, Nam is a trading partner now and mccain hugged his commie captors a few years ago. England left China and India, France left North Africa and so did Italy and germany and Spain............. now the USA continues where the others wised up and left. and who but idiots like you cry for the lost souls of "Iran, Iraq, Yemen, Afganistan, Syria, Lebanon, Libya,"......... cry all you want..... but YOU go there you hypocrite and "build it" YOURSELF if you want to reform them.......jeez and redistribute YOUR own money to your insane effort to rule the 100's of millions of people you hate.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349102317479</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349102587975-19</Id><Topic><Title>Romney: ‘My heart aches’ for struggling Americans</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348714581626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Editor's note: The following text is from a speech delivered by Democratic pollster a Patrick Caddell on September 21. It was delivered at Accuracy in Media's Conference: Obamanation: A Day of Truth. The title of the speech was “The Audacity of Corruption.” For more on Accuracy in Media, click here. Mainstream media is threatening our country's future I think we’re at the most dangerous time in our political history in terms of the balance of power in the role that the media plays in whether or not we maintain a free democracy or not. You know, when I first started in politics – and for a long time before that – everyone on both sides, Democrats and Republicans, despised the press commonly, because they were SOBs to everybody. Which is exactly what they should be. They were unrelenting. Whatever the biases were, they were essentially equal-opportunity people. That changed in 1980. There are a lot of reasons for it. It changed—an important point in the Dukakis-Bush election, when the press literally was trying to get Dukakis elected by ignoring what was happening in Massachusetts, with a candidate who was running on the platform of “He will do for America what he did for Massachusetts”—while they were on the verge of bankruptcy. Also the change from evening news emphasis to morning news by the networks is another factor that’s been pointed out to me. Most recently, what I call the nepotism that exists, where people get jobs—they’re married to people who are in the administration, or in politics, whatever. But the overwhelming bias has become very real and very dangerous. We have a First Amendment for one reason. We have a First Amendment not because the Founding Fathers liked the press—they hated the press—but they believed, as [Thomas] Jefferson said, that in order to have a free country, in order to be a free people, we needed a free press. That was the job—so there was an implicit bargain in the First Amendment, the press being the only institution, at that time, which was in our process of which there was no checks and balances. We designed a constitutional system with many checks and balances. The one that had no checks and balances was the press, and that was done under an implicit understanding that, somehow, the press would protect the people from the government and the power by telling—somehow allowing—people to have the truth. That is being abrogated as we speak, and has been for some time. It is now creating the danger that I spoke to. This morning, just this morning, Gallup released their latest poll on the trust, how much trust [the American people have in the press] —when it comes to reporting the news accurately, fairly, and fully, and [the level of their distrust] it’s the highest in history. For the first time, 60 percent of the people said they had “Not very much” or “None at all.” Of course there was a partisan break: There were 40 percent who believed it did, Democrats, 58 percent believed that it was fair and accurate, Republicans were 26 percent, independents were 31 percent. So there is this contempt for the media – or this belief—and there are many other polls that show it as well. I want to just use a few examples, because I think we crossed the line the last few weeks that is terrifying. A few weeks ago I wrote a piece which was called “The Audacity of Cronyism” in Breitbart, and my talk today is “The Audacity of Corruption.” What I pointed out was, that it was appalling that Valerie Jarrett had a Secret Service detail. A staff member in the White House who is a senior aide and has a full Secret Service detail, even while on vacation, and nobody in the press had asked why. That has become more poignant, as I said, last week, when we discovered that we had an American ambassador, on the anniversary of 9/11, who was without adequate security—while she still has a Secret Service detail assigned to her full-time, at a massive cost, and no one in the media has gone to ask why.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349102587975</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 10:43:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349103952519-20</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>hsiugmz98463</Username><Timestamp>1349103952519</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:05:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349104124320-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan says you're too stupid to understand his tax plan and he doesn't have time to explain it, unless you are a billionaire</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349031784672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan either has verbiage in this tax plan that screws the middle class or he doesn't understand the plan himself.</Msg><Username>hansstuk</Username><Timestamp>1349104124320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:08:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349104450806-22</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens wants YOU to pay for increased defense spending</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349013136273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's just it - he promises to increase spending but has no plan on how to pay for it. The plan assumes the wealthy will be "successful" and pay taxes. The GOP are a bunch of fakes when it comes to being fiscal conservatives - they're really just social conservatives who want to cut funding to planned parenthood and NPR -</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1349104450806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349104503979-23</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trickle down only works if the wealthy spend their money. Currently the wealthy are either 1.) investing, 2.) Saving. They are not 3.) spending more on random things in the USA.</Msg><Username>hansstuk</Username><Timestamp>1349104503979</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349104637477-24</Id><Title>Headline on Yahoo News</Title><Msg>"Does Wall Street Love Obama?" Of course they do. He's a stooge for the banksters like every President since at least Woodrow Wilson. He's handed out trillions of dollars to banks both here and abroad for which you and your children are abligated. Like B'rer Rabbit; "Oh please don't throw me in that briar patch, I hates it worse than poison". All the time knowing that he was "born and bred in the briar patch". His "Justice?" Dept. even says it was okay to lie and deceive people when selling them the worthless "derivatives" that caused the housing markets to collapse. I always thought that was fraud. Then between him and Bush they fill all the money handling departments in government with the very people that committed the fraud. And, "conservative" fools still defend Bush and "liberal" fools excuse the Kenyan.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349104637477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349105038205-25</Id><Title>TSTRQ</Title><Msg>TSTRQ IS ALIVE AGAIN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bonkp1</Username><Timestamp>1349105038205</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:23:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349105330558-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is stealing from our children</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349061165266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He knows it's progeny theft but the boy do not care.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349105330558</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349105540114-27</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool. Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>kendalrqu9376</Username><Timestamp>1349105540114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349105689049-28</Id><Topic><Title>why wouldn't they hate USA “imperialism,” as it used to be called?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348932118550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thing none of the anti imperialistic countries never murdered their citizens. Like what is happening in all the Mooslim countries that the Bummer wants to befriend. America bad, all third world countries good.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349105689049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 11:34:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349108227429-29</Id><Topic><Title>why wouldn't they hate USA “imperialism,” as it used to be called?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348932118550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Good thing none of the anti imperialistic countries never murdered their citizens" as in the Puritans hanging quakers in the USA , or the Civil War, or the USA murdering a million people in SE asia, or the USA giving Saddam money and weapons to kill a million Iranians, or the USA murdering hundreds of thousands in Iraq looking for wmd or whatever?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349108227429</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349108339877-30</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>yeejnq625</Username><Timestamp>1349108339877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349108483534-31</Id><Title>Mormons want revenge on the USA government?</Title><Msg>("Joseph Smith had a supposed vision (prophecy) that one day a Mormon would become President of the United States, FOR THE EXPRESS PURPOSE, of letting the Mormon Church take over the U.S. Government") Former Mormon Explains Why Mitt Romney Should Never Be President By Sarah Wood Written by: James Martin (former LDS and strongly against Romney for reasons as listed below) (EDITOR’S NOTE: We’re sharing this opinion of Mitt Romney, written by a former member of the LDS Church, unedited and uncensored. Addicting Info is not endorsing this article, or attacking the LDS Church, but we would like to give James Martin a forum to share his unique perspective.) Romney: The first thing you need to know about Mitt Romney is that he is a Mormon, aka a member of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints. They call themselves Christians, but they have so thoroughly brainwashed their members that anything the church says…goes. No matter how much Mitt Romney says he would keep his church separate from Government, and how he would never let the church come in and run Government, commands of the church come first and foremost in Mormon minds. If the church wanted Mitt to let them come in (AND THEY WOULD) and help or direct the Government, that is how it would be. Why? Because the church leaders would supposedly have a “vision” that it is God’s will. The church is all about trying to prop up the image of its founder, Joseph Smith. Joseph Smith had a supposed vision (prophecy) that one day a Mormon would become President of the United States, FOR THE EXPRESS PURPOSE, of letting the Mormon Church take over the U.S. Government. You can take it to the bank, that if Romney were President, the church leaders would have another “vision,” that a church takeover must happen. By the way, that prophecy was simple revenge for perceived wrongs done to Joseph Smith by the government. Nevertheless they treat all his prophecies seriously, no matter how ridiculous they are......</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349108483534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349111428335-32</Id><Title>Mooslims Want Revenge on US</Title><Msg>And Obama is doing it for them. Another gaff by messy, Mormons are going to take over the world. LOL!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349111428335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349111440173-33</Id><Title>Bill Cosby *I'm 83 and Tired!*</Title><Msg>I'm 83. Except for brief period in the 50's when I was doing my National Service, I've worked hard since I was 17. Except for some serious health challenges, I put in 50-hour weeks, and didn't call in sick in nearly 40 years. I made a reasonable salary, but I didn't inherit my job or my income, and I worked to get where I am. Given the economy, it looks as though retirement was a bad idea, and I'm tired. Very tired. I'm tired of being told that I have to "spread the wealth" to people who don't have my work ethic. I'm tired of being told the government will take the money I earned, by force if necessary, and give it to people too lazy to earn it. I'm tired of being told that Islam is a "Religion of Peace," when every day I can read dozens of stories of Muslim men killing their sisters, wives and daughters for their family "honor"; of Muslims rioting over some slight offense; of Muslims murdering Christian and Jews because they aren't "believers"; of Muslims burning schools for girls; of Muslims stoning teenage rape victims to death for "adultery"; of Muslims mutilating the genitals of little girls; all in the name of Allah, because the Qur'an and Shari'a law tells them to. I'm tired of being told that out of "tolerance for other cultures" we must let Saudi Arabia and other Arab countries use our oil money to fund mosques and madrassa Islamic schools to preach hate in Australia, New Zealand UK, America and Canada, while no one from these countries are allowed to fund a church, synagogue or religious school in Saudi Arabia or any other Arab country to teach love and tolerance... I'm tired of being told I must lower my living standard to fight global warming, which no one is allowed to debate. I'm tired of being told that drug addicts have a disease, and I must help support and treat them, and pay for the damage they do. Did a giant germ rush out of a dark alley, grab them, and stuff white powder up their noses or stick a needle in their arm while they tried to fight it off? I'm tired of hearing wealthy athletes, entertainers and politicians of all parties talking about innocent mistakes, stupid mistakes or youthful mistakes, when we all know they think their only mistake was getting caught. I'm tired of people with a sense of entitlement, rich or poor. I'm really tired of people who don't take responsibility for their lives and actions. I'm tired of hearing them blame the government, or discrimination or big-whatever for their problems. I'm also tired and fed up with seeing young men and women in their teens and early 20's be-deck themselves in tattoos and face studs, thereby making themselves un-employable and claiming money from the Government. Yes, I'm damn tired. But I'm also glad to be 83.. Because, mostly, I'm not going to have to see the world these people are making. I'm just sorry for my granddaughter and their children. Thank God I'm on the way out and not on the way in.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349111440173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:10:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349111676270-34</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>brigetterss5338</Username><Timestamp>1349111676270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349112269390-35</Id><Title>Obama's "No Jobs" Economy Keeps "Inflation &amp; Rates" In Check!!</Title><Msg>YeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!! What a Victory!! So take another lap, Obama... and be sure and bring your boy Bernanke along for the jog! So what if the Federal &amp; State Debt Debacle has EXPLODED!! Now everyone can go re-finance their "foreclosed" homes at 3% and invest their remaining $2100 in "Life Savings" at 2%!! You guys are just the Very Very Best!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349112269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349112432663-36</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Cosby *I'm 83 and Tired!*</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349111440173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:10:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post... assuming it's not another fake!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1349112432663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349112666504-37</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Cosby *I'm 83 and Tired!*</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349111440173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:10:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turns out it is a fake... it was actuallly written by a Marine Corps vet, Robert Hall!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1349112666504</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349114626363-38</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. I love it.</Msg><Username>elenorayis0729</Username><Timestamp>1349114626363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349116961636-39</Id><Title>Bernanke announces we turning Japanese</Title><Msg>The election is over. 4 more years of misery starting with the announcement that we are in a recession right after the election.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349116961636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349117036450-40</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>niaski08446</Username><Timestamp>1349117036450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349117560554-41</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gov't Employees Among Top Campaign Contributors to Obama... P Jobs Outlook Weak as Companies Reporting Cost Cuts... U.S. MILITARY DEATHS IN AFGHANISTAN HIT 2,000.... AFGHAN SOLDIER KILLS 2 MORE AMERICAN TROOPS... 3 US SOLDIERS KILLED BY MOTORCYCLE BOMBER... Biden Misstates Number Of Fallen Heroes... Military absentee ballots going AWOL in 2012... CA approves driver's licenses for young illegals...</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1349117560554</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349118885316-42</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>ettaqnt05534</Username><Timestamp>1349118885316</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349119025317-43</Id><Title>Why Is MSNBC #1</Title><Msg>#1 for bogus video skills. This isn't the first time but Joe "left field" Scarborough showed a clip of Romney calling Ryan a great guy and the video suggests the audience started chanting "Ryan, Ryan". Romney responded by telling them to say "Romney,Ryan". Scarborough in his arrogant stupidity, bashed Romney. The audience was actually chanting "Romney, Romney" when he told them to say "Romney, Ryan" not the other way around. Even The Huff and Puff Post slapped Joe for the intentional misleading #$%$. When the evidence proved Joe was an idiot, the network didn't bother to follow up or apologize. Desperate, dishonest Dems, always will be. Maybe messy could get a job at MSNBC, if they want bogus, messy's their guy.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349119025317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120226480-44</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>janeysoq7371</Username><Timestamp>1349120226480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120381498-45</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sen. Graham: Obama move on defense layoff notices 'patently illegal' By Jeremy Herb - 10/01/12 02:45 PM ET Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.) says that he will do anything he can to block the Obama administration from reimbursing defense contractors for severance costs if the firms don’t send layoff notices to employees. The Obama administration issued guidance Friday that said defense firms’ costs would be covered if they have to layoff workers due to canceled contracts under the across-the-board cuts set to take effect Jan. 2. Click here to find out more! The layoff notices have become a politically charged issue because they could have come just four days ahead of the election because of a 60-day notice required by federal law for mass layoffs. Graham and other Republicans were livid after the Obama administration issued the guidance on Friday telling contractors that their legal costs would be covered due to canceled contracts under sequestration, but only if they did not issue layoff notices before sequestration occurs — and before the November election. “I will do everything in my power to make sure not one taxpayer dollar is spent reimbursing companies for failure to comply with WARN Act,” Graham told The Hill in a phone interview Monday. “That is so beyond the pale — I think it’s patently illegal.” The guidance prompted Lockheed Martin — which had previously threatened to send out notices of potential layoffs to all of its 123,000 employees — to say Monday it would not send notices this year under the Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification (WARN) Act. House Armed Services Chairman Buck McKeon (R-Calif.) called the administration’s guidance “politically motivated memos with dubious grounding in the law.” “It appears companies will bow to the threat implicit in last week's OMB guidance; withhold notices today or the government might not cover your court costs down the road. Let me be clear, neither the OMB guidance nor the Lockheed decision will protect a single defense industry job if sequestration occurs in January,” McKeon said in a statement.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349120381498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349120975688-46</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop whining. Time to pay the piper. Obama has waited four years to raise taxes. You can't stop this train. The election is over, sukka. 4 more years.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349120975688</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349121948179-47</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Things must really su*ck. Uncle Ben and a bunch of Fed governors came out to verbally pump up the markets as soon as the market dropped to the same level before the Bernanke's QE forever announcement 2 weeks ago. GDP revised downward.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349121948179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349122183624-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's "No Jobs" Economy Keeps "Inflation &amp; Rates" In Check!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349112269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:24:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what if the Federal &amp; State Debt has EXPLODED!! Now everyone can go re-finance their "foreclosed" homes at 3% and invest their remaining $2100 in "Life Savings" at 2%!! You guys are just the Very Very Best! *** Now you can afford $10 per pound ground beef and $7 gasoline. That's good inflation. Everyone will get paid more than $250K per year so Obama's tax the rich policy will apply to everyone -- we are a country of rich people. We are the richest country in the world!!! 4 MORE YEARS!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349122183624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349122465314-49</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>bernardinamsl4615</Username><Timestamp>1349122465314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349122812893-50</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke announces we turning Japanese</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349116961636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Bummer is recrowned, we are headed for 16 more recession like years just like the Japanese. Sorry folks, that's what raising taxes and having a govt run economy produces.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349122812893</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349122862269-51</Id><Title>Who on earth is Mark Hurd Married to?</Title><Msg>That dirtbag has a wedding ring on right now on CNBC. What gold-digger did he marry?</Msg><Username>getanid61_is_a_conman</Username><Timestamp>1349122862269</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349122897164-52</Id><Topic><Title>Mormons want revenge on the USA government?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349108483534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Garbage post. Blablablablabla!!!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349122897164</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:21:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349123014905-53</Id><Topic><Title>Mooslims Want Revenge on US</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349111428335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got some in Libya last week. Oops, that was just a little spontaneous uprising by some friendlies.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349123014905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349123308859-54</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens wants YOU to pay for increased defense spending</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349013136273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The plan presumes we will grow our economy like we have in the past. Romney knows, unlike the Bummer, that business is our friend, not the enemy. If govt got the he'll out of the way, America could prosper. Remember Reagan and his eight successful years. Trickle down prosperity, not trickle up poverty.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349123308859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349124095205-55</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>johnkdd58540</Username><Timestamp>1349098479312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 09:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>lilaekj8221</Username><Timestamp>1349124095205</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349124239429-56</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan says you're too stupid to understand his tax plan and he doesn't have time to explain it, unless you are a billionaire</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349031784672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:03:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryanne said only the sheldon adelson types get his tax plan, which is why he donated $100million to the gop....... billionaires will pay less and the middleclass will pay more.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349124239429</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349124665433-57</Id><Topic><Title>Mormons want revenge on the USA government?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349108483534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry Reid and Obama are Mormons. Cast them out!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349124665433</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349125227720-58</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke announces we turning Japanese</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349116961636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote for Obama and pick up your new cellphone on the way out. Of course, since it's a gubment paid phone, Big Brother gets to listen in on your conversations. You can also use the phone as a personal vibrator. Obama's callin me again. I'm gonna come to the meetin and get me a slice of what she's havin.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349125227720</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:00:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349125760499-59</Id><Title>Bush appointee Bernanke doing a good job</Title><Msg>On February 1, 2006, President Bush appointed Bernanke to a fourteen-year term as a member of the Federal Reserve Board of Governors, and to a four-year term as Chairman. In 2010 Bush appointee was reappointed and the gop said OK! (Bernanke was confirmed for a second term as Chairman on January 28, 2010, by a 70–30 vote of the full Senate..........there were 18 gop votes against)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349125760499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349125803326-60</Id><Title>Even before debates, electoral map appears largely written in stone</Title><Msg>Republicans should stay home and not bother to vote! Such is the wisdom of our biased polls and biased media.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349125803326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349125988496-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's "No Jobs" Economy Keeps "Inflation &amp; Rates" In Check!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349112269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:24:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously, America will be certifiably insane if they re-elect Obama! But the irresponsibly addicted "Users" are very close to outnumbering the "Doers!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349125988496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349126082018-62</Id><Topic><Title>Even before debates, electoral map appears largely written in stone</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349125803326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no Wisdom from the Press/Media... only PC Pigshyt!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1349126082018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349127326760-63</Id><Title>TAKEOVER NOKIA ?</Title><Msg>ORACLE CAN !!!!</Msg><Username>barronsfanatic</Username><Timestamp>1349127326760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349127970955-64</Id><Title>Mittens: My fellow dressage horse riding plutocrats</Title><Msg>unless we cut foodstamps and other similar pleb handouts, our taxes might have to go as high as some of the "little people" in the middleclass. So , we must broaden the base and make the poor and the middleclass pay more, and after all it's for their own good of course.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349127970955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349131446502-65</Id><Topic><Title>2000 Soldiers Now Dead In The Afghanistan Shyt-Hole! One More Killed Today!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1349023241713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:40:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And three more US soldiers were shot and killed yesterday by yet another f'ing Islamic "Trainee"! A total waste... fighting for the Kenyan POS who hates America and is trying to gut it! White Americans, and decent Blacks and Hispanics, who for some odd reason want to vote for this fraud and con-artist have got be totally clueless!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1349131446502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 18:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349134295234-66</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens: My fellow dressage horse riding plutocrats</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349127970955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bogus Bogus, What Mitt said was if we cut unnecessary waste in government, aid to countries that don't want us there, entitlement programs and free phones, the middleclass will have taxes lowered and the "lazy people" aka liberal goons, will have to get out and work. Mormons are planning to take over the world. LOL! Hide your underwear.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349134295234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349134800479-67</Id><Title>Obama spews more #$%$. about Romney</Title><Msg>What a pathetic clown. He ain't done jack. Prolong the misery. 4 more years of bullsheet from Obama.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349134800479</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349134918865-68</Id><Topic><Title>TAKEOVER NOKIA ?</Title><Username>barronsfanatic</Username><Timestamp>1349127326760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nokia once the largest cap in Europe now selling for pennies and at only 1/3 book value. J.P. Morgan would know what to do.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349134918865</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349135019306-69</Id><Topic><Title>Even before debates, electoral map appears largely written in stone</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349125803326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:10:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No reason to vote for Obama. It's a done deal. Stay home. Rip up your early voting forms. Obama has been declared the winner by acclamation once again.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349135019306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349135209649-70</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's "No Jobs" Economy Keeps "Inflation &amp; Rates" In Check!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349112269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:24:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, I think I'll vote for Obama this time. 4 more years we will all be equal. I like Obama's plan to tax the sheet out of black athletes, movie stars and ugly crass clowns like Bill Maher who aren't even funny.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349135209649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349135452122-71</Id><Topic><Title>Bush appointee Bernanke doing a good job</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349125760499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:09:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uncle Ben has single-handedly propped up the U.S. economy in spite of an incompetent President and a bickering partisan Congress that shouldn't get paid unless they pass a budget. Imagine if we had a real President who didn't undermine our allies and bash American business. IMPEACH REID, PELOSI and NOBAMA. UNCLE BEN FOR PRESIDENT!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349135452122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349135528617-72</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke announces we turning Japanese</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349116961636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't eat the sushi!!! What happened to Carl? He must hate the new format.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349135528617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 19:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349138650367-73</Id><Title>My Taxes Invested, jokes on us.</Title><Msg>Where's that bleeping buckwheat? GM recalls 41,000 cars for fuel problems. I can lose money all by myself, I don't need the government to invest it in ventures that are failing or have mulitple production problems. Obama will raise taxes just to cover all the blunders he's backed.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349138650367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 20:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349139271745-74</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's "No Jobs" Economy Keeps "Inflation &amp; Rates" In Check!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349112269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:24:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An Obama administration appointee has resigned in connection with another bombshell report detailing the waste of taxpayer money at feel-good conferences -- this time, at a pair of Veterans Affairs summits in Orlando that cost more than $6 million. John Sepulveda, who as assistant secretary for human resources and administration was the agency's top HR official, resigned just as the VA Office of Inspector General released its 150-page report on the conferences, held on his watch in July and August 2011. The report said he "abdicated his responsibilities" in overseeing the conferences, leading to "numerous examples of excessive costs, and unnecessary and unsupported expenditures." The resignation follows that of General Services Administration chief Martha Johnson, who stepped down following a report on a 2010 Vegas conference for GSA that cost taxpayers more than $800,000. The Veterans Affairs conferences were far costlier, with the planning described as "dysfunctional" by the IG report. And the IG report included allegations that Sepulveda made a false statement to investigators, and that other VA employees broke federal law and conduct policies by accepting improper gifts from hotels during the selection process. The conferences for the department's human resources employees included a litany of expenses covering everything from whimsical videos to karaoke to hors d'oeuvres, including artisan cheese displays. One of those expenses, a video parody of the movie "Patton" in which an actor pep-talked the audience about HR "mission imperatives" in the style of the original movie's opening scene, had already drawn lawmakers' attention earlier this year when the nearly $50,000 expense first surfaced. The IG report, though, documented another $16,500 video expense for a so-called "Happy Face Video." This was a daily video recap of the prior day's conference events, which according to the report was "improperly authorized." The report specifically flagged $762,000 in "unauthorized, unnecessary, and/or wasteful expenses" -- which included the "Patton" video, as well as $43,000 in awards paid to staffers "for their roles in the management of these conferences." The IG's office tallied $6.1 million in total costs, though acknowledged the full price tag could be even higher.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349139271745</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 20:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349139386805-75</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's "No Jobs" Economy Keeps "Inflation &amp; Rates" In Check!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349112269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:24:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Requests from military voters for absentee ballots have dropped significantly since 2008, according to newly released statistics, prompting claims that the Department of Defense is dragging its feet in enacting a law meant to boost military voting. The drop in the battleground states of Virginia and Ohio is among the most pronounced. According to statistics released Monday by The Military Voter Protection Project, the number of absentee ballot requests by both military members and other overseas voters in the two states has dropped 70 percent since 2008. Virginia had nearly 42,000 total requests in 2008, compared with a little more than 12,000 this year, according to the MVP Project. Ohio had more than 32,000 in 2008, compared with 9,700 this year. The number of military voters specifically -- as opposed to military and overseas voters -- was not broken down in the latest set of statistics, but military-only numbers released by the MVP Project in August documented a similar drop-off in applications. At the time, military ballot requests in Virginia were down 92 percent. Several other states showed a precipitous drop since 2008, including Alabama, North Carolina and Florida. "We need to make military voting the highest priority. ... and we need to do it now," MVP Project founder Eric Eversole told Fox News. Sen. John Cornyn, R-Texas, said the numbers mark a "serious failure" by the Pentagon. "This is an unacceptable failure by Pentagon leaders to comply with the law and ensure our service members and their families are able to exercise one of the most fundamental rights for which they sacrifice every day," he said in a statement.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1349139386805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 20:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349139998296-76</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's "No Jobs" Economy Keeps "Inflation &amp; Rates" In Check!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1349112269390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:24:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ATLANTA - An Atlanta man says a parking officer criticized his Mitt Romney bumper sticker and then slapped a ticket on his vehicle. The Georgia Republican Party is incensed about the incident and is urging Mayor Kasim Reed to speak out. The motorist admits that he was illegally parked, but is upset over the ticketing officer's reaction to the bumper sticker. "I overheard her say that, when she saw the sticker on the back of my car, the Mitt Romney sticker, ‘Oh, I'm definitely going to give you a ticket now,'" he said. Georgia Republican Party Chairman Sue Everhart said she was surprised to hear of the incident. "I am just amazed that this happened in this city, and I know this is not what Mayor Reed would like to see his employees do. It reflects on the whole city," said Everhart. The motorist said that he'll pay the ticket, but thinks that he's due an apology. "It sounded like she was almost insulted by the fact that I had a Mitt Romney sticker on the back of my car," he said. The mayor's officer and Park Atlanta, the company the enforces parking in the city, had not responded to FOX 5's request for comment as of Thursday afternoon.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1349139998296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 21:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349142997509-77</Id><Topic><Title>TAKEOVER NOKIA ?</Title><Username>barronsfanatic</Username><Timestamp>1349127326760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yet another proof that "book value" has no value.</Msg><Username>economist_too</Username><Timestamp>1349142997509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 21:56:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349143393766-78</Id><Title>ORCL Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Msg>I hope everyone is... my guess is that a lot of you are struggling and don't know what your next move is which is deadly in this game. Make sure that you are getting up to date info on ORCL and making the most of your trades. Gotta be in it to win it... but if you are in it and are lost, start your research here. Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- goo.gl/Nmjhk</Msg><Username>alexis.mitchell1374</Username><Timestamp>1349143393766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 22:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349144161105-79</Id><Topic><Title>2000 Soldiers Now Dead In The Afghanistan Shyt-Hole! One More Killed Today!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1349023241713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:40:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>..Obama: Debate prep is ‘a drag’ . .By Olivier Knox, Yahoo! News White House Correspondent President Barack Obama phones volunteers to thank them for their efforts during a visit to at a local Obama campaign …President Barack Obama, holed up at a swank Las Vegas-area resort to get ready for his first debate with Mitt Romney, jokingly told a volunteer on Monday that debate prep can be "a drag." Obama popped in his campaign's field office in Henderson, Nev., to give staff there a pep talk and phone a few volunteers, including Andrea Stinger. Pool reporter Carol Lee of the Wall Street Journal collected his comments. "We had a great prep, and it was a lot of fun," he told Stinger. "It's very nice. Although basically they're keeping me indoors all the time. It's a drag. They're making me do my homework." Obama campaign spokeswoman Jen Psaki declined to shed much light on the president's debate prep sessions, in which Democratic Sen. John Kerry has been playing Romney. But she again described how one of Obama's key goals was battling his tendency to be long-winded. The president is trying to "make sure he is sharpening his answers and shortening the time it takes to make them." ...</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1349144161105</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 22:16:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349149120008-80</Id><Topic><Title>TAKEOVER NOKIA ?</Title><Username>barronsfanatic</Username><Timestamp>1349127326760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 17:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ORCL EYES ON nok</Msg><Username>concordkitchens</Username><Timestamp>1349149120008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 23:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>