<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349843651537-1</Id><Title>DRAM $0.64 with $6.5M Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's AMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products</Title><Msg>Dataram Corporation (NASDAQ: DRAM) has announced a huge deal with AMD on September 8. 2012 that is sure to take it to the next level in terms of revenues and net income. The stock is completely under the radar and a reason why its 0.2 X sales valuation giving it a $6.5 million market cap. The company is already almost break-even even before the upcoming AMD-related windfall. DRAM has a strong balance sheet with ZERO long term debt. Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk. AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products, increasing performance, eliminating bottlenecks and improving the gaming experience on the PC as well as other applications requiring fast processing like complex engineering simulation models. AMD Radeon RAMDisk utility will be available from October to December this year. DRAM develops, manufactures, and markets large capacity memory products primarily used in high performance network servers and workstations worldwide. The company has more than 70 Fortune 100 customers and it’s been in business since 1967. On September 8, 2012 TechNews Science and Technology published the following article about Advanced Micro Devices (NYSE: AMD) plans to launch an aggressive campaign to encourage all editions of its AMD Memory modules for desktops, and to achieve this has made an agreement with Dataram (NASDAQ: DRAM) known developer of memory modules for servers, workstations and desktops, plus other solutions and associated services; agreement that will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk and come free with AMD Memory memory modules. AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times offer up to 525% higher in games and applications (better than that offered by SSDs), increasing performance, eliminating bottlenecks and improving the gaming experience on the PC. AMD Radeon RAMDisk utility will be available from October to December this year, and although AMD or Dataram gave more details on its operation, we assume that this utility to create a RAM disk to use by way of a fast disk cache, based on the Game and application profiles present in the Catalyst Control Center utility, which comes bundled with graphics cards, motherboards (chipset) and AMD APUs. On September 14, 2012, DRAM stated the following in its fiscal 1Q 2013 earnings report: During this quarter the Company entered into two agreements which we expect will generate growth and profits for Dataram in 2013 and beyond: - An agreement with AMD provides for Dataram to develop and sell AMD licensed and branded versions of its RAMDisk software. AMD’s Radeon RAMDisk will target the gaming enthusiast community. - An agreement with Shoreline Memory Inc. ("Shoreline") and the other with Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. ("AMD") for the purpose of expanding our customer base and product offerings. The Shoreline Agreement provides for Dataram to fulfill 50% of the orders Shoreline receives from its primary customers. Management believes these agreements will provide new revenue sources and expanded markets for the Company's products. Mr. Freeman concluded, “These recent agreements and other new opportunities we are currently pursuing should provide new sources of revenue, profit and growth for Dataram in 2013 and beyond. The experience, knowledge and assets we have gained from our current RAMDisk product, in the development of caching software and in solid state products are building a strong foundation for growth.” DRAM is also an unrecognized cloud play. DRAM makes the XcelaSAN memory/storage family of products for cloud and all other applications. The company recently received $5 million from a Japanese company to allow the non-exclusive right to manufacture products using the XcelaSAN technology. ABOUT DRAM Dataram Corporation (NASDAQ: DRAM), an independent memory manufacturer, develops, manufactures, and markets large capacity memory products primarily used in high performance network servers and workstations worldwide. It offers customized memory solutions for original equipment manufacturers (OEMs) and compatible memory for computers manufactured by various companies. The company also manufactures a line of memory products for Intel and AMD motherboard based servers. In addition, it develops, manufactures, and markets a line of storage caching products. The company sells its memory products to OEMs, distributors, value-added resellers, and end-users. Dataram Corporation was founded in 1967 and is based in Princeton, New Jersey</Msg><Username>bt.bigten</Username><Timestamp>1349843651537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349846573922-2</Id><Title>Obama Wants to use Spy Drones in USA!</Title><Msg>On Wilcow! show (e.g. BlazeTV) it was announced that the Obama Admin is arranging for up to 30,000 Drones to be used over the USA. Currently there is no existing law as to how the spy drones can be used (except that they can't be armed.) A member of ACLU was on Wilcow! show arguing that we need legislation to assure that the are used in "appropriate" ways. (Say, only with legal warrants for serious crimes.) But certain law enforcement officials want the ability to track everybody, everywhere, at all times. Big Brother is WATCHING!</Msg><Username>goodgod000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349846573922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349846766358-3</Id><Title>SMILE! You're on Candid Camera!</Title><Msg>Program On NPR Radio: The kind of video cameras used on police cars cost only $15,000 to mount. They film constantly and wirelessly send images to home servers. If your car is on the street it is likely that it's license plate has been photoed, with GPS coordinates. There are arguments about how long the police can retain the data collected on citizens cars where there is no probable cause to believe the citizen is involved in illegal activity. But car repossession operators have also discovered the cameras. And the $15,000 cost is small. There are national organizations of private data collectors who pay to have their spy cars driven day and night to record all the license plates of everybody, everywhere. If they desire to reposes your car, they look up the license plate in their database and pick a convenient time and place for them to grab your car. (I wonder how long it will be before private detective agencies and divorce lawyers get wind of this database?) Just because I'm paranoid, doesn't mean they're not out to get me!</Msg><Username>goodgod000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349846766358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:26:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349847109626-4</Id><Title>Puddles of Goo? Brainless Slime Molds Have Memories</Title><Msg>Physarum leaves a slime trail of "memory." When Physarum was able to detect its own trail, it reached the food about three times more often and about 30 percent faster, on average. Slime molds blinded to their own trails spent almost 10 times longer pointlessly re-exploring areas they had already visited. Too bad Liberals don't have memories about how badly communism &amp; socialism have failed every time they have been tried. Liberals leave lots of slime trails too!</Msg><Username>goodgod000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349847109626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875107021-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Wants to use Spy Drones in USA!</Title><Username>goodgod000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349846573922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:22:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what an idiot. old, old old news..... from bush era...... heck why not ban cops and cop radars and so forth? nothing like the pro criminal conservative ajole like you...... who are all for sticking a probe up a woman's vagina , but against using drones to fly over polluting CAFOs.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1349875107021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349875729552-6</Id><Title>Tired of 4 years of socialism</Title><Msg>CEO to Workers: You'll Likely Be Fired If Obama Is Re-elected. We don't get fooled again.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349875729552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349875742413-7</Id><Title>"remember, Reagan proved deficits don't matter" D##K Cheney, GOP, like Mittens</Title><Msg>"unless money is loosened up, the sucker could go down" W. bush, gop, like mittens..... who is actually just a rerun of bush.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349875742413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:29:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875823394-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Wants to use Spy Drones in USA!</Title><Username>goodgod000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349846573922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:22:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Brother is watching you. They have pre-cogs who can detect think crimes. Take your soma and call me in the morning.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349875823394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:30:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875996088-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama getting illegal donations funneled through China!</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349839497438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama congratulates Hugo Chavez, socialist dictator and enemy of America, on his fraudulent re-election.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349875996088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349876484067-10</Id><Topic><Title>Have you noticed hardwaredummyfromleftfield's MO?</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349822312519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He says stupid stuff on one day. Every sane person refutes him. Next day he says the same stupid stuff again as if nothing happened. Everybody refutes him again. Third day he says same stupid stuff again as if it was new and fresh. *** It's the standard S8T8F8U Obama brainwashed lemming protocol. Obama ain't done nuttin for blacks. He's made things worse. Watch for the Biden gaffe. Tsunami will ensure Obama celebrates a quiet anniversary next year. No one will want to talk to him or Michelle. Get out and STAY OUT!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349876484067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877422663-11</Id><Topic><Title>New Nickname for Obama</Title><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1349823238197</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Bird is on public assistance. Obama wants to keep him there, just like he wants to do with a majority of the population. The dependency agenda in actions.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1349877422663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878094101-12</Id><Topic><Title>"remember, Reagan proved deficits don't matter" D##K Cheney, GOP, like Mittens</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349875742413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cheney aways had his heart fixed at hospitals that the government has "taken over" to use a Mitt lie of an expression. why did he never complain about "socialist" healthcare at Bethesda Naval Hospital?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349878094101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878319666-13</Id><Topic><Title>Sesame Street requests Obama take down Big Bird ad</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349808986191</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 14:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big Bird Obama ad blowback -- Obama has big bird eyes. President Obama campaign ad gets blowback from Sesame Street owners who demand he cancel his ad. Obama talk like Big Bird when he want to.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349878319666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349878470932-14</Id><Title>Occupy Sesame Street fails</Title><Msg>Obama gets blowback...comes out bashing banks again...says strongest mortgage bank in USA (Wells Fargo) is a fraud. Do we really need 4 more years of this #$%$.? We don't get fooled again!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349878470932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878684967-15</Id><Topic><Title>DRAM $0.64 with $6.5M Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's AMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products</Title><Username>bt.bigten</Username><Timestamp>1349843651537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:34:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am looking at DRAM's Level 2 and it seems like there are not many shares for sale. One buying push and this one could sail to $1+</Msg><Username>jonny.deener</Username><Timestamp>1349878684967</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879572537-16</Id><Title>We need a Mosque of Latter Day Prophets!</Title><Msg>International and evangelical! It will fix Islam!</Msg><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349879572537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:32:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879977486-17</Id><Title>Rasmussen Poll: Romney Leads in 11 Swing States</Title><Msg>Obama is imploding. Mitt Romney continues rising in the polls, and is leading President Barack Obama in 11 key swing states 49 to 47 percent. Biden will sink the ship tomorrow. Loose lips. Obama shoulda picked Hillary.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349879977486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349880095090-18</Id><Title>Steve Wynn, former Obama supporter says, *I created 250,000 jobs! Obama NONE!*</Title><Msg>Mr. Wynn is tired of wealthy people being caricatured by Obama as a greedy millionaires and billionaires who don't pay their fair share. He says, "I give 120% of may annual salary to charity. How much do you give, Mr. President!" This former Obama supporter now says Obama is the worst president in his lifetime!</Msg><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349880095090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880157692-19</Id><Topic><Title>"remember, Reagan proved deficits don't matter" D##K Cheney, GOP, like Mittens</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349875742413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least Pubs like Reagan and Bush knew the difference between billions and trillions. Get a clue Bozo.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349880157692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880293468-20</Id><Topic><Title>We need a Mosque of Latter Day Prophets!</Title><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349879572537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:32:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have all the men who love Sharia Law living as women for the rest of their lives! It will be a cure to the next generation of dip sticks!</Msg><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349880293468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880313562-21</Id><Topic><Title>"remember, Reagan proved deficits don't matter" D##K Cheney, GOP, like Mittens</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349875742413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheney had his heart fixed free of cost like the 50 percent who pay nothing for their free health care. Obummercare gonna just let HHS head and 15 member board just let you DIE. Like the previous response, get a clue Bozo.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349880313562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349880587005-22</Id><Title>Romney now leads in 11 swing states</Title><Msg>America the Beautiful. Socialism/Communism on the wane.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349880587005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880755084-23</Id><Topic><Title>We need a Mosque of Latter Day Prophets!</Title><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349879572537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:32:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you imagine hardwaregurufromtheheartland wearing a burqa and living as he would have women live for the rest of his life! NO ACCESS TO THE INTERNET! The WORLD would be a better place!</Msg><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349880755084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880799323-24</Id><Topic><Title>We need a Mosque of Latter Day Prophets!</Title><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349879572537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:32:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!!!!</Msg><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349880799323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880909098-25</Id><Topic><Title>Occupy Sesame Street fails</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349878470932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBABA IS A FAILURE!</Msg><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349880909098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880981714-26</Id><Topic><Title>Have you noticed hardwaredummyfromleftfield's MO?</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349822312519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need to try and punish Eric Holder for treason.</Msg><Username>thevoiceofbibleprophecy</Username><Timestamp>1349880981714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349881935154-27</Id><Title>W's last budget request was 63% more than his first..Obama's 2012 is about 2% more than his first</Title><Msg>W's fy 2009 budget request was 43% more than the one he requested in 2005. who increased federal spending the most? Obama's 2012 is about 2% more that his 2010 budget (his first) isn't it clear who has increased federal government spending more? fy 2002 budget ....1.9 trillion 2006 budget ....2.7 trillion.........(submitted in 2005)..... a 42% increase...over 2002 WOW. quite an increase! 2009........Bush requested $3.1 trillion.....63% more than his first.... fy 2010 3.72 trillion 2011 3.63 trillion 2012 3.79 trillion...... a 1.9 % increase over his first budget fy 2010</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349881935154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349882127495-28</Id><Title>Mitten's wears Frenchified mormon underwear?</Title><Msg>nothing worse than frilly mormon underwear. Maybe that is why he hates half of Americans and said it's not his job to represent them</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349882127495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:15:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882189070-29</Id><Topic><Title>W's last budget request was 63% more than his first..Obama's 2012 is about 2% more than his first</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349881935154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:12:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Mark Twain once said, there are lies , damn;$&amp; lies, and just plain statistics.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349882189070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349882436954-30</Id><Title>Jack Welch gotta be right</Title><Msg>A drop of .4 percent unemployment in one month has happened only four times in the last sixty-five years and these were in times that the economy was strongly rebounding. A GDP of 1.5 percent is anything but a strong economy. Lies, damn&amp;$):@ lies, and statistics again.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349882436954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349882471900-31</Id><Title>A CEO to his employees</Title><Msg>Long, but worth reading Subject: Message from David Siegel Date:Mon, 08 Oct 2012 13:58:05 -0400 (EDT) From: [David Siegel] To: [All employees] To All My Valued Employees, As most of you know our company, Westgate Resorts, has continued to succeed in spite of a very dismal economy. There is no question that the economy has changed for the worse and we have not seen any improvement over the past four years. In spite of all of the challenges we have faced, the good news is this: The economy doesn't currently pose a threat to your job. What does threaten your job however, is another 4 years of the same Presidential administration. Of course, as your employer, I can't tell you whom to vote for, and I certainly wouldn't interfere with your right to vote for whomever you choose. In fact, I encourage you to vote for whomever you think will serve your interests the best. However, let me share a few facts that might help you decide what is in your best interest.The current administration and members of the press have perpetuated an environment that casts employers against employees. They want you to believe that we live in a class system where the rich get richer, the poor get poorer. They label us the "1%" and imply that we are somehow immune to the challenges that face our country. This could not be further from the truth. Sure, you may have heard about the big home that I'm building. I'm sure many people think that I live a privileged life. However, what you don't see or hear is the true story behind any success that I have achieved. I started this company over 42 years ago. At that time, I lived in a very modest home. I converted my garage into an office so I could put forth 100% effort into building a company, which by the way, would eventually employ you. We didn't eat in fancy restaurants or take expensive vacations because every dollar I made went back into this company. I drove an old used car, and often times, I stayed home on weekends, while my friends went out drinking and partying. In fact, I was married to my business — hard work, discipline, and sacrifice. Meanwhile, many of my friends got regular jobs. They worked 40 hours a week and made a nice income, and they spent every dime they earned. They drove flashy cars and lived in expensive homes and wore fancy designer clothes. My friends refinanced their mortgages and lived a life of luxury. I, however, did not. I put my time, my money, and my life into this business —-with a vision that eventually, some day, I too, will be able to afford to buy whatever I wanted. Even to this day, every dime I earn goes back into this company. Over the past four years I have had to stop building my dream house, cut back on all of my expenses, and take my kids out of private schools simply to keep this company strong and to keep you employed. Just think about this – most of you arrive at work in the morning and leave that afternoon and the rest of your time is yours to do as you please. But not me- there is no "off" button for me. When you leave the office, you are done and you have a weekend all to yourself. I unfortunately do not have that freedom. I eat, live, and breathe this company every minute of the day, every day of the week. There is no rest. There is no weekend. There is no happy hour. I know many of you work hard and do a great job, but I'm the one who has to sign every check, pay every expense, and make sure that this company continues to succeed. Unfortunately, what most people see is the nice house and the lavish lifestyle. What the press certainly does not want you to see, is the true story of the hard work and sacrifices I've made. Now, the economy is falling apart and people like me who made all the right decisions and invested in themselves are being forced to bail out all the people who didn't. The people that overspent their paychecks suddenly feel entitled to the same luxuries that I earned and sacrificed 42 years of my life for. Yes, business ownership has its benefits, but the price I've paid is steep and not without wounds. Unfortunately, the costs of running a business have gotten out of control, and let me tell you why: We are being taxed to death and the government thinks we don't pay enough. We pay state taxes, federal taxes, property taxes, sales and use taxes, payroll taxes, workers compensation taxes and unemployment taxes. I even have to hire an entire department to manage all these taxes. The question I have is this: Who is really stimulating the economy? Is it the Government that wants to take money from those who have earned it and give it to those who have not, or is it people like me who built a company out of his garage and directly employs over 7000 people and hosts over 3 million people per year with a great vacation? Obviously, our present government believes that taking my money is the right economic stimulus for this country. The fact is, if I deducted 50 percent of your paycheck you'd quit and you wouldn't work here. I mean, why should you? Who wants to get rewarded only 50 percent of their hard work? Well, that's what happens to me. Here is what most people don't understand and the press and our Government has chosen to ignore — to stimulate the economy you need to stimulate what runs the economy. Instead of raising my taxes and depositing that money into the Washington black-hole, let me spend it on growing the company, hire more employees, and generate substantial economic growth. My employees will enjoy the wealth of that tax cut in the form of promotions and better salaries. But that is not what our current Government wants you to believe. They want you to believe that it somehow makes sense to take more from those who create wealth and give it to those who do not, and somehow our economy will improve. They don't want you to know that the "1%", as they like to label us, pay more than 31% of all the taxes in this country. Thomas Jefferson, the author of our great Constitution, once said, "democracy" will cease to exist when you take away from those who are willing to work and give to those who would not." Business is at the heart of America and always has been. To restart it, you must stimulate business, not kill it. However, the power brokers in Washington believe redistributing wealth is the essential driver of the American economic engine. Nothing could be further from the truth and this is the type of change they want. So where am I going with all this? It's quite simple. If any new taxes are levied on me, or my company, as our current President plans, I will have no choice but to reduce the size of this company. Rather than grow this company I will be forced to cut back. This means fewer jobs, less benefits and certainly less opportunity for everyone. So, when you make your decision to vote, ask yourself, which candidate understands the economics of business ownership and who doesn't? Whose policies will endanger your job? Answer those questions and you should know who might be the one capable of protecting and saving your job. While the media wants to tell you to believe the "1 percenters" are bad, I'm telling you they are not. They create most of the jobs. If you lose your job, it won't be at the hands of the "1%"; it will be at the hands of a political hurricane that swept through this country. You see, I can no longer support a system that penalizes the productive and gives to the unproductive. My motivation to work and to provide jobs will be destroyed, and with it, so will your opportunities. If that happens, you can find me in the Caribbean sitting on the beach, under a palm tree, retired, and with no employees to worry about. Signed, your boss, David Siegel</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349882471900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882713657-32</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wears Frenchified mormon underwear?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349882127495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:15:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hate is a strong word. I think he resents the 47 percent who contribute little to Obummers wasteful spending habits. Or maybe he resents the millions Mouchelle spends on her vacations on the taxpayers dime. Better yet, the additional revenue drain that his expanded govt poicies put on America, like the 837 czars he has appointed so far.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349882713657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883044951-33</Id><Topic><Title>Rasmussen Poll: Romney Leads in 11 Swing States</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349879977486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why doesn't the Bummer just run on his superb record. Why isn't Axlerod espousing the virtues of the Bummers last four years. Well, never mind. Just a senior moment.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349883044951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883449595-34</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's wears Frenchified mormon underwear?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349882127495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:15:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Frilly?" I was in the Army with many Mormans. Some wore what we called "Mormon Chaps", Nothing more than knee length tights that showed they had done a certain ritual in their church. I would trust Mormons many times over most of the Kenyan's gang.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349883449595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883477648-35</Id><Topic><Title>W's last budget request was 63% more than his first..Obama's 2012 is about 2% more than his first</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349881935154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:12:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there's no doubt Bush inherited a bunch of credit cards with zero balances and the managed to max them out while telling people "deficits don't matter". And the GOP has people thinking they're fiscally conservative???</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1349883477648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885201243-36</Id><Topic><Title>W's last budget request was 63% more than his first..Obama's 2012 is about 2% more than his first</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349881935154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:12:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you would know all about lies. You are one of the most dishonest people posting here, and your comment is typical of your hypocrisy and weasel nature... the fact is, george w bush, gop REQUESTED $3.1 trillion for fy 2009. that is about 42% more than he requested in 2005 for fy 2006, and 63% more than he requested in 2002. when you compare obama's budget requests or even the actual spending, there is a 2% increase from fy2012 from fy 2010.......easy to see who has increased federal government spending more, isn't it? Now wonder you are such a weasel when it comes to facts and the real world.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349885201243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885561171-37</Id><Topic><Title>A CEO to his employees</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349882471900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>boss to employees: you can suck my rear end and vote for who i tell you to vote for or you are fired. I will lie to you and abuse you. and never mind that i am a tax cheat who who leave town if i don't get my way and continue with the lowest taxes in generation or even get them lowered, it will leave the country traitor that i am..... but of course i will expect you to pay taxes to protect me overseas and to let me come back if the locals over there try to make me pay for anything, then you can take me back like the USA did for Mitten's family, who was on welfare when the came running back to the USA.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349885561171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886125494-38</Id><Topic><Title>A CEO to his employees</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349882471900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>boss to employees: " i am a weinie traitor and you are my slave so you have to listen to my politics. and remember my hero the bully and robber baron Jay Gould who said : "I can hire one half of the working class to kill the other half."............ Never forget that even though i am a liar and a traitor you must do as i tell you or i will run away! and you will still have to pay taxes to protect me overseas and to let me come back if it all goes bad, like what happened to Mitt's family" "also nevermind that i am whining about the lowest taxes in generations and that the higher tax Clinton era saw FAR MORE job creation than the gop era of bush." "now, each of you, my employees, can come and kiss my rear end to show that you will do as i have told you to do", and don't forget that all new brides must let me have them first, as is the way rulers such as myself"</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349886125494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349886294705-39</Id><Title>It's a terrible sin to call someone a "LIAR" when he/she isn't....</Title><Msg>All those demorat mouths will pay the price when their report card comes forward. There will be a lot of tongues on fire for a long time....</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1349886294705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:24:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349886526075-40</Id><Title>Voters trust Romney more than Obama</Title><Msg>Who needs 4 more years of bashing American business, lies and broken promises? Time to get back to work!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349886526075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349886909232-41</Id><Title>Have you also noticed</Title><Msg>That high profile celebs and entertainers who were hitched to Obama's wagon in 2008 are not speaking out this time for him. I remember Chris Rock glorifying Obama and never missing a chance to bash Bush. Obama is following in Bush's footsteps and Chris says nothing, won't say anything bad and can't say anything good. Sean Penn absent and incognito. Oprah completely disappeared from the political podium. James Carville, an Obama cheerleader before has left the round table discussions that he headed. Obama has pretty much let down his most ardent supporters and the most unhappy was Chris Matthews who was taken away in a straight jacket to emphasize his discontent. He could be on SNL.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349886909232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888364330-42</Id><Topic><Title>A CEO to his employees</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349882471900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Envious, aren't you Mesa? Envy is one of the 7 deadly sins. It will eat you up.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349888364330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349889060617-43</Id><Title>billionaire koch brothers praise votes of gop bigots who have written in support of slavery.</Title><Msg>"Americans for Prosperity, the super PAC backed by billionaires David and Charles Koch, has distributed mail praising votes cast by two members of the Arkansas House of Representatives who have written in support of slavery. The mailings -- which do not focus on slavery or racial issues -- were distributed as part of an AFP plan to blanket Arkansas on behalf of Republican state legislative candidates as the GOP battles to retake the state legislature for the first time since the Civil War. The two legislators -- state Reps. Jon Hubbard of Jonesboro and Loy Mauch of Bismarck -- have a history of pro-slavery positions, according to recent reporting by the Arkansas Times. Hubbard was revealed to have written that slavery may "have been a blessing" in a 2010 book, while Mauch authored a series of letters to the editor in the last decade that espoused pro-slavery views, writing that former President Abraham Lincoln was a "neurotic Northern war criminal" and comparing Lincoln and Civil War generals to Nazis.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349889060617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889470733-44</Id><Topic><Title>A CEO to his employees</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349882471900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sad pathetic brat seaburg. sure, right, i am envious of a #$%$ traitor who is such a jackas.s he forces his politics on his employees...... i hope he leaves the country and then when the same happens to him as it did to mitten's family, he should not be allowed to come back to the nation he whines about paying his fair share to...... and it is likely, #$%$, that i pay a higher burden in taxes than either you or him. and for sure , unlike #$%$ like you two, i have served the nation in combat, have my campaign medal, and belong to the vfw. You are such a coward, weasel, and dishonest person that i have no idea how you can stand yourself.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349889470733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349889969724-45</Id><Title>come on you weasel republicans</Title><Msg>. explain how mitten's miraculous fix of medicare gets paid for: All 55 and older get the full, as is , no changes to, medicare....... and all under age 55 get the same , if they "choose" it over a mitten's voucher.............. so , medicare went from being near broke, to totally fixed , good to go AS IS for EVERYONE.. even those younger than 55 can choose traditional as is medicare as per mitt's promise at the debate......................wow!.......... .details, please you weasels.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349889969724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890904847-46</Id><Topic><Title>Voters trust Romney more than Obama</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349886526075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul Ryan, Joe Biden, Lara Logan, Stacey Dash, and Big Bird Wednesday, October 10, 2012 - The Tygrrrr Express by Eric Golub SOUTH FLORIDA, October 10, 2012 – President Barack Obama had an air of invincibility built by belief in his own intellectual superiority and reinforced by his supporters. Yet the veneer came crashing down when he was crushed in his debate with Governor Mitt Romney. In a twisted cruel fate that could not happen to a "nicer" guy, Mr. Obama has sent current Vice President Joe Biden to the rescue. The issue is not that Mr. Biden is an entertaining gaffe machine who is never held accountable for comments that would be treated by the media as idiocy if uttered by Republicans. The issue is not even that his opponent Congressman Paul Ryan is an intellectual titan, who unlike many politicians, actually does know what he is talking about. What really matters is that the deck is stacked against Mr. Biden. Mr. Ryan has to argue that Mr. Obama's policies are a disaster, and that a change is imperative. Mr. Biden has to defend the indefensible. He will play the loyal attack dog and get in the gutter. It is expected of him. Mr. Biden cannot brag about his experience. Spending thirty years in Congress is not a selling point. He certainly cannot brag about his foreign policy experience. The media neglects to mention that he recommended breaking Iraq into three separate nations. Mr. Ryan will bring this up if necessary. Simply put, Mr. Biden has hung around the Senate for three decades without accomplishing much. Without surfing the internet thoroughly, most people off of the top of their heads cannot mention anything Joe Biden has done. Therefore, Mr. Biden will continue the Obama tradition of treating debates as school playground "rankout contests" that are not so funny when adult Americans are suffering. The war on women will be mentioned. Perhaps Mr. Ryan will mention that the real war on women happened in the Middle East, where reporter Logan was sexually assaulted while her assailants yelled "Jew" over and over. Ms. Logan is not Jewish, but she is one women who understands that keeping women safe is not about Sandra Fluke and her platitudes. It is about creating a stable world. Ms. Logan made it clear that the Obama administration are a bunch of foreign policy incompetents who are doing nothing as the world burns. If Biden dares try to continue the Stephanie Cutter and Barack Obama strategy of blaming Romney for the deaths of others, then perhaps Mr. Obama's policies can be blamed for the assault on Ms. Logan. After the gender card, Mr. Biden will be tempted to play the race card. Actress Stacey Dash, a black woman, just announced her support for Mr. Romney. Liberals responded on Twitter by spewing racist venom at her. This is what liberals due to minority conservatives, and Mr. Obama and Mr. Biden never have the honor or the decency to stand up and condemn such rhetoric. Mr. Obama preached from his pulpit that he wanted a more civil tone, which meant that his side should lash out while conservatives are silenced. Then Mr. Biden will make imbecilic remarks about Big Bird. If ever there was proof that liberals are a bunch of children, just observe the ridiculous commercial focusing on Big Bird. While liberals talk about Big Bird, the Middle East is burning, and Americans are now learning that the administration covered up the truth of the September 11th, 2012 attacks. They were planned and requests for more security were ignored by the administration. This is in addition to the coverup over green energy fraud from Solyndra and their failed cousins, as well as an anti-gun control sting known as Fast and Furious that left an American border agent killed. Joe Biden will spend the entire debate trying to change the subject. He will say that Mr. Romney and Mr. Ryan will make things worse, but ignore who has actually failed in front of us all the last four years. While he and the liberals live onSesame Street, the rest of us will focus on improving the real world. Not everybody agrees with the ideas Mr. Ryan puts forth, but at least he has them. As for Mr. Biden, it will take every ounce of discipline for Mr. Ryan not to ask questions that many of us ask. Joe, what do you do all day? What have you been doing the last four years? Why are you even here? What are you going to do the next four years? Has Mr. Obama even told you? Mr. Ryan is so incredibly superior to Mr. Biden that he has to guard against overconfidence. Unlike Mr. Obama, Mr. Ryan possesses humility, which should solve that problem. The media may be tempted to judge the race based on the "point spread" of expectations, where Mr. Biden "wins" if he fails to actually light himself on fire on the stage like Daffy Duck. The times are serious, and Mr. Ryan is a serious thinker and policy analyst. He is that rare mix of interesting wonk. Mr. Biden is that rare combination of a man who has nothing to say while saying virtually everything, or anything</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349890904847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892148391-47</Id><Topic><Title>If Romney wins it will be bad for the nation, a worse disaster than bush most likely</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349802000491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:00:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if the mitten's wins the gop will own medicare and social security , so their whiny lies about them will have to stop, they will own these "entitlements" they used to hate . and i guess i will just have to take my Romney tax cuts on top of my bush tax cuts and add them into the unchanged , as is, "entitlement" Romeny and the gop promise me. Thanks gop, you will own medicare and social security and you have promised them as is for most of the boomers who will be on them out into the 2040s...... and you promised the same traditional medicare for all younger than 55 if they "choose" it............ so finally, if Romney wins the gop will have to shut up about the "entitlements" which are no longer a problem.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349892148391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894055167-48</Id><Topic><Title>Voters trust Romney more than Obama</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349886526075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:28:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well stated. Ryan has a grip on the fiscal cliff that faces America. If they get into real economic matters, Biden is in big trouble.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349894055167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894394004-49</Id><Topic><Title>If Romney wins it will be bad for the nation, a worse disaster than bush most likely</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349802000491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 13:00:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disaster. Disaster. What the he'll do you libiots think the past four years have been. If it got any worse, Canada and Mexico will look at America as a third world country. Obummer has no clue about anything except it's nice to phiss away money to unions and green fools. Oh, and it's nice for Mouchelle and kids to spend millions of our tax dollars on vacations abroad. Another clueless #$%$. E.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349894394004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894694690-50</Id><Topic><Title>come on you weasel republicans</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349889969724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:26:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grow our economy with free enterprise, not govt as king. Reagan did it by lowering tax rates, reducing roadblocks to success for small and large companies, Amazing what man can do if govt just gets out of the way. Again, for the clueless. Reagan doubled tax revenues in just eight years. Trickle down works. Trickle up poverty doesn't.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349894694690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:44:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349895132084-51</Id><Topic><Title>A CEO to his employees</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349882471900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:21:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you exemplify my contempt for the left. You call this guy a traitor. Care to explain why? You make no sense. Force his politics on employees? Hardly. He just provided them with a straight answer as to what will happen if Obama is re-elected. And there you go again with that fair share crap the left loves to spew so much. How does your combat experience enter into the debate? Oh I see. It's to bolster your cred when that trash leftist drivel rolls down your chin. Call me a brat? I take care of my own, always have. My kids take care of themselves. I do not expect to live off the sweat of others. No one owes me anything in tht regard.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1349895132084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349895513489-52</Id><Topic><Title>W's last budget request was 63% more than his first..Obama's 2012 is about 2% more than his first</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349881935154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:12:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least Bush summited a budget, unlike Obummer and Dingy Harry. Easy to see who has contributed to our national debt more than any other president in history. Easy to see who tried to buy union votes by screwing the GM bondholders. Easy to see who wasted more money on green crap than any other president in history. Easy to see who lied more about being transparent in govt matters. Easy to see who promulgated 932 executive orders in under four years, while all presidents before him passed one-sixth as many. Easy to see who has hired so many lobbyists after saying he would never have a lobbyist in his administration. Easy to see who has so many tax cheats in his administration. Easy to see who has alienated so many foreign countries who were considered friends. Easy to see who is an anti imperialists because of his socialist background. Easy to see which presidential family has spent millions of dollars on vacations abroad, at the tax payees expense. These are facts and are the real world. Get a clue libiot.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1349895513489</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897602340-53</Id><Topic><Title>Have you noticed hardwaredummyfromleftfield's MO?</Title><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349822312519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 18:38:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See, he's doing it today too. Same stupid CBO numbers rehashed the Democrat way.</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349897602340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897855790-54</Id><Title>Democrats claim: Only Obama can save Big Bird and Elmo!</Title><Msg>Too bad he didn't care to save Ambassador Chris Stevens. IRS data shows that Sesame Workshop (owners of Big Bird and Elmo) are worth around $350 million and earn about $114 million per year. Seems to me that Ambassador Chris Stevens was more desperately in need of saving.</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349897855790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898196854-55</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats claim: Only Obama can save Big Bird and Elmo!</Title><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349897855790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even Sesame Workshop has said they don't really need a government subsidy. But Ambassador Chris Stevens was begging Obama Admin for backup. But Obama needed a "spontaneous riot" to fit into his UN speech about capitulating America's First Amendment and supporting the Islamic extremists proposed international law of banning defamation of Islam. What can I say: If you want to make an omelet you have to crack some eggs. Ambassador Chris Stevens and the other four America's were (in Obama's mind) a worthy sacrifice as martyrs to Islam! ***</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349898196854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349899022302-56</Id><Title>david siegel rehashed an old chain letter, which is out on snopes</Title><Msg>this guy and his trophy bimbo are building a 90K sq ft house, the largest in the us, and i should feel sorry for him? stop being so gullible, you drooling idiots. lol</Msg><Username>mister_molester</Username><Timestamp>1349899022302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899141001-57</Id><Topic><Title>W's last budget request was 63% more than his first..Obama's 2012 is about 2% more than his first</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1349881935154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:12:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you're saying start ridiculously high so subsequent budgets don't look so good? Stay away from the market...you obviously don't understand numbers.</Msg><Username>eddiekosmic</Username><Timestamp>1349899141001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902038665-58</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats claim: Only Obama can save Big Bird and Elmo!</Title><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349897855790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Associated Press issued a mea culpa Wednesday after it was criticized for releasing a photo earlier this week that showed Republican presidential Mitt Romney bending over while a seemingly astonished schoolgirl gawked at him from behind. In 2008 critics also took both the Reuters and Associated Press to task when photos of then-vice presidential candidate Sarah Palin's legs and high heels were featured in photos and young male supporters appeared to be looking up her skirt. The most egregious photo came from Reuters photographer Carlos Barria. Reuters ran this caption with the photo: "A supporter listens to Republican vice presidential nominee Alaska Governor Sarah Palin during a rally in Bethlehem, Pennsylvania October 8, 2008. REUTERS/Carlos Barria." The Associated Press ran this caption with the photo of Ms. Palin's legs and shoes: "Supporters listen to Republican vice presidential running mate, Alaska Gov. Sarah Palin, legs visible, during a rally with Republican presidential candidate, Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz., not visible, in Bethlehem, Pa., Wednesday, Oct. 8, 2008. (AP Photo/Gerald Herbert)." Will Reuters and AP apologize for the photos of Palin’s legs? Read more: http://www.foxnews.com/opinion/2012/10/10/bias-alert-flashback-remember-photos-palin-legs/#ixzz28vmoq3lR</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1349902038665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:47:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902061321-59</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats claim: Only Obama can save Big Bird and Elmo!</Title><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1349897855790</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:37:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Associated Press issued a mea culpa Wednesday after it was criticized for releasing a photo earlier this week that showed Republican presidential Mitt Romney bending over while a seemingly astonished schoolgirl gawked at him from behind. In 2008 critics also took both the Reuters and Associated Press to task when photos of then-vice presidential candidate Sarah Palin's legs and high heels were featured in photos and young male supporters appeared to be looking up her skirt. The most egregious photo came from Reuters photographer Carlos Barria. Reuters ran this caption with the photo: "A supporter listens to Republican vice presidential nominee Alaska Governor Sarah Palin during a rally in Bethlehem, Pennsylvania October 8, 2008. REUTERS/Carlos Barria." The Associated Press ran this caption with the photo of Ms. Palin's legs and shoes: "Supporters listen to Republican vice presidential running mate, Alaska Gov. Sarah Palin, legs visible, during a rally with Republican presidential candidate, Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz., not visible, in Bethlehem, Pa., Wednesday, Oct. 8, 2008. (AP Photo/Gerald Herbert)." Will Reuters and AP apologize for the photos of Palin’s legs?</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349902061321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902602247-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Wants to use Spy Drones in USA!</Title><Username>goodgod000000001</Username><Timestamp>1349846573922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:22:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You wingnuts are in a bind. Who should you hate Obama or the ACLU??? 'Tis a puzzlement1</Msg><Username>dumb_quest</Username><Timestamp>1349902602247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902970708-61</Id><Topic><Title>Rasmussen Poll: Romney Leads in 11 Swing States</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349879977486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen---- snicker, snicker!</Msg><Username>economist_too</Username><Timestamp>1349902970708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906099276-62</Id><Topic><Title>6 Years ago, Democrats seized control of congress...</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349727991031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney, of course, was referring to the fact that 47% of Americans don't pay federal income tax. He insinuated that they contribute nothing to government so why would they vote for someone that wants to tax them less (Romney) instead of give them more free money (Obama). Democrats rightly point out that the 47% still pay FICA tax if they work as employees. 2 points: 1. FICA funds Social Security, which was created as an "insurance program". FICA isn't a tax, it's an "insurance premium"... and it's been made increasingly progressive as time has passed. 2. The employe also pays FICA for his employees (60% of americans surveyed didn't know that... I wonder how THEY'LL vote). It used to be that the employee paid 6.2% of his pay toward FICA, and the employer paid 6.2%... or half of it. A couple years ago, Obama reduced the employee's FICA to 4.2%... so that he'd stimulate the economy by taking it to Walmart to buy Chinese stuff... but he left the employer's portion of FICA at 6.2%... ... meaning that now the employer provides 60% of his employees' Social Security... ... and that employer might well be part of the top 1%... who collectively provide 38% of all government revenues that come from the individual federal income tax. Amazing... yet Obama still says it's "unfair" and has his followers actually BELEIVING that. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1349906099276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:54:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349912071087-63</Id><Title>Downplaying Libya, Fateful For Obama</Title><Msg>Romney won't have to go to any lengths to secure the election. Obama has put a noose around his own neck and Libya is just the last in a string of dodging his responsibility. How does any Pres look at the consequences of what happened in Libya and not feel some measure of regret and remorse? Not this guy, he backs off and we hear nothing. Hillary should have been mindful of the situation that was brewing and why didn't she step up and demand heightened security? State Dept Officials are having a hard time explaining what went wrong after the fact. Whatever they say will not be good for Obama, is my guess and rightly so.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349912071087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349917818908-64</Id><Topic><Title>Downplaying Libya, Fateful For Obama</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1349912071087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:34:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were 230 "security incidents" (e.g. caused by organized terrorists) in Libya before the attack on on embassy in Libya. According to Barack Obama the 231st incident (the attack on our embassy) was caused by spontaneous civil disorder over an obscure video. Obama continues with the lie that it was a spontaneous riot over a video. I wonder which member of the Muslim Brotherhood, working in the Obama Admin, told him that. But our congressional investigation is clearly showing that there was not riot before the attack. There was only a heavily armed attack. And that the Obama Administration had plenty of warning, months in advance, that it was coming.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1349917818908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349918700333-65</Id><Topic><Title>It's a terrible sin to call someone a "LIAR" when he/she isn't....</Title><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1349886294705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:24:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mandan? Is that a reference to Mandan "Indians?" Most don't know it but those "Indians" when first found in Minnesota by early explorers were blond and blue eyed. No one really knows where they came from. Some think they were descended from early Vikings that traveled from the East Coast to middle America. Most also don't know of the Whites that lived in So. America and even on Easter Island. Think "Kennebunk Man".</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1349918700333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349919461741-66</Id><Topic><Title>Rasmussen Poll: Romney Leads in 11 Swing States</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349879977486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IBD/TIPP Poll Sponsored by: IBD/TIPP 2012 Presidential Election Daily Tracking Poll Day 2: Oct. 10, 2012 Romney: +5.0 Romney’s lead widened to 5 points from 2 points on Tuesday, as he continues to chip away at key Obama support. Romney’s edge among independents widened to 20 points from 18 just a day before. Obama’s lead among women narrowed from 10 points to 8 points. Romney also continues to make inroads among middle-class voters, moving from a 6-point lead against Obama with this group to a 10-point lead. The current data include only polls taken after Romney’s resounding debate win over Obama on Oct. 3.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1349919461741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349920021365-67</Id><Topic><Title>Rasmussen Poll: Romney Leads in 11 Swing States</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349879977486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Mexican telecom mogul who holds the title of world's richest man, and one of President Obama's top donors are both getting even richer from the U.S. government program that supplies so-called "Obamaphones" to the poor. Carlos Slim, who has an estimated net worth of $70 billion, owns a controlling stake in TracFone, which makes $10 per phone for each device it provides to poor Americans. The company, whose president and CEO is Frederick “F.J.” Pollak, also makes money from extra minutes and data plans it sells to subscribers who get phones and service through the government's Lifeline program. The program, which began in the mid-1980s, has exploded in the past four years after being expanded from supplying landlines to the poor to providing cellular phones. “I’m not against a company making a profit. If they are making money off lifeline, the blame goes to the federal government for creating the program." - Rep. Tim Griffin (R-AR) The phones came into the national spotlight after a viral video surfaced on YouTube in which a Cleveland, Ohio, woman praised the president, saying he needed to be re-elected because he gives out free phones. “Everybody in Cleveland, every minority, got an Obama phone. Keep Obama as president. He gave us a phone. He gonna do more,” the woman said in the video. Slim’s Movil America owns TracFone and recently snapped up service provider Simple Mobile for $100 million. TracFones and Simple Mobile service are huge players in the Lifeline program through the company's “SafeLink Wireless” brand. TracFone had 3.8 million subscribers through the federal program as of late 2011. Pollak has donated at least $156,500 to Democratic candidates and committees this cycle, including at least $50,000 to the Obama campaign. His wife, Abigail, is a campaign bundler for Obama and has raised more than $632,000 for the president this cycle, and more than $1.5 million since 2007. She has personally contributed more than $200,000 to Democratic candidates and committees since 2008. The Pollaks hosted Obama at their Miami Beach home in June for a $40,000-per-plate fundraising dinner, and hosted a similar event with Michelle Obama in July 2008. The couple personally donated a combined $66,200 to Obama’s re-election effort that year.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1349920021365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349921493442-68</Id><Title>Obama or your job</Title><Msg>Don't bite the hand that feeds ya.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349921493442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349924755773-69</Id><Title>Obamagate -- cover-up of 9/11 Libya attack</Title><Msg>There was no mass protest against a film in Bengazzi. It was a quiet night at the embassy before the attack. Al Queda is re-forming in Libya. Obama told a BIG LIE and the LIB MEDIA SLURPED IT DOWN...</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349924755773</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349924919446-70</Id><Title>Jack Welch back in the USSR</Title><Msg>Freedom of Speech is a thing of the past. You cannot say anything attacking Dear Leader. What part of Shut the F*** UP DO YOU NOT UNDERSTAND????</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1349924919446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>