<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346299583132-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama took Home Ec. for His Science Requirement</Title><Username>i_got_yer_big_finger_right_here</Username><Timestamp>1346207319357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:28:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like everything else, Nobama failed Home Ec. also. You say he did not fail, show me his college and law school grades as proof. Until I see proof, Nobama failed everything.</Msg><Username>ltclou</Username><Timestamp>1346299583132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 00:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346318689000-2</Id><Title>hey Mesa</Title><Msg>In her speech last night, Condi Rice talked about how people should not be jealous and envious of another's success. Were you paying attention?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346318689000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 05:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346321949000-3</Id><Title>beware of open mics</Title><Msg>as this guy from Yahoo news found out. "Romney's happy to see black people drown" http://www.politico.com/news/stories/0812/80405.html?hp=l5</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346321949000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 06:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346324159000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Mahr on Leno right now,,,he said Ryan is DEFICIT CREATOR, not deficit hawk</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346300635000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 00:23:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sooner this piece of sub-human excrement, Bill Maher, ends up face down in a Park Ave rain-filled ditch the better!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346324159000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 06:55:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346326236000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan claimed Obama to blame for GM plant closing BEFORE</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346319998000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 05:46:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No he didn't you stupid POS... he said Obama promised in a 2008 campaign stop that the plant would remain open.... but it was closed and has never been reopened! Ryan blamed Obama for Promising Bullshyt... which is all we ever get from this incompetent fool! As Ryan said, Obama tries to turn his Promises into his Record! That's all Obama has to run on... Pigshyt Promises!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346326236000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 07:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346326457000-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Press Love Their Hatchet &amp; Fluff Jobs!!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1346258103000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:35:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MSNBC, CNN, NBC, CBS, ABC, PBS, NPR, HBO and The NY Times... all PC left-wing Nanny State Democrat Pumping Whores!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_press_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346326457000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 07:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346327676000-7</Id><Title>the racist season</Title><Msg>great piece here. From the dems' point of view everything is racist. It's all they got. Of course, if everything is racist then nothing is racist. That's the effect of the dems dumbing it down so far and so often. When real racism shows up no one believes it. http://www.politico.com/news/stories/0812/80430.html</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346327676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 07:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346331047000-8</Id><Title>Obama's Levee Rebuild In New Orleans Another Failure!</Title><Msg>The stupid SOB's turned Plaquemines Parish into a swimming pool... leaving the backside levee weak and low and the front-side along the Mississippi stronger and higher! So naturally the water flowed in from the backside, topping that levee, and could not escape... at least not until they blow up the levee on the Mississippi! The flooding was worse than in Katrina! A few PUMPS inside the Mississippi Levee would have prevented the 10 ft flooding!! STUPID!!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346331047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346334564744-9</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1346278937608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new regulations will have people driving the highways at 70+MPH in plastic shells.... this is actually Obama's SS &amp; Medicare plan as highway deaths will go up 10 fold and payments will decrease dramatically</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1346334564744</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 09:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346337098000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Levee Rebuild In New Orleans Another Failure!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346331047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is that the same person you give no credit for getting OBL? lol</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1346337098000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346337595000-11</Id><Topic><Title>What a day!</Title><Username>phyliss_maude</Username><Timestamp>1346329944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Getting good benefit.</Msg><Username>karissa_consuelo</Username><Timestamp>1346337595000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346339279000-12</Id><Topic><Title>What a day!</Title><Username>phyliss_maude</Username><Timestamp>1346329944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are best.</Msg><Username>roxane_jewell</Username><Timestamp>1346339279000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346339522000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Levee Rebuild In New Orleans Another Failure!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346331047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong Putz... I give your boy Obama all the credit in the world for sitting in the Oval Office or in a Limo and telling people to "go do it"! Nothing More... be it with Bin Laden or the New Orleans levees! As such, at the very least, his name gets to be associated with both of those missions... as well as, BTW, the butchering of 22 Navy Seals who died only because Obama insisted on doing weeks and weeks of self-congratulatory pumping and spewing to the world!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346339522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346341384182-14</Id><Topic><Title>LIES and half truths</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1346334967018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 09:56:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No conscience</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341384182</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346341785481-15</Id><Topic><Title>New mileage standards would double fuel efficiency</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1346278937608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one will buy them. Will buy trucks instead. Can't put the family and all the things to carry in a small lightweight vehicle. We already had mileage standards for cars and it ended large cars, it sent people to 14 mpg SUV's instead of 18-20mpg sedans. Stupid politicians think they can mandate technological change. They have been subsidizing solar since the failed Dept of Energy and still do after Solyndra. Foolish waste of money by ideologues with zero technical nor economic understanding.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1346341785481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:49:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346341926412-16</Id><Topic><Title>gop to tax the rich and corporations LESS</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346260705708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:18:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Considering more companies are incorporating outside of the US it would be a lot smarter to get a smaller amount in taxes from them and have them stay than zero when they leave. Stupid shortsighted tax policies we have in place.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1346341926412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346341971269-17</Id><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Msg>Only thing they really care about is money. What's up with the anti-science? What's up with all the lying? What's up with all the concern for the rich/investor class but none for the working class? What's up with the relentless complaining about Obama but no constructive/realistic counter-proposals? Mitt Romney/Paul Ryan emblematic of the party. I'm starting to hate all you bullshltters.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346343851439-18</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am surprised that you know a word like emblematic</Msg><Username>bearteu01</Username><Timestamp>1346343851439</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346343907626-19</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their is no conscience in pretending a tax hike on the rich will be more than a drop in the ocean of debt. There is no conscience in not addressing entitlement reform. Their is no conscience in forcing young people into failing entitlement systems. There is no conscience in pretending to be anti war while having even more die in needless wars during the Obama term over than the Bush years. Their is no conscience in runnning up more debt pretending against all evidence, past and present, that massive government spending has ever worked to create an economic recovery. Their is no conscience in taking away peoples options and choices on health insurance. Their is no conscience in overriding the constitution with executive orders, devaluing elected representation.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1346343907626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346343936023-20</Id><Topic><Title>gop to tax the rich and corporations LESS</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346260705708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:18:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok, let those companies move their people to the cayman islands, they can live there and work there and raise their kids there, but screw if they think they can sell their products here and not pay taxes.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346343936023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346344200978-21</Id><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Msg>Romney gift to corporations in 2015, a $96 billion tax cut, a trillion over ten years..... guess who gets to make that up? not the Romney types who will be paying ZERO income taxes...... so who will be paying for the increased military spending the gop pumps, and the promises romeny makes to the boomers of FULL as is entitlements?.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346344799000-22</Id><Topic><Title>FU corpiss you overflowing w/S</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346342656000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:04:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOLOL!! You're so full of Democrat PC Pigshyt, baggerboy, that Truth may well kill you! Gee... what a delightful thought! Pigs dying of Truth!!! The perfect solution!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346344799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346345538000-23</Id><Topic><Title>What a day!</Title><Username>phyliss_maude</Username><Timestamp>1346329944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 08:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>tresa_shanna</Username><Timestamp>1346345538000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346345938202-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney caved in to extremist loons when he picked Ryan in a hail mary pass</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346159569041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 09:12:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris Matthews and MSNBC Now Claim the Word 'Chicago' Is Racist By Rusty Weiss | August 30, 2012 | 00:12 248 742 Reddit1 13 A A Chris Matthews was on Hardball tonight covering the Republican National Convention with guests Eugene Robinson of the Washington Post and John Heilemann of New York Magazine. In what is seemingly the natural progression of things these days with Matthews, the subject of the 'otherization' of the President was being discussed. Because, if you weren't aware already, Barack Obama is black, and any time a Republican chooses to discuss the failure that is his administration, the media will be there to quickly remind you that they only feel that way because of his skin color. But tonight's episode of race-baiting with Chris Matthews was a bit odd in that the panelists somehow came to the conclusion that reminding people of the President's roots in Chicago politics is racist. In fact, simply saying Chicago is racist. (Video below). Robinson sets the racial tone by saying (h/t The Right Newz): "It's all part of this Barack Obama as 'other' sort of blanket campaign that has been waged by the Republican Party for some time now. It may be gaining some traction now, though I wonder why now as opposed to a bit closer to election." Matthews then demonstrates his mind-numbing ability to take an idiotic statement, amplify it, and subsequently make it exponentially more idiotic coming from his mouth, when he said this: "Yea, well let me ask you about that gentleman. What about now, is this constant barrage of assaults, saying the guy is basically playing an old game of demagoguery politics, where you take the money from the worker bees and give it to the poor people to buy votes. That's basically what they're charging him with. Old big-style, big-city machine of 50 years ago."</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346345938202</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346346537103-25</Id><Title>Ryan lies about everything</Title><Msg>he makes it seem like he is just a regular guy,Ryan says , "I still live on the same block where I grew up," but he doesn't mention that he happens to live in a 5,800-square-foot mansion that is listed on the historic register.............nor does he mention that he came to DC at age 21 and has been there ever since working for those who buy him the $350 bottles of wine he is fond of.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346346537103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346346714978-26</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>messy, you missed the best part. Romney is gutting government and cutting spending, they won't need more taxes. No tax hikes for anyone and tax cuts for the middleclass continue. In 5 years we should be half way out of debt. Obama struck out. Let Romney have at bat.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346346714978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346347045000-27</Id><Title>being successful in business</Title><Msg>"Being successful in business. That's a good thing." -----------Paul Ryan</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346347045000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346347239077-28</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Romney is gutting government and cutting spending" ##############################################################################not anytime soon, and the spending cuts are unclear, vague in the future promises..... the tax CUTS are up front, and right off the bat romney will rack up the HUGEST deficits in history.... i doubt he even intends to keep his promise to the elderly and the boomers to give them full as is medicare and social security, typical lying gop to buy their votes with promises he has no intention of keeping.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346347239077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346349050530-29</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax hikes on the rich would raise big money. You are right both parties need to address entitlements. Wars are on Bush's platter, largely. You are right about debt, but both sides are complicit. Romney's stated plans to cut taxes and spend more on the military, with no mention of what's to be cut, are pie in the sky. Neither party is adult enough to support Simpson-Bowles as they should. Regarding choice in health coverage, Obamacare/Romneycare have no bearing on this. I live in Massachusetts. With mandated insurance you can still choose your plan or your doctors, same as before.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346349050530</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346349492592-30</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buying votes with promises he has no intention of keeping. Sort of like Obama? The difference is Romney has a unique plan, it's called responsibility to the voters. Obama's loyalty lies with the fat cats on WS. You libs sure are freaking out with your own lies about Romney. The problem is you're surmising what he will and won't do. You're in for a shock.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346349492592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346351381965-31</Id><Title>Ryan Driving LIbs Nuts</Title><Msg>Why are you so jealous of the rich, messy? Ryan didn't pick his parents or his fortuante circumstances. The Kennedy's didn't either and Teddy was the biggest bull thrower in Wash. Only thing going for him was the family name and $$$$$$$$. Does that count? Idiot!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346351381965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346352423957-32</Id><Title>Ryan is just a liar and an extremist</Title><Msg>USA would already have a good bipartisan debt deal were it not for the lunatic Ryan who made sure Simpson-bowles and the "gang of six" debt deals got wrecked. Ryan is just a snotty brat grover norquist type who says "compromise is like date rape" and "drown the government"....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346352423957</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346353039967-33</Id><Title>Mitt made his money loading up companies with debt, then taking millions and leaving town</Title><Msg>"And this is where we get to the hypocrisy at the heart of Mitt Romney. Everyone knows that he is fantastically rich, having scored great success, the legend goes, as a "turnaround specialist," a shrewd financial operator who revived moribund companies as a high-priced consultant for a storied Wall Street private equity firm. But what most voters don't know is the way Mitt Romney actually made his fortune: by borrowing vast sums of money that other people were forced to pay back. This is the plain, stark reality that has somehow eluded America's top political journalists for two consecutive presidential campaigns: Mitt Romney is one of the greatest and most irresponsible debt creators of all time. In the past few decades, in fact, Romney has piled more debt onto more unsuspecting companies, written more gigantic checks that other people have to cover, than perhaps all but a handful of people on planet Earth. By making debt the centerpiece of his campaign, Romney was making a calculated bluff of historic dimensions – placing a massive all-in bet on the rank incompetence of the American press corps. The result has been a brilliant comedy: A man makes a $250 million fortune loading up companies with debt and then extracting million-dollar fees from those same companies, in exchange for the generous service of telling them who needs to be fired in order to finance the debt payments he saddled them with in the first place. That same man then runs for president riding an image of children roasting on flames of debt, choosing as his running mate perhaps the only politician in America more pompous and self-righteous on the subject of the evils of borrowed money than the candidate himself. If Romney pulls off this whopper, you'll have to tip your hat to him: No one in history has ever successfully run for president riding this big of a lie. It's almost enough to make you think he really is qualified for the White House."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346353039967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346353397910-34</Id><Title>how #$%$ Mittens made his money</Title><Msg>"the way Mitt Romney actually made his fortune: by borrowing vast sums of money that other people were forced to pay back. ..... Mitt Romney is one of the greatest and most irresponsible debt creators of all time. ...... [Mittens] ...makes a $250 million fortune loading up companies with debt and then extracting million-dollar fees from those same companies, in exchange for the generous service of telling them who needs to be fired in order to finance the debt payments he saddled them with in the first place. ......................... ......................................................................................................................................................................................................... That same man then runs for president riding an image of children roasting on flames of debt, choosing as his running mate perhaps the only politician in America more pompous and self-righteous on the subject of the evils of borrowed money than the candidate himself. ........." matt taibi</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346353397910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346354456399-35</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's tax hikes on the rich are estimated at the high end to raise $65 billion. On 1.2 trillion dollar debt estimated for this year. Likely would raise only about 1/2 that based on prior experience. The mandate is for full coverage low deductible plans. Far more expensive and more insurance than most need. Does an older couple or a couple that had a vasectomy or tubes tied need to purchase maternity coverage? Would it be better to get a high deductible and save on the annual premiums? That is an attack on freedom to make the best decision for yourself and family and guarantees people will pay far more for insurance than needed. Obamacare is big insurance companies best friend. What they wouldn't want is open competition accross state borders, options to choose appropriate levels of coverage. Repeal it!</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1346354456399</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:20:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346355786351-36</Id><Topic><Title>Greedy OIL industry holding</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1346245848278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 09:10:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kid, I told you, as long as the US keeps up the Warmongering in the ME, Oil will be HIGH! SHOVE OBAMAMMY UP YOUR AXX!!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1346355786351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346360329480-37</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney’s welfare ad is accurate Published: 5:29 PM 08/29/2012 Poor Mickey Kaus. He’s the liberal intellectual (not an oxymoron — he’s the last known living “liberal intellectual”) lefties on TV are usually stealing from, but now that this welfare reform maven has concluded that Romney’s welfare ad is basically correct, liberals refuse to acknowledge his existence. The non-Fox media have formed a solid front in denouncing Romney’s welfare ad for daring to point out that Obama has gutted the work requirements of the 1996 welfare reform bill. The New York Times claims that Romney’s ad “falsely” charges Obama with eliminating work requirements. CNN rates the ad “false.” Underemployed hack Howard Fineman says Romney’s ad “is just flat out wrong on the facts” and “that every fair analyst, every fact checker” has said it’s “just factually wrong.” When a campaign ad induces this much hysteria, you know Romney has struck gold. On closer examination, it turns out that by “every fair analyst,” Fineman means a bunch of liberals quoting one another. This is how the media’s “fact checkers” operate when it comes to a Republican campaign ad. One not very well-informed person (or a heavily biased person) announces that Romney’s welfare ad is false, and the rest of the herd quote him, without anyone ever bothering to examine the facts, much less citing anyone who knows what he’s talking about. (KAUS: Obama’s misleading welfare ad) It is striking that everyone who actually knows something about the 1996 welfare reform law says that Romney’s ad is accurate. One of the principal authors of the 1996 welfare reform, Robert Rector of the Heritage Foundation, and Douglas Besharov, who advised Hillary Clinton on the 1996 welfare reform law, say Romney’s ad is accurate. Ads by Google Andrew Grossman, also of Heritage, produced something the MSM “fact checkers” avoid: a specific and detailed explanation of how the new waivers will allow states to evade the work requirements. Even Ron Haskins, one of the reform bill’s authors now at the liberal Brookings Institution — cited far and wide for “blasting” Romney’s ad — doesn’t deny the Obama administration plans to waive the work requirements. He just says he supports waivers for “job training.” That’s not disputing the accuracy of Romney’s ads. A lot of Americans don’t support waiving the work requirements, even for “job training.” Mitt Romney thinks they should know that that’s what Obama is doing. And liberal Kaus — whom liberal hacks are usually plagiarizing from — has written a series of blog posts explaining in detail why the Times is wrong and Romney’s ad is not incorrect. True, he says the ad is “oversimplified,” but I think most people grasp that a 30-second ad will not provide the lush analytical detail of a Kausfiles blog posting. (SEE ALSO: The Daily Caller’s Kausfiles blog) We know liberals are reading Kausfiles; why aren’t they stealing from him this time?</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346360329480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346360357513-38</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New York Times Puts 'Son of Satan' Ryan on Front Page 3:50 PM, Aug 30, 2012 • By MICHAEL WARREN Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts Here's the front page for the New York Times's national edition, the day after Paul Ryan's speech at the Republican National Convention: Peter Roskam, the Illinois Republican congressman and deputy majority whip, said the front page makes Ryan look like the "son of Satan." "It's the biggest day of his life, and this how the New York Times depicts it?" Roskam told THE WEEKLY STANDARD here in Tampa.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1346360357513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346360425748-39</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama's tax hikes on the rich are estimated at the high end to raise $65 billion." @@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ so you say but, wow, that would almost make up for the $96 billion he wants to cut from corporate taxes his first year of a trillion over 10 years........ but of course there is no need to tax the rich to make up for the corporate tax cut.... just killing the middleclass deduction for a home mortgage will raise over $90 billion a year........see how easy it is for the Rich to pay nothing?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346360425748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346363041886-40</Id><Title>ajole liars of gop &amp; voter id</Title><Msg>Consider the demographics: Absentee voters across the country tend to be older and whiter — just like the Republican Party.................HENCE.............................................................................................................................New voter ID law has loophole: Absentee ballots Wednesday, August 22, 2012 A loophole exists in the voter ID law that will require all Pennsylvanians voting on Nov. 6 to produce government-issued identification documents that include photos, or some narrowly-defined acceptable substitutes. The framers of the law did not address absentee ballots. The requirements for obtaining absentee ballots do not include a requirement to produce a photo ID document.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346363041886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346365220995-41</Id><Title>Romney's Welfare Ad</Title><Msg>atomic, good post. . An example of the truth hurting and lib goons smother another lib for agreeing. This should raise the hysteria another level. Dems having trouble in Obamaville. A point in that article was smack-on...... "fair analysts" meaning libs agreeing with each other. Priceless.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346365220995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346366533317-42</Id><Topic><Title>how #$%$ Mittens made his money</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346353397910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:03:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Kenyan is pretty good at borrowing money too. Much more than Romney ever has. He's borrowed it from the shysters at the "Fed" and you and I and our children and trheir children in perpetuity will be paying the vigorish to those usurors. Ever find out how the Kenyan got 14 million? That's his net worth. How about John Kerry? I hear this billionaire is going to address the Dem. convention. Wonder if he will tell them the name he was born with. Rather doubt it. "Only the name has been changed to protect the guilty."</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1346366533317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346367066466-43</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You, like most idiots, think businesses pay taxes. They are counted as overhead and added to the cost of your goods and services. Plus. the added cost makes our goods less competitive overseas. I've mentioned before that the only tax should be a flat rate tax on all income above a set poverty level. No one under that level should pay any tax hidden or otherwise. That would also eliminate a great many CPA jobs, IRS employees and tax lawyers that could go to work in productive jobs. Gee, you reckon that's the reason nothing is done about the iniquitous tax code? All those parasites make a good living off of it.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1346367066466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346367449000-44</Id><Topic><Title>It’s wrong to say Obama promised he’d keep the plant open – because he did not.</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1346362148000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:29:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is the President of Phony Worthless Promises! And he did promise not only to keep GM plants open but to reopen closed plants!! What Ryan said was exactly true! He never said Obama closed the plant in his hometown... only that it was closed within a year of Obama's visit in 2008... and was never reopned! Today he said... “Well, it's still idle... this is the story of the Obama economy - a man running for president in 2008 making all these grand promises and then none of them occurring. He got elected. He put his policies in place and the plant still shut down.”</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346367449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346367518000-45</Id><Topic><Title>being successful in business</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346347045000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:17:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drop, I don't care what you think. Or what some poll says. Being successful is good. I think you've had some success in life. Do you begrudge your own accomplishments? Your response would suggest that you must. Achieving some success, did it occur at the expense of others? As I think you think the pie is finite, whatever money you've made must have happened at someone else's expense. Do you think so? Your attitude suggests that's what you think.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346367518000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346368806602-46</Id><Title>Romney Welfare AD</Title><Msg>atomic, good post. The truth hurts and liberals bash one of their own who agrees with Romney. This should bring the hysteria to a new level. Too enjoyable. A point in that article that was smack-on......"fair analysts" meaning libs who agree with each others opinion. Priceless.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346368806602</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 19:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346369879423-47</Id><Title>New Format Is Crap</Title><Msg>My Romney Ad post took so long to appear, I posted it again. Yahoo better get back to the drawing board, this is ridiculous.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346369879423</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 19:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346374753000-48</Id><Topic><Title>slow move higher</Title><Username>georgegrey35</Username><Timestamp>1346340534000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job guys</Msg><Username>aaron23deandre</Username><Timestamp>1346374753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 20:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346375063509-49</Id><Title>Oracle taking a ton of criticism over Java Applet security issues</Title><Msg>They've failed to fix the Zero-days virus and it's all over twitter.</Msg><Username>cacacgtcaa</Username><Timestamp>1346375063509</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346376882000-50</Id><Topic><Title>slow move higher</Title><Username>georgegrey35</Username><Timestamp>1346340534000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing thoughts....</Msg><Username>devynporter31</Username><Timestamp>1346376882000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346377424000-51</Id><Title>America, you have a choice!</Title><Msg>Romney = Great man : Obama = PUTZ!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346377424000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:43:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346379774105-52</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More poppycock, libiot crap from Messsssssebird.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346379774105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346379964820-53</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: party with no conscience</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346341971269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Egbird, move out of Mass. and join America.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346379964820</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 22:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346382834768-54</Id><Topic><Title>Greedy OIL industry holding</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1346245848278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 09:10:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phyllis, those risk takers should be run by the govt, then see what the price of oil is.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346382834768</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346382915565-55</Id><Topic><Title>US home prices show consistent 12-month gains</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1346252693536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 11:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yipeeyaho cowboy.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346382915565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346383029167-56</Id><Topic><Title>ajole liars of gop &amp; voter id</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346363041886</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:44:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absentee ballots are all checked for validity.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346383029167</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346383429846-57</Id><Topic><Title>how #$%$ Mittens made his money</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346353397910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:03:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More liberal lunacy about someone who educated himself, made good choices, became a success, saved an American olympics, tithes to his church, served his country, gives to charities, and has to listen to idiots like Deluckbird. I guess he didn't build that business by himself, it was govt who took all the risks.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346383429846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346383667872-58</Id><Title>Growth vs. Poverty</Title><Msg>America needs to make a choice between trickle down economics vs. trickle up poverty. Remember, Reagan doubled tax revenues in just eight years while Dumbocraps in Congress under the Tipster spent it all plus more. Bush economy was doing fine until those same Dumbocraps aided the implosion of housing in America. Case closed.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346383667872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346384047281-59</Id><Title>Japan keeps taxing at higher rates</Title><Msg>And continues their descent into economic gloom. That's where the libiots want to take us. They and their inane leader are truly clueless. No idea of business success in America. They are shameful.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346384047281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346384382343-60</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan is just a liar and an extremist</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346352423957</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:47:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hyperbole personified. Dumbo didn't like the spending cuts to the takers of the country, I.e. Welfare recipients, food stampers, Acorn, NPR, and all the other Dumbo supporters. It was an equal opportunity withdrawal from sanity.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346384382343</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346384520353-61</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt made his money loading up companies with debt, then taking millions and leaving town</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346353039967</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:57:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More poppycock from the poppycock specialist. Libiots hate successful people, they want dependency.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346384520353</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346384594000-62</Id><Title>Obama FAILED!</Title><Msg>Its time to get a President who is a SUCCESS! VOTE ROMNEY IN NOVEMBER!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346384594000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346384652715-63</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan lies about everything</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1346346537103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More hate for a successful person. Think his wife may have contributed to their success. She still has her law license, unlike Mouchelle.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346384652715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:44:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>