<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348748904019-1</Id><Title>Obama Regime Says "Women Not Concerned About Last FOUR Years"!</Title><Msg>"Only the next FOUR"! YeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaa! But of course, we all know just how "Stupid" the women of, by and for the Obama Regime are... always trashing "Real Experience" and "Results" and going for the "Hope &amp; Change" thingy... and when that doesn't work out, begging for more! I mean, how the F else could this PT Barnum wannabee have been elected in the 1st place!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1348748904019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348749641980-2</Id><Topic><Title>Americans say Obama's ads are more honest</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348710731941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, the Bummer has been so successful that his ads are completely honest. Get a clue.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348749641980</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348749779470-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Pro Life!</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348683010773</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 14:10:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ignorance is rampant among Donkeys.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348749779470</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348750525715-4</Id><Title>Romney says we aleady have universal healthcare!</Title><Msg>he recently said an ambulance will pick you up an take you to the ER! free! so no problem with healthcare! previously he has said doing healthcare at the ER was stupid and wastefull! and totally socialist......... that's why he had to do a Stalinist mandate for his Romniecommiecare in Ma. which he said was the "responsible " way to go.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348750525715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 08:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348751049347-5</Id><Title>Hey gop whiners and cowards on the ME</Title><Msg>Built it yourself, On your OWN, just form a brigade of "democracy spreaders" voluteers and get your whiny lazy cowardly rear ends over their and fight for your favorite dictator, monarch or maybe join up with the IDF, in which case maybe YOU can murder Americans citizens like Rachel Corrie or the 3 dozen crew of the USS liberty murdered with napalm and machine gun fire in a deliberate attack. "three Israeli French-made Mirage III fighters attacked with 72 rockets, napalm and machine guns. They wounded McGonagle and killed the chief NSA officer Allen Bloom. The attack was filmed in its entirety through the Andrew Jackson’s periscope. Documents released in 1977 under the Freedom of Information Act show clearly that Israel knew the Liberty’s identity and that General Moshe Dyan ordered the sinking over the protest of close advisors. "</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348751049347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348752567200-6</Id><Topic><Title>Americans say Obama's ads are more honest</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348710731941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2Q GDP revised down to 1.3% from 1.7%... Durable orders drop 13.2%... SANTELLI: 'Depressingly weak'... Santelli on GDP Numbers: 'Depressingly Weak' 8:57 AM, Sep 27, 2012 • By DANIEL HALPER Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts This morning, Rick Santelli said the revised GDP numbers are "depressingly weak": CNBC reports on the numbers: New durable goods orders in August fell by the most since the recession and a separate reading on the broader U.S. economy came in much weaker than expected. But weekly jobless claims sank to a two-month low, in a hopeful sign for the labor market. New orders for long-lasting U.S. manufactured goods in August fell by the most in 3 1/2 years, pointing to a sharp slowdown in factory activity even as a gauge of planned business spending rebounded. The Commerce Department said on Thursday durable goods orders dived 13.2 percent, the largest drop since January 2009, when the economy was in the throes of a recession. Orders for July were revised down to show a 3.3 percent increase instead of the previously reported 4.1 percent gain.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348752567200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348752592344-7</Id><Topic><Title>Americans say Obama's ads are more honest</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348710731941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you forgot to mention the 'poll' was taken by 'Esquire' ....lol</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1348752592344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348755370312-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare... the "anti-jobs" entitlement</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348507971847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WSJ: The more we learn, the more Benghazi looks like a gross security failure... MOSCOW TIMES: Why Putin Endorses Obama</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1348755370312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348756217205-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare... the "anti-jobs" entitlement</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1348507971847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fed Virtually Funding the Entire US Deficit: Lindsey Published: Wednesday, 26 Sep 2012 | 12:02 PM ET Text Size By: Justin Menza Federal Reserve Building, Washington, D.C. Raymond Boyd | Michael Ochs Archives | Getty Images The latest round of extraordinary Federal Reserve stimulus is risky and leaves little room to maneuver should another crisis hit, economist Lawrence Lindsey told CNBC’s “Squawk Box” on Wednesday. Lindsey said that with the Fed purchasing at least $40 billion a month in mortgage debt through QE3, “they are buying the entire deficit.” (Read more: Fed Pulls Trigger, to Buy Mortgages in Effort to Lower Rates.) “I have no problem doing extraordinary things in extraordinary times,” said Lindsey, a former White House economic advisor under former president George W. Bush who now runs his own consulting firm. Lindsay said he agreed with the Fed’s first two rounds of quantitative easing. Now, with the economy now growing closer to its trend rate, “doing something that’s really out of the ordinary is risking things.” He added, “If this becomes the new ordinary, it’s hard to imagine the Fed’s maneuvering room” should another crisis hit. (Read More: Why Fed Policy Just Like the NFL Refs: El-Erian.) The central bank's recently announced bid to stimulate the economy has also taken the pressure off politicians to deal with the U.S. fiscal cliff, Lindsay argued, which could result in destabilizing tax hikes and spending cuts automatically taking effect early next year. “The Fed, maybe because it can't do otherwise, has told the Congress: 'We're going to buy your bonds no matter what,'” Lindsey said. “I think that's keeping the pressure off the president, off the Congress.” The effective of QE3 on interest rates may also keep Congress from reining in borrowing. “If the (Fed) chairman’s estimates of the effectiveness of QE3 on interest rates come true, we’re going to be down to an average cost of borrowing for the government of 0.6 of a percentage point,” Lindsey said. “Why would any Congress not borrow and spend if they could borrow at 60 basis points?”</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1348756217205</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348756226461-10</Id><Topic><Title>Hey gop whiners and cowards on the ME</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348751049347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hikemanymiles, since you are one of the biggest lunatics who thinks the USA can control the lives of hundreds of millions of muslims in several countries, why don't you and your ilk just own it and "build it" all on your own, you can volunteer and go there to support your favorite dictator, monarch, or perhaps join the IDF, in which case at least you will get Israel's universal healthcare with free abortions.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348756226461</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348757137132-11</Id><Topic><Title>Americans say Obama's ads are more honest</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348710731941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is campaigning on a promise to raise taxes. If Obama is re-elected, USA will go over fiscal cliff. Obama will blame Republicans. There's no way out. It will just be worse with Obama going back to bashing business and dividing the country.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348757137132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 10:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348759453199-12</Id><Title>"Fiscal Cliff"</Title><Msg>Headline on Yahoo says corporate officials worried about the coming fiscal cliff. Liver lips is doing the same thing the Weimar Republic of Germany did in the 1920's. They borrowed from those nice people, the Rothschilds, as if there was no end to the Ponzi scheme they operated. Liver lips is doing the same thing. It didn't work for the Weimar Republic and it won't work here. It's already happening in countries like Greece and Spain. The only country that has any sense is Iceland. They told the nice usurors to go to hell that the debt they created was a fraud. There economy is rebounding rapidly. At one time Iceland had the highest per capita income in the world. Bet it's close to that now. Our per capita income has declined by about 8% under Liver Lips and the Dems.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348759453199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348759483122-13</Id><Topic><Title>Americans say Obama's ads are more honest</Title><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348710731941</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen 43% Expect Better Economy if Romney Wins; 34% Say Same of Obama Daily Presidential Tracking Poll: Obama 46%, Romney 46% Swing State Daily Tracking: Obama 46%, Romney 46%</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1348759483122</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348759588225-14</Id><Topic><Title>"Fiscal Cliff"</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348759453199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:24:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's Romney's plan? cut taxes and increase military spending? that's all I've really heard -the rest is speculation. What swing voter would vote for that if they're really concerned about a fiscal cliff?</Msg><Username>iseek_the_truth_03</Username><Timestamp>1348759588225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348759751464-15</Id><Topic><Title>Hey gop whiners and cowards on the ME</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348751049347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two Israeli pilots refused to attack. They were punished heavily. This also proves they knew it was an American ship. The piece of human excrement known as LBJ ordered planes that had been scrambled for the defense of the Liberty back to the carrier. He said he "Didn't want to embarrass "Israel". Just goes to show who really runs things in this country.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348759751464</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348760198242-16</Id><Title>Drudge Headline</Title><Msg>"He has my vote. He gave me a phone." That sums up very well Obama's strategy to win.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348760198242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348761739379-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama sticking to silly movie excuse</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348676874158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:27:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He sticks to it and gets no questions nor challenge from the press. They don't want to be called racist for questioning him even when Hilary had to say it was a planned terrorist attack.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1348761739379</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348761878079-18</Id><Topic><Title>How naive was Obama when he said he could talk to Mahmoud Ahmadinejad ?</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1348675530448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:05:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahmandinejad is treating Obama like the subsitute teacher.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1348761878079</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348764561974-19</Id><Title>Oracle Beats IBM DB2 on Performance and Price/Performance - ORCL heading to $200+</Title><Msg>Read the article "Oracle Achieves Record TPC-C Benchmark Result on 2 Processor System" Since ORCL beats IBM, it should worth more than IBM's share price; if not now, one day in the future! Good Luck Longs.</Msg><Username>chirobondhu</Username><Timestamp>1348764561974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348764962976-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama sticking to silly movie excuse</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348676874158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:27:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>against mounting evidence that al-qaeda was behind the Libyan attack, the bamster is starting to come clean. Obama has no defense against the truth.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348764962976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 12:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348765448673-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama sticking to silly movie excuse</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348676874158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:27:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barney Frank: Pot brownie made me sleepy By Justin Sink - 09/27/12 08:18 AM ET Retiring Rep. Barney Frank (D-Mass.) said he once tried a pot-infused brownie — and it made him sleepy. Frank is an advocate of legalizing and taxing marijuana, but he said Wednesday night that he does not regularly use the illegal drug. "No, I don't," Frank told CNN when asked if he smoked marijuana. “I smoke a cigar or two a day. I did have a brownie once. It made me sleepy.”</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1348765448673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348766887753-22</Id><Topic><Title>Drudge Headline</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348760198242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not only does that woman believe Obama gave her the phone, Obama is paying her monthly bill. How many Americans actually realize there is a oprogram to gives out free phones to minorities? You libs out there, are you cool with that? Nevermind. Of course you are.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348766887753</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 13:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348771525219-23</Id><Title>candidates gaffes</Title><Msg>Which of the following gaffes from each of our candidates has the greatest potential for motivating the other's base and persuading people in general to get out and vote? 1) Obama's "you didn't build that. Someone else made that happen," 2) Romney's 47% remark</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348771525219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348772681542-24</Id><Title>time has passed for Akin to drop out</Title><Msg>so the question is whether repub establishment will endorse Akin or would they rather see a lefty win in Mo? Dangerous question, I know. It wouldn't surprise me if guys like Rove and McConnell would rather see McCaskill win.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348772681542</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 15:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348776807070-25</Id><Topic><Title>Hey gop whiners and cowards on the ME</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348751049347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When news of the attack reached Washington, the Joint Chiefs of Staff ordered a counterstrike by U.S. A-4 Skyhawks on the Israeli MTB (Motorboat/Torpedo Base) at Haifa but the order was countermanded by President Johnson. .......... ..................Former U.S. intelligence officials said later that the White House had not pressed Israel harder because Israel was party to several U.S. covert operations meant to oust Nasser of Egypt which Israel would release to the world, poisoning the American position in the Arab world. Apparently the threat worked"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348776807070</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348777022954-26</Id><Topic><Title>candidates gaffes</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348771525219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 14:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for one thing the Obama remark was taken out of context, and the gop is 100% dishones about it . Obama SPECIFICALLY stated that he was referring to roads, bridges , schools and etc...... which btw romeny has said EXACXTLY the same thing on many occasions, it is a simple truth.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348777022954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348777091175-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama sticking to silly movie excuse</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348676874158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:27:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOOK: Taxpayers spent $1.4 billion on Obamas last year... Taxpayers spent $1.4 billion dollars on everything from staffing, housing, flying and entertaining President Obama and his family last year, according to the author of a new book on taxpayer-funded presidential perks. In comparison, British taxpayers spent just $57.8 million on the royal family. Author Robert Keith Gray writes in “Presidential Perks Gone Royal” that Obama isn’t the only president to have taken advantage of the expensive trappings of his office. But the amount of money spent on the first family, he argues, has risen tremendously under the Obama administration and needs to be reined in. Gray told The Daily Caller that the $1.4 billion spent on the Obama family last year is the “total cost of the presidency,” factoring the cost of the “biggest staff in history at the highest wages ever,” a 50 percent increase in the numbers of appointed czars and an Air Force One “running with the frequency of a scheduled air line.” “The most concerning thing, I think, is the use of taxpayer funds to actually abet his re-election,” Gray, who worked in the Eisenhower administration and for other Republican presidents, said in an interview with TheDC on Wednesday. “The press has been so slow in picking up on this extraordinary increase in the president’s expenses,” Gray told TheDC. (RELATED: Five shocking truths about Michelle Obama) Specifically, Gray said taxpayer dollars are subsidizing Obama’s re-election effort when he uses Air Force One to jet across the country campaigning. Royal family cost Brits $58 million...</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348777091175</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:18:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348777659954-28</Id><Title>Politifact rates Mitt's you didn't build it nonsense. FALSE</Title><Msg>amazing that the theme of the RNC was a total 100% lie and gross distortion. which politifact verifies was FALSE....... as ANYONE who listened to the enitire Obama statement and not the gross out of context dishonest snip of it used by the LIAR Romney: from politifact "Putting Mitt Romney's attacks on 'You didn't build that' to the Truth-O-Meter" Our ruling In speeches and videos, the Romney campaign has repeatedly distorted Obama's words. By plucking two sentences out of context, Romney twists the president's remarks and ignores their real meaning. The preceding sentences make clear that Obama was talking about the importance of government-provided infrastructure and education to the success of private businesses. Romney also conveniently ignores Obama's clear summary of his message, that "the point is ... that when we succeed, we succeed because of our individual initiative, but also because we do things together." By leaving out the "individual initiative" reference, Romney and his supporters have misled viewers and given a false impression. For that, we rate the claim False."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348777659954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348778035958-29</Id><Topic><Title>Politifact rates Mitt's you didn't build it nonsense. FALSE</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348777659954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:27:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy, the Dumbocraps would never do that huh. But the Bummer does indeed feel that way cause he is a true believer in redistribution and govt intervention in all of business.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348778035958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348778210863-30</Id><Topic><Title>Hey gop whiners and cowards on the ME</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348751049347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was Bush's fault for sure. Guess Messsssssebird thinks the Mooslims would be better allies. I know of 3000 different families in NY who would disagree.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348778210863</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348778482206-31</Id><Title>Politifact rates Mitts comment on the 47%........ FALSE.... ZERO truth on the truth 0 meter</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney says voters who support Barack Obama are “people who pay no income tax” The "48, 49 percent" that supports President Barack Obama are "people who pay no income tax." Mitt Romney on Thursday, May 17th, 2012 in a surreptitiously recorded speech to donors at a fundraiser Poltifact rates this as FALSE...................... Mitt is just a LIAR who hates half of all Americans and says it's not his job to represent them.... and the truth is most of those people are working families, seniors, jr military with families and so on..... many of them vote gop too..... probably not this time though, now that Mitt has called them Moochers.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348778482206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348786751258-32</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens used to "harvest" companies while at Bain.</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1348781487167</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:31:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Know who controls Bain Capital? I do. You need to look it up. It's the same gang that controlled the security at the airports the 9/11 planes left from. They also provide the scanning devices at the airports. Interestingly, Marvin Bush sits on the board of of the company in charge of the airport security.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348786751258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 18:59:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348789367073-33</Id><Title>Congratulations to Barack "Apologize, Appease, and Bend Over with Sphincter Spread Wide" Obama</Title><Msg>You have successfully empowered the 7th century values of the mudslum disease world wide. May you hang from a tree soon.</Msg><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1348789367073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:42:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348791555436-34</Id><Topic><Title>Drudge Headline</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348760198242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are more liberals in Calif so that makes me a minority. Where do I apply for my phone? Isn't it only fair that if the Democrats are wasting taxpayer money for free stuff, I should get in on the bonus before they run out of money? Seriously, it would take more than a phone for Obama to get my vote, starting with a new washer and dryer, so energy efficient they last 6 to 7 years or maybe longer if you don't use it every other day . You have no idea the bumbling, blustering, bunch of bureaucrats we are stuck with. It's like they're trying to outdo Obama. Pretty darn close.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1348791555436</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 20:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348792260939-35</Id><Topic><Title>Congratulations to Barack "Apologize, Appease, and Bend Over with Sphincter Spread Wide" Obama</Title><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1348789367073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:42:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh my. He talks out his #$%$!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348792260939</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 20:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348796331553-36</Id><Topic><Title>Drudge Headline</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1348760198242</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do “Obama phones” come from? September 27, 2012 | 2:25 pm 54Comments Charlie Spiering Commentary Staff Writer The Washington Examiner Photo - This video of an Obama supporter bragging about having an “Obama phone” has gone viral on the web, but where do these “free cell phones” come from? The program is called Lifeline, established in 1984 was originally created to subsidize landline phone service for low income Americans, funded by government-collected telecommunication fees, paid by consumers. In 2008, the program was expanded to support cell phones which quickly escalated the cost of the program. In 2008 the program cost $772 million, but by 2011 it cost $1.6 billion. A 2011 audit found that 269,000 wireless Lifeline subscribers were receiving free phones and monthly service from two or more carriers. Several websites have been created to promote “free” government cell phones, including the”The Obama Cell Phone” website at Obamaphone.net. Rep. Tim Griffin R-Ark. has proposed a bill to eliminate federal subsidies for free cell phones and has produced a great YouTube video highlighting the runaway cost of the program. The program has also been highlighted for reform by Senator Claire McCaskill D-Mo. Pressure to reform the program led the FCC to announce an effort in February to “reduce the potential for fraud while cutting red tape for consumers and providers” by the end of 2013.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1348796331553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 21:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348803035525-37</Id><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Msg>yeah mittens i want my tax cut NOW and plus the medicare you promise ME with no cuts! You fixed it and i get cash back...... how easy is that?!!!! so why is the gop always whining about medicare being broke and you fix it, i get a tax cut plus no change, full , as is medicare????</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348803188281-38</Id><Topic><Title>Congratulations to Barack "Apologize, Appease, and Bend Over with Sphincter Spread Wide" Obama</Title><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1348789367073</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 19:42:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you go #$%$, build it yourself, and redistribute your own wealth to israel you cksker coward.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803188281</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348803386263-39</Id><Topic><Title>Hey gop whiners and cowards on the ME</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348751049347</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:04:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go there your selves you tush limbaugh #$%$ heros... and redistribute your own money to the mid east . what a bunch of nazi cksukers you are. just charge, you stupid #$%$wipes, and spread democracy in the mid east, build it on you own, hypocrites.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803386263</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>