<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345550741000-1</Id><Title>Obama &amp; Democrats Laughing All The Way To The Microphones!</Title><Msg>to pontificate, with the utmost sincerity (LOL!!), on the stupid Akin rape comments... "rape is rape"! Wow! Isn't he wonderful!! The truth is that they could give a flying rats azzs about women or rape, save how it can generate them a few more VOTES!! Democrats are simply Rape, Gay, Gender and Race "BAITERS" to the core! YeeeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa! What a Country! We love all that "Hope &amp; Change" stuff!!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1345550741000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345552400000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Akin still leads McCaskill after rape comment</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345550633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we'll find out today if Akin is about public service or himself. From what I've heard him say so far, it looks like the latter.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1345552400000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345553390000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama &amp; Democrats Laughing All The Way To The Microphones!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1345550741000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:05:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But not nearly as much as Democrat Pigs, Obama on down, overplay everything like the phony 2-bit frauds and liars they are!! Eat shyt and die, Pig!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1345553390000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345554435000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Akin still leads McCaskill after rape comment</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345550633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:03:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he will be out of it before the day is over. What an idiotic comment. The guy has got to go.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345554435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345555611000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Consider yourself to get the top deals with Oracle Corporatio</Title><Username>nickolas.james73</Username><Timestamp>1345552406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This journal taught me a lot before I was in the market. After spending over 3.5 years in the area, I’m giving you a suggestion- ‘Only buy something that you'd be perfectly happy to hold if the market shut down for ten years.’ All the best.</Msg><Username>adan.mills57</Username><Timestamp>1345555611000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345555657000-6</Id><Topic><Title>we were better off in the Clinton years</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345466300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Dems laying the ground work for the mortgage collapse" you are such a liar. that was the work of party of DEREGULATION, moron. the same who pushed and pumped and cajoled and took money to do the deregulations of the S&amp;Ls, electricity and investment banks allowed back into home mortgages..... all the result of the "free market" allowed , ONCE AGAIN, to do what it had been REGULATED and PREVENTED from doing since dem NEW DEAL legislation. the 1933 Glass–Steagall Act was undone by the 3 gop Gramm–Leach–Bliley Act Respective versions of the legislation were introduced in the U.S. Senate by Phil Gramm (Republican of Texas) and in the U.S. House of Representatives by Jim Leach (R-Iowa). The third lawmaker associated with the bill was Rep. Thomas J. Bliley, Jr. (R-Virginia), Chairman of the House Commerce Committee from 1995 to 2001. During debate in the House of Representatives, Rep. John Dingell (Democrat of Michigan) argued that the bill would result in banks becoming "too big to fail." Dingell further argued that this would necessarily result in a bailout by the Federal Government.[4]</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345555657000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345555933000-7</Id><Topic><Title>we were better off in the Clinton years</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345466300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bill was pushed by Robert Rubin and Lawrence Summers, had a higher % of democrats than republicans supporting it and was signed by Clinton. McCain was voted against it. Still that does not explain the source of the subprime mortgages. Article below explains it. http://news.investors.com/article/622833/201208201832/cbs-60-minutes-misrepresented-subprime-crisis.htm?p=2</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345555933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345556540000-8</Id><Topic><Title>we were better off in the Clinton years</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345466300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fact is the GOP pumped a gop bill gramm, leach and biley. and the mantra OF the gop is DEREGULATION...... gramm also did the infamous Enron loophole, which when the dems tried to get rid of it BUSH vetoed their efforts.... Sen. Gramm was blocking Senate action based on his continued insistence that the bill be expanded to prevent the SEC from regulating swaps, and the desire to broaden the protections against CFTC regulation for “bank products.”[61] In 2008 Congress enacted into law over President Bush’s veto an Omnibus Farm Bill that contained the “Close the Enron Loophole Act.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345556540000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345557109000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Dropkick has killed this board!</Title><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1345482353000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:05:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FIVE STARS!</Msg><Username>wournos.aileen</Username><Timestamp>1345557109000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345557532000-10</Id><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Msg>The GOP's Deregulation Obsession [the gop] have launched an unprecedented antiregulation campaign, with the goal of blocking new safeguards against corporate wrongdoing and rolling back environmental, health, financial and other regulatory protections. “The current situation might be characterized as the Contract With America on steroids,” ... that make this period more dangerous than the mid-1990s. “First, these antiregulatory advocates are using high unemployment as a wedge, claiming that regulations are job killers. ..... In reality, it was insufficient controls on Wall Street that facilitated the financial crash and the Great Recession, which threw  8 million people out of work. Even when they impose modest short-term costs on businesses, health, safety and environmental protections also commonly create jobs by spurring innovation to address new standards. But opponents of public protections discard such evidence, relying instead on deceptive studies written by those committed to bolstering their deregulation crusade. http://www.thenation.com/article/163921/gops-deregulation-obsession#</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345557874000-11</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't insufficient controls, it was ineffective government. Harry Markopolos showed the SEC that Madoff's scheme was not mathematically possible back in the 90's. SEC did nothing. Long after Sarbanes-Oxley fraud was still occuring, more government failure. Dodd-Frank did nothing to solve too big too fail and nothing to deal with the financial disasters of Fannie/Freddie. After thorough failure of government regulation you want to pay for more. Now government rewards bad management with bailouts for the big banks and auto companies. Enron shows the marketplace works, fraud is dealt with by bankrupcty and the end of the fraudulent business. A far stronger penalty than the SEC would ever impliment.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345557874000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345558450000-12</Id><Title>the gop rag WSJ celebrated the end of glass Glass-Steagall</Title><Msg>The Wall Street Journal celebrated the agreement to end such restrictions with an editorial declaring that the banks had been unfairly scapegoated for the Great Depression. The headline of one Journal article detailing the impact of the proposed law declared, "Finally, 1929 Begins to Fade." (how quickly the WSJ forgot the work of WS "The more than five thousand bank failures between the Crash and the New Deal's rescue operation in March 1933 wiped out some $7 billion in depositors' money. Accelerating foreclosures on defaulted home mortgages—150,000 homeowners lost their property in 1930, 200,000 in 1931, 250,000 in 1932—stripped millions of people of both shelter and life savings at a single stroke and menaced the balance sheets of thousands of surviving banks" (David Kennedy, Freedom from Fear, Oxford University Press, 1999, pp. 162-63). The separation of banking and the stock exchange was ordered in response to revelations of the gross corruption and manipulation of the market by giant banking houses, above all the House of Morgan, which organized huge corporate mergers for its own profit and awarded preferential access to share issues to favored politicians and businessmen. Such insider trading played a major role in the speculative boom which preceded the 1929 crash.)</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345558450000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:14:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345559011000-13</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you ARE 100% WRONG ABOUT ENRON, the states that didn't deregulate have CHEAPER electric rates. and as ANYONE can see there is LESS competition, because... oh guess what.... now after a flurry of mergers and so on there are LESS but BIGGER electric providers.... so once again the VERY reason for the regulation in the first place... to stop utes from forming price fixing monoplies is happening again. &amp; "the repeal of Glass-Steagall in 1999 was part of a broad deregulatory push, championed by the likes of Fed chief Alan Greenspan, Sen. Phil Gramm (R-Tex.) and Treasury Secretary Robert Rubin, that eliminated much of the oversight on Wall Street. Freed from onerous regulation, the banks could “innovate” and grow and the gop continues to pump their deregulation mantra: "characterized as the Contract With America on steroids,” ... that make this period more dangerous than the mid-1990s. “First, these antiregulatory advocates are using high unemployment as a wedge, claiming that regulations are job killers. ..... In reality, it was insufficient controls on Wall Street that facilitated the financial crash and the Great Recession, which threw  8 million people out of work. Even when they impose modest short-term costs on businesses, health, safety and environmental protections also commonly create jobs by spurring innovation to address new standards. But opponents of public protections discard such evidence, relying instead on deceptive studies written by those committed to bolstering their deregulation crusade." and the banking dereg which began with the gop in the 80s was sure a huge success, huh? the S&amp; L fraud and manipulation and then the wall street investment bank fraud and manipulation..... nice work!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345559011000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345559088000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Consider yourself to get the top deals with Oracle Corporatio</Title><Username>nickolas.james73</Username><Timestamp>1345552406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read your comments with interest - thanks for continuing to post.</Msg><Username>deborah.beasley18</Username><Timestamp>1345559088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345559168000-15</Id><Topic><Title>we were better off in the Clinton years</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345466300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So again, you blame the dotbomb era on Bush tax cuts? You have no defense for the millions of jobs lost following Clintons term, as a result of the stock bubble. But we should give credit to Clinton for 23M of them. Way to go Whacko! Yes, the Dems were the trigger for the mortgage mess. Did you read the article provided by goodnick? It explains it in simple detail for you to understand, or maybe not.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1345559168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345559247000-16</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it wasn't for TARP the free market would have worked just fine. The ones that took on too much risk would fail. Hint not all the banks that got TARP money wanted it. The properly managed would have gained market share. Government instead perpetuated the poorly managed. Our entire economy is worse off for not letting market forces dish out the penatlies.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345559247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345559292000-17</Id><Title>pub weird ideas: legitimate rape</Title><Msg>"legitimate rape" can't get a woman pregnant. Pubs strange notions. Get the slope out of your forehead and step into the twenty-first century.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345559292000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:28:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345559906000-18</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure , your type calls the great depression "just fine". you would be ok with 25% unemployment, stocks down 90%, gdp down 50% ....and the . "The more than five thousand bank failures between the Crash and the New Deal's rescue operation in March 1933 wiped out some $7 billion in depositors' money. Accelerating foreclosures on defaulted home mortgages—150,000 homeowners lost their property in 1930, 200,000 in 1931, 250,000 in 1932—stripped millions of people of both shelter and life savings at a single stroke and menaced the balance sheets of thousands of surviving banks" that is whAT THE GOP MANTRA OF DEREGULATION IS ALL ABOUT, RIGHT? FREEING UP THE MARKETS? Wall Street just loves to run "free" hence beginning in the 80s for over 30 years they paid hundreds of millions to get back to the freedom they had before the 1st great depression to manipulate and commit fraud. you, for one sure bought into their mantra to eliminate much of the oversight on Wall Street. only YOU and YOUR type are true beleivers that Freed from onerous regulation, the banks and wall street could “innovate” and grow....... jeez..........regulated captialism worked just fine before the gop began the deregulations which resulted in another great depression....</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345559906000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345560042000-19</Id><Topic><Title>pub weird ideas: legitimate rape</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345559292000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:28:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Changing the subject is typical of you when your stupid comments get run over. What it means by legitimate rape is that it wasn't consensual. Stick with material you can comprehend, like Hans Christian Anderson.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1345560042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:40:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345560248000-20</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Obama loves Wall Street, the capitalist hub. Goldman Sachs in particular. Why not mention that?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1345560248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345560267000-21</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All caused by the Federal Reserve. Another creation of government that should be eliminated. This was not the same. A number of the big banks did not need nor want TARP money. The fact that it was paid back so quickly proved it. A few politically connected ones would have went under and took their campaign contributions along with Geithner and Paulson with them. We would have been far better off. Amazing, I now have mesa backing wall street bailouts.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345560267000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345560561000-22</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loved it so much he made Geithner, the guy that should have provided oversight of the banks at the NY Fed, his treasury secretary. They guy that also blew off the LIBOR rate manipulation scandal and one of the rich that did not pay his fair share of taxes. LOL</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345560561000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345560908000-23</Id><Title>Obama Doesn't Take Navy Seals Seriously!</Title><Msg>Naturally!! This arrogant POS doesn't take anyone seriously who criticizes him for being the incompetent fool that he is... getting 22 Seals and 8 other Americans killed by running his mouth 24/7 for weeks on end telling the world what HE had done, what HE had planned, what HE had organized, what HE had approved... to find and kill Bin Laden! The truth is that Obama did Jackshyt save to take directions from Valerie Jarrett and kill the operation on 3 occasions before finally approving it! Obama is a shameless self-promoting Rat!!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1345560908000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345561318000-24</Id><Title>Skinny Dipping in Israel</Title><Msg>The story about a politician swimming in the buff isn't the real story...nooooo not at all - that part is rediculous really. the story is about these GOP members on an all paid junket, a booze fest supported by a radical conservative group seeking unwaivering military support from the US. Thes GOP members called the trip a "fact finding mission" - fact is, they're getting hundreds of thousands of campaign dollars from this supporter.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345561318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345561409000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Consider yourself to get the top deals with Oracle Corporatio</Title><Username>nickolas.james73</Username><Timestamp>1345552406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least 200 after buybacks and will have a dividend of 10dollars a share good plan</Msg><Username>sylvia_sylvia67</Username><Timestamp>1345561409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345561453000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporatio - The Valuable Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>wfederico38</Username><Timestamp>1345559784000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:36:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Super link! Time to load up!</Msg><Username>cole.coleman79</Username><Timestamp>1345561453000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345561461000-27</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right, most of Obama's friends are thieves and capitalists but liberals think he's a commie like them. They haven't figured it out yet.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1345561461000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345561527000-28</Id><Topic><Title>pub weird ideas: legitimate rape</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345559292000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:28:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go ahead and get behind a loser politician that is on film saying "legitimate rape" - because the rest of your klan is telling the guy to step off. between that statement and Rush Limbaugh - I can't see why any self respecting woman would support the GOP.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345561527000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345561967000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Skinny Dipping in Israel</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345561318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:01:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sort of like Obama's Secret Service in Columbia with the escort service. What was the price tag for that? And you paid for that one. Keep them coming, Krusty.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1345561967000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345562974000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Skinny Dipping in Israel</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345561318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:01:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP members on a "fact finding mission" in Israel - an all expense paid booze fest? you're comparing that with the secret service fiasco in Columbia? you're going to have to do better than that</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345562974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345563192000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Consider yourself to get the top deals with Oracle Corporatio</Title><Username>nickolas.james73</Username><Timestamp>1345552406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just promise to come back on here if it works. That's all I ask.</Msg><Username>kim.sloan60</Username><Timestamp>1345563192000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345563199000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Doesn't Take Navy Seals Seriously!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1345560908000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:55:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blah blah blah blah blah obama now get zero credit for making the call to take out OBL but gets all the blame for a black hawk down? sounds like sour grapes you can bet Bush and Rumsfeld should be ashamed of the Pat Tilman cover up.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345563199000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345563421000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Skinny Dipping in Israel</Title><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345561318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:01:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the story is about these GOP members on an all paid junket, a booze fest supported by a radical conservative group seeking unwaivering military support from the US. " YEP, THat is the disgrace..... they are stupid for getting in a tizzy because one of their own was swimming naked where jesus "walked on water"... and no doubt that drunken pub peed in the pool too.... but who cares about that it's trivial compared to the horde of pubs that were there on the junket with their wives and staffers and buddies..</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345563421000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:37:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345563547000-34</Id><Topic><Title>we were better off in the Clinton years</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345466300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doofus, take it up with the rightwing rag the WSJ who said: "The Bush administration created about three million jobs (net) over its eight years, a fraction of the 23 million jobs created under President Bill Clinton‘s administration and only slightly better than President George H.W. Bush did in his four years in office." WSJ</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345563547000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345563779000-35</Id><Title>gop offers universal healthcare to pregnant women?</Title><Msg>gop offers universal healthcare to pregnant women and all newborn children? Report: GOP platform to again call for abortion ban</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345563779000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345564025000-36</Id><Title>Romney admits gop medicare cuts will hit seniors NOW!</Title><Msg>Romney camp admits Medicare cuts will hit current seniors by Joan McCarter Senior citizen with empty wallet, surrounded by pill bottles. That cynical ploy of the Romney/Ryan plan to gut Medicare, but to keep the senior vote by putting those cuts off on the next batch of retirees is looking increasingly empty. That's because their plan to repeal Obamacare, and to "restore" the $716 billion in provider cuts means that Romney/Ryan will either have to make up those funds with revenues or with cuts to current seniors, because without that money, Medicare becomes insolvent by 2016. The Republican allergy to new revenue pretty much determines they'll squeeze that money out of seniors, and Romney advisors are admitting it. Romney campaign advisor Ed Gillespie was the first to admit they'd target current seniors by raising the eligibility age for Medicare. And now another advisor is admitting that benefits cuts are definitely on the table. Avik Roy, an outside health care adviser to the Romney campaign, admits that committing to billions of dollars in higher Medicare spending in the near-term will make it difficult for Romney to achieve its separate goal of reducing overall federal spending to modern lows. But he notes thatRomney could make up the difference elsewhere in the budget or, by “mak[ing] other changes to the Medicare program, such as increased means-testing, that don’t alter the program’s basic structure.” Means testing would apply to people on Medicare now, and it would be a cut to benefits, benefits that retirees earned through years of work and contributing to the system. That's not the only thing seniors would be losing under Romney/Ryan. If the Affordable Care Act is repealed, with it goes the $4.1 billion seniors and disabled people have saved on prescription drugs. That amounts to an average of $768 in annual savings for Medicare patients, a significant chunk of money for anyone on a fixed income. Also gone with repeal are the free cancer screenings, mammograms and other preventive services. Romney and Ryan are lying, no surprise, when they say that anyone on Medicare now won't see a change in their benefits. They're playing a shell game with American seniors.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345564025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:47:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345564207000-37</Id><Title>Ryan lied to his mom about medicare?</Title><Msg>ryanrommey cuts WILL hit current seniors, but i don't think that is what Ryan told his mom or the senior crowd he paraded his mom in front of like a trick pony. "..... That's because their plan to repeal Obamacare, and to "restore" the $716 billion in provider cuts means that Romney/Ryan will either have to make up those funds with revenues or with cuts to current seniors, because without that money, Medicare becomes insolvent by 2016. The Republican allergy to new revenue pretty much determines they'll squeeze that money out of seniors, and Romney advisors are admitting it. Romney campaign advisor Ed Gillespie was the first to admit they'd target current seniors by raising the eligibility age for Medicare. And now another advisor is admitting that benefits cuts are definitely on the table. Avik Roy, an outside health care adviser to the Romney campaign, admits that committing to billions of dollars in higher Medicare spending in the near-term will make it difficult for Romney to achieve its separate goal of reducing overall federal spending to modern lows. But he notes thatRomney could make up the difference elsewhere in the budget or, by “mak[ing] other changes to the Medicare program, such as increased means-testing, that don’t alter the program’s basic structure.” Means testing would apply to people on Medicare now, and it would be a cut to benefits, benefits that retirees earned through years of work and contributing to the system. That's not the only thing seniors would be losing under Romney/Ryan. If the Affordable Care Act is repealed, with it goes the $4.1 billion seniors and disabled people have saved on prescription drugs. That amounts to an average of $768 in annual savings for Medicare patients, a significant chunk of money for anyone on a fixed income. Also gone with repeal are the free cancer screenings, mammograms and other preventive services."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345564207000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345565149000-38</Id><Topic><Title>we were better off in the Clinton years</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345466300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I'm taking it up with you. You declared it to be something to brag about. Probably half or more of those 23M jobs were wiped out with the dotbomb dropping. You don't, won't take that into account. Consider that it was early 2001 that the full extent of the market bust took effect, then we had 9-11, then comes the mortgage fallout. You're bias lets you accept whatever foolish reports or opinions you read or hear. You can't blame Bush for the actions of others, in this case the crooks that destroyed companies and Democrats who changed the formula for lending. Your bias lets you accept whatever foolish reports or opinions you read or hear. It's predictable.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1345565149000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:05:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345565568000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Consider yourself to get the top deals with Oracle Corporatio</Title><Username>nickolas.james73</Username><Timestamp>1345552406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, Ill be buying more tomorrow.</Msg><Username>kim.sloan60</Username><Timestamp>1345565568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345565632000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan lied to his mom about medicare?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345564207000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:50:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thing liberals are so stupid. What Ryan is not telling you is that the Repubs plan to do away with unnecessary bureaucratic agencies that have 5 people doing 1 job. Medicare will benefit. I like it.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1345565632000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345565801000-41</Id><Topic><Title>we were better off in the Clinton years</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345466300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Sure, we were better off with Clinton, when the dotcom bubble, false economy was booming. Then it imploded right after Bush was elected. Amazing how liberals forget how this had a major impact on the financial security of millions of people." did you notice how you said it imploded AFTER Bush took office. Because the last implosion and TARP happened BEFORE Obama took office. not that it matters - because you think Obama is to blame for the slow economy.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345565801000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345566072000-42</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mesa the big time supporter of bailouts of the big banks, corporate welfare, and crony capitalism.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345566072000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345566177000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Doesn't Take Navy Seals Seriously!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1345560908000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:55:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt!! It was Obama's big F'ing fat self-pumping MOUTH that got those 22 Seals, and 8 others Americans, killed! The Tillman cover-up started at the platoon level... and made it up to the General Staff in Afghanistan... but dammm well not to the White House! Obama and many of his Pig Staff should be tried and jailed for Treason!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1345566177000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345566383000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Doesn't Take Navy Seals Seriously!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1345560908000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:55:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it wasn't like Obama said "Bring it on" like the little guy in the cowboy hat said</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345566383000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345566516000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Doesn't Take Navy Seals Seriously!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1345560908000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:55:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't imagine Navy Seals finding out they are actually following orders of Valerie Jarrett.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345566516000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345566831000-46</Id><Topic><Title>we were better off in the Clinton years</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345466300000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:38:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the WSJ is correct, clinton has BY FAR the better job record than bush. bush was a total disaster: clinton year before elected UE = 7.5% year after he left office UE = 5.7% bush year before elected UE = 4% year after he left office UE = 9.7% clinton midterm to end of term UE 4.9% to 4.7% bush midterm to end of term UE = 5.5% to 9% http://data.bls.gov/timeseries/LNU04000000?years_option=all_years&amp;periods_option=specific_periods&amp;periods=Annual+Data</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345566831000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345566917000-47</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" supporter of bailouts of the big banks, corporate welfare, and crony capitalism" you just described Romney and Ryan, so i take it you are not voting for them?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345566917000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345567249000-48</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am describing you. You supported the banking bailout. Believe Wall Street deserves tax money. You supported the auto bailouts. Big wealthy companies living at the expense of the taxpayer for no good reason yet you support all of it. Then complain about corporate welfare? You really are clueless.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345567249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345567836000-49</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mccain palin romney ryan all supported TARP ryan also asked for stimulus money, btw. i take it you are not voting for a prez this year? Romney Ryan are just what you describe AND they are big pumpers of DEREGULATION that so far have resulted in the disasters that had to be bailed out.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345567836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:50:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345568085000-50</Id><Title>why didn't Ryan offer MOM the voucher medicare?</Title><Msg>see what phonies and frauds the gop are? Ryan paraded his mom like a trick pony to assure seniors that medicare would be AS IS for THEM and AS IS for all age 53 or 54 NOW. If his "premium support" medicare is so good, why didn't he offer his MOM a chance to choose it? NOW?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345568085000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345568497000-51</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a big believer in deregulation. I am an opponent of bailouts. You believe in regulation that doesn't work, want the government to spend even more on failed regulation and you want them to bailout big business as well. As for voting there are other issues. I want medicare vouchers, private accounts for SS, tax reform, Obamacare repealed. Obama has got to go, even the uber liberal Newsweek posted a cover story saying the same.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345568497000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345568661000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan lied to his mom about medicare?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345564207000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:50:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are the stupid one , anyone but you can see that the "premium support" romneyann medicare is a lousy deal, why do you think Ryan didn't just offer it to his mom and all the seniors he assured would be getting the FULL AS IS medicare? Why do you think the seniors had to be assured they WOULD NOT have to take the Romneyann "premium support" voucher medicare?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345568661000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345568667000-53</Id><Title>Uptrending RSI and MACD on Oracle Corporation</Title><Msg>Cool chart setup today, might be a buyer at this level on Oracle Corporation http://STOCKMARKETSHAREPRICES.INFO</Msg><Username>valeneplahs</Username><Timestamp>1345568667000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345568963000-54</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I want medicare vouchers" you must think it odd that Ryan's mom doesn't want the voucher and NOBODY would choose it NOW, which is why Ryan was out there parading his mom to assure seniors that they would NOT have to take the romneyann voucher medicare. i think it is hilarious that YOU do want it, and YOU may get it it! and thanks for paying for MY and Ryan's mom's FULL as is medicare!!! lol.. and i am OK with the tax cut too!..... jeez what hardtimes..... tax cuts for the rich and full AS IS medicare and social security for most of the boomers...... PLUS increased military spending...... amazing!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345568963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345569393000-55</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How soon will Obama reinstate the "up-tick" rule for short selling? How soon do you think Obama will reinstate the Glass-Steagl Act?</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1345569393000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345569613000-56</Id><Topic><Title>Dropkick has killed this board!</Title><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1345482353000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:05:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am in awe of all the meaningless posts and one-star attacks!!! I feel sorry for these clowns.</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1345569613000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:20:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345569766000-57</Id><Topic><Title>db carl,,.HOW can I be ruining the board?</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345504234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:10:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You keep posting repetitively on silly comments! Then, you incite the one-star bandit into a frenzy of one star attacks and the board is completely ruined!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1345569766000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345570173000-58</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How soon do you think Obama will reinstate the Glass-Steagl Act" what difference would it make now moron? the damage was done. and besides the gop congress would throw a fit and not cooperate . in 2008 the dems did get rid of the infamous "enron loophole" but they had to do it over W's veto...... now anything the dems do gets stonewalled by the pub house, but you are too dishonest to mention that, aren't you?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345570173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345570256000-59</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>65% short of the money needed to fund medicare benefits. The voucher or just let government start setting prices so fewer and few doctors will see medicare patients. Unfortunately that is the current choice. As always if I had been given the choice I would have said no thanks to SS and Medicare. Only hope young people are given that choice eventually.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345570256000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345570408000-60</Id><Topic><Title>why didn't Ryan offer MOM the voucher medicare?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345568085000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan's mom did say that she wants the ryanromney "premium support" voucher medicare NOW right? and the crowd of seniors did agree and demand to trade their FULL, AS IS medicare for a Ryan voucher NOW , right?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345570408000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345570655000-61</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bla bla bla. i guess you missed it that money is no problem. hence.... MORE tax cuts for the rich..... and Ryan's mom and boomers like me get the FULL, AS IS medicare and social security!!! plus INCREASED military spending..... so why are you whining about money? what part of tax cut don't you understand?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345570655000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345571643000-62</Id><Title>Biden going to GOP convention?</Title><Msg>if true, what's the angle? http://dailycaller.com/2012/08/21/secret-service-prepping-for-biden-to-appear-at-gop-convention-says-drudge/</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1345571643000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345572158000-63</Id><Topic><Title>Biden going to GOP convention?</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1345571643000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is a more interesting thought on who should be invited to speak at the Republican convention. "Following the recommendation of a friend with "a lifetime of hotel- and restaurant-management experience," McGovern bought a small hotel and restaurant, the Stratford Inn in Connecticut. He poured his savings into the place, investing his seven year's worth of post-Senate earnings from the lecture circuit. A contributing factor to the failure, according to McGovern, was the regulations that make it tough to make a profit. In a mea culpa that should chill every lefty on the Hill, McGovern said: "I wish I had known more firsthand about the concerns and problems of American businesspeople while I was a U.S. senator and later a presidential nominee. That knowledge would have made me a better legislator and a more worthy aspirant to the White House." http://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/2012/08/16/recruit_george_mcgovern_to_speak__at_the_republican_convention/page/full/ As for Biden, he could show up as a pinata. One whack for every stupid comment he has ever made.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345572158000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345572401000-64</Id><Topic><Title>why didn't Ryan offer MOM the voucher medicare?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345568085000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If ryanromeny "premium support" medicare is so good, why didn't ryan offer his MOM a chance to choose it? NOW? why didn't MOM demand the voucher NOW...... why didn't the seniors in the audience demand Ryan 'premium support" NOW?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345572401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345574878000-65</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must have missed Jon Corzine, skated on his dealings at Goldman Sachs, althought the voters in NJ were smart enough to send him packing. Skating on his dealings at MF Global, Holder has his back, just keep bundling those campaign contributions. Now Corzine is ready to start a new hedge fund. Regulation is great, to ignore them just send your campaign contributions care of Obama/Biden 2012. You will end up on Holder's do not prosecute list.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345574878000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:47:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345579197000-66</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dimwit, what are you whining about? You want no rules. the gop is the party of deregulation and no rules........ jeez, bush even vetoed the dem attempt to get rid of the infamous "enron loophole". now the gop obstructs any and all dem plans, and they are running on MORE deregulation . Anti-Regulation Bill Passed By House GOP 07/26/12 WASHINGTON -- The Republican-led House on Thursday passed legislation that would freeze major government regulations The latest GOP attempt to rein in Obama administration's rulemaking</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345579197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345579553000-67</Id><Topic><Title>why didn't Ryan offer MOM the voucher medicare?</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345568085000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ryan's mom peed on sonny boy's voucher plan.She didn't say one good thing about it and all the seniors didn't want it either, they were glad to hear they would NOT be getting the ryan plan...... that WAS ryan's point. the gop will NOT sc,.r..oo YOU over with the Ryan plan, YOU get the full, as is, medicare........</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345579553000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345579978000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Consider yourself to get the top deals with Oracle Corporatio</Title><Username>nickolas.james73</Username><Timestamp>1345552406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope this has the effect you think, I put the majority of my position for sale Great idea. Did it!</Msg><Username>marks.robin77</Username><Timestamp>1345579978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345580092000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Consider yourself to get the top deals with Oracle Corporatio</Title><Username>nickolas.james73</Username><Timestamp>1345552406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds good to me. With everything that's happening, I'd hate to be on the sidelines WHEN it pops again.</Msg><Username>marks.robin77</Username><Timestamp>1345580092000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345580680000-70</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds good to me. We already know that one, the government does not do well at enforcing regulations and two, there are many bad unintended consequences. What is the penalty for closing the Enron loophole? How much does it cost to enforce this rule? Is it as bad as bankruptcy and destruction of the entire company which costs zero to enforce? The free market is far better at punishing fraud.</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345580680000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345580755000-71</Id><Topic><Title>Biden going to GOP convention?</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1345571643000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know if he is going to the convention but not a peep since he went to the woodshed.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1345580755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345580841000-72</Id><Topic><Title>the Stratford Inn</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345572831000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe it was McGovern who hired Larry, Darrell and Darrell</Msg><Username>goodnicknamesaregone</Username><Timestamp>1345580841000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345581182000-73</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporatio - The Valuable Ticket has been Issued. Did u Get yours?</Title><Username>wfederico38</Username><Timestamp>1345559784000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:36:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holding it tight.Good luck to all</Msg><Username>pattonswanson36</Username><Timestamp>1345581182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:33:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345583430000-74</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'the government does not do well at enforcing regulations' they did just fine until the gop began undoing the depression era regulations in the reagan years..... over 50 years of the markets working well...... too well for the wall street fraud and greedsters, so right off with the S&amp;L dereg...... FRAUD and manipulation and billions in bail outs. ditto for the electric markets ... fraud and manipulation and a huge mess that has resulted in LESS competition.Nothing like letting wall street traders get between you and what was once your locally run utility, greedy wall streeters now run the utes for themselves, previously they were run for and by local communities. No more Dallas light and power, for instance, now it's some corporation run by private equity outfit from the cayman islands or what ever. and ditto for letting wall street ONCE AGAIN get into home mortgages ... and btw, even Ryans's mom doesn't want the ryan voucher for medicare....</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345583430000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345584328000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Biden is GOING to TAMPA! NOT to scum convention</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345583645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who gives a rats azss where this POS Biden goes, you clueless POS! For all I care he can go to hell tomorrow!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1345584328000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345585259000-76</Id><Topic><Title>Biden is GOING to TAMPA! NOT to scum convention</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345583645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is indeed of the Dingy Harry mold, a worthless POS.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1345585259000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:40:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345585357000-77</Id><Topic><Title>gop birthcontrol</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345485924000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:05:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in gop world rape is a form of birthcontrol?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345585357000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345585398000-78</Id><Topic><Title>Republican National Convention Happening During Peak Of Tampa Hurricane Season</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345583890000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:18:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only storm will be the worthless POS protesters running around trying to destroy Tampa. Police need to not be nice to some of these idiots.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1345585398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:43:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345585595000-79</Id><Topic><Title>Consider yourself to get the top deals with Oracle Corporatio</Title><Username>nickolas.james73</Username><Timestamp>1345552406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:33:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**** this share has a Bright future......</Msg><Username>bobbie.bailey75</Username><Timestamp>1345585595000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345586056000-80</Id><Topic><Title>the GOP is STILL pumping deregulation</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345557532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For you meathead Dumbocraps, Medicare is not sustainable. It is trillions in arrears and must change. Vouchers is one solution, as is rationing, and increasing premiums for recipients. At least Republicans are making an attempt to resolve the problem long term.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1345586056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345586399000-81</Id><Title>gop the authority on rape &amp; "prostitutes" &amp; "sl uts"</Title><Msg>"If it's a legitimate rape, the female body has ways to try to shut that whole thing down."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345586399000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345587173000-82</Id><Title>so it's all about Akin</Title><Msg>it is past 5:00 pm central time and Akins has not stepped out. So it is all about Akin and his career.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1345587173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:12:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345587659000-83</Id><Topic><Title>Biden going to GOP convention?</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1345571643000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:54:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP Convention theme, "We built this" What a way to sock it to 'em. Romney is collecting money from tradtionally Democrat cities. Does this mean less money for Obama? Dems didn't believe the Obama bubble would pop, it has.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1345587659000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345588450000-84</Id><Topic><Title>the Stratford Inn</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345572831000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 14:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Larry, Darrell and Darrell. I loved Bob Newhart. I still watch the reruns of when he played a psychiatrist. That was great comedy. The sitcoms today are just not funny and those reality shows are supposed to be entertainment?? Who is interested in the everyday drama of the Kardasians or Mobwives? You can't get more phony than those bimbos. I bet they're Democrats.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1345588450000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:34:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345591377000-85</Id><Title>Hey NFNY, THE YOHOHO COCKROACHSKO!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>YA'LL BE THE PRESIDANTE OF YA COCKROACHVILLA, AGAIN?????? CAUZ THE ONLY RESIDENTS THERE ARE ALL CONJOINED WITH YA, THROUGH YA LEAKING REAR: IVAN, PETER, RUNNER, BULLSHEET, MOVEON_MOVEOUT, ANNIE, SEEBUG, GOODNICKNAME,,,,!!!! BUT!!! OF COURSE!!! YEHA!!! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>nfny.is_yohoho_cockroachsko</Username><Timestamp>1345591377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345599651000-86</Id><Topic><Title>so it's all about Akin</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1345587173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:12:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he's certainly got the attention of Romney and the GOP who would like to clear the mess out of the way before the convention. "Mongo like rape" -Blazing Sadles</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345599651000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345599688000-87</Id><Topic><Title>This board sure sucks like carl,..because of carl the gay dude</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345585432000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:43:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, ding-dong .... I am not Gay!!! FOOL!!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1345599688000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345599726000-88</Id><Topic><Title>Republican National Convention Happening During Peak Of Tampa Hurricane Season</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345583890000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:18:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good thing they have thoughts and prayers on their side</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1345599726000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345599775000-89</Id><Topic><Title>You keep posting repetitively on silly comments!</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345569920000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:25:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My posts have a point, Your posts are just silly! WAKE UP AND SMELL THE COFFEE!!!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1345599775000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345599976000-90</Id><Topic><Title>Hey NFNY, THE YOHOHO COCKROACHSKO!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>nfny.is_yohoho_cockroachsko</Username><Timestamp>1345591377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:22:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yo ....beeeaaachhh, suck my fat one!!! I bury those cockroaches!!!</Msg><Username>ivanthedestroyer111</Username><Timestamp>1345599976000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345600581000-91</Id><Title>Americans tune out Afghan war as fighting rages on</Title><Msg>Our lives money and treasure are being wasted on a war Obama lost long ago. Meanwhile or "progressive" media would rather talk about "legitimate rape." ***** KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — It was once President Barack Obama's "war of necessity." Now, it's America's forgotten war. The Afghan conflict generates barely a whisper on the U.S. presidential campaign trail. It's not a hot topic at the office water cooler or in the halls of Congress — even though more than 80,000 American troops are still fighting here and dying at a rate of one a day. 12 years later and at what result? Public opinion remains largely negative toward the war, with 66 percent opposed to it and just 27 percent in favor in a May AP-GfK poll. More recently, a Quinnipiac University poll found that 60 percent of registered voters felt the U.S. should no longer be involved in Afghanistan. Just 31 percent said the U.S. is doing the right thing by fighting there now. [. . .] More than 1,950 Americans have died in Afghanistan and thousands more have been wounded [. . .] Candidate Obama promised to refocus America's resources on Afghanistan. But by the time President Obama sent 33,000 more troops to Afghanistan in December 2009, [it was already a failed policy] and sapped resolve to build a viable Afghan state. [Obama and], his administration [failed with] Afghanistan's seemingly intractable problems of poverty and corruption. The American people have grown weary [...]. [American troops have been killed by accidents or murdered] in attacks from members of the Afghan security forces — either disgruntled turncoats or Taliban infiltrators. Meanwhile, Obama and his incompetent Administration will continue their failed policies through at least 2014.</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1345600581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345601435000-92</Id><Title>Media DEMANDED Resignation of Repub for *Legitimate Rape* COMMENT!!!</Title><Msg>Meanwhile a Democrat Congressman was caught having sex with a 17 year old girl! But THAT didn't make the news! I guess that was a "Legitimate Rape"?</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1345601435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345603503000-93</Id><Title>Voter ID is About LEGITIMATE Voting!</Title><Msg>By LEGITIMATE US Citizens! This will keep the voting process from being "legitimately raped!" We'll even concede Barack H. Obama's vote as a legitimate vote, by a legitimate citizen who is...legitimate!!! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1345603503000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:45:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345605340000-94</Id><Topic><Title>Americans tune out Afghan war as fighting rages on</Title><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1345600581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's what was going on four years ago: Liberal news media was making multiple reports per-day listing every soldier that was killed, with names and photographs and back stories. A tally of the American dead from the beginning of the war was included with every report. Liberal news media are all scum. Just like you.</Msg><Username>dumbbuttuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345605340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345605417000-95</Id><Topic><Title>Voter ID is About LEGITIMATE Voting!</Title><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1345603503000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:45:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be great if we could keep imbeciles like you from voting!</Msg><Username>dumbbuttuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345605417000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345605579000-96</Id><Topic><Title>so it's all about Akin</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1345587173000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:12:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that any different than Charles Rangle and his career? For that matter, Joe Biden, Nancy Pelosi, Harry Reid and Maxine Waters have all said really stupid, offensive and unAmerican things. But none of them has been asked to step down. It's REALLY all about DEMOCRATS maintaining their majority and power.</Msg><Username>dumbbuttuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345605579000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345605708000-97</Id><Topic><Title>This board sure sucks like carl,..because of carl the gay dude</Title><Username>dropkickuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345585432000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:43:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why he is inadequate!</Msg><Username>dumbbuttuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345605708000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345605794000-98</Id><Topic><Title>Media DEMANDED Resignation of Repub for *Legitimate Rape* COMMENT!!!</Title><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1345601435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 22:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>F-off yerself! You, Obama and ALL DEMOCRATS are scum! And Obama is a FAILURE!</Msg><Username>dumbbuttuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345605794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345606134000-99</Id><Topic><Title>gop birthcontrol</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1345485924000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:05:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Claire McCaskill is the Democrat, FOOL! And SHE didn't make the stupid comment.</Msg><Username>dumbbuttuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345606134000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345606461000-100</Id><Title>PROOF of how much trouble Barry the Kenyan is in!!!!!</Title><Msg>No paid lib psycho bloggers on the message boards anymore! Just the few lib low-life trolls who've been here since Bush. Anyone remember back in 2008 when they were swarming every Yahoo board? Either Soros pulled the plug on his funding or they are waiting until closer to the election because they were so ineffective before. I believe Soros pulled the plug because there has been talk of a Media Matters is BROKE. I think it's also because the conservatives have the facts on the Republican side and it's too hard to sell the bucket of crap that the Dems must sell to win.</Msg><Username>dumbbuttuuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1345606461000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 23:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>