<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348922194416-1</Id><Topic><Title>Politifact rates Mitts comment on the 47%........ FALSE.... ZERO truth on the truth 0 meter</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348778482206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 16:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from politifact: "Our ruling Romney said that the "48, 49 percent" that supports President Barack Obama are "people who pay no income tax." But the polls and income tax data don't back this up. Obama gets substantial support from people earning more than $50,000 -- and 90 percent of them, or more, do pay taxes. And Romney gets lots of support from seniors, many of whom have no income tax liability. We rate the claim False."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348922194416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348922578532-2</Id><Title>romney advisors writing WSJ op-ed articles : 23 pieces in the WSJ’s op-ed pages attacked President Obama or praised Romney without the writers acknowledging their political connections to Romney</Title><Msg>(jeez, PAID Romney shills posing as op-ed writers) Veteran journalists attack Murdoch paper for failure to disclose writers’ political sympathies The Wall Street Journal has been criticised by senior US journalists for failing to disclose that 10 of its op-ed writers are Mitt Romney advisers. According to an inquiry by Media Matters, 23 pieces in the WSJ’s op-ed pages attacked President Obama or praised Romney without the writers acknowledging their political connections to Romney. Max Frankel, a former New York Times executive editor, called the lack of disclosure “shameless.” He added: “They ought to put a banner saying Romney has approved of this page… It looks like the Wall Street Journal editorial and op ed pages have enlisted in the campaign. They should be disclosing that.” “Not disclosing is inexcusable,” declared Stephen Henderson, editorial page editor of the Detroit Free Press. “It is important to disclose that so that the reader can evaluate the argument intelligently,” said Nicholas Goldberg, Los Angeles Times editorial page editor, adding that transparency is “absolutely essential.”</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348922578532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348925296265-3</Id><Topic><Title>romney advisors writing WSJ op-ed articles : 23 pieces in the WSJ’s op-ed pages attacked President Obama or praised Romney without the writers acknowledging their political connections to Romney</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348922578532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:42:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's skeletons are about to come out of the closet for Halloween!!! BWHHAHHAHHAHHAHHAHHAHHA!!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348925296265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 09:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348925372202-4</Id><Topic><Title>Corporations ARE running America</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348851763872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Corporations aren't hiring 'cause they don't like Obama. Prolong the misery. 4 more years.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348925372202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 09:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348925553998-5</Id><Topic><Title>"Fiscal Cliff"</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1348759453199</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:24:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the Bush tax rate cuts expire. The Obama payroll tax holiday expires. Cap gains go up. You think 75% is bad in France. With state, local and federal taxes, Obama and his political buddies are gonna take all you've got.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348925553998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 09:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348925704372-6</Id><Topic><Title>Book value is 9 yet dummies line up to pay 30</Title><Username>heartbreaker_toom</Username><Timestamp>1348681003611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:36:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A world inflated by cheap money. The more money Bernanke prints, the slower the economy gets. The next Obama recession started in May. Buy high and sell higher to a greater fool.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348925704372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 09:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348926698288-7</Id><Title>stupid crazy neocons think they own the mideast and can control the lives of 100s of millions of people</Title><Msg>The crazy stupid neocons with their jumping up and down while farting, foaming and yapping "mooslims are after me", "mooselimbs are after me"... 'mooselims are coming" are quite the idiot spectacle Please just charge on over there yourselves and "build it" yourself and redistribute your money to burn up on your insane quest to rule the hundreds of millions of people you hate so much you burn their holy books, trash their churches and murder innocent sikhs here in the usa because you are stupid enough to think they are muslims. Before you launch off on your newest loon crusade , you should consult Ron Paul and ask him about blow back, the one thing he got right.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348926698288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 09:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348929214673-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will say anything to get re-elected</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348888267871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sick World. And, most people are dumber then rocks. You will see another 4-years of Obama!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1348929214673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348932118550-9</Id><Title>why wouldn't they hate USA “imperialism,” as it used to be called?</Title><Msg>"Many Americans believe they are innocent bystanders in the Muslim world, or involved there on an altruistic “mission” to uplift the benighted natives, to selflessly shoulder the heavy burden of policing the unruly globe, or abroad to wage an unending struggle against the dark forces of what we call “terrorism.” What they do not at all understand is that the American imperium’s goal is to advance its own strategic, economic and political goals and keep much of the planet under its influence. In the last century, such ambitions and behavior used to be called “imperialism,” a practice that became synonymous with the British Empire. At its apogee, the Britain Empire ruled one quarter of the globe and most of the world’s seas and oceans. At the heart of this vast empire lay its “jewel,” India. Britain’s rule over India was known as the British Raj (raj meaning rule in Hindi). In 2008, I published my second book, “American Raj.” I sought to distill my fifty years of experience in the Muslim world to explain to Americans what was really going on in the troubled region, why it was so violent and unstable, and our own errors in fostering this problem. I tried to show what a positive role America could play for the entire Muslim world." eric margolis</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348932118550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348936171011-10</Id><Topic><Title>romney advisors writing WSJ op-ed articles : 23 pieces in the WSJ’s op-ed pages attacked President Obama or praised Romney without the writers acknowledging their political connections to Romney</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348922578532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:42:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama administration tells contractors again: Don’t issue layoff notices 09/28/12 07:25 PM ET The Obama administration issued new guidance intended for defense contractors Friday afternoon, reiterating the administration’s position that the companies should not be issuing layoff notices over sequestration before the November elections. The Labor Department issued guidance in July saying it would be “inappropriate” for contractors to issue notices of potential layoffs tied to sequestration cuts. But a few contractors, most notably Lockheed Martin, said they still were considering whether to issue the notices — which would be sent out just days before the November election. Posted: 3:52 p.m. Friday, Aug. 17, 2012 1 million Ohioans using free phone program Fees on phone bills pay for $1.5 billion national Lifeline program By Josh Sweigart Staff Writer A program that provides subsidized phone service to low-income individuals has nearly doubled in size in Ohio in the past year — now covering more than a million people. At the same time, federal officials say they’re reining in waste, fraud and abuse in the program.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1348936171011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348939600262-11</Id><Title>More Gaffes From Messy</Title><Msg>Imperial America is taking over the world with radical, neo-con warmongering. Sounds like a page from Ghangis Kahn's to do list. Witness how dumb and deranged messy is. He condemns Bush for wanting to spread Democracy yet he loves the idea of spreading communism in this country or the spread of mooslim law protected by the anti-christian progressive goons. He missed the part about Is-lams objective of taking over the world. We will resist as fearlessly as extreme factions of Is-lam resist "Imperial" America to keep their subjects under barbaric laws. Count on it.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348939600262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 13:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348941637545-12</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mittens will rack up the biggest deficts in history and the gop can threaten default again by refusing to raise the debt ceiling....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348941637545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348941903630-13</Id><Title>don't work for a living if you want to lower your taxes , and other Mitten's tax evasion ideas</Title><Msg>Romney Tax Tips: 10 Ways to Stiff the IRS Shielding your millions from Uncle Sam—how American is that? By Josh Harkinson Unlike Mitt Romney, most Americans who will pay their taxes today can't afford fancy accountants. But Romney has reluctantly made public his tax returns, and thus shared valuable strategies to ensure that he pays a far lower rate than, say, Warren Buffett's secretary. Citizens for Tax Justice [1] recently waded through Romney's 2010 return—in which his $22 million in income was miraculously taxed at just 13.9 percent [2]—to come up with a handy primer for how you, too, can beat the IRS at its own game. To paraphrase: 1. Don't work for a living The tax rate on money earned actually working ("salaries and wages") can be more than double the rate on money earned sitting around watching your investments go up in value ("capital gains"), thanks to the work of other people. Almost all of Romney's income is taxed as capital gains. 2. If you work, disguise your compensation as capital gains About half of the $15 million in capital gains and dividend income Romney reported in 2010 was actually compensation for his work at Bain Capital. But using a tax loophole favored by private-equity guys, he was able to get paid by taking equity stakes in deals that he put together ("carried interest," in tax parlance) instead of in the proletarian form of a fully taxable salary. Bonus: This allowed Bain to avoid paying Medicare payroll taxes. 3. Give to charity—but not with cash, checks, or money orders In 2010, Romney was able to write off $1.5 million worth of Domino's Pizza stock he donated to a charity. It is likely that he originally received the stock as compensation from Bain, in which case the price he paid for it would have been close to zero. In this scenario, by donating the stock instead of selling it and donating the cash, Romney would have saved about $220,000 in taxes. 4. Give to charity—but not now Romney's return reports income from the W. Mitt Romney 1996 Charitable Remainder UniTrust. Not only is the trust tax exempt, but when Romney set it up 16 years ago, he got a tax deduction for making a charitable donation. Though the money in the trust is eventually supposed to go to charity, Romney can receive income from the trust for a number of years—quite possibly for the rest of his life. 5. Give to charity—your own In 2010 Romney made a tax-deductible, $1.5 million donation to the Tyler Charitable Foundation, which he controls. Commanding your own foundation allows you to curry favor with political and business allies by donating money to their pet organizations and causes. For instance, in 2010 the Tyler Charitable Foundation donated [3] $100,000 to to the George W. Bush Library. 6. Do not invest in America Certain foreign investment vehicles allow you to avoid certain taxes. For example, Romney's Individual Retirement Account could bypass the Unrelated Business Income Tax by investing through a foreign corporation. Though it's hard to know whether Romney availed himself of those kinds of savings, he has invested substantially in foreign entities, including ones based in offshore tax havens such as Bermuda, the Cayman Islands, and Luxembourg. 7. Invest in sexy financial instruments Romney earned $415,000 from an investment that gets special tax treatment: Through an accounting loophole, 60 percent of the profits from the investment are treated as long-term capital gains, a designation that has tax benefits, no matter how long the investment is held. 8. Borrow money to invest While you can't deduct interest from car loans or credit cards, you can write off interest on the money you borrow to make certain types of investments—for instance, if you borrow from a broker to buy stock (a "margin loan"). Portfolio management fees are also write-offs. A fellow like Romney, who makes his millions mainly from investments, could probably deduct a fair sum. 9. Push the limits of the law When you engage in a type of transaction that the IRS views as potentially abusive, you must disclose it in a separate form. In 2010, Romney filed six such forms. 10. Be part of the 1 percent When it comes to taxes, it costs money to save money. You'll need to hire lawyers to help you set up tax-exempt charities and trusts or exploit offshore tax havens—and a professional money manager if you plan to invest in sexy financial instruments. It probably won't be cost effective if you aren't already rich, but any hard-working son of a governor can land a job at a private-equity firm and start getting paid in carried interest. Bonus: You might make enough money to one day run for president.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348941903630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348942823296-14</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>vinaout959</Username><Timestamp>1348932708310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:31:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>capriceecw895</Username><Timestamp>1348942823296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348943375893-15</Id><Title>COLA increase for social secuity will be 8% for 2013, thanks Obama</Title><Msg>you have my vote.........ha ha........just kidding, but the cola should be announced next month and is expected to be around 2%.</Msg><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1348943375893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348943989954-16</Id><Topic><Title>COLA increase for social secuity will be 8% for 2013, thanks Obama</Title><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1348943375893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:29:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gubment workers should get no raises -- U.S. and local gubments are broke. They should take it out on the bas*tud mayor or state governor or state rep who has wasted taxpayer's money by colluding with the public unions. The cupboard is bare. The politicians have robbed the taxpayers and they should be thrown in jail.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348943989954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348944055684-17</Id><Topic><Title>Daily Presidential Tracking Poll: Obama 46%, Romney 46%</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348700004031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 18:53:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You gonna get a rude awakening my friend. BWHHAHHAHHAHHAHHAAAAAAAAA!!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348944055684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:40:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348944298774-18</Id><Title>Rasmussen Reports daily tracking poll in reality: Obama 48% Romney 46%</Title><Msg>Saturday, September 29, 2012 The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Saturday shows President Obama attracting support from 48% of voters nationwide, while Mitt Romney earns the vote from 46%.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348944298774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348944304578-19</Id><Title>Rasmussen Reports daily tracking poll in reality: Obama 48% Romney 46%</Title><Msg>Saturday, September 29, 2012 The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Saturday shows President Obama attracting support from 48% of voters nationwide, while Mitt Romney earns the vote from 46%.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348944304578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348944359526-20</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>vinaout959</Username><Timestamp>1348932708310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:31:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>marhtazii482</Username><Timestamp>1348944359526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348944753123-21</Id><Title>Gallup: Obama 50%, Romney 44% among registered voters</Title><Msg>Rasmussen Reports daily tracking must be part of the conspiracy since they also show Obama pulling ahead.....Obama 48%......Mittens 46%</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348944753123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348945633440-22</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (ORCL)</Title><Username>vinaout959</Username><Timestamp>1348932708310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:31:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>giselehsg77012</Username><Timestamp>1348945633440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 15:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348946061365-23</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Actually Dumber Than We Thought!</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1348259898791</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:38:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The last 40 days of the Obama disaster. Hope is on the way!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348946061365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 15:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348946350371-24</Id><Title>When does QE4 begin?</Title><Msg>Uncle Ben needs to start QE4. Obama has stolen from the future and destroyed the economy. MORE EXTRAORDINARY MONETARY POLICY IS REQUIRED BECAUSE OBAMA HAS SPENT AMERICA INTO A GREEK HOLE LIKE A DRUNKEN SAILOR.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348946350371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 15:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348946475915-25</Id><Topic><Title>Gallup: Obama 50%, Romney 44% among registered voters</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348944753123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:52:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Projections are based on 2008 voter turnout which will be far, far lower for illegal aliens.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348946475915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 15:21:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348947874370-26</Id><Title>Uncle Ben for President!!!</Title><Msg>QE is simply a fake program where the Fed "creates money on a computer to buy their own securities." They just change the amount on the computer by $40 Billion each month. What difference is that going to make to the corporations who do the hiring? None. Nobody's going to be doing any hiring until there's some clarity on fiscal policy. That won't come until January, if then. Lame duck session after the election is only 10 days. The path of least resistance is to do nothing. There will be protests in the streets of D.C. There won't be a re-election party. With the weakness here and apparent worsening condition of Europe the Fed is going to go even bigger than buying $40 billion worth of mortgage backed securities per month. When asked if this equates to QE4, Parker said, "we suspect they'll do more. What they've announced so far just appears too small to us to offset the weaker economic data." We are all going to be millionaires!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348947874370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 15:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348953208839-27</Id><Topic><Title>Read this new report on Oracle Corporation</Title><Username>calandrareidenbach</Username><Timestamp>1348939005640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 13:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you do with a drunken sailor... Early in the morning?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348953208839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 17:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348957327321-28</Id><Topic><Title>Rasmussen Reports daily tracking poll in reality: Obama 48% Romney 46%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348944304578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:45:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rassmuss to polls is like fox to "news",,face it.......America has.....thus far REJECTED romknee 100%, F off,</Msg><Username>dropkicksomemore7</Username><Timestamp>1348957327321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:22:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348958906724-29</Id><Topic><Title>Rasmussen Reports daily tracking poll in reality: Obama 48% Romney 46%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348944304578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:45:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get a clue -- Obama can't seem to get over 47%. You are headed for a rude awakening and then you go over a fiscal cliff. That's a 1-2 punch. Only 35% of the country thinks he's going the right way. The undecideds always go to the challenger. Fewer illegal aliens will be able to vote this time. We need a turnaround specialist not a clown.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1348958906724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348959769153-30</Id><Title>Debates Seen As the Tarnishing of Obama's Image</Title><Msg>He's the obfuscator in chief. His orations of impressive words will not work this time. Romney will easily trip him on a dozen issues. Obama should not go after Romney's taxes or he's going to be made a fool of. The Dems might as well record his speeches from 2008 and O just has to move his mouth.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348959769153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348969505664-31</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt puulease give me a tax cut to save the USA and reduce the deficit and increase defense spending with</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348803035525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:30:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bummer has exceeded all debt projections in America. He holds the record Big Bird. He just went into shock recently. He was told two Brazillians were killed in Afganistan and his eyes crossed. After recovering, he asked Axlerod and Hilary, how much is a Brazillian.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348969505664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348969599910-32</Id><Topic><Title>More Gaffes From Messy</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348939600262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 13:26:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Methinks Messssssebird be a closet Mooslim.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348969599910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348969871452-33</Id><Topic><Title>why wouldn't they hate USA “imperialism,” as it used to be called?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348932118550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America never coveted other lands like the empires in Europe. America never stole from foreign lands. If deals for resources were made, leaders of both countries agreed to the deal. Foreign leaders may have skimmed off the top, maybe even American leaders too like the Pelosi clan does.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348969871452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348970078520-34</Id><Topic><Title>don't work for a living if you want to lower your taxes , and other Mitten's tax evasion ideas</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1348941903630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bottom line, did he break any tax laws? So should he apologize for being a smart business man with good tax lawyers. Why are libiots so resentful of success. Unless it's a fellow libiot like the communist Soros.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1348970078520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348974454562-35</Id><Title>Factcheck Vanzinf.</Title><Msg>No, messy is not a closet mooslim. Any religion is an abomination to him. Spreading Democracy is abhorrant but spreading communism is a good thing. His derangement has reached critical mass. These goons think we should follow the lead of countries that slaughtered millions of their own people for the sake of lifelong power. Mao, Stalin, Castro. Like I said, we will resist as fearlessly as Is-lam resists Democracy. messy can move to China and work on a labor farm like a good commie.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1348974454562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 23:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>