<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347285725112-1</Id><Title>Obama is quite the businessman...</Title><Msg>His Government Motors sells the Chevy Volt for $40,000..... Its Costs GM $89,000 to make them... Not to worry... in a streak of Genius... he gives 2 year leases for $5,000... While the car only depreciates $10,000 in that time frame He was losing $50,000 a unit... so he devised a plan to lose $55,000 and with a straight face.. they say they will make up the losses on volume... which in theory is actually possible as costs are spread over more vehicles.... But the #s say they would have to sell more than 1000Xs the current # of units sold... while 3 competitors bring cheaper versions of an electric car to market</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1347285725112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347285749517-2</Id><Topic><Title>Romney says screw specifics and details------ just shut up and trust me---no details are needed</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347209682170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 12:54:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Thugs Rough Up Gallup For Polls They Don’t Like By Dick Morris on September 10, 2012 The Obama Administration’s Justice Department announced, on August 22nd, that it was joining a lawsuit by a former Gallup employee and whistleblower against the Gallup Corporation for allegedly overcharging the government on polling work. The announcement comes on the heels of a confrontation between Gallup staffers and Obama strategist David Axelrod in which he accused the company of using out of date sampling methods which, he said, generated polling data negative to the president. The whistleblower’s lawsuit has been kicking around since 2009, but the Justice Department joined the suit only after the run-in between Axelrod and Gallup in April of this year. In a scene right out of a typical authoritarian regime, Fox News reports that “employees at the venerable Gallup polling firm suggested they felt threatened by Obama campaign adviser David Axelrod when he questioned the methodology of a mid-April poll showing Mitt Romney leading the president – according to internal emails published Thursday.” That poll that sent Axelrod ballistic showed Romney leading Obama 48-43 percent. The Daily Caller published e mails that started when Axelrod sent a tweet to Gallup saying the tracking poll was “saddled with some methodological problems” and directing followers to a National Journal story in which a professor suggested outdated sampling. According to the email chain titled “Axelrod vs. Gallup,” the White House in addition asked that a Gallup staffer “come over and explain our methodology,” which was apparently perceived as a subtle threat. Fox News reported that “a Gallup official said in an email he thought Axelrod’s pressure ‘sounds a little like a Godfather situation.’” Gallup refused to change its methodology to suit the White House. And the Justice Department intervention in the whistleblower suit came three months later. The whistleblower, Michael Lindley, claims that Gallup violated the False Claims Act by overcharging the federal government for its services to the U.S. Mint, the State Department and other federal agencies. The Justice Department plans to add Gallup’s work with FEMA to the list of alleged overcharges covered in the lawsuit. Lindley charged that Gallup overestimated the number of hours of field work that the government surveys would require and that it billed the feds based on the inflated estimates. According to the Washington Times, Lindley worked for the Obama campaign in 2008 as an Iowa field organizer based out of Council Bluffs, Iowa. As the election progresses, this blatant effort to influence Gallup’s data and its poll numbers is an example of Chicago political thugs at their worst.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1347285749517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347286576040-3</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there were many good things while reagan was pres, but I remember the term rolling recession, tax cuts for companies building plants overseas, and trippling nat. debt form less than 1 trillion to 3 trillion. lowwered the top tax from 70% to 28% starting us on this spiral of ballooning nat.debt</Msg><Username>caray11</Username><Timestamp>1347286576040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:16:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347287687156-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is quite the businessman...</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1347285725112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The govt is trying to subsidize research on electric cars, as they are the way of the future. Before you get all pissy about it, the govt subsidizes a lot of things: space exploration, medical research, agricultural practices, gas and oil production and supply (you can add the cost of Middle East wars here), etc. etc. etc.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347287687156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347290202313-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is quite the businessman...</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1347285725112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sure are a big fan of failure, aren't you? Guess that's why you're so in love with Blobama.</Msg><Username>uguyssuk</Username><Timestamp>1347290202313</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347290609395-6</Id><Title>Anyone Else Having Problems w/ 'Start New Topic' &amp; 'Reply' Using IE9!??</Title><Msg>They only seem to work with Chrome &amp; Firefox... no longer IE9!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1347290609395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347292117966-7</Id><Title>Bought some Sept 32 puts</Title><Msg>Will they disappoint?</Msg><Username>jmcbride383</Username><Timestamp>1347292117966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347293205639-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Carl</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347146908504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would never take my eye off the us government as suspect thouth. It does not bode well for them that there has not been another credible attack since! Yahoo, is a FREAK SHOW, YOU CANT EVEN POST URLS ANYMORE! GO TO INFOWARS WEBSITE, THE ITALIAN SUPREME COURT "PRESIDENT" BELIEvES 911 was a FALSE FLAG. I WOULD AGREE, HE HAS A POINT, BUT WHAT IS ANYONE GOING TO DO ABOUT IT?</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293205639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347293541485-9</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Carl</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347146908504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And, on 9/11 or a week after, I said “YOU DON’T ALLOW BANDITS TO LEAD NATIONS TO WAR.” QUOTING: TSUN TZU, ART OF WAR, BECAUSE IT WILL BRING DISASTER TO YOUR TREASURY. 911 was a police matter, if it was only 20, and therefore, the us government is responsible for this reckless campaign of terror and murder, which has destroyed the treasury, constitution and millions of lives! Reichstag Fire, and countless campaigns in history show examples of government murdering their own people to gain power. Sure, the US is Suspect, however, unlikely, because it seems this AL QUADEA never existed except as a CIA MURDER DRONE!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293541485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347293735312-10</Id><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Msg>I posted on the topic, what is your view? There are some interesting possibilities? I heard the President of the Italian Supreme Court has called 9./11 a false flag. I think that Warrents much attention on the subject.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347293866325-11</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Obama Avoiding the Poor Jobs Report?</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1347232147933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No ... the Question is, Why are the republicans not rubbing it in his FACE? You do know the U-6 Figures are over 15%, now, comrade, if you repubs play your cards right you could throw him out of office for trying to LIE and MANIPULATE REPORTS! THATS CORRUPTION AND BREACH OF FIDUCIARY RESPONSIBILITY!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293866325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347295408064-12</Id><Title>Oracle Corporation is showing historic technical movement</Title><Msg>Oracle Corporation looks really unstable right now. Check out this site for the latest updates in Oracle Corporation goo.gl/NCrA2</Msg><Username>helenniforos</Username><Timestamp>1347295408064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347297977610-13</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Else Having Problems w/ 'Start New Topic' &amp; 'Reply' Using IE9!??</Title><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1347290609395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:23:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The solution is that the Message Board no longer works in IE9 "Compatability View"!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1347297977610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347298030932-14</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know what happened, but the official story for building 7 seems very unlikely. If you have dozens of steel columns supporting a building, they don't all disappear from 1 second to the next. This cannot happen. Look at the video. The fire cannot explain this.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347298030932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347299209389-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get that the proposed raises of taxes on the 1+% is mostly symbolic. So maybe we should raise the top brackets more. The top rate was 92% to pay for WW II. That would be real not just symbolic.</Msg><Username>economist_too</Username><Timestamp>1347299209389</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347299861330-16</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What experience do you have with large airliners nearly full of jet fuel soaking skyscrapers, to justify your tin-hatted opinion,</Msg><Username>dumb_quest</Username><Timestamp>1347299861330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:57:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300341424-17</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not in question that thousands of pounds of Jet Fuel can melt Steel Beams, however, I would say, that on impact the superstructure was significantly weakened beyond hope. Thousands of Pounds of 757 moving at 500-mph, it would surly slice through superstructure like a Hot Knife through butter, then add the Fuel. Now, the Us government has Gained too much power, and they look very suspicious “fornicating” with Al Quadea Groups in Syria and Libya. Therefore, there seems to be a plot and that Plot should be investigated. We are not all fools who Cry in their BEER for Patriotic Buffoonism!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347300341424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300688906-18</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tower One and Two were destroyed by the Aircraft. Building Seven By Fire and Debris. I don’t know the specifics, lots of Fire, and if the Fires were beyond hope, the due to the situation, I would not be surprised if they ordered a controlled demolition of building Seven. The complete Lack of any further Attacks is very Suspicious. The Supplying of Al Quadea in Libya and Syria is Very Suspicious! The mystery of Bin Ladens Death is Very Suspicious! And, it does seem that the us could have planned (or used this attack) to base their mechanizations for total global conquest!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347300688906</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300859236-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Obama Avoiding the Poor Jobs Report?</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1347232147933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soft on Wall Street Dems weak on corporate crime Last Updated: 12:29 AM, September 10, 2012 Among the many falsehoods pushed at last week’s Democratic Convention is that this is the party of the people, unafraid to hold Corporate America responsible for its many ills. Judging by the records of the last two Democratic administrations, just the opposite appears to be true. Certainly, President Obama and, to some extent, Bill Clinton like to talk a good game in terms of class warfare, but under both men, real corporate crime-fighting has been at best a side issue — despite the immense amounts of white-collar fraud their administrations faced. Corzine: Well-connected Democrat is facing no charges despite losing $1.6 billion — whereas Bush team jailed Republican fat cats. UPI Corzine: Well-connected Democrat is facing no charges despite losing $1.6 billion — whereas Bush team jailed Republican fat cats. In fact, neither Obama nor Clinton can hold a candle to the corporate crime-fighting record of George W. Bush, that supposed lapdog for large corporate interests. Consider: As we near the four-year anniversary of the financial crisis, not a single Wall Street fat cat has been charged with violations of securities laws in connection with the 2008 collapse. Then we have the outlandish case of MF Global, the brokerage firm run into the ground nearly a year ago by Obama’s pal and campaign-cash bundler, Jon Corzine. It isn’t just that the former Goldman Sachs CEO and New Jersey governor took outsized trading risks that destroyed the firm; his firm appears to have misused and lost $1.6 billion in customer funds in the process. Under securities laws, those customer funds were supposed to be kept sacrosanct — yet not a single MF Global employee, much less Corzine, has been charged in the matter by the Obama Justice Department or the Securities and Exchange Commission. For obvious reasons, Clinton’s putrid record on corporate crime went unmentioned as he rewrote history during his speech. (It wasn’t all that got left out as he tried to make people believe they’re doing just fine after four years of Obamanomics. He also skipped over the fact that the ’90s economy only got strong after he turned right by cutting deals with the Republicans to cut taxes and spending and to reform welfare.) Simply put: The law-enforcement agencies under Clinton turned a blind eye to one of modern history’s biggest corporate crime waves. Forget insider trading, where traders are basically ripping off each other. During the Clinton years, big Wall Street firms came up with new and imaginative ways to screw the average investor — who for the first time was turning to the stock market to save for retirement. Yet there wasn’t much of a peep from Bubba’s Justice Department or the corporate watchdogs at his Securities and Exchange Commission. One such rip-off involved feeding small investors fraudulent research reports so they’d buy overvalued (and overhyped) Internet stocks — but there were many more, most of which came to light after the tech bubble burst in March 2000 and small investors lost countless billions in savings. Those research scandals were initially uncovered by a Democrat — New York then-Attorney General Eliot Spitzer. But the Bush SEC shared in the enforcement of the cases. The Bush Justice Department and SEC also started the investigations that have led to Obama’s one arguable area of success on Wall Street crime — insider-trading prosecutions. But the victims of insider trading are mostly other traders, not the average Joe — this isn’t the sort of corporate crime that ruins Main Street. Anyway, lots else got prosecuted under Bush. The accounting fraud at Enron, a Houston-based energy company with ties to the Republican Party, brought immediate indictments against individuals like Bush friend Ken Lay. One major firm, accounting giant Arthur Andersen, was forced out of business. The same thing with Worldcom, another accounting fraud prosecuted in the Bush era that landed its CEO in jail. As it happens, the last major financial firm to be run out of business after being hit with criminal charges (prior to Arthur Andersen) was Drexel Burnham Lambert — and that was accomplished by President Ronald Reagan’s US attorney for Manhattan, a guy named Rudy Giuliani. Of course, Bush’s record of corporate crime fighting was far from perfect. Much of the risk-taking that led to the 2008 collapse occurred under the nose of his regulators — but these practices started to explode during the Clinton years. The bigger point here is that, if you’re really keeping a score card on who’s going after corporate America’s bad guys, the Democrats may talk a good game but have very little to show for it. Keep that in mind the next time President Obama says how much he detests the Wall Street fat cats.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347300859236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347300963736-20</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Trade towers were built on the cheap. The Structure was of a poor design. Fire-proofing was totally absent ... not suprising. The Construct was similar -by comparison- to a car, FULL FRAME or UNIT-BODY. THE TOWERS WERE DOOMED, as they were of Unit-body design. the outer structure carried the load, therefore, by proportion, the impact severed the load carrying capacity, the Fire, further degraded trusses and beams transferring load to the outer-skeletal super-structure.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347300963736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:16:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347301981183-21</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What experience do you have with large airliners nearly full of jet fuel soaking skyscrapers, to justify your tin-hatted opinion, ------------------------------------------------------------ Building WTC7 wasn't hit by aircrafts and/or jet fuel.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347301981183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302131939-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Obama Avoiding the Poor Jobs Report?</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1347232147933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are riight they are sell-outs and panders, like the Republicans. But Obama did say a few things that hurt the bankers feelings. Isn't that enough? :)</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347302131939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302231260-23</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if the Fires were beyond hope, the due to the situation, I would not be surprised if they ordered a controlled demolition of building Seven. ------------------------- Normally it takes weeks to organize a controlled demolition. They wouldn't do it with a fire in the building. The official story is that the fire caused the collapse. This is not a good explanation. No steel frame building ever fell due to fire. Even if it did fall, it wouldn't fall the way it did.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347302231260</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302664700-24</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Carl</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347146908504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check out the first attempt to bring down the World Trade Center. Info was all contained in sworn testimony in a New York court. FBI had a paid fink in with the bombers. Through him they obtained the ingredients of the bomb from the FBI. He then told them the time and place they were going to set the bomb off. They did NOTHING to stop it. Why was there a stand down of the whole No. Amer. Air Defense system on 9/11? Coincidence? Bush's buddies at PNAC had called for a "Pearl Harbor type event" to get us into the middle East a few years before. "False Flag" events are more common than you think. "COINTELPRO" in the South during the 60's was rife with them. The U.S.S. Liberty was an attempt at one that failed and then was covered up as a "mistake" by the con man from Texas.. Check out "The Lavon Affair" also from the 60's. Only fools trust government to tell the truth about much of anything.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1347302664700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302667840-25</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Carl</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347146908504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check out the first attempt to bring down the World Trade Center. Info was all contained in sworn testimony in a New York court. FBI had a paid fink in with the bombers. Through him they obtained the ingredients of the bomb from the FBI. He then told them the time and place they were going to set the bomb off. They did NOTHING to stop it. Why was there a stand down of the whole No. Amer. Air Defense system on 9/11? Coincidence? Bush's buddies at PNAC had called for a "Pearl Harbor type event" to get us into the middle East a few years before. "False Flag" events are more common than you think. "COINTELPRO" in the South during the 60's was rife with them. The U.S.S. Liberty was an attempt at one that failed and then was covered up as a "mistake" by the con man from Texas.. Check out "The Lavon Affair" also from the 60's. Only fools trust government to tell the truth about much of anything.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1347302667840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347303703397-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Carl</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347146908504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a f'ing clue, chump! Only fools trust fools for anything but Pigshyt! stu·pid    [stoo-pid, styoo‐] Show IPA adjective, stu·pid·er, stu·pid·est, noun adjective 1. lacking ordinary quickness and keenness of mind; dull. 2. characterized by or proceeding from mental dullness; foolish; senseless: a stupid question. 3. tediously dull, especially due to lack of meaning or sense; inane; pointless: a stupid party. 4. annoying or irritating; troublesome: Turn off that stupid radio. 5. in a state of stupor; stupefied: stupid from fatigue.</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1347303703397</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:01:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347303941639-27</Id><Title>Gee! Will The Great Bernanke Bail-Out His Buddy Obama!!</Title><Msg>Sure he will! What's another f'ing trillion down the sewer to either of these Pigs! QE III... YeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaaaa!! Bring it on baby!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347303941639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347304186025-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Carl</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347146908504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a f'ing clue, chump! Only fools trust fools for anything but Pigshyt! ------------------------------ I'm an engineer and I believe the laws of physics trump people's beliefs. You on the other hand believe any story that comes your way. You probably still believe that Iraq was attacked because of WMDs.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347304186025</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347304286913-29</Id><Topic><Title>Gee! Will The Great Bernanke Bail-Out His Buddy Obama!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347303941639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:05:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure he will! -------------------------- Now that Romney said he wouldn't keep him, Bernanke's only chance to keep his job is to help Obama.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347304286913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306565096-30</Id><Topic><Title>Gee! Will The Great Bernanke Bail-Out His Buddy Obama!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347303941639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:05:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right... and who would expect him to do anything that might benefit the Country at the expense of his own career! YeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa! Government servants... always serving themselves!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347306565096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306725213-31</Id><Topic><Title>Gee! Will The Great Bernanke Bail-Out His Buddy Obama!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347303941639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:05:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turn Down $400 Million Deal, 16% Pay Raise... Have Highest Average Salary In Nation... Average $76,000 per year before benefits... SOME SCHOOLS OPEN -- BUT JUST TO SERVE FREE MEALS... 400,000 STUDENTS UNLEASHED... Cops Pour Onto Streets to Deal With 'Unsupervised Kids'... GODFATHER 'DISAPPOINTED,' VOWS TO END STRIKE... Rahm's kids' school open; attend elite $25,000-a-year 'lab'... Romney blasts... NOT PRESENT: Obama no comment... 79% of Chicago 8th Graders 'Not Proficient in Reading'...</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347306725213</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347307157721-32</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, thats why "I think" it was blown. The military has people trained with pre-fab Demo-Charges to Quickly Blow Down a Building. I dont know how much of building 7s structure was damaged from impact or debris? Interesting, we have another 7 to add to my collection of 7s. I think, however, it is possible, that debris from tower one and two could have damaged number 7??</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347307157721</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347308142799-33</Id><Topic><Title>nazyo, where did you go?</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347293735312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:15:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a grid of columns. The pictures show the building largely undamaged after the 2 towers fell. If it was damaged locally, it cannot explain the fall of the (large) parts that were undamaged. Or part of building would fall and then pull the rest. What cannot happen is the whole building falls like if all columns suddenly had disappeared. Google 9/11: Blueprint for Truth.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1347308142799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347308284115-34</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Supporter , Top Hollywood Director Believes Incest Is Acceptable September 10, 2012 10:43 AM LAS VEGAS (CBS Las Vegas) – A top Hollywood director finds it acceptable for people to commit incest. In an interview with The Wrap, director Nick Cassavetes believes no one should judge a brother and sister being with each other if they are in love. “I’m not saying this is an absolute but in a way, if you’re not having kids – who gives a damn? Love who you want. Isn’t that what we say? Gay marriage – love who you want?” Cassavetes told The Wrap. “If it’s your brother or sister it’s super-weird, but if you look at it, you’re not hurting anybody except every single person who freaks out because you’re in love with one another.” Cassavetes added that he does not have experience with incest. The comments come after he unveiled his latest movie “Yellow” – in which a woman had an incestuous affair with her brother that is in prison – at the Toronto Film Festival. The movie does not yet have a distributor in the states. Cassavetes also directed “Alpha Dog” and “The Notebook.”</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1347308284115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347309407174-35</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>September 10, 2012, 11:58 a.m. ET 'A Strike of Choice' Article Comments (103) more in Political Diary » smaller Larger By MATTHEW PAYNE Chicago Public Schools are closed today. And as a result 350,000 students will need to find something else to do. Why? Teachers unions, of course. The Chicago Teachers Union went on strike today after failing to reach an agreement with the city on a new contract. The contract would, among other things, require teachers to undergo performance evaluations that could be used to fire underperforming instructors. Enlarge Image image image Bloomberg Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel "Recognizing the board's fiscal woes, we are not far apart on compensation," union president Karen Lewis explained in a press release. "However, we are apart on benefits. We want to maintain the existing health benefits. Another concern is evaluation procedures. After the initial phase-in of the new evaluation system it could result in 6,000 teachers (or nearly 30 percent of our members) being discharged within one or two years. This is unacceptable." What's really unacceptable here is the fact that despite having among the highest paid teachers in the country, only 56% of Chicago Public School students graduate high school. Last school year only 31% of Chicago high school students met or exceeded Illinois state academic standards. And despite the district's $700 million budget deficit, Chicago teachers unions still demanded a 30% raise. City officials have sent more than 20 proposals to the union in the past week. But apparently none have been good enough. "I believe this is avoidable because this is a strike of choice," Democratic Mayor Rahm Emanuel said at a news conference last night. The unions, as usual, claim to be acting in the best interests of students. "We must do things differently in this city if we are to provide our students with the education they so rightfully deserve," said Ms. Lewis. If that were really the case, however, telling the teachers she represents to show up to class would be a better start.</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1347309407174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347310639089-36</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marc A. Thiessen Marc A. Thiessen Opinion Writer Why is Obama skipping more than half of his daily intelligence meetings? By Marc A. Thiessen, Monday, September 10, 10:41 AM President Obama is touting his foreign policy experience on the campaign trail, but startling new statistics suggest that national security has not necessarily been the personal priority the president makes it out to be. It turns out that more than half the time, the commander in chief does not attend his daily intelligence meeting. The Government Accountability Institute, an investigative research organization, examined President Obama’s schedule from the day he took office until mid-June 2012, to see how often he attended his Presidential Daily Brief (PDB) — the meeting at which he is briefed on the most critical intelligence threats to the country. During his first 1,225 days in office, Obama attended his PDB just 536 times — or 43.8 percent of the time. During 2011 and the first half of 2012, his attendance became even less frequent — falling to just over 38 percent. By contrast, Obama’s predecessor, George W. Bush almost never missed his daily intelligence meeting. I asked National Security Council spokesman Tommy Vietor about the findings, and whether there were any instances where the president attended the intelligence meeting that were not on his public schedule. Vietor did not dispute the numbers, but said the fact that the president, during a time of war, does not attend his daily intelligence meeting on a daily basis is “not particularly interesting or useful.” He says that the president reads his PDB every day, and he disagreed with the suggestion that there is any difference whatsoever between simply reading the briefing book and having an interactive discussion of its contents with top national security and intelligence officials where the president can probe assumptions and ask questions. “I actually don’t agree at all,” Vietor told me in an e-mail, “The president gets the information he needs from the intelligence community each day.” Yet Vietor also directed me to a Post story written this year in which Obama officials discuss the importance of the intelligence meeting and extol how brilliantly the president runs it. “Obama reads the PDB ahead of time and comes to the morning meeting with questions. Intelligence briefers are there to answer those questions, expand on a point or raise a new issue,” The Post reported. “One regular participant in the roughly 500 Oval Office sessions during Obama’s presidency said the meetings show a president consistently participating in an exploration of foreign policy and intelligence issues.” Not so consistently, it seems. Since Obama officials have actively promoted the way the president runs his daily intelligence meeting as evidence of his national security leadership (even releasing a photo of him receiving the briefing on an iPad), it is fair to ask why he skips the daily meeting so often.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1347310639089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347311069966-37</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why is Obama skipping more than half of his daily intelligence meetings?" you should ask why W skipped killing bin laden for a decade of occupations in Bushraq and Bushghanistan that cost tens of thousands of US casualties and a couple trillion dollars.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1347311069966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347312510366-38</Id><Title>1st time since 1998, the House of Representatives voted to maintain the current military budget rather than increase Pentagon spending</Title><Msg>Even House Republicans can't stomach spending $17,000 on a helicopter drip pan. by Miriam Pemberton and Gabriel Rossman Here's a milestone of sorts. In July, for the first time since 1998, the House of Representatives voted to maintain the current military budget rather than increase Pentagon spending. It's the first step toward bringing the budget down.(Military Port Shield, an OtherWords cartoon by Khalil Bendib) Within the bill, which included more than $600 billion for the military, the House embedded a few gestures toward fiscal sanity. Most important was the decision of 89 Republicans to join most Democrats in shaving a billion bucks off the budget that House Republican leaders had proposed. That's mostly a symbolic move in a budget of this size, but worth celebrating nevertheless. Rep. Hal Rogers (R-KY), the chair of the House committee in charge of spending, wanted a contract for his district in Kentucky to buy $17,000 drip pans for Black Hawk helicopters.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347312510366</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347318663691-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is quite the businessman...</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1347285725112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently you support political paybacks for campaign donations, pork barrel spending. Crony capitalism. The Koch family gets bashed because all they want is none of the above so they can compete on even terms. See the WSJ article from Charles Koch dated Sept 9th</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1347318663691</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347318804264-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Obama Avoiding the Poor Jobs Report?</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1347232147933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course Obama is not responsible for the economy. George Bush is even 4 years after he is out of office. ROFLMAO As for Europe that should have been an enormous opportunity not a problem. We should have reduced corporate tax rate, holiday on repatriated money. Sucked in all that capital from Europe to grow our economy. It is called competition. Time for us to do some and quit whining.</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1347318804264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347325302309-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is quite the businessman...</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1347285725112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You saying we should get rid of NASA or what?</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347325302309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347325766736-42</Id><Title>Where's George W?</Title><Msg>Where's Waldo? If Romney and Ryan are advocating more neo-con Mideast policy (see Iran), and less regulation of Wall Street, and lower taxes on the well-to-do, all of which they support, then why is George W not being touted??? These are largely an extension of policies that the Bush regime was pushing. Where's George W , our role-model????</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347325766736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>