<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351340454373-1</Id><Topic><Title>here is what the gop in congress have done the last few years to screw the 99%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289898135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Putting corporations that ship American jobs overseas before American workers 1. Protect federal funding for corporations that offshored or outsourced American jobs overseas (H. Res. 38, Roll no. 19) 2. Protect corporations that outsource American jobs overseas in violation of the National Labor Relations Act (H.R. 2587, Roll no. 710) 3. Protect ability of foreign countries, like China, to engage in the unfair trade practice of currency manipulation that hurts American jobs (H.R. 3078, Roll no. 780) 4. Protect corporations that outsource or plan to outsource American jobs overseas in labor elections (H.R. 3094, Roll no. 869) Protecting massive tax breaks for the wealthiest at the expense of middle class families 5. Protect tax breaks for millionaires instead of relief for middle class families (H.R. 491, Roll no. 922) 6. Hold hostage a tax cut for middle class families to protect tax breaks for the wealthiest 2% (H.AMDT 1475 to H.R. 6169, Roll no. 550) Attacking Medicare, Social Security and programs that help older Americans 7. End the Medicare guarantee (H. Con. Res. 34, Roll no. 277) 8. Against prohibiting ending the Medicare guarantee and turning it into a voucher system (H.R. 5, Roll no. 41) 9. Against ensuring that no funds can be used privatize and cut Social Security and Medicare (H.J.Res. 48, Roll no. 178) 10. End initiative to protect seniors who have worked a lifetime to own a home and earn financial stability (H.R. 830, Roll no. 170) 11. Against protecting preventative health care funding for seniors (H.R. 1217, Roll no. 263) 12. Against protecting seniors from abusive, predatory, unfair, and deceptive financial practices (H.R. 1315, Roll no. 620) Attacking women’s health and safety 13. Limit the ability of women to access reproductive health care (H.R. 3, Roll no. 292) 14. Take away the right of women with private health insurance to choose how they spend their own money in purchasing health insurance covering reproductive health care (H.R. 358, Roll no. 789) 15. Weaken protections for battered immigrant women who are legally here (H.R. 4970, Roll no. 258) 16. Remove protections for LGBT victims of domestic violence (H.R. 4970, Roll no. 258) 17. Against access to life-saving health care for women (H.R. 358, Roll no. 788) 18. Against protecting the medical records of victims of rape and incest (H.R. 3, Roll no. 291) 19. Eliminate funding for Planned Parenthood (H.AMDT. 95 to H.R. 1, Roll no. 93) 20. Repeal protections to ensure that health insurance companies can’t discriminate on the basis of gender (H.R. 2, Roll no. 14) Against giving middle class families a fair shake, weakening consumer protections 21. Decease Americans ability to access to affordable health care, weaken protections for Americans with pre-existing conditions, and end health care benefits (H.R. 2, Roll no. 14) 22. Block restoring Pell grants that help millions of Americans afford tuition for higher education (H.R. 1, Roll no. 146) 23. Block requirement that charter schools conduct criminal background checks for felons, registered sex offenders, and child abusers (H.R. 2218, Roll no. 704) 24. Weaken and delay consumer protections against abusive, deceptive and unfair financial practices – including for credit cards, mortgages and student loans – putting Wall Street before Main Street families (H.R. 1315, Roll no. 621) 25. Abolish help for families who are underwater to refinance into lower-cost mortgages they can afford to repay (H.R. 830, Roll no. 171) 26. Eliminate short-term loans for up to 33,000 homeowners who lost their jobs through no fault of their own and are at risk of losing their homes (H.R. 836, Roll no. 174) 27. Eliminate efforts to strengthen neighborhoods that were hard hit by the housing bubble burst (H.R. 861, Roll no. 188) 28. Against protecting against gas price increases for American families (H.R. 1938, Roll no. 649) 29. Protect oil and gas speculators that drive up gas prices (H.R. 2112, Roll no. 458) 30. Restrict ability of agencies to protect consumer health and safety (H.R 10, Roll no. 901) 31. Jeopardize funding for Amber Alerts (H.R. 1076, Roll no. 191) 32. Slash funding for programs that put food on the table for low income families and repeal programs that help working families (H.R. 5652, Roll no. 247) Putting special interests before a government of, by, and for the people 33. Increase the influence of secret special interest groups in campaigns by eliminating options for citizens to have a voice in elections (H.R. 359, Roll no. 25) 34. Weaken protections to ensure that every vote counts, including those of service members (H.R. 672, Roll no. 466) 35. Protect pay for Members of Congress during a government shutdown (H.R. 1255, Roll no. 223) Putting Big Oil before the environment and middle class families 36. Protect unnecessary taxpayer subsidies for Big Oil (H.J. Res. 44, Roll no. 153) 37. Reward oil companies that owe fines and penalties for damage in the Gulf Coast (H.R. 1229, Roll no. 308) 38. Protect Big Oil and corporate jet owners at the expense of middle class families (S. 627, Roll no. 676) 39. Against protecting seniors and children from lung disease (H.R. 910, Roll no. 248) 40. Prevent the EPA from addressing serious health threats from carbon pollution, including increased childhood asthma (H.R. 910, Roll no. 249) 41. Make broad swaths of the Atlantic and Pacific Coasts automatically open to lease for offshore oil drilling (H.R. 1231, Roll no. 320) 42. Weaken the Clean Air Act (H.R. 2021, Roll no. 478) 43. Against safeguards that protect our drinking water from arsenic and perchlorate (H.R. 2018, Roll no. 572) 44. Cut water quality funding (H. Amdt 143 to H.R. 1, Roll no. 123) 45. Substantially cut environmental protection (H. Con Res. 34, Roll no. 277) 46. Protect polluters over children and pregnant women (H.R. 2681, Roll no. 763) 47. Protect polluters over people who live in nursing homes and assisted living facilities (H.R. 2250, Roll no. 790) 48. Against protecting the public from toxic dust know to cause cancer and brain damage (H.R. 1633, Roll no. 911) 49. Undermine clean air standards (H.R. 1633, Roll no. 912) 50. Weaken live-saving protection from cross-state pollution (H.R. 2401, Roll no. 741) 51. Block the EPA mercury and air toxics standards that are estimated to save 12,000 every year and more than 1 million asthma attacks (H.AMDT.799 to H.R 2401, Roll no. 737)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351340454373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351340571032-2</Id><Title>gop in congress Putting corporations that ship American jobs overseas before American workers</Title><Msg>gop voted to protect outsorcing of jobs, it's their RECORD. Putting corporations that ship American jobs overseas before American workers 1. Protect federal funding for corporations that offshored or outsourced American jobs overseas (H. Res. 38, Roll no. 19) 2. Protect corporations that outsource American jobs overseas in violation of the National Labor Relations Act (H.R. 2587, Roll no. 710) 3. Protect ability of foreign countries, like China, to engage in the unfair trade practice of currency manipulation that hurts American jobs (H.R. 3078, Roll no. 780) 4. Protect corporations that outsource or plan to outsource American jobs overseas in labor elections (H.R. 3094, Roll no. 869)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351340571032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351340726652-3</Id><Title>gop congress record of attacking medicare, ss</Title><Msg>Protecting massive tax breaks for the wealthiest at the expense of middle class families 5. Protect tax breaks for millionaires instead of relief for middle class families (H.R. 491, Roll no. 922) 6. Hold hostage a tax cut for middle class families to protect tax breaks for the wealthiest 2% (H.AMDT 1475 to H.R. 6169, Roll no. 550) Attacking Medicare, Social Security and programs that help older Americans 7. End the Medicare guarantee (H. Con. Res. 34, Roll no. 277) 8. Against prohibiting ending the Medicare guarantee and turning it into a voucher system (H.R. 5, Roll no. 41) 9. Against ensuring that no funds can be used privatize and cut Social Security and Medicare (H.J.Res. 48, Roll no. 178) 10. End initiative to protect seniors who have worked a lifetime to own a home and earn financial stability (H.R. 830, Roll no. 170) 11. Against protecting preventative health care funding for seniors (H.R. 1217, Roll no. 263) 12. Against protecting seniors from abusive, predatory, unfair, and deceptive financial practices (H.R. 1315, Roll no. 620)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351340726652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351340799552-4</Id><Title>gop in congress recent record Against giving middle class families a fair shake, weakening consumer protections</Title><Msg>Against giving middle class families a fair shake, weakening consumer protections 21. Decease Americans ability to access to affordable health care, weaken protections for Americans with pre-existing conditions, and end health care benefits (H.R. 2, Roll no. 14) 22. Block restoring Pell grants that help millions of Americans afford tuition for higher education (H.R. 1, Roll no. 146) 23. Block requirement that charter schools conduct criminal background checks for felons, registered sex offenders, and child abusers (H.R. 2218, Roll no. 704) 24. Weaken and delay consumer protections against abusive, deceptive and unfair financial practices – including for credit cards, mortgages and student loans – putting Wall Street before Main Street families (H.R. 1315, Roll no. 621) 25. Abolish help for families who are underwater to refinance into lower-cost mortgages they can afford to repay (H.R. 830, Roll no. 171) 26. Eliminate short-term loans for up to 33,000 homeowners who lost their jobs through no fault of their own and are at risk of losing their homes (H.R. 836, Roll no. 174) 27. Eliminate efforts to strengthen neighborhoods that were hard hit by the housing bubble burst (H.R. 861, Roll no. 188) 28. Against protecting against gas price increases for American families (H.R. 1938, Roll no. 649) 29. Protect oil and gas speculators that drive up gas prices (H.R. 2112, Roll no. 458) 30. Restrict ability of agencies to protect consumer health and safety (H.R 10, Roll no. 901) 31. Jeopardize funding for Amber Alerts (H.R. 1076, Roll no. 191) 32. Slash funding for programs that put food on the table for low income families and repeal programs that help working families (H.R. 5652, Roll no. 247)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351340799552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351340872132-5</Id><Title>gop in congress Putting special interests before a government of, by, and for the people</Title><Msg>Putting special interests before a government of, by, and for the people 33. Increase the influence of secret special interest groups in campaigns by eliminating options for citizens to have a voice in elections (H.R. 359, Roll no. 25) 34. Weaken protections to ensure that every vote counts, including those of service members (H.R. 672, Roll no. 466) 35. Protect pay for Members of Congress during a government shutdown (H.R. 1255, Roll no. 223) Putting Big Oil before the environment and middle class families 36. Protect unnecessary taxpayer subsidies for Big Oil (H.J. Res. 44, Roll no. 153) 37. Reward oil companies that owe fines and penalties for damage in the Gulf Coast (H.R. 1229, Roll no. 308) 38. Protect Big Oil and corporate jet owners at the expense of middle class families (S. 627, Roll no. 676) 39. Against protecting seniors and children from lung disease (H.R. 910, Roll no. 248) 40. Prevent the EPA from addressing serious health threats from carbon pollution, including increased childhood asthma (H.R. 910, Roll no. 249) 41. Make broad swaths of the Atlantic and Pacific Coasts automatically open to lease for offshore oil drilling (H.R. 1231, Roll no. 320) 42. Weaken the Clean Air Act (H.R. 2021, Roll no. 478) 43. Against safeguards that protect our drinking water from arsenic and perchlorate (H.R. 2018, Roll no. 572) 44. Cut water quality funding (H. Amdt 143 to H.R. 1, Roll no. 123) 45. Substantially cut environmental protection (H. Con Res. 34, Roll no. 277) 46. Protect polluters over children and pregnant women (H.R. 2681, Roll no. 763) 47. Protect polluters over people who live in nursing homes and assisted living facilities (H.R. 2250, Roll no. 790) 48. Against protecting the public from toxic dust know to cause cancer and brain damage (H.R. 1633, Roll no. 911) 49. Undermine clean air standards (H.R. 1633, Roll no. 912) 50. Weaken live-saving protection from cross-state pollution (H.R. 2401, Roll no. 741) 51. Block the EPA mercury and air toxics standards that are estimated to save 12,000 every year and more than 1 million asthma attacks (H.AMDT.799 to H.R 2401, Roll no. 737)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351340872132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351341833555-6</Id><Title>gop and their paymasters</Title><Msg>In a frenzy, House Republicans have voted to repeal the “Affordable Care Act” 33 times. Be assured their hatred for Obamacare is not because they want full Medicare for all. It is because they want to voucherize Medicare and hand patients over to the avaricious Aetnas and the Pfizers who return the favor with campaign cash. ralph nader</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351341833555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351341925676-7</Id><Title>the republicans have it in for women</Title><Msg>The Republicans seem to have it in for women and not just against health insurance covering reproductive health care, Planned Parenthood’s other services, or privacy for the medical records of victims of rape and incest. The Republicans en-mass voted to repeal protections to stop health insurance companies from discriminating on the basis of gender. On other consumer protections – forget it. The Republicans are indentured to the worst of their corporate paymasters. The Republicans either do nothing to help or actually push for rollbacks. No minimum wage to give 30 million Americans the same pay workers got back in 1968, adjusted for inflation. The Chamber of Commerce says no. So Boehner and Cantor curtsy. ralph nader</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351341925676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351342328750-8</Id><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Msg>AP poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks 57% are racist toward hispanics (who could have doubted it?,,,,,,, a gop pres contenter's family vacation house was named Camp N@@@@@head ......and this bum had ted nugent wearing the stars and bars play at his inauguaral ball)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351342591591-9</Id><Title>ORCL</Title><Msg>Have you seen the 2 page profile here ➡.ws/ORCL</Msg><Username>rubiegjaq694439</Username><Timestamp>1351342591591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346188848-10</Id><Topic><Title>Crazy ORCL Rumors!</Title><Username>carmenfarrell259</Username><Timestamp>1350908751137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:25:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, we're going to $40. It's going to be Yuuuuugggeeee!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351346188848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346332026-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 4 points over Mittens in Ohio.... cheney and fukwad beck no help to sweaty Mitt</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351305542205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 22:39:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wisconsin: Obama 49%, Romney 49% Libs are getting desperate. Obama is drowning. Hurricane Sandy is gonna take him under!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351346332026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346561288-12</Id><Topic><Title>THIS FORMAT SUCKS DDIICCKK!!! YAHOO MUST BE GOING BK ... SELL,SELL, SELL!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351285786709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:09:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No worries Carl. Marrissa has it under control. This new format does suk and so does Obama. The thumbs are better than the star ratings filter I'm sure you agree.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351346561288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346782412-13</Id><Topic><Title>Remarkable Update for ORCL. Read Now!</Title><Username>luisanderson380</Username><Timestamp>1350042834701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:53:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your little pump and dump scheme uses small sham loser companies on pink sheets. No thanks Buddy. Free advise that's meant to screw ya. Stay away from this toxic dung.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351346782412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351346943686-14</Id><Topic><Title>obama the SCHMOOZER....</Title><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1351263581009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:59:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 to 5 stupid Obama voters are eliminating each other on the South Side of Chicago every day. Only stupid Obama voters vote for Obama again. None of the black leaders in Chicago endorse him. He's screwed everyone over.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351346943686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351347249227-15</Id><Title>Des Moines Register endorses Romney</Title><Msg>Des Moines Register Hits Obama They endorsed Obama in 2008 but weren't going to make that mistake again! The editor-in-chief of The Des Moines Register published a pointed criticism of President Barack Obama Tuesday night for his campaign's refusal to go on the record when the president lobbied for the newspaper's presidential endorsement. Republican nominee Mitt Romney did agree to go on the record with the Register -- and even met with the editorial board in person during an Iowa campaign stop, which Obama declined to do. "Despite at least 28 campaign stops and 11 days in our state, we never could convince his team to carve out a few moments for our editorial board."</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351347249227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351347575958-16</Id><Title>Obama's Hostage Crisis</Title><Msg>Al-Qaida leader urges kidnapping of Westerners That's what you get for apologizing Bozo. The leader of al-Qaida has urged Muslims to kidnap Westerners to exchange for imprisoned jihadists, including a blind cleric serving a life sentence in the United States for a 1993 plot to blow up New York City landmarks.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351347575958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351347821205-17</Id><Topic><Title>Newt's prediction</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351252964456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:02:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has barely gotten over 47% most of his Presidency. Obama has lost a lot of support around the country. Many, many people who voted for him in 2008 won't make the same mistake again. Who wants to prolong the misery 4 more years? Newt is probably right on the mark. What are you going to do without your god? BWHHAHHAHHAAA!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351347821205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351348120728-18</Id><Title>More Democrats refuse to endorse Obama</Title><Msg>More Democrats bail on Obama and refuse to endorse him Most troublingly for President Obama are many Democrats who have refused to endorse Obama for president in 2012. Democrats fleeing from Obama include North Carolina congressmen Mike McIntyre and Larry Kissell, plus candidate Hayden Rogers and also Senator Claire McCaskill of Missouri. They didn't even go to the Democratic Convention in North Carolina this year.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351348120728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351348271373-19</Id><Title>Hugo Chavez and Vladimir Putin endorse Obama</Title><Msg>Wink. Wink. They know they can manipulate the clown.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351348271373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351348498965-20</Id><Title>Another centrist Dem who refuses to salute Obama</Title><Msg>Elected Dems in the states of West Virginia, Pennsylvania and New York have already gone on record as refusing to endorse the clown. We needed a Real Democrat in the White House not a commie.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351348498965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:34:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351348580818-21</Id><Title>African-American Church Leaders Condemn Obama For Gay Marriage</Title><Msg>Obama is losing the black vote. He might only get 80% instead of 95%.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351348580818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:36:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351348732581-22</Id><Title>LA Daily News Endorses Romney</Title><Msg>Endorsement: Mitt Romney for president - LA Newspaper Group (LA Daily News, Press-Telegram, etc.) Four years ago, as America faced serious trouble at home and abroad, this news organization embraced the need for bold change to a different brand of leadership and endorsed Barack Obama for president. That assessment of the depth of the nation's problems and the most promising solution was correct in 2008. Regrettably, it applies no less in 2012, after nearly a full term of Obama's administration. This is why the editorial board urges voters to choose Mitt Romney for president in the Nov. 6 election. He is the leader this country needs for the future. Obama suk. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351348732581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351348992226-23</Id><Title>Black minister asks Christians to vote for Romney</Title><Msg>Obama/Panetta Continue To Suppress Military Vote. Early voting ballots are not getting to soldiers.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351348992226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351349087668-24</Id><Title>Obama will be impeached for Benghazi if re-elected</Title><Msg>He's either the next McGovern or the next Nixon. He won't show his face again in public for 30 years.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351349087668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351349215998-25</Id><Title>Obama's failed leadership</Title><Msg>Democrat Idiot: From the mouth of Joe Biden at a SEAL’s memorial service – “Did your son always have balls the size of cue balls?” Failed Leadership: "Father of slain SEAL Tyrone Woods accuses White House of murder" - hero dies because of White House leadership incompetence Failed Leadership: Obama administration denied pleas for help during attack on Benghazi – resources to help and save Americans were available Failed Leadership: Obama refused to use an on-scene AC-130U gunship that could have stopped the Benghazi attack Failed Leadership: Hillary Clinton requested more security for Benghazi and Obama declined to provide it Failed Leadership: Obama’s never ending politics before patriotism gets people killed [video] Failed Leadership: Still no accounting for the successful terrorist attack on Camp Bastion – 7% of irreplaceable Marine aircraft were destroyed Polls&amp; Surveys: 49% of voters are Republican, 46% are Democrats - a 15-point swing since 2008, which an incompetent Obama has caused (... with some help from Pelosi and Reid too) Polls &amp; Surveys: Romney holds 7 point lead in daily tracking poll - 54% disapprove of Obama's performance Polls &amp; Surveys: Romney climbs to 5 point lead in Gallup poll Polls &amp; Surveys: Romney, Obama tied in Wisconsin - Obama won Wisconsin by 14 points in 2008 The Election: Based on Romney momentum, major Republicans are now talking landslide, plus taking Senate</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351349215998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351349536828-26</Id><Title>Obama imitates Putin with political virginity ad</Title><Msg>President Obama\u0019s is targeting young, stupid and impressionable voters with a double-entendre-laden YouTube ad that imitates one Vladimir Putin used to appeal to the young to win his presidential election earlier this year. Obama using Commie tactics on U.S. voters</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351349536828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351349538055-27</Id><Title>Obama imitates Putin with political virginity ad</Title><Msg>President Obama\u0019s is targeting young, stupid and impressionable voters with a double-entendre-laden YouTube ad that imitates one Vladimir Putin used to appeal to the young to win his presidential election earlier this year. Obama using Commie tactics on U.S. voters</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351349538055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351349921415-28</Id><Topic><Title>THIS FORMAT SUCKS DDIICCKK!!! YAHOO MUST BE GOING BK ... SELL,SELL, SELL!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351285786709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:09:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, it killed the one star bandit.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351349921415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351349955349-29</Id><Title>Sen. Harry Reid Hospitalized</Title><Msg>A bump in the road Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid was rushed to the hospital following a six-car crash near Las Vegas on Friday. Senator Reid’s caravan accounted for four of the cars involved in the accident, which happened shortly after 1 p.m. PST on a major highway in Nevada.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351349955349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 10:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351350387549-30</Id><Title>Florida Sun-Sentinel Dumps Barack Obama For Mitt Romney</Title><Msg>Lots of major newspapers around the country are jumping on the Romney bandwagon. The wheels are coming off the Obama bus. No wonder Michelle was pleading with voters to vote early.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351350387549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351351035350-31</Id><Title>Source: Obama had horrible grades at Harvard</Title><Msg>Obama Got Worst Grades In Harvard University’s History Limbaugh said that he was cajoled into taking a phone call from a potential source who told him the bombshell information about President Obama. “They went to school with Barack Obama at Harvard,” said Limbaugh. “And the guy told me that Obama got the lowest grades that any Harvard graduate ever got and that a bunch of professors gave him B’s and C’s when he didn’t even show up to class.” Obama is a freaking scam artist!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351351035350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351351097496-32</Id><Topic><Title>We Getting Serious About ORCL</Title><Username>sheriemerson396</Username><Timestamp>1350736592417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 08:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get serious. The Macros are all that matter.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351351097496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:18:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351351693864-33</Id><Title>Obama's classmates from Harvard speak</Title><Msg>Brad Berenson, class of ’91, threw their support to Obama for Harvard Law Review over Jew David Goldberg. However, “Obama was not a uniter. To portray him as someone who brought everyone together wouldn’t be accurate,” said Berenson. To the more politically left-wing members of the Harvard Law Review, this was too much, says Berenson, and Obama clashed with them on occasion. The first skirmish between Obama and the far left members of the Law Review started early. Several of the more left-wing members of the Harvard Law Review wanted Obama to appoint them to positions on the coveted masthead, but Obama, says Berenson, appointed his people. “I’m as conservative as they come—I didn’t vote for him in ’08 and won’t be voting for him in ’12." A do nothing at Harvard Rob Fischer, a close friend of Obama back at Harvard, said Obama never wrote a bylined piece as editor of the law review. It was a title only.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351351693864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351352685426-34</Id><Title>Obama was affirmative action pick for Harvard Law Review</Title><Msg>Harvard Law Review on Obama's election: "It took 91 years to elect a woman, and it wasn`t until last year that an Asian was elected by his fellow editors to the position."</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351352685426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351352912802-35</Id><Title>Harvard classmate says Obama was a foreign exchange student</Title><Msg>One of Obama's classmates has come out with the bombshell that he attended schools as a foreign exchange student. Which means he is not a naturally born citizen, his birth certificate is fake and he is ineligible to be president. A terrible set of FACTS the dems seem more than willing to ignore. Naturally, Democrats are eager to ignore this incredibly development which is perhaps the greatest scandal to ever hit the White House and instead ramped up their parroting about Mitt's taxes. I tend to think Obama spending millions to seal his college history and perpetuate this lie on the american public is nothing short of incredible. There comes a time when you need to wake up and smell the roses instead of blindly towing your party line. Any decent american should see be outraged at these epic lies being spewed by the Obama machine. I agree Romney and Ryan are not the dream team I was hoping for, but I'll take them any day over this fraud that we currently have in our white house.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351352912802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:48:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351353021377-36</Id><Topic><Title>the republicans have it in for women</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351341925676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351353021377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351353054449-37</Id><Topic><Title>gop and their paymasters</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351341833555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351353054449</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351353092606-38</Id><Topic><Title>gop congress record of attacking medicare, ss</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351340726652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop record of attacking medicare is a disgrace</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351353092606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351353229505-39</Id><Topic><Title>gop in congress recent record Against giving middle class families a fair shake, weakening consumer protections</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351340799552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:26:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt cares about 125% of the people, sure...... he says differently when is with his wealthy base.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351353229505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351353301754-40</Id><Topic><Title>Cheney &amp; Beck help Mitt unveil his new theme of "real change..."..... seriously</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289222773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:07:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheney &amp; Beck help Mitt unveil his new theme of "real change..."..... lol</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351353301754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351353416498-41</Id><Title>Fidel Castro on death bed endorses Obama</Title><Msg>This is really pathetic.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351353416498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 11:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351353630188-42</Id><Title>gop is "full of racists", says an honest republican</Title><Msg>Colin Powell's former chief of staff condemned the Republican Party on Friday night, telling MSNBC's Ed Schultz, "My party is full of racists." Retired Army Col. Lawrence Wilkerson made the comment in response to Mitt Romney campaign surrogate John Sununu's suggestion on Thursday that Powell's endorsement of President Barack Obama's re-election was motivated by race. Wilkerson, who served as Powell's chief of staff when the general was secretary of state during the first George W. Bush term, told Schultz that he respected Sununu "as a Republican, as a member of my party," but did not "have any respect for the integrity of the position that [Sununu] seemed to codify."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351353630188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351353632445-43</Id><Title>Rasmussen: Romney 50% Obama 46%</Title><Msg>The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Saturday shows Mitt Romney attracting support from 50% of voters nationwide, while President Obama earns the vote from 46%. Two percent (1%) prefer some other candidate, and another two percent (2%) are undecided. This is the fifth consecutive day that Romney has been at the 50% level of support. He has enjoyed a three- or four-point edge on each of those days. New polling shows that the race is tied in Wisconsin, a result confirmed by the fact that the Badger State is receiving visits from Obama, Romney, Paul Ryan and Joe Biden. The importance of this state in the Electoral College battle is hard to overstate. Scott Rasmussen suggests in his weekly newspaper column that Wisconsin May Be the New Ohio this year. That’s a startling result given that the president won Wisconsin by 14 points in 2008.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351353632445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351353738671-44</Id><Title>Obama slipping in Pennsylvania and Minnesota</Title><Msg>Obama's lead in states he thought were a lock is crumbling into statistical margin of error. PA has moved into toss-up status.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351353738671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351353800137-45</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in the questions measuring explicit racism 79 percent among Republicans compared with 32 percent among Democrats are prejudiced</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351353800137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351353834336-46</Id><Topic><Title>gop is "full of racists", says an honest republican</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351353630188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Powell endorses Obama because he is black. Obama's negative ads are creating damaging blowback on Obama. Axelrod should be fired.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351353834336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351353938404-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obama 4 points over Mittens in Ohio.... cheney and fukwad beck no help to sweaty Mitt</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351305542205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 22:39:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama 4 points over Mittens in Ohio.... cheney and beck no help to sweaty Mitt</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351353938404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351353972518-48</Id><Title>Obama: next 4 years will be worse</Title><Msg>4 deaths in Libya were a “bump in the road.” “If you have a small business, you didn’t build that.” Conservatives cling to guns and religion. He tells the Des Moines Register he has a plan to deal with immigration but wants to keep it off the record. Telling the Russian president he’ll have more flexibility when he doesn’t face re-election. Prepare to dive off the fiscal cliff you stupid lemmings.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351353972518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351354063782-49</Id><Topic><Title>gop is "full of racists", says an honest republican</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351353630188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course there are no racists in the Dem. Party. The Black Panthers and Black Muslims love everyone don't they? Besides what is wrong with preferring your ow kind? People that point a finger always have four pointing back at themselves. I've had a belly full of lying hypocritical "non" racists.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351354063782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:07:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351354107295-50</Id><Title>Newspaper Endorsements Pour In for Romney/Ryan: NH, MA, WV, TX, MI, VA, NY, D.C.</Title><Msg>Romney’s The One Four years ago the voters put their faith in a man who offered vague promises of hope and change at a time when any change looked like a good idea and hope was in short supply. What this nation got in Barack Obama was a president who used an economic crisis to further his redistributionist agenda — and, not surprisingly, failed miserably at restoring American prosperity. Oh, he brought change all right — to a government-knows-best philosophy that has given us four years of high unemployment, higher gas prices, a $16 trillion deficit, and a job-killing regulatory environment. Enough! This isn’t the kind of change anyone can believe in. We don't get fooled again! Throw the bas*tuds out.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351354107295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351354212895-51</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>measured how, Mesa? Love to see the questions. I know you stinkin' libs see racists behind every tree. IN your view, and indeed the views of many lib commentors, talk of reducing food stamp expenditures is racist. Forcing people off welfare in favor of work is racist. Even whites who voted for Obama in '08 but won't won't for him now are racists. Do I have that right, Mesa? Of course I do.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351354212895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351354336396-52</Id><Title>Communist Party USA endorses Obama</Title><Msg>We needed a Real Democrat in the White House. The biggest dirty trick of all is fooling voters into thinking there is no difference. The huge voter surge in 2008 elected President Barack Obama, the first African American president, thinking he was a Democrat. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351354336396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351354589131-53</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stupid person, the poll question are easily obtainable, i found them simply by googling AP Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks and heck, you favorite gop prz candidate Perry hung out at Camp N@@@@rhead, so what does that tell you about him and about you?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351354589131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351354762757-54</Id><Title>Blacks for Romney: Obama's a scrub</Title><Msg>Obama ain't done nuttin for the black community Still, Americans are suffering. They have lost their jobs, they have lost their home, and in many situations, they have lost hope. For the black community, the situation is even more dire. Black unemployment hovers around 14 percent, compared to 8 percent unemployment overall. For black teenagers, the number more than doubles, as 38 percent of black teens are unemployed. It is not just the undereducated black Americans who are suffering — 6.6 percent of black Americans with at least a bachelor’s degree are unemployed, a rate 50 percent higher than the overall unemployment rate for those with a four-year college degree. Since 2007, black median household income has declined by 11 percent — the largest decline of all major racial and ethnic groups. In 2011, the poverty rate among black Americans was 27.5 percent. The poverty rate among blacks living in families headed by women is 41 percent. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351354762757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351354817861-55</Id><Title>Mittens was lying about Jeep outsourcing to China</Title><Msg>"Here we go again with Willard telling about his thousandth or so lie out on the campaign trail, but this time we find out that apparently badly sourced right wing blogs are his fact checking department. Explains a lot, doesn't it? Romney repeats false claim of Jeep outsourcing to China; Chrysler refutes story: Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney repeated a false claim Thursday night that Chrysler Group may move all Jeep vehicle production to China, drawing criticism from the Obama campaign, which said the Michigan native had blatantly skewed a news wire story. Romney’s comments came the same day that the Free Press reported that 1,100 new Chrysler workers will begin making the Jeep Grand Cherokee and Dodge Durango SUVs at a plant in Detroit next week. “I saw a story today that one of the great manufacturers in this state, Jeep, now owned by the Italians, is thinking of moving all production to China,” Romney said during a rally in Defiance, Ohio, before 12,000 cheering supporters, according to several reports. “I will fight for every good job in America, I’m going to fight to make sure trade is fair, and if it’s fair, America will win. Romney apparently was referencing conservative bloggers who misrepresented a Bloomberg story from Monday that discussed Chrysler’s decision to consider starting Jeep production in China, the world’s largest new-vehicle market. That story, while accurate, sparked a raft of other stories and blogs that incorrectly concluded that Chrysler might close plants or move Jeep production from the U.S. to China. Gualberto Ranieri, Chrysler’s vice president of communications, criticized those stories Thursday even before Romney made his comments. “Let’s set the record straight: Jeep has no intention of shifting production of its Jeep models out of North America to China,” Ranieri said. “It’s simply reviewing the opportunities to return Jeep output to China, for the world’s largest auto market. U.S. Jeep assembly lines will continue to stay in operation.” A spokesperson for the Romney campaign declined to comment. In fact, Chrysler is investing $500 million at its Toledo North Assembly Plant and plans to add 1,105 new workers by the third quarter of 2013 to build an all-new SUV that will replace the Jeep Liberty. Production of the new SUV will begin next summer and the hiring process for the new workers, who are scheduled to start by the next fall, has begun, said Chrysler spokeswoman Jodi Tinson. Romney’s comments were immediately skewered by auto industry observers and Romney’s political opponents because Chrysler added about 7,000 workers in the U.S. and Canada since emerging from Chapter 11 bankruptcy in 2009. As Rachel also noted earlier in her reporting, Romney was out there deriding the stimulus program at... you guessed it... a company that benefited from stimulus funds. This man just lies every time his mouth is open. You'd think he'd pick his audience a little more carefully though, since all he did is make himself look like a blathering idiot less than two weeks from the election, when voters are paying attention, and when voters in the states that were saved by the auto bailout know better than to believe him."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351354817861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:20:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351354858090-56</Id><Title>Obama’s hand outs are a form of slavery</Title><Msg>Many black-owned businesses struggle to gain access to capital that would enable expansion or fund operating costs. Sixty percent of startups are in the white community. Compare that with just 9 percent of startups coming from the black community. Mr. Romney will reform regulatory policies that can help black-owned businesses increase and thrive. He will reform Dodd-Frank and allow more money to be accessible to responsible black community banks so they can get money into the hands of responsible black entrepreneurs. Lower capital gains taxes and dividends also will incentivize growth in the black community.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351354858090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351354969593-57</Id><Title>Stupid nytimes rejoice that people are taking more debt</Title><Msg>Rise in Household Debt Might Be Sign of a Strengthening Recovery ------------------------------- Why people taking more debt would be a sign of a "resilient" recovery? We just had a huge crisis that was caused by people taking debt to consume... The article is incredibly superficial: not a word on the current debt level (i.e. still very high) and what constitutes a normal debt level (i.e. much less), and on how high it can get before causing a problem. As for boosting the economy, that's assuming that the gov deficit will not shrink, which it will. Not a word either of what is the strategy here: grow debt to the sky again? What the hell do they think will happen when inevitably people pay back these debt (or default on it)? (i.e. they will spend less) This is a perfect example of how authorities in this country, including Bush, Obama, Romney, Bernanke etc... all think purely short term and are all bent on making Americans take more debts without regard for the future.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1351354969593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351355047032-58</Id><Title>Obama's black vote support slipping</Title><Msg>More than 95 percent of black voters voted Democratic in the last election. Obama's taken the black vote for granted thinking black folks will all vote for someone who says he's black. However, a recent poll showed the percentage of black Americans who have a “strongly positive” view of Mr. Obama has slipped from 83 percent to 58 percent. Those numbers show black Americans are paying attention, and they don’t like what they see. I grew up in inner-city Atlanta, and I can tell you the most conservative people I know are my neighbors in the black community. It isn’t just in Atlanta. Thirty-three percent of Americans in the black community self-identify as conservatives. They are anti-abortion, and they believe marriage should be between a man and a woman. Black Americans need to vote their values in November, and they will find themselves more aligned with Mr. Romney and the Republican Party.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351355047032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351355449385-59</Id><Title>will gop throw a tantrum over a Mittens debt ceiling hike?</Title><Msg>I know mittens promised he will not hike the debt ceiling ........but he also promises more tax cuts, and increased military spending........ so, i think he will do as the kings of debt ceiling hikes Reagan and Bush did, and request many more increase, just another mitt flipflop.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351355449385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351355704387-60</Id><Title>Obama's black vote support slipping</Title><Msg>Duh Bro Gotta Go. We Be Po and Outa Dough</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351355704387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351355839330-61</Id><Title>Obama's SAT scores worse than Dubya's</Title><Msg>Obama was accepted into Columbia in one of the easiest years to gain access in the modern history of the college, that his SAT scores may well have been lower than George W. Bush’s, and that the “transfer program” between Columbia and Occidental that Obama writes of in Dreams From My Father simply didn’t exist. Obama was accepted into Columbia without revealing his grades at all. On March 11, 1981, Occidental College’s faculty voted to reestablish GPAs on transcripts. Obama had already filled out an application to transfer to Columbia, meaning he transferred to Columbia without having to reveal his freshmen and sophomore grades. “GPAs were dropped from student transcripts during the late 1960s, in an effort to de-emphasis grades and stress learning for its own sake,” wrote Arpie Balekjian in the student newspaper, The Occidental. (Arpie Balekjian, “Faculty Reestablishes GPAs on Transcripts,” The Occidental, March 13, 1981) A source from Obama’s Occidental days confirms that the old policy was in effect when Obama transferred.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351355839330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351356035541-62</Id><Title>Gallup: Romney 51% Obama 46%</Title><Msg>According to today’s Gallup tracking poll, Mitt Romney’s lead over incumbent President Barack Obama has stretched to a five point margin. Romney is now up among likely voters 51% to 46%. Yesterday, the tracking poll had Romney up by only three points, 50% to 47%. Romney's lead is increasing. Michelle is begging blacks to vote early before the sheet hits the fan. Obama's ads are punching himself in the face. From Big Bird to binders to bayonets to ads suggesting that voting for Obama is like losing your virginity, this campaign has minimized the issues the American people face. And Obama's paying the price for it. The trends are clearly against Barack Obama. It has been three weeks – the October 9, 2012, tracking poll – since Barack Obama was even tied with Romney. And after the final presidential debate, which liberals widely believed Barack Obama won, the polls have not shifted to Obama at all. BYE BYE OBAMA.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351356035541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351356400042-63</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whever Perry hung out says not a thing about me. Strange that you would think so. I can't wait for the reactions from you stinkin' libs when Romney wins. It will be chalked up to racism, no doubt in my mind. It will be fun to watch your pin head explode.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351356400042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351357529021-64</Id><Title>Fact: Obama's College GPA = 0.0</Title><Msg>Occidental College gave no grades. Obama's GPA was 0.0 when he transferred to Columbia.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351357529021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351358020675-65</Id><Topic><Title>Mitts miracle cure snake oil is Free, better than free... you get cash back!!!</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351282077503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:07:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tax cuts AND deficit reduction!!! tax cuts AND increased military spending and nation building!!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351358020675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351358060184-66</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is voter fraud being committed in Ohio? By: Sara Marie Brenner 10/26/2012 09:25 PM RESIZE: AAA Print 2.6K COLUMBUS, Ohio — Two volunteer poll workers at an Ohio voting station told Human Events that they observed van loads of Ohio residents born in Somalia — the state is home to the second-largest Somali population in the United States — being driven to the voting station and guided by Democratic interpreters on the voting process. No Republican interpreters were present, according to these volunteers. While it’s not unusual for get-out-the-vote groups to help voters get to the polls, the volunteers who talked to Human Events observed a number of troubling and questionable activities. A source, who wishes to remain anonymous, is a volunteer outside the Morse Road polling center. She has witnessed Somalis who cannot speak English come to the polling center. They are brought in groups, by van or bus. The Democrats hand them a slate card and say, “vote Brown all the way down.” Given that Sherrod Brown is the incumbent Democrat Senator in Ohio, one can assume that this is the reference. Non-English speaking voters may use an interpreter. The interpreters are permitted by law to interpret for the individual voting; however, they are forbidden from influencing their vote in any way. Another source who also wishes to remain anonymous has seen Democrat interpreters show the non-English speaking Somalis how to vote the Democrat slate that they were handed outside. According to this second source, there are not any Republican Somali interpreters available. The logical follow-up question is whether a non-English speaking person is an American citizen. Although Republican leadership in Ohio passed a voting reform law, it was repealed by the legislature itself after the Democrats threatened a referendum. According to the Ohio Secretary of State’s web site, someone wanting to vote early in Ohio must supply one of the following in writing on the absentee ballot form, whether voting early by mail or in person: an Ohio driver’s license number; the last four digits of the social security number; or a copy of a current and valid photo identification, military identification, or a current — within the last 12 months — utility bill, including cell phone bill, bank statement, government check, paycheck, or other government document that shows the person’s name and address in addition to the voter registration acknowledgement. The voter is not required to show the driver’s license or social security card, but must merely write it on the absentee ballot request form. While the individual would be required to show a utility bill, bank statement or other printed document if he or she chooses that option, this is in lieu of writing the driver’s license or social security number. Therefore, the information cannot be checked against the Bureau of Motor Vehicles or other state databases. Essentially, a person is asked to check a box stating that they are a citizen, and the poll worker is to trust that they are the person who is listed on the item being shown or the information being written. In other words, someone can be an illegal resident of the state of Ohio and the United States, get an apartment, turn on the heat, bring in the Columbia Gas bill, register to vote by the deadline, and vote by showing that same bill. There is then no verification that this individual is a citizen of the United States. Matt McClellan, the press secretary for Ohio Secretary of State Jon Husted, explained, “There is a process to challenge a voter’s eligibility. The point in time for a challenge to be brought ended mid October. A poll worker could challenge a voter if they had questions as to whether or not a voter was registered or eligible to vote.” However, if the poll worker does not raise the issue at the time the voting occurs, that person’s vote will otherwise be counted on election day along with everyone else’s vote. McClellan was not aware of any reports of irregularities at the Morse Road voting place in Franklin County. Two phone calls and a text message to the Public Information Office at the Franklin County Board of Elections were not returned. According to the Somali Community Association of Ohio’s web site, over 45,000 Somalis live in Ohio. Only 40 percent have become citizens of the United States, and only 25 percent speak English well enough to get a job. The second source mentioned has seen voter intimidation at this same voting place. A Mitt Romney bus stopped near the voting center, approximately 30 Democrats who were outside handing out the slate cards rushed over to the bus. They yelled at the bus, and swarmed around its door when anyone attempted to exit the bus. This, from the “tolerant left.” All elements of this story are still developing and will be updated as new information is uncovered. Stay tuned.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351358060184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:14:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351358095686-67</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeffco ‘Democrat Of The Year’ Convicted Of Felony Theft October 26, 2012 5:54 PM Share on email 383 JEFFERSON COUNTY, Colo. (CBS4)- The woman named “Democrat of The Year” this year by the Jefferson County Democratic Party has been convicted of felony theft by a Jefferson County jury for stealing from a developmentally disabled 71-year-old woman. “The jury did right,” said Cindy Maxwell, an advocate for the victim. On Thursday, a jury convicted 66-year-old Estelle Carson of felony identify theft and felony theft from an at risk adult for stealing checks from the woman and using them to pay her own cable, cell phone and internet bills. The victim is partially blind, developmentally disabled, has cerebral palsy and is confined to a wheelchair. She is on a fixed income of $596 per month according to the Jefferson County District Attorney’s Office. Nearly as bothersome as the theft itself to Maxwell and other supporters of the victim, is the fact the Jefferson County Democratic Party was made aware of the ongoing criminal investigation and honored Carson anyway. According to documents obtained by CBS4, in November of 2011, the Jeffco Democratic Party announced it planned to honor Carson for her activism on behalf of Democratic causes and her efforts to register voters. But three days before the January 8 gala, advocates for the victim contacted the party via email and phone informing them of the criminal investigation. One wrote “I am completely appalled,” to learn of the planned honor. The woman suggested the Democratic Party should “un-invite Estelle and not follow through with this honor.”</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351358095686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351358120712-68</Id><Topic><Title>stupid poor republican tattoos "R" on his face for $15K paid by a stupid rich republican</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351288286082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:51:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs are disgusting</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351358120712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351358281793-69</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>express prejudice toward blacks whether they recognize those feelings or not .................................................................................................................................................................that interesting. Whether they recognize those feeling or not. How subjective! Like reduction in welfare expenditures is racist. Whites just don't recognize it. bwhahahahaha. LMAOROF</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351358281793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:18:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351358352855-70</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens was lying about Jeep outsourcing to China</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351354817861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitten's said he has a plan for people with preexisting conditions....... what was it again? the ER?</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351358352855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351358551385-71</Id><Title>Obama sinking due to his own negative ads</Title><Msg>He's punching himself in the face. It's working great. Keep it up Axelrod! BWHGGHAHHAHHAHHAAAAA!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351358551385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351358606870-72</Id><Topic><Title>stupid poor republican tattoos "R" on his face for $15K paid by a stupid rich republican</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351288286082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:51:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>suk to be you Obama lemming -- ready to dive over the fiscal cliff?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351358606870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351358680656-73</Id><Title>Sandy to sweep Obama out of D.C.</Title><Msg>She's goin to blow him out of town. The perfect storm.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351358680656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351359091758-74</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No we just harbor prejudice against DA liberals who voted for an incompetent black.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351359091758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 13:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351364385575-75</Id><Title>Obama Imploding Swing State Tracking: Romney 51%, Obama 45%</Title><Msg>Saturday, October 27, 2012 The full Swing State tracking update offers a combined view of the results from 11 key states won by President Obama in 2008 and thought to be competitive in 2012. The states collectively hold 146 Electoral College votes and include Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Michigan, Nevada, New Hampshire, North Carolina, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Virginia and Wisconsin. If you do not already have a Rasmussen Reader account, subscribe now. In the 11 these swing states, Mitt Romney earns 51% of the vote to Obama’s 45%. Romney has now led for 10 straight days. *** Your vulgar negative POS lying Irish bas*tud fraud is getting punched in his face like he deserves for destroying peoples lives and bankrupting the country for the last 4 years. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351364385575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 14:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351364561589-76</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: Majority harbor prejudice against blacks</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351342328750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OLUMBUS, Ohio — Two volunteer poll workers at an Ohio voting station told Human Events that they observed van loads of Ohio residents born in Somalia — the state is home to the second-largest Somali population in the United States — being driven to the voting station and guided by Democratic interpreters on the voting process. *** Check their papers. If they ain't legal, ship 'em off to Gitmo. These illegal alien bas*tuds are stealing American jobs. Throw the bas*tuds out!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351364561589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351365454029-77</Id><Title>Sweaty mitt is so incompetent he repeats stupid lies like the one about Jeep outsourced to china</Title><Msg>Mitt is so incompetent he shows up at a foreign policy debate spouting off that iran is land locked and needs syria for access to the sea. Mitt is so incompetent that one minute he says defense spending cuts would cost jobs and the next he says the government does not create jobs.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351365454029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351365743170-78</Id><Title>Reagan was the first to compare voting to virginity, you idiot whiners</Title><Msg>"This isn’t the first time that analogy has been used; in fact, Ronald Reagan made a similar comparison in 1980 while he was reaching out to blue-collar voters. Here’s what Reagan said: “I know what it’s like to pull the Republican lever for the first time, because I used to be a Democrat myself, and I can tell you it only hurts for a minute and then it feels just great.” Now compare that to what Dunham said: “Your first time shouldn’t be with just anybody. You want to do it with a great guy … someone who really cares about and understands women.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351365743170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351365994326-79</Id><Title>romnesia , gopnesia and just plain stupid whiny hypocrite republicans</Title><Msg>It’s a joke that Ronald Reagan originally made, thirty years ago, about voting Republican for the first time: “I know what it’s like to pull the Republican lever for the first time, because I used to be a Democrat myself, and I can tell you it only hurts for a minute and then it feels just great.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351365994326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351367390247-80</Id><Title>Obama releases college transcripts</Title><Msg>I have exclusively obtained Obama's college transcripts, and it's quite clear why he didn't want them released. I'll just give you the highlights: • His birth name isn't "Barack Hussein Obama Jr." As politically problematic as that pseudonym proved to be, it turns out it is a significant improvement on his real name, "DeathToAmerica Obama Jr." • Each page of the transcript has a stamp in Arabic. It translates to: Never to be released under penalty of death, by order of the caliphate ... • His college loan application was co-signed by Idi Amin. • Several of his grades were changed from C to A, with a handwritten notation: "Affirmative Action." • It turns out he was not president of the Harvard Law Review. He was president of the Harvard Shariah Law Review. • In retrospect, his admission application probably should have been more carefully vetted for possible irregularities. It contained letters of recommendation from Barry White, Martin Luther King Jr. and Frederick Douglass. • He took his junior year abroad in Ho Chi Minh City. • He was president of the Foreign-Born Students Association. • His senior thesis in economics, a new paradigm for wealth-distribution in America, was titled "Mugging Whitey."</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351367390247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 15:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351371182985-81</Id><Topic><Title>Stupid nytimes rejoice that people are taking more debt</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1351354969593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:22:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People are using debt to pay debt, a picture of desperation not recovery.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351371182985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 16:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351383749112-82</Id><Topic><Title>Stupid nytimes rejoice that people are taking more debt</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1351354969593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:22:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In Iowa, disappointment with Obama runs deep AFP 10/27/2012 1:57:30 AM In Iowa, a rural state of outsized political importance, retired nurse Pauline McAreavy is among thousands eager to vote against President Barack Obama after four years of disappointment. McAreavy holds a personal grudge against the president that dates back to 2008, when she hosted Obama's supporters for three weeks in the Midwestern state that nurtured his improbable White House dreams. She never got a thank you note for her small role in helping land Obama in the White House, but McAreavy's antagonism goes deeper, the product of broken promises and accumulated disillusion with the "hope" promised by the man who has billed himself an "adopted son" of Iowa. "Obama gave us this 'no red, no blue state' America," said McAreavy, 78. "I was fooled, I kick myself everyday," she said. "I said: 'In four years I'll get you buddy -- and I'm going to.'" Her home lies in the state's Iowa County, where residents gave exactly the same number of votes to Obama and his Republican rival John McCain in the 2008 elections: 4,173 votes each. The Obama campaign is hoping that Iowa voters will reject his Republican challenger Mitt Romney, a former Massachusetts governor who failed to win the Iowa caucus nominating contests in either of his two presidential runs, in 2008 and 2012. But McAreavy is among many voters in midwestern Iowa -- which kicks off the presidential nominating contests every four years -- who have abandoned their allegiance to Obama's platform. Their lack of support, revealed in two dozen interviews with Iowa County residents, is at the heart of the president's challenge in seeking a second term in what has become a very tightly contested White House race. Sweeping in front of her house in Williamsburg, McAreavy recalled how she had thought Obama would bring a politically divided country together and that electing the first African American president of the United States would be "wonderful" for this country. "He didn't, he tore us more apart. I did feel maybe the world didn't like America, but the world hates us more now than they did before!" she said. The Obama boat is leaking. Many voters who chose Obama last time around are quick to vent frustration over the discrepancy between what they had hoped from a historic Obama presidency and what actually transpired. Almost no McCain voters, meanwhile, seem ready to cast a ballot for the Democrat. Even if Obama wins the state of Iowa and the entire election this year, the victory will be narrow and will lack the sweet taste of 2008. Back then, Obama got 54 percent of vote in Iowa against 44 percent for McCain. But in this race, no poll gives him more than 51 percent, and Romney is only two points behind, on average. "I don't think he pulled Congress together enough to do something. He's not a leader," said McAreavy. "He's more worried about his reelection. It infuriates me when after what happened in Libya, he went to a fundraiser in Las Vegas." Even the president's supporters -- and there are still legions of them -- are gloomy. Many cite Republican control of the House of Representatives and its sizeable contingent in the Senate as extenuating circumstances. All search for excuses. "Every election it's the lesser of two evils," said Williamsburg librarian Carol Uhlmann, a 72-year-old registered Democrat. "In Afghanistan, why can't we get out now? Why are we over there and all those little situations if we're not being directly attacked?" Inside the Williamsburg Public Library, a woman playing with a young girl has already decided not to vote for Obama, like she did four years ago. "I'm going to go with the change," said the woman, who would only give her first name Ann. That evening, Romney addressed supporters just an hour's drive away, while Obama gave a campaign speech in Davenport 80 miles (130 kilometers) to the east. "This is where it all began four years ago -- on your front porches, in your backyards. This is where the movement for change began," he said. "And Iowa, you will once again choose the path that we take from here." But disenchantment with Obama is not the only factor explaining Romney's impressive climb up the polls, as the Republican steadily builds his base of support while softening his public image. Romney was not the first choice for Sarah, an 89-year-old Lutheran, because he is of Mormon faith. But she has grown accustomed to the him thanks to repeated campaign appearances that are a tradition in Iowa, which likes to see its candidates up close, shake their hands and look them in the eyes. Sarah said she became especially comfortable after seeing Romney's large family -- he has five sons -- on television. And she is far from being alone. National polls by the Washington, DC-based Pew Center show that Romney's favorability ratings jumped from just 37 percent in July to 50 percent in October. Even young people, among Obama's most ardent supporters in 2008, appear disillusioned. Sam Tracy, who delivers beer in Marengo, said he plans to abstain from voting, disgusted by the political impasse in Washington. In 2008, the registered Independent proudly cast a vote for Obama in an election that made the history books. "Based on what we were coming from, there was a lot of enthusiasm for Obama, but now that he's in office, the shine has worn off," Tracy said.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1351383749112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 20:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351384592355-83</Id><Topic><Title>Stupid nytimes rejoice that people are taking more debt</Title><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1351354969593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 12:22:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's the Obama model. It's the path to Greece. Obama is a fiscal idiot! The stimulus failed. Obama's policies failed. Obama is creating a global economic depression. THROW THE BAS*TUD OUT!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1351384592355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 20:36:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351385606022-84</Id><Title>My My</Title><Msg>Look at messy, still pimping for Obama. He's as desperate as Candy Crowley looking for something to make Obama look appealing. You just can't sell broken down goods as new, like a horse with a broken leg or a car with no transmission. Buyers remorse makes everyone wiser, except messy.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351385606022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 20:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351391750160-85</Id><Title>"I've always been a rodent and rabbit hunter. Small varmints, if you will." Mittens romney</Title><Msg>corporations are people, binders of women, 47%,$10,000 bet, "I'm not a big-game hunter. I've made that very clear. I've always been a rodent and rabbit hunter. Small varmints, if you will." "I purchased a gun when I was a young man. I've been a hunter pretty much all my life." (Romney's campaign later said he'd been hunting twice, once when he was 15, and once in 2006 at a Republican fundraiser "You sit down with your attorneys and tell you what you have to do, but obviously the president of the United States has to do what's in the best interest of the United States against a potential threat." --on whether he would consult Congress about invading Iran Mittens</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351391750160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-27 22:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>