<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346668013000-1</Id><Title>The GW Bush Recession ENDED In JUNE 2009!!</Title><Msg>So WTF did Obama really "Inherit"!! Obama inherited a Mortgage based "Financial Catastrophe" which was driven, orchestrated and led largely by the Democrat Party (Senator Obama among them), backed by their University and Press/Media whores! And the ever so "evil" Mortgage Bankers and Wall Streeters did little more than FOLLOW the bidding of Democrat Power Brokers, which began in earnest under Bill Clinton, who did more to deregulate and pump Debt-Beat Housing than anyone! Indeed, Bush and Congressional Republicans tried to stop the Catastrophe and reign in Fannie Freddie 17 times during the Bush Presidency... but Democrats blocked it every time, OBAMA voting with them and cheering them on!! In fact, Obama was the 3rd largest recipient of Fannie Freddie Graft in Congress, just behind Frank and Dodd! INHERITED MY AZZS!!!!!! It's a GD Lie, top to bottom!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1346668013000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 06:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346671530000-2</Id><Title>Obama Regime Saves New Orleans... Floods All The Suburbs!</Title><Msg>They really know how to turn a brand new upgraded Levee System protecting New Orleans into a Dam &amp; man-made Lake for all those surrounding it! And all this, after Democrat run Governments in the City, in the Parish, in the State and the in Federal Government did Jackshyt for decades... knowing full well that New Orleans was disaster waiting to happen! Indeed, it was Bill Clinton and his Coon-azzs Lousiana sidekick, James Carville, who were the last ones who could have actually upgraded the levees and prevented the Katrina disaster... which BTW, had virtually NOTHING to do with any failures by FEMA! And what did the Clinton's do just before leaving office in 2000... they set up yet another CYA FIVE-Year Army Corps of Engineers "STUDY" of the problem and how to fix it! YeeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaa!! What a Country!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1346671530000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 07:25:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346674588000-3</Id><Title>Obama Begs For Biggest Bail-Out Of All! His OWN!</Title><Msg>He wants the American people to bail him out of a totally failed Presidency... a House of Cards engineered and propped up by Democrat Party lies and a massive cover-up and charade by their Press-Media whores!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1346674588000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346677115180-4</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHARLOTTE, N.C. – College students from across North Carolina will arrive in Charlotte by the busload. Same with members of predominantly black churches in neighboring South Carolina. Their goal: help fill a 74,000-seat outdoor stadium to capacity when President Obama accepts the Democratic nomination Thursday night. Anything short of a full house on the final night of the Democratic Party's national convention will be instant fodder for Republicans eager to use empty seats as symbols of waning voter enthusiasm for Obama. Democrats have been fretting for months over whether the president can draw a capacity crowd at Bank of America Stadium. Polls show voter enthusiasm is down, as are Obama's crowds for his battleground state campaign rallies. Obama advisers insist the stadium will be filled when Obama delivers his speech one way or another. Vice President Joe Biden also will speak Thursday night, along with Massachusetts Sen. John Kerry, who will vouch for Obama's national security credentials.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1346677115180</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346677184316-5</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suppression! DNC Charlotte: Identification required, even just near convention site Posted at 11:49 am on September 2, 2012 by Twitchy Staff | View Comments Andrew A Bair @ProLifePolitics Wait! You need a photo ID to get into the DNC? Gosh. Could they be more racist? #VoterID 1 Sep 12 Reply Retweet Favorite Oh, dear! What will Ellen Barkin, Michael Moore, Joe Biden, the NAACP, Attorney General Eric Holder and his apologists, Rep. Keith Ellison, and other unhinged leftists (redundant) say about this suppress-y turn of events? As they have told us, over and over, there is nothing more bigoted than requiring photo identification. Well, except for maybe “kitchen cabinets” and “chairs.“ What will Rob Delaney say about this latest “suppression?”</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1346677184316</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 08:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346677398756-6</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mother Of Fallen SEAL Rebukes Obama, Clinton The Gateway Pundit: Karen Vaughn, mother of fallen Navy Seal of Aaron Carson Vaughn, reacts to Barack Obama's campaign ad "One Chance." Karen and Billy Vaughn lost their son Aaron last year in Afghanistan. Video courtesy of Andrew Marcus.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346677398756</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346678278631-7</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Axelrod: America in a 'better position' today than four years ago Comments (791) | 9/2/12 9:30 AM EDT Are Americans better off today than they were four years ago? That's the question Fox News Sunday host Chris Wallace immediately posed to President Barack Obama's Senior Adviser David Axelrod, who didn't quite answer directly. "We're in a much better position than we were four years ago." Axelrod said, citing, for example, how the nation has experienced 29 straight months of outstanding jobs growth. He acknowledged that the nation's economy isn't where Obama would like it to be, but that is the fault of Bush.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1346678278631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346678858135-8</Id><Topic><Title>GOP = trillions in tax cuts to rich, and trillions in tax hikes to the middle class</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346344200978</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did Syria and Iran become our 'allies'????? ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ Biden claims Romney wants war with Iran and Syria (CN) - Vice President Joe Biden claimed Sunday that Mitt Romney, the Republican presidential nominee, might engage in war with Syria and Iran if elected president in November. "He said it was a mistake to end the war in Iraq and bring all of our warriors home," Biden said at a campaign stop in Pennsylvania. "He said it was a mistake to set an end date for our warriors in Afghanistan and bring them home. He implies by the speech that he's ready to go to war against our allies Syria and Iran."</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1346678858135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:27:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346680236135-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obamanure fails the Commander in Chief Test</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346643700920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 23:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rassmussen: Romney 48% Obama 44% and dropping.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1346680236135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:50:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346680574684-10</Id><Topic><Title>Bill Maher rips on the gop conveniently forgetting most of the entire Bush presidency</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346621778126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:36:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton on Obama: 'A Few Years Ago, This Guy Would Have Been Carrying Our Bags' 5:51 PM, Sep 2, 2012 • By DANIEL HALPER Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts Former President Bill Clinton tried to get former senator Ted Kennedy to endorse Hillay Clinton for president in the 2008 election by describing Barack Obama this way: "A few years ago, this guy would have been carrying our bags." This anecdote is revealed in a New Yorker article on the relationship between Bill Clinton and Obama: Tim Russert told me that, according to his sources, Bill Clinton, in an effort to secure an endorsement for Hillary from Ted Kennedy, said to Kennedy, “A few years ago, this guy would have been carrying our bags.” Clinton is giving a keynote address at the Democratic convention this week in Charlotte, North Carolina. *** Hillary will be in Asia instead of the DNC. Obama doesn't want her to steal the spotlight. Biden the clown goes down with/on/inside the captain.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1346680574684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 09:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346682198736-11</Id><Title>gop offshoring jobs</Title><Msg>why Pay USA workers in the USA when sweat shops can be set up offshore and chinese laborers IMPORTED to slave away there? The current GOP platfrom has an item to stop any minimum wage on these islands..... nice work gop.... and nice work Abramoff and Reed protecting this gop business paradise..... are you happy the sleazebag Ralph Reed is back in town? No doubt he was the one pushing for this in the gop platform: No minimum wage for the Mariana Islands. “The Pacific territories should have flexibility to determine the minimum wage, which has seriously restricted progress in the private sector.”</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346682198736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346685797319-12</Id><Title>GOP: Party of Liars</Title><Msg>What's up with all the bullshlt, and all you bullshltters who accept it? It's come to this? Can't even have an honest debate about anything? Can only malign and not have any realistic alternatives? Can't even explain your taxes? Obama's bad enough, but you guys are disgusting.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346685797319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346685851284-13</Id><Topic><Title>gop offshoring jobs</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346682198736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Democrats increased minimum wage back in 2007 or 2008, there was a special exemption so the higer minimum wages did not apply in American Samoa. The reason was that Nancy Pelosi's husband has significant investments in pinnapple processing in American Samoa and she &amp; he didn't wish to pat the higher minimum wage to their workers. I guess they don't want American Samoa to be a liberal workers paradise! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1346685851284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346686023943-14</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: Party of Liars</Title><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346685797319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And trying to obscure where campaign contributions come from? So elections can be bought by plutocrats pulling the strings behind the scene, to buy off the political system for personal gain? You think this is HEALTHY for this country?</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1346686023943</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346687901000-15</Id><Title>the latest unPC phrases you can 't say</Title><Msg>this according to the Diversity Director at the Dept of State 1) hold down the fort- apparently offensive to American Indians. Dagtes back to the cowboy-indian days 2) rule of thumb- in the old days apparently rule of thumb derives from the size of a stick a man could beat his wife with. If the stick was wider than your thumb you couldn't beat her with it. 3) going Dutch- offensive to the Dutch. Are the Dutch known to be cheap?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1346687901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346690496320-16</Id><Topic><Title>gop offshoring jobs</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346682198736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to mention Feinstein and her husband using the slave labor in China. Their worth out of the country is staggering.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346690496320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 12:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346699603109-17</Id><Topic><Title>gop offshoring jobs</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346682198736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Minimum wage should be abolished. Another burr in the business community like the other dictates of libiots who have no concept of running a business.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346699603109</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 15:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346701490206-18</Id><Topic><Title>Romney fails the Commander in Chief Test</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346590378910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 08:52:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He hasn't been commander in chief yet. But the Bummer has been a total success?!@&amp;$)(;:(.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346701490206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 15:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346701634043-19</Id><Title>If Obummer elected</Title><Msg>He has to confront the failure of the last four years of the past president. An unenviable job-an impossible task.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346701634043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 15:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346701726225-20</Id><Topic><Title>gop offshoring jobs</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346682198736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And GE moving factories to China.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346701726225</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 15:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346701756867-21</Id><Topic><Title>gop offshoring jobs</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346682198736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Govt Motors moving facilities to Mexico.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346701756867</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 15:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346703344177-22</Id><Topic><Title>gop offshoring jobs</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346682198736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are just a liar of course. In fact, after 2007 USA minimum wage law DOES apply in American Samoa. and in fact Pelosi supported that as Snopes points out....you are just a liar and what you posted was an internet hoax....... and the fact is the GOP PLATFORM wants to make sure USA min wage law does not apply in the Marianas, where the imported sweat shop labor "guest" workers outnumber the local population...... nice work,,, import chinese slaves, get rid of USA minimum wages as PART OF THE GOP PLATFORM. why Pay USA workers in the USA when sweat shops can be set up offshore and chinese laborers IMPORTED to slave away there?............</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346703344177</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 16:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346704850029-23</Id><Title>Ryan's labor day words to USA workers (Ryan has voted for free-trade pacts — including the extension of most-favored-nation trading status to China — that have been absolutely devastating to his hometown and other communities in his southeastern Wisconsin district.)</Title><Msg>("So what should I have to work for to get a job?" the man asked. "Should I have to work the same wages as in China? Should I have to work for $1 an hour?" Ryan tried to brush his questioner off. ) Paul Ryan's Labor Day Promise to American Workers: Candy, a Sports Schedule, and Nothing Else by John Nichols ......With his speech to the Republican National Convention in Tampa, Paul Ryan attempted to reposition himself as someone other than the millionaire son of privilege and career politician that he is..... ..........Janesville used to be a major manufacturing center. Now it has fallen on hard times. Like so many manufacturing communities in the Great Lakes region, it has been rocked by the outsourcing of U.S. jobs. That's not Ryan's concern, however. Since his election to the House in 1998, Ryan has voted for free-trade pacts — including the extension of most-favored-nation trading status to China — that have been absolutely devastating to his hometown and other communities in his southeastern Wisconsin district................... As he marched with other politicians in the Janesville Labor Day parade, the congressman was confronted by Wisconsin workers who were struggling with high unemployment and bleak prospects. A man was videotaped asking what his representative planned to do to aid Ryan's unemployed constituents. "So what should I have to work for to get a job?" the man asked. "Should I have to work the same wages as in China? Should I have to work for $1 an hour?" Ryan tried to brush his questioner off. But when the man persisted, saying, "C'mon, we're all here to have a good time." When he was reminded that it was Labor Day, which would seem to be an appropriate time to discuss unemployment and the condition of workers, Ryan finally offered something: "Would you like some candy?" Ryan asked. "Would you like a Packer-Badger schedule?" Candy or a sports schedule. That's all job-seeking Wisconsinites ever got from Paul Ryan. And that's all job-seeking Americans will ever get from him.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346704850029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 16:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346709869374-24</Id><Title>Sweat Shops Offshore</Title><Msg>That's just another way of distributing the wealth. What's the problem? Feinstein is OK with it. If it weren't for American companies and free trade, those countries would still be eating out of coconut shells.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346709869374</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 18:04:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346712060318-25</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan's labor day words to USA workers (Ryan has voted for free-trade pacts — including the extension of most-favored-nation trading status to China — that have been absolutely devastating to his hometown and other communities in his southeastern Wisconsin district.)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346704850029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 16:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's suppose a Wisconsinian asked Obama the same question in 2010. He would have gotten the same old line of hope and change and that's all they ever got from him.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346712060318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 18:41:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346716137879-26</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan's labor day words to USA workers (Ryan has voted for free-trade pacts — including the extension of most-favored-nation trading status to China — that have been absolutely devastating to his hometown and other communities in his southeastern Wisconsin district.)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346704850029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 16:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why doesn't Obama cut trade with China? The devastation is not just in Wisconsin, DA.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346716137879</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 19:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346718584664-27</Id><Topic><Title>If Obummer elected</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1346701634043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 15:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's been a complete disaster. Prolong the misery. Obama's policies have put America in a hole.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1346718584664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 20:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346719745030-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan's labor day words to USA workers (Ryan has voted for free-trade pacts — including the extension of most-favored-nation trading status to China — that have been absolutely devastating to his hometown and other communities in his southeastern Wisconsin district.)</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1346704850029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 16:40:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trouble for Dems in North Carolina ahead of convention FOX NEWS Last Updated: 11:56 AM, September 3, 2012 Posted: 11:55 AM, September 3, 2012 Share on email Share on facebook More Sharing ServicesMore Print CHARLOTTE, N.C. -- The main drag through downtown Charlotte looked a bit like Times Square on Sunday night, as revelers and out-of-towners converged to gawk at the flashing city around them. The electric scene before the start of the Democratic National Convention belies the trouble under the surface. For Democrats, North Carolina was an awkward choice and represents some of the challenges President Obama faces this Election Day. Unemployment here is at 9.6 percent, well above the national average. The governor of the state, Democrat Bev Perdue, was rated as the least popular governor in the country in a recent survey and does not plan to seek re-election. The state's laws also run counter to Democrats' publicly held positions. It is a right-to-work state, meaning workers cannot be forced to pay union dues -- and meaning unions weren't too thrilled about the decision to host the convention here. AFL-CIO President Richard Trumka said in a memo last month that the union "won't be buying skyboxes or bringing a big staff to the convention," and other big labor groups have declined to contribute to the cost of the convention, after doing so in 2008.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1346719745030</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 20:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346720380099-29</Id><Title>Blacks want to know</Title><Msg>where are the jobs? Forget it, you be talking to an empty chair.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1346720380099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 20:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>