<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351249553505-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; Anne made millions from the auto industry bail out he ""condemns"" jeez</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351185416226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:16:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Noonan: When Americans Saw the Real Obama Why the Denver debate changed everything. By PEGGY NOONAN We all say Ohio, Ohio, Ohio. But it's all still Denver, Denver, and the mystery that maybe isn't a mystery at all. If Cincinnati and Lake County go for Mitt Romney on Nov. 6 it will be because of what happened in Denver on Oct. 3. If Barack Obama barely scrapes through, if there's a bloody and prolonged recount, it too will be because of Denver. Nothing echoes out like that debate. It was the moment that allowed Mr. Romney to break through, that allowed dismay with the incumbent to coalesce, that allowed voters to consider the alternative. What the debate did to the president is what the Yankees' 0-4 series against the Tigers did at least momentarily, to the team's relationship with their city. "Dear Yankees, We don't date losers. Signed, New Yorkers" read the Post's headline. America doesn't date losers either. Why was the first debate so toxic for the president? Because the one thing he couldn't do if he was going to win the election is let all the pent-up resentment toward him erupt. Americans had gotten used to him as The President. Whatever his policy choices, whatever general direction he seemed to put in place he was The President, a man who had gotten there through natural gifts and what all politicians need, good fortune. What he couldn't do was present himself, when everyone was looking, as smaller than you thought. Petulant, put upon, above it all, full of himself. He couldn't afford to make himself look less impressive than the challenger in terms of command, grasp of facts, size. But that's what he did. And in some utterly new way the president was revealed, exposed. All the people whose job it is to surround and explain him, to act as his buffers and protectors—they weren't there. It was him on the stage, alone with a competitor. He didn't have a teleprompter, and so his failure seemed to underscore the cliché that the prompter is a kind of umbilical cord for him, something that provides nourishment, the thing he needs to sound good. He is not by any means a stupid man but he has become a boring one; he drones, he is predictable, it's never new. The teleprompter adds substance, or at least safety. *** A great and assumed question, the one that's still floating out there, is what exactly happened when Mr. Obama did himself in? What led to it? Was it the catastrophic execution of an arguably sound strategy? Perhaps the idea was to show the president was so unimpressed by his challenger that he could coolly keep him at bay by not engaging. Maybe Mr. Obama's handlers advised: "The American people aren't impressed by this flip-flopping, outsourcing plutocrat, and you will deepen your bond with the American people, Mr. President, by expressing in your bearing, through your manner and language, how unimpressed you are, too." So he sat back and let Mr. Romney come forward. Mr. But Romney was poised, knowledgable, presidential. It was a mistake to let that come forward! Peggy Noonan's Blog Daily declarations from the Wall Street Journal columnist. Was it the catastrophic execution of a truly bad strategy? Maybe they assumed the election was already pretty much in the bag, don't sweat it, just be your glitteringly brilliant self and let Duncan the Wonder Horse go out there and turn people off. But nothing was in the bag. The sheer number of people who watched—a historic 70 million—suggests a lot of voters were still making up their minds. Maybe the president himself didn't think he could possibly be beaten because he's so beloved. Presidents are always given good news, to keep their spirits up. The poll numbers he'd been seeing, the get-out-the-vote reports, the extraordinary Internet effort to connect with every lonely person in America, which is a lot of persons—maybe everything he was hearing left him thinking his position was impregnable. But maybe these questions are all off. Maybe what happened isn't a mystery at all. That, anyway, is the view expressed this week by a member of the U.S. Senate who served there with Mr Obama and has met with him in the White House. People back home, he said, sometimes wonder what happened with the president in the debate. The senator said, I paraphrase: I sort of have to tell them that it wasn't a miscalculation or a weird moment. I tell them: I know him, and that was him. That guy on the stage, that's the real Obama.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351249553505</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 07:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351252964456-2</Id><Title>Newt's prediction</Title><Msg>Newt Gingrich is predicting that this election will be a near-landslide victory for Mitt Romney. “I believe the minimum result will be 53-47 Romney, over 300 electoral votes, and the Republicans will pick up the Senate,” the former House speaker said Thursday night on Fox News’s “On the Record with Greta Van Susteren.” .................................................................................................................................... seems reasonable. I think maybe it will be 55-45 Romney.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351252964456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351253461099-3</Id><Topic><Title>Should you keep from ORCL? Take a look at why.</Title><Username>kemble.randy</Username><Timestamp>1351092179547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:22:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am happy i read that before buying</Msg><Username>vice.jeffery</Username><Timestamp>1351253461099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351255928475-4</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; Anne made millions from the auto industry bail out he ""condemns"" jeez</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351185416226</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:16:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny that Mitt didn't mention his connection to Delphi and the millions of $$ he made RECENTLY shipping those jobs off to china. romney and the vulture capitalists at work: "After the hedge fund takeover of Delphi, the squeeze on workers intensified through attacks on their pensions. During its years of economic trouble, Delphi had been chronically shorting payments to its pension funds—and by July 2009, they were underfunded by $7 billion. That month, Singer’s hedge fund group won the bid for control of Delphi’s stock and made clear they would neither make up the shortfall nor pay any more US worker pensions. Checkmated by the hedge funders, the government’s Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation agreed to take over Delphi’s pension payments. The PBGC would eat the shortfall."</Msg><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1351255928475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351256106684-5</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt PROMISED NO DEBT ceiling increase</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351183557256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 12:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you sure mittens math adds up? deficit reduction, more military spending, more war mongering and nation building, and we get cash back?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351256106684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351256376341-6</Id><Title>billy graham upgraded mormonism from cult to real religion (righties modify their religious dogma on political whims)</Title><Msg>Pope, however stands fast that both evangelical protestantism AND Mormonism are cults. Pope Says Catholicism Is the One True Church "These ecclesial Communities which, specifically because of the absence of the sacramental priesthood, have not preserved the genuine and integral substance of the Eucharistic Mystery cannot, according to Catholic doctrine, be called "Churches" in the proper sense." Pope Benedict XVI so there, just be thankful the puritans can't still hang people for being 'heretics" like they did quakers in early America.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351256376341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:59:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351256739641-7</Id><Title>Romney met with 93 yr old Graham for political gain.</Title><Msg>Asheville pastors said they were not impressed with the meeting between the Grahams and Romney and noted that any shift in the evangelical association’s view of Mormonism would be unusual. The Rev. Joe Hoffman, of First Congregational United Church of Christ, said he believes Romney met with Graham for political gain. He hopes the meeting would not influence the way people vote. “I would hope that all people — evangelical Christians, liberal Christians, everybody — would not look for the endorsement of one religious leader to help them make their vote,” he said. “I think they should be looking at the issues involved in the campaign.” The Rev. Keith Ogden, of Hill Street Baptist Church, put it more bluntly last week, saying the meeting was “hogwash.” Romney has faced difficulty with evangelical voters, in part because some believe his Mormon faith means he is not a Christian. He needs those voters, especially in the South, to win the White House. Article calling Mormonism 'cult' disappears from Graham website Change on Graham page comes after Romney meeting , Oct 15, 2012</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351256739641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351256934508-8</Id><Title>Billy Graham Faces Backlash Over Mormon 'Cult' Removal</Title><Msg>(RNS) The Rev. Samuel Wynn admired Billy Graham and his evangelistic association for decades, joining its spiritual crusades and urging fellow Christians to do the same. But no more. "I will never again support anything by the Billy Graham Evangelistic Association," said Wynn, the superintendent of a United Methodist Church district in Fayetteville, N.C. The source of Wynn's ire: The BGEA's recent removal of language on its website calling Mormonism a "cult." The scrubbing followed GOP presidential nominee Mitt Romney's pilgrimage to Billy Graham's mountaintop home in Montreat, N.C. After the Oct. 11 meeting, Graham pledged to "do all I can to help" Romney, according to a campaign aide. The BGEA said it cut the "cult" language "because we do not wish to participate in a theological debate about something that has become politicized during this campaign." But Wynn and other conservative Christians accuse Graham of putting partisanship above piety and risking Christian souls to help Romney, a Mormon, win the White House. "My question to Billy Graham is, What's more important for the kingdom of God: politics or the message of Jesus Christ?" said Wynn.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351256934508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351257071957-9</Id><Topic><Title>Game changing report ORCL</Title><Username>paul_truby</Username><Timestamp>1351187234961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 13:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>vice.jeffery</Username><Timestamp>1351257071957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351258044375-10</Id><Title>Obama holds lead in key swing states in latest polls</Title><Msg>Two new polls show Obama still holding lead over Romney in Ohio, Nevada yahoo news 2 hours 13 minutes ago.. . Washington, Oct. 26 (ANI): President Barack Obama is stubbornly clinging to his electoral advantage over Republican rival Mitt Romney in swing states, two polls have found. Time Magazine released a new Ohio Poll in which Romney was trailing in the Buckeye State by five points. Last week's NBC News/Wall Street Journal/Marist survey showed that Romney was trialing behind by five points in Ohio</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351258044375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351258345709-11</Id><Title>Colbert’s Counter-Offer To Trump: One Million Dollars To Become ‘Teabagger’</Title><Msg>Last night on The Colbert Report, Stephen Colbert made Trump a counter-offer: One million dollars, to the charity of Trump’s choice: “Anything…’Save The Children,’ ‘Feed The Children,’ ‘Put The Children On Child Apprentice,’ whatever. One million actual dollars…If you will let me dip my balls in your mouth.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351258345709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351259402629-12</Id><Title>gdp was negative 9% or so when bush left town in 2008</Title><Msg>what a mess. No doubt the gop and a prez mccain would have made the mess worse, likely taking UE to over 12%. Obama as done a good job, stopped a great depression from happening, and the improvements are clear to see . UE is trending down and gdp is growing and improving. the gop have been total ajoles and have not helped one bit, their entire effort has been to try and make things worse so they can oust a dem president.......... and now romney offers his rightwing childish base promise of lower taxes AND increasese military spending AND deficit reduction.....jeez.... he may as well be handing out lolly pops to all you suckers.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351259402629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351260292358-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama holds lead in key swing states in latest polls</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351258044375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:27:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Likable no more By Jennifer Rubin Way back when President Obama was “likable” and Mitt Romney wasn’t and the media were delighted to harp on the topic, Republicans would acknowledge, “Yup, he has a rotten record, but the voters sure do like him.” They’d then shake their heads and express amazement. “Why do they like him?” Republicans, by and large, never did. They saw in Obama the intellectual lightweight of the sort they saw in school, the fellow who thought himself the smartest guy in the room and wasn’t particularly nice or kind or even funny. This was the guy who told Hillary Clinton she was “likable enough.” Well before the election they saw a guy who didn’t miss a beat in his prepared remarks, nor shed a tear when the Fort Hood massacre occurred. This was the fellow who labeled opponents as evil or dumb, and either way, he told us, ready to put party over country. Republicans got why voters liked Bill Clinton; heck, many of them liked Clinton, but they never understood why the remote, condescending president would be liked by ordinary voters. The mistake was in assuming the American people knew him like they did. Like a sulky teenager at Grandma’s house, Obama managed to put a smile on his face and make small talk when the voters were looking. Americans really wanted to like him, really wanted to feel good about their 2008 choice. Then came the debates and Obama’s petty, angry reaction that followed. Oops, the mask slipped. Why was he rudely not making eye contact in Denver? Why was his VP being so obnoxious when that nice, young man was trying to explain all about taxes? With each debate Obama’s nice-guy persona melted until there was nothing left of it. Now the sullen teen didn’t care to be on his best behavior. He sneered and insulted, leaving the big things about the country to harp on the small and petty things about his nemesis. It began with trivial things (Big Bird), moved on to personal jabs (“binders full of women,” “Romnesia”) and wound up with vulgarities (“bull*****r”) and the disgusting insinuation that his opponents didn’t understand that “rape is rape.” Who was this guy? Welcome to our world, the Republicans muse. The irony is that not only was Mitt Romney, upon further inspection, plenty likable, but Obama showed himself not to be likable, let alone admirable. Obama is scrambling to try to turn out his base, understanding that amid the insults, sneers and pettiness he lost a great deal of the moderate middle of the electorate, especially women. The catch here is that he’s done nothing to inspire them either. This may be one of those exceptions to the “nice guys finish last” rule. Romney hopes that, in the end, voters find Obama not likable enough.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351260292358</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351260866643-14</Id><Title>Do Mitt's ideas really work? Take a look at gop run NJ</Title><Msg>Republicans have hailed New Jersey as a shining model of austerity, . New Jersey ranked 47th in economic growth last year. When Gov. Chris Christie took office in 2010 and began to impose austerity measures, New Jersey ranked 35th in its unemployment rate; now it ranks 48th. nice work gop.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351260866643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:14:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351261029182-15</Id><Title>“Osama’s Dead and G.M. Is Alive.”</Title><Msg>" Obama’s initial economic stimulus created at least 1.4 million jobs, according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office. But that wasn’t enough, and it was partly negated by austerity in state and local governments. Still, America’s economy is now the fastest growing among major countries in the West, and Britain’s is shrinking. Which would you prefer? I’m not suggesting Obama distribute bumper stickers saying: “It Could Be Worse.” He might want to “Osama’s Dead and G.M. Is Alive.” it would have been MUCH worse had Mccain won...... UE would have gone to 12% or more and still be there.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351261029182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351261853081-16</Id><Title>DOES PSEC REALLY OFFER A 10% YIELD OR AM I SEEING THINGS???</Title><Msg>ANYONE??</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1351261853081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351262123612-17</Id><Title>gop wierdness and hateful attitude toward women</Title><Msg>Todd Akin uttered his now-famous line that women rarely get pregnant from “legitimate rape,” Wisconsin state representative Roger Rivard told a newspaper reporter that “some girls rape easy.” Republican Richard Mourdock.......... pregnancy from rape "something that God intended"- Issa's all male panel to look into women's health issues Tush Limpbalz calling women who speak out on women's health issures "sluts" and "prostitutes"</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351262123612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351262868609-18</Id><Topic><Title>gdp was negative 9% or so when bush left town in 2008</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351259402629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 09:50:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>former Secretary of State Colin Powell, a Republican ,praised Obama's handling of the economic recovery, telling "CBS This Morning," ''I think we've begun to come out of the dive and we're gaining altitude."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351262868609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351262869505-19</Id><Topic><Title>gop wierdness and hateful attitude toward women</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351262123612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:35:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Billy Bob Clinton. Serial female molester and accused rapist. But that's okay with you as he's another phony "liberal" who sold his soul to the Devil. I understand he's very upset at Hillary now for taking the hit for the Kenyan over Benghazi. He's already made some strong remarks about the Kenyan. Bet more comes out real soon.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351262869505</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351263224333-20</Id><Topic><Title>“Osama’s Dead and G.M. Is Alive.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351261029182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:17:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Osama died in Dubai in 2001 of Marfans Disease. They kept the fairy tale alive with their cy-ops machine to abet the taking of our freedoms. BOTH Dems. and Reps. are guilty. They are now arming Al Queda militia in Syria and did it before in Libya. The guy killed in the safe house (Not an embassy) was involved in smuggling the arms in before Khadafi's murder and was back there trying to cover his tracks. I think they shut him up to hide what they did.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351263224333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351263297543-21</Id><Topic><Title>germany pulled its gold out of bank of england!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351198874826</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 17:01:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MLPs Carl.... That's where the highest tax deferred yields are with huge unit(share) price appreciation... and of course I'm on board for deep sea oil drillers</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1351263297543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351263412571-22</Id><Topic><Title>“Osama’s Dead and G.M. Is Alive.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351261029182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:17:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barack musta consulted with Hilary on that... remember Commerce Sec Ron Brown?</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1351263412571</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351263581009-23</Id><Title>obama the SCHMOOZER....</Title><Msg>All those rounds on the golf course and those talk shows didn't help the schmoozer man. he's in deep du du and the animals in the zoo are SCREAMING....</Msg><Username>mandan14shooter</Username><Timestamp>1351263581009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351263607319-24</Id><Topic><Title>gop wierdness and hateful attitude toward women</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351262123612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:35:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>serial adulterer Newt more than cancels out clinton , they are just alike..... and hypocrite, Newt was a recent gop prez candidate...... and then you have your diaper wearing, whoring senator vitter who remains in the Senate. and still the gop has the weird ideas about women.......and a bum who said that rape is god's work is currently running for the senate and Mitten's supports him.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351263607319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 11:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351263673322-25</Id><Title>stock holders: voting your wallet?</Title><Msg>"Since Kennedy took office, the Democratic S&amp;P fund logged a 992 percent gain, versus 109 percent growth for the opposition party, even though Democrats occupied the White House for 23 years over the period, compared with 28 years of Republican presidential leadership. The annualized return for 23 years of Democratic administrations is 11 percent, or four times the 2.7 percent annualized return during 28 years of Republican presidencies."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351263673322</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 11:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351264230228-26</Id><Topic><Title>“Osama’s Dead and G.M. Is Alive.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351261029182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:17:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Operation Security to air anti-Obama ads during 'SEAL Team Six' broadcast By Hollie McKay Published October 26, 2012 As the political propaganda controversy surrounding Harvey Weinstein’s “SEAL Team Six: The Raid of Osama bin Laden” continues, OPSEC (Operation Security) told to FOX411 that it will air ads in key battleground markets during its broadcast on the National Geographic Channel two days before the election. After learning of the suspicious timing and Weinstein’s instruction to make the President a key character in the movie that spotlights the detailed process that went into the killing of bin Laden, OPSEC, a group of former Intelligence officers and Special Operations members concerned with the impact of increasing informational leaks, immediately sought approval to run their commercial “Bump in the Road.” According to a press release, the ad seeks to “hit the Obama Administration for not telling the truth about the attacks in Libya that cost the U.S. Ambassador, two former SEALs and another U.S. diplomat their lives while also having politicized the raid that killed Osama bin Laden.” “President Obama wanted credit after our military killed bin Laden. Highly classified secrets were leaked, endangering real heroes and their families. But when terrorists kill SEALs and diplomats in Libya, this administration doesn’t tell the truth about what happened, and the President says it is just a bump in the road,” Scott Taylor, former Navy SEAL and president of the group, proclaims in the 30-second spot. “There is nothing acceptable about playing politics with national security and American lives… Aren’t some things more important than politics?” “Bump in the Road” was filmed about three weeks ago and is already airing on some stations in Ohio and Virginia. A rep for OPSEC said that the spot has been approved by National Geographic, although the channel was not able to immediately comment on the issue. “As soon as we heard the film was slanted to promote (Obama) and conveniently come out just before the election, making him the President look strong on foreign policy and national security we knew we had to do something,” Taylor told us. “The Obama administration has grossly exploited bin Laden’s death, and all the leaked information has hindered operations and put lives at risk.” In an earlier interview with 411’s Pop Tarts column, the director of “SEAL Team Six,” John Stockwell, insisted that maintaining a high level of national security was his top priority, and some information he had heard was not included in the film for that very purpose. “We were very careful not to compromise our national security,” he said. Stockwell and Weinstein have both denied that the movie was in any way politically-skewed or intended to sway votes in Obama’s favor. National Geographic also asserted that “SEAL Team Six” was in no way “propaganda,” and that the timing of the broadcast was simply to take advantage of their exclusive rights and the fall programming schedule.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351264230228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 11:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351264251039-27</Id><Topic><Title>Do Mitt's ideas really work? Take a look at gop run NJ</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351260866643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:14:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop austerity has increased UE in NJ...... and it is still higher than when the fat rebublican began his miracle plan to fix everything, create jobs galore and plus cash back and lolly pops for all. unemployment rate in New Jersey is 9.8 percent</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351264251039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 11:10:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351271948296-28</Id><Topic><Title>Do Mitt's ideas really work? Take a look at gop run NJ</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351260866643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:14:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this what Obama's green-energy future looks like? By: David Harsanyi 10/26/2012 10:24 AM It was one of Barack Obama’s favorite green-energy companies. And green-energy companies, according to the president, are one of the best ways to facilitate economic growth. Well, yesterday, The Denver Post detailed the criminal investigation of Abound Solar, a defunct solar-panel manufacturer in Colorado that was run on taxpayer “investments,” for securities fraud, consumer fraud and financial misrepresentation. Abound shuttered its Colorado plant during the summer and filed for bankruptcy, leaving “125 workers without jobs and taxpayers holding the bag for up to $60 million in defaulted loans.” (Human Events senior reporter Audrey Hudson has already detailed the efforts by the House to investigate the company.) Here’s what Weld County prosecutors are looking into: The securities-fraud investigation stems from allegations that “officials at Abound Solar knew products the company was selling were defective, and then asked investors to invest in the company without telling them about the defective products,” the DA’s office said in a news release. Similarly, the consumer-fraud allegation is that Abound knowingly sold defective panels to customers. The third subject of investigation is that Abound allegedly misled financial institutions when the company was seeking loans. Since Obama’s “jobs plan” brochure pins the nation’s economic future on the growth of “green-energy jobs” — in fact, it’s one of two areas in the glossy pamphlet that has anything to do with job growth – it seems fair to judge the campaign’s case for the future using one of the companies it touted in the past. Abound was rolled out continually by the administration, the subject of numerous mainstream news stories regarding the stimulus in particular and clean energy generally. Here is Obama touting Abound Solar personally in a weekly address in 2009. The president claims the project will create 2,000 construction jobs and 1,500 permanent jobs.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1351271948296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351271973192-29</Id><Title>blame game</Title><Msg>you libs out there, when Obama loses who will you blame for the loss? Will you blame Obama himself? Will you blame liberalism? Will you blame Bush (proobably will)?. My guess is that Obama will be blamed big time. Why? Because it can never ever be blamed on liberalism. I mean, liberalism is a religion, right? A religion cannot be blamed.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351271973192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351273613904-30</Id><Topic><Title>“Osama’s Dead and G.M. Is Alive.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351261029182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:17:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poll: 36% say Democrat voter fraud major issue Only 38 percent of Americans think voter fraud is a problem where they live. Americans think voter fraud happens, but just not in their backyards, according to a poll released Friday. More than two-thirds of registered voters think voter fraud is a problem in the United States to some degree, according to a Monmouth University poll, but only 38 percent think it’s a problem where they live. Thirty-six percent of voters believe fraud is a major problem and and 33 percent think it’s a minor problem. One fifth of voters don’t think fraud is an issue.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1351273613904</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351273627519-31</Id><Topic><Title>Should you keep from ORCL? Take a look at why.</Title><Username>kemble.randy</Username><Timestamp>1351092179547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-24 11:22:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very informative. Thank you</Msg><Username>roosevelt.magers</Username><Timestamp>1351273627519</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351273894864-32</Id><Topic><Title>Newt's prediction</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351252964456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:02:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop BSing for a min. The best predictors, markets, give Obama at 63% chance against Romney 37% chance. The Grinch is a loser. And you too.</Msg><Username>nazyoyo</Username><Timestamp>1351273894864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351273952284-33</Id><Title>Benghazi</Title><Msg>Everything Obama does has a political calculation. Did he calculate the benefits of responding in a way Americans expect the Commander-in-Chief to respond...by sending in the military to kick rears and save Americans? He'd be a hero if he responded that way. Instead, he chose a convoluted alternative.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351273952284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351274040254-34</Id><Topic><Title>Newt's prediction</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351252964456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:02:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>speaking of BSing. Jeez.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351274040254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351275287610-35</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351273952284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:52:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your assessment makes sense to most thinking people. Just for comparison sake, how would the left have reacted if Libya happened under Bush and he turned his back on Americans asking for protection? This is a fundamental flaw with liberals, they never see the obvious incompetence of Obama or any other rep. It comes down to the fact they don't want to admit he's been a gross mistake.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351275287610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:14:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351275351963-36</Id><Topic><Title>Newt's prediction</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351252964456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 08:02:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm correct is saying that Obama is going down for the count. On the other hand, maybe that ad that likens voting for Obama to losing your virginity will push Obama over the top. That was a classy ad Phil. Wouldn't you agree?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351275351963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351275530726-37</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351273952284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:52:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am quite sure that it never occurred to Obama to respond militarily and kick rear ends. Not part of their thought process.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351275530726</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351277953177-38</Id><Title>Biden's at it again. This time a $500 trillion tax cut</Title><Msg>Vice President Joe Biden claims at a campaign event in Wisconsin that Republicans voted for a "$500 Trillion Tax Cut" "But you can't erase what you've already done, they've voted to extend tax cuts for the very wealthy, giving a $500 trillion dollar tax-cut to 120,000 families. .................................................................................................................................. There are plenty of libs who will believe that.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351277953177</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351281896386-39</Id><Topic><Title>Biden's at it again. This time a $500 trillion tax cut</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351277953177</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he said $5 trillion, stupid. and sure, Mitt is going to pay off the nation's debts, increase military spending and nation building, it leaves medicare as is for most boomers, and not only that but his snake oil will not cost a thing! In fact Mitt promises cash back and a lolly pop for all you suckers.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351281896386</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351282077503-40</Id><Title>Mitts miracle cure snake oil is Free, better than free... you get cash back!!!</Title><Msg>tax cuts AND deficit reduction!!! tax cuts AND increased military spending and nation building!! Tax cuts AND medicare as is for all 55 and above, and even those younger if they "choose" it!!!</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351282077503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:07:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351282890438-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Companies &amp; Wealthy Investors Sitting on Tons of Cash</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351017853410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:44:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That reality is that this election, more than any other in my lifetime, is about Obama's ideology of anti-capitalism (eg: socialism) VS Romney's ieology of capitalism and the private sector. Throughout history, the power of capitalism has been behind the growth and the wealth of nations, and socialism has been responsible for the destruction of the wealth of nations. Our grandparents left to us a vibrant country... what would they say if they could see what kind of a country we're leaving for OUR children? We can do them proud if we bite the bullet, reign in government, empower capitalism and the private sector, enact laws that attract investment capital to the U.S. and start GROWING OUR ECONOMY AGAIN! Romney has proven that he can do that... with balanced budgets and working across the isle in Mass, running the Olympics in the "black" for the first time in history, and buying a repairing beaten-down companies at Bain Capital. Even if you don't like his political ideology, you can't argue that he isn't the most qualified candidate to lead a country as any that we've seen in decades. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351282890438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351282924465-42</Id><Title>Mitt's debated that Iran is land locked and needs syria to get access to the sea</Title><Msg>Mitt is just plain ignorant, that was not a mere slip of the tongue. Mitt no doubt believes the earth is 9000 yrs old, dinosaurs were on the ark and, he is so dishonest he refuses to show 10 years of tax returns, and forgot to mention that he and anne made millions on the the deals to save the US auto industry that he recently denounced........</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351282924465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351282977531-43</Id><Topic><Title>Do Mitt's ideas really work? Take a look at gop run NJ</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351260866643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:14:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop austerity has increased UE in NJ...... and it is still higher than when the fat rebublican began his miracle plan to fix everything, create jobs galore and plus cash back and lolly pops for all. unemployment rate in New Jersey is 9.8 percent</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351282977531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:22:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351285208220-44</Id><Topic><Title>Do Mitt's ideas really work? Take a look at gop run NJ</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351260866643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 10:14:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Over $60,000 in Welfare Spent Per Household in Poverty 3:27 PM, Oct 26, 2012 • By DANIEL HALPER New data compiled by the Senate Budget Committee shows that, last year, the United States spent over $60,000 to support welfare programs per each household that is in poverty. The calculations are based on data from the Census, the Office of Management and Budget, and the Congressional Research Services. "According to the Census’s American Community Survey, the number of households with incomes below the poverty line in 2011 was 16,807,795," the Senate Budget Committee notes. "If you divide total federal and state spending by the number of households with incomes below the poverty line, the average spending per household in poverty was $61,194 in 2011." This dollar figure is almost three times the amount the average household on poverty lives on per year. "If the spending on these programs were converted into cash, and distributed exclusively to the nation’s households below the poverty line, this cash amount would be over 2.5 times the federal poverty threshold for a family of four, which in 2011 was $22,350 (see table in this link)," the Republicans on the Senate Budget Committee note. To be clear, not all households living below the poverty line receive $61,194 worth of assistance per year. After all, many above the poverty line also receive benefits from social welfare programs (e.g. pell grants). But if welfare is meant to help bring those below the poverty line to a better place, it helps demonstrate that numbers do not add up. A congressional report from CRS recently revealed that the United States now spends more on means-tested welfare than any other item in the federal budget—including Social Security, Medicare, or national defense. Including state contributions to the roughly 80 federal poverty programs, the total amount spent in 2011 was approximately $1 trillion. Federal spending alone on these programs was up 32 percent since 2008. The U.S. Census Bureau estimated that almost 110 million Americans received some form of means-tested welfare in 2011. These figures exclude entitlements like Medicare and Social Security to which people contribute, and they refer exclusively to low-income direct and indirect financial support—such as food stamps, public housing, child care, energy assistance, direct cash aid, etc. For instance, 47 million Americans currently receive food stamps, and USDA has engaged in an aggressive outreach campaign to boost enrollment even further, arguing that “every dollar of SNAP benefits generates $1.84 in the economy… It’s the most direct stimulus you can get.” (Economic growth, however, is weaker this year than the two years prior, even as food stamp “stimulus” has reached an all-time high.)</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1351285208220</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:00:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351285786709-45</Id><Title>THIS FORMAT SUCKS DDIICCKK!!! YAHOO MUST BE GOING BK ... SELL,SELL, SELL!</Title><Msg>YES, THATS HOW IT LOOKS YAHOO, CHEESEY!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351285786709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351286049778-46</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351273952284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:52:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What have I been saying for over a year now. Obama is a Murderer and he Murders Illegally for poll numbers. Libya is in total chaos ( active genocide is occuring) and if the truth got out it would doom the murderer’s re-election campaign. Gadaffi was not the enemy, Obama is! Al Quadea will launch thier next 9/11 from libya where they have control of an international airport, plus the newest man-portable sams availible!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1351286049778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351287813553-47</Id><Topic><Title>blame game</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351271973192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stupid, stupid seabug. who did Bush blame for 911?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351287813553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351288286082-48</Id><Title>stupid poor republican tattoos "R" on his face for $15K paid by a stupid rich republican</Title><Msg>a man has auctioned off space on the side of his head, where he tattooed Mitt Romney's presidential campaign "R" logo in a 5-by-2-inch spot for a bid of $15, 000. ....he was paid $15,000 by a Republican , who preferred to remain anonymous, to get the Romney logo permanently inked on the side of his head.............</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351288286082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351288610682-49</Id><Topic><Title>Mitts miracle cure snake oil is Free, better than free... you get cash back!!!</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351282077503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 16:07:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt has no details on the HUGE spending cuts he must be planning...... if this flimflam man gets elected, his fraud will be seen fast..... he has promised and sworn a pledge to not raise the debt ceiling unless the budget is cut, capped and balanced......... so you know he won't be raising the debt ceiling.......... lol.......... and heck.... if he does the gop will throw a tantrum.........</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351288610682</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 17:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351288927444-50</Id><Topic><Title>blame game</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351271973192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's easy The media, including debate moderators, should be blamed for such vacuous and shallow coverage of the candidates and their positions. It's pathetic. There is very little adult discussion of issues. It's all head fakes and #$%$ and little digging to figure out what the implications of statements are. Easy example: how does Romney's animated distaste for Obamacare get ANY credence whatsoever, as it is modeled very closely on Romneycare. Huh?</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1351288927444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351289222773-51</Id><Title>Cheney &amp; Beck help Mitt unveil his new theme of "real change..."..... seriously</Title><Msg>Evidently Mittens didn't like his previous 8,472 incarnations, so in Ohio he's now unveiled his new theme of "real change, change that offers promise (that) the future will be better than the past." And hey, what better person to lead that charge and headline his big Texas fundraiser than...umm...Dick Cheney? Also Glenn Beck.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289222773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351289898135-52</Id><Title>here is what the gop in congress have done the last few years to screw the 99%</Title><Msg>gop in congress have been Putting corporations that ship American jobs overseas before American workers Protecting massive tax breaks for the wealthiest at the expense of middle class families Attacking Medicare, Social Security and programs that help older Americans Attacking women’s health and safety Against giving middle class families a fair shake, weakening consumer protections Putting special interests before a government of, by, and for the people Putting Big Oil before the environment and middle class families National Defense, Homeland Security, and Veterans 52. Block increase in combat pay for troops (H.R. 1540, Roll no. 374) 53. Block protection for Gold Star widows and members of the Armed Services facing foreclosure (H.R. 839, Roll no. 197) 54. Block protection to guarantee our troops will get paid during a GOP-led government shutdown (H.R. 1363, Roll no. 246) 55. Block ensuring air marshals are deployed on the highest-risk flights (H.R. 658, Roll no. 219) 56. Prevent the Department of Homeland Security from considering the natural security impact of climate change (H.AMDT. 378 to H.R. 2017, Roll no. 392) 57. Block additional funding to increase protection for public transit, rail lines, and buses considered vulnerable to attack (H.R. 2017, Roll no. 408) 58. Against protecting housing assistance for veterans and service members (H.R. 836, Roll no. 173) 59. Block additional funding to help veterans who are returning and mobilizing, as well as their families (H.R. 2219, Roll no. 531) 60. Protect predatory lenders who target veterans (H.R. 2940, Roll no. 827</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289898135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351291523924-53</Id><Topic><Title>Biden's at it again. This time a $500 trillion tax cut</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351277953177</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the post I quoted said $500 trillion. Didn;t make it up. You stinking libs.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351291523924</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351291698194-54</Id><Topic><Title>blame game</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351271973192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phil, the biased left wing media is already planning the blame game when Romney wins. When that happens it won't be liberalism.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351291698194</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351291937883-55</Id><Topic><Title>Biden's at it again. This time a $500 trillion tax cut</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351277953177</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:59:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa, I just watched the video. Biden said $500 trillion. You stinkin' idiot. Do a little homework before you go off half cocked. You are a first class joke, ya chump.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351291937883</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:52:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351292765492-56</Id><Title>And Now A Summary of This Weeks Highlights</Title><Msg>Liberal Logic--It's obvious you know your losing when your entire party has spent the last week obsessed with the word "binders". Obama retracts his comment that it was a degrading film that caused the attacks in Libya. He now proclaims that since it occured in our consulate, it's workplace violence. Vote Romney/Ryan-2012 because everyone can't be on food stamps.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351292765492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 19:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351293254796-57</Id><Topic><Title>blame game</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351271973192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phil, you didn't say what about my post was stupid. And try to give me an intelligent answer, okay?</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351293254796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 19:14:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351293431879-58</Id><Title>voting for Obama likened to losing virginity</Title><Msg>I'm sure you libs saw that video. What do you think of it? Intelligent? Effective? What say you? Desperation I think.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1351293431879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 19:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351296280966-59</Id><Title>Obama Wants to Know</Title><Msg>Who's this Ben Gahzi guy they're talking about? He getting more press than the Pres. So did Big Bird.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351296280966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 20:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351296409011-60</Id><Topic><Title>here is what the gop in congress have done the last few years to screw the 99%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289898135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry Reid, Nancy Pelosi, and the democrats took over complete control of congress in the 2006 election and declared everything George Bush might propose "dead on arrival". Is the point of your post that the economic crash of 2008, 2 years after Pelosi and Reid took over, the fault of Pelosi, Reid and the democrat congress? S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351296409011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 20:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351296704245-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Companies &amp; Wealthy Investors Sitting on Tons of Cash</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351017853410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:44:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>... he was speaking to Romney on those subjects just as a 6th grader might speak when he neener-neener's a playground rival. Hard to believe that was anything even remotely coming from a "commander in chief". S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351296704245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 20:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351296881066-62</Id><Topic><Title>here is what the gop in congress have done the last few years to screw the 99%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289898135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One of the worst offenders in shipping jobs overseas is super "liberal" billionaire Senator Diane Feinstein of California. Her and her husband Berg own FOUR corporations in China robbing Americans of their jobs. Plus the Chi-Coms profit by it and use the money to build their milkitary. I consider the Chi-Coms to still be our enemy. Aiding and abetting an enemy of the U.S. is called what now? Maybe you are on board with it?</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1351296881066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 20:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351298194296-63</Id><Topic><Title>here is what the gop in congress have done the last few years to screw the 99%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289898135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right, lewcor. They top the list for overseas investment. But one correction, her husband is Blum, the heir to the Blum Candy fortune. They left that enterprise when See's and Ghiradelli became the top chocolate sellers in the bay area. And speaking of, I've had chocolates from all over the world, France, Germany, Denmark, Belgium, Switzerland and there is none better than See's.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1351298194296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 20:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351300818149-64</Id><Topic><Title>here is what the gop in congress have done the last few years to screw the 99%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289898135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely not</Msg><Username>aturdaturdaturd</Username><Timestamp>1351300818149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351301238235-65</Id><Topic><Title>here is what the gop in congress have done the last few years to screw the 99%</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289898135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Delucksbird, a chicken in every pot, The Great Society, The War on Poverty, and class warfare wrapped in a Donkey blanket. What a tool.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351301238235</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:27:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351301333175-66</Id><Topic><Title>Obama: Companies &amp; Wealthy Investors Sitting on Tons of Cash</Title><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1351017853410</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 14:44:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>National Association of Manufacturers Report Shows Grim Economic Future Friday, 26 Oct 2012 11:08 AM By Henry J. Reske The effects of the coming “fiscal cliff” are already being felt in the U.S. economy, cutting 0.6 percent from GDP growth this year with huge job losses, drops in personal income, and a possible recession in 2013 on the horizon, a new report by the National Association of Manufacturers shows. The report, “Fiscal Shock: America’s Economic Crisis,” paints a grim picture of the failure of the government to address the looming $100 million in budget cuts adopted last year by Congress and the end of $400 million in tax cuts. “The worst could be ahead,” the report said. “If the fiscal contraction happens, the economy will almost certainly experience a recession in 2013 and significantly slower growth through 2014. “From 2012 to 2015, the economy will lose 12.8 percent of the average annual real GDP it could have attained with moderate growth, sapping critical resources from all economic sectors. Job losses will be dramatic. By 2014, the fiscal contraction will result in almost 6 million jobs lost, and the unemployment rate could reach more than 11 percent. Households will take a big hit. Real personal disposable income will drop almost 10 percent by 2015. “ The report also maintains that manufacturers of consumer goods will see large “contractions of their industries,” as will defense contractors and predicts it will take “most of the decade for economic activity and employment levels to recover from the fiscal shock.” The report added that another recession could “permanently reduce living standards in the United States.” The report called the potential job loss “dramatic” and said the economy could lose 3.6 million jobs by 2013 and in 2014, “the peak year of loss, employment is 5.7 million jobs lower relative to the baseline.” The unemployment level could be at nearly 12 percent in 2014 and remain poor through 2015. “Even if the Administration and Congress resolve the uncertainty before the end of the year, economic growth already has sustained significant damage,” the report concluded. “The short-term fiscal contraction set for 2013 will trigger long-run durable losses to GDP, productivity, and real income. “Even under the best-case scenario, it will take almost a decade for economic activity and employment to reach the levels they would have reached without a fiscal shock. While the spending cuts and tax increases reduce the federal deficit and debt, the substantial negative consequences of not addressing the end-of-year fiscal crisis before it happens will be devastating.”</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1351301333175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351301414097-67</Id><Topic><Title>Cheney &amp; Beck help Mitt unveil his new theme of "real change..."..... seriously</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289222773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:07:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have witnessed real change for the last four years. Another change coming in Nov. Libiots are idiots.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351301414097</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351301448344-68</Id><Topic><Title>Cheney &amp; Beck help Mitt unveil his new theme of "real change..."..... seriously</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289222773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:07:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or is that being redundant.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1351301448344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 21:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351305256599-69</Id><Topic><Title>Cheney &amp; Beck help Mitt unveil his new theme of "real change..."..... seriously</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351289222773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 18:07:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fukwad beck and #$%$ cheney are considered 'change' by the #$%$ mittens.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1351305256599</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 22:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351305542205-70</Id><Title>Obama 4 points over Mittens in Ohio.... cheney and fukwad beck no help to sweaty Mitt</Title><Msg>sweaty liar and snake oil fraud mitt is going down "According to a CNN/ORC International survey released Friday, President Barack Obama holds a four point advantage over Republican nominee Mitt Romney in the contest for Ohio's much-fought-over 18 electoral votes. Fifty-percent of likely voters questioned in the poll say they are backing the president, with 46% supporting the former Massachusetts governor. Obama's four-point advantage is within the survey's sampling error."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1351305542205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 22:39:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>