<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347018871785-1</Id><Title>The Search For One Tittle of Truth In Obama's Speech...</Title><Msg>continued throughtout the night and into the early monring hours but as of yet, none to be found!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1347018871785</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 07:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347021871885-2</Id><Title>Obama Kicks Another 368,000 People OUT of The Work Force!!</Title><Msg>But geewiz... the Unemployment rate goes down to 8.1%! YeeeeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaa! It's so wonderful to know that 368,000 people have given up looking for work, in only one month, or have simply been trashed by the Obama Regime to pump up their Unemployment Rate! And then, beyond that... there were only 93,000 New Jobs for the month... well below estimates of 150,000!!! The Economy continues to sink deeper and deeper into the Obama, Pelosi, Reid Rat-hole! Bad News for The Regime and America... but we do have dozens more of Obama's "Promises"!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347021871885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347022142298-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Speech Filled With Dozens of Specific... "Promises"!!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346972730669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:05:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>US economy adds 96K jobs, rate falls to 8.1 pct. US economy adds 96K jobs; unemployment rate falls to 8.1 pct. as more people end job searches Associated PressBy Christopher s Rugaber, AP Economics Writer | Associated Press – 3 minutes 52 seconds ago Email 1 Print WASHINGTON (AP) -- U.S. employers added 96,000 jobs last month, a weak figure that could slow any momentum President Barack Obama hoped to gain from his speech to the Democratic National Convention. The unemployment rate fell to 8.1 percent from 8.3 percent in July, the Labor Department said Friday. But that was only because more people gave up looking for work. The government only counts people as unemployed if they are actively searching. The government also said 41,000 fewer jobs were created in July and June than first estimated. The economy has added just 139,000 jobs a month since the beginning of the year, below 2011's average of 153,000. Dow Jones industrial futures, which had been up before the report, fell soon after it was released. The hiring figures and unemployment rate will be among the most politically consequential of the campaign. They arrive just as the presidential race enters its final stretch. Jobs are the core issue, and the report could sway some undecided voters. There will be two additional employment reports before Election Day Nov. 6. But by then, more Americans will have made up their minds. In his speech Thursday night, Obama acknowledged incomplete progress in repairing the still-struggling economy and asked voters to remain patient. "The truth is, it will take more than a few years for us to solve challenges that have built up over the decades," Obama said. Tepid hiring could nudge the Federal Reserve to announce some new action to boost growth after its meeting next week. The report was weak throughout. In addition to those who've given up looking for work, many young Americans are avoiding the job market by remaining in school. All told, the proportion of the population that is either working or looking for work fell to 63.5 percent. That's the lowest level in 31 years for the labor force participation rate. Average hourly wages dipped a penny to $23.52 and are only slightly ahead of inflation in the past year. The average work week was unchanged in August after being revised downward in July to 34.4 hours. And the number of temporary jobs fell for the first time in five months. Both figures suggest that companies are seeing less demand for their services and need fewer workers. Many of the jobs were in lower-paying industries such as retail, which added 6,100 jobs, and hotels, restaurants and other leisure industries, which gained 34,000. Higher-paying manufacturing jobs fell by 15,000, the most in two years.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1347022142298</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347023295136-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's Speech Filled With Dozens of Specific... "Promises"!!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1346972730669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:05:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts.....plus more Bush neocon military spending...... WOW!!!! and plus FULL...... medicare and social security for ALL on them or ALL within in 10 years of it, meaning MOST ALL boomers!!!!! WOW!!!!.......oh, and sure there will be plenty TRICKLE DOWN from the rich and the vulture capitalists the types who send their money to the Cayman islands......oh yeah and of course full Bushcare at the ER: The Emergency Medical Treatment and Active Labor Act, 1986 reagan and gop senate created what became known as Bushcare at the ER ........... this act: requires hospitals to provide care to anyone needing emergency healthcare treatment regardless of citizenship, legal status or ability to pay. There are no reimbursement provisions. gop wants to defeat the ACA so the middleclass can continue to pay for Bushcare at the ER with higher health insurance premiums. Bushcare at the ER adds over $1500 a year to each family's health insurance. the hidden gop healthcare tax amounts to about 4% for a family making $40K, and about .003% for a romney type making $45 million</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023295136</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347023457307-5</Id><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Msg>what a pair of laffer curve neocon BSers: Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts.....plus more Bush neocon military spending...... WOW!!!! and plus FULL...... medicare and social security for ALL on them or ALL within in 10 years of it, meaning MOST ALL boomers!!!!! WOW!!!!.......oh, and sure there will be plenty TRICKLE DOWN from the rich and the vulture capitalists the types who send their money to the Cayman islands......oh yeah and of course full Bushcare at the ER: The Emergency Medical Treatment and Active Labor Act, 1986 reagan and gop senate created what became known as Bushcare at the ER ........... this act: requires hospitals to provide care to anyone needing emergency healthcare treatment regardless of citizenship, legal status or ability to pay. There are no reimbursement provisions. gop wants to defeat the ACA so the middleclass can continue to pay for Bushcare at the ER with higher health insurance premiums. Bushcare at the ER adds over $1500 a year to each family's health insurance. the hidden gop healthcare tax amounts to about 4% for a family making $40K, and about .003% for a romney type making $45 million............................</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347024357321-6</Id><Title>Faux "News " part of Mitten's campaign team?</Title><Msg>Another Fox News Contributor Isn't Disclosed As A Member Of Romney's Campaign ERIC HANANOKI Fox News contributor Elaine Chao has recently appeared on Fox Business to criticize Obama over the economy and push the falsehood that he stripped the work requirement from welfare. During these appearances, Fox didn't disclose that Chao is a national chair of Mitt Romney's presidential campaign. Fox News has made it a regular practice to not disclose some of its frequent guests' ties to the Romney campaign. News Corp., the parent company of Fox News, recently nominated Chao to join its Board of Directors. Chao is married to Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-KY).</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347024357321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347025246657-7</Id><Title>GOP: “We left him a total mess. He hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough. So fire him and put us back in.”</Title><Msg>GOP platform: : “We left him a total mess. He hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough. So fire him and put us back in.” clinton summary of the gop platform is right on.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347025246657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347026131454-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Kicks Another 368,000 People OUT of The Work Force!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347021871885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah Yes! The sickening realities of nearly four years under the boot of the Obama Regime! No work in an ever declining vanishing workforce!</Msg><Username>inherited_myazzs</Username><Timestamp>1347026131454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347026730765-9</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: “We left him a total mess. He hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough. So fire him and put us back in.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347025246657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obam inherited far less of a Mess than Reagan! He inherited less unemployment, far less inflation and dramatically lower interest rates... and most of the 'horribles' that he did inherit were from his own Genepool! So here we are, 4 years later, and Obama has done Jackshyt... save to waste Trillions on "Crony Phony Capitalism" and beg the FED to do the same! Trillions &amp; Trillions of Taxpayer dollars down the sewer and NOW over $16,000,000,000,000 in DEBT! And... as for the horribles of the "Financial Crisis", it was Democrats (Obama prominently among them!!) who were clearly at the CENTER of the Mortgage Debacle... for over a decade, pumping and humping garbage underwriting of Mortgages by Banks, the ubiquitous bundling of Mortgage Backed Securities and the creation of Credit Default Swaps, all deliberately intended to put Tens of Millions of homes into the hands of Tens of Million of Deadbeats! And it worked... at least until it Exploded! Inherited A Mess, My Azzs!! The Democrat Party was at the Core of The Mess!!</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347026730765</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 10:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347029903594-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Kicks Another 368,000 People OUT of The Work Force!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347021871885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DNC Convention DNC delegates: Let’s ban corporate profits! By: David Harsanyi 9/6/2012 11:31 AM At the Democratic National Convention, where one speaker after the next swears they love free enterprise, delegates and attendees (maybe some media, who knows?) were asked by Peter Schiff, posing as a anti-corporate activist, if they would support capping or banning corporate profit. Well, there seems to be plenty of enthusiasm for the idea in Charlotte this week — and not from the fringe. “We deliberately avoided speaking with the occupy protestors camping outside in tents to get a more “mainstream” Democratic perspective,” writes Schiff. And remember, it’s the Tea Party that’s supposed to be radical.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347029903594</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 10:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347030722069-11</Id><Title>roads, bridges, schools, and runways</Title><Msg>those are the only things that come to mind for Abama when he thinks of the economy. He is obsessed with bridges and roads and teachers. Crazy.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1347030722069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347031390803-12</Id><Topic><Title>roads, bridges, schools, and runways</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1347030722069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh? What's so crazy about it? Methinks you're just trying again to find something anything to complain about. Infrastructure is the role of govt and it is constantly in need of upgrades. Ask your local businessmen (especially those shipping stuff around) whether it's so irrelevant. Frrrrt</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347031390803</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:23:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347031489959-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Kicks Another 368,000 People OUT of The Work Force!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347021871885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who says it's Obama doofus? What's he got to do with melt-down in Europe? Explain that, go ahead.</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347031489959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347031550085-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Kicks Another 368,000 People OUT of The Work Force!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347021871885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Baloney</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347031550085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347031582520-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Kicks Another 368,000 People OUT of The Work Force!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347021871885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax the rich Spend the money on infrastructure improvements</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347031582520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347031587775-16</Id><Title>Abuse of human rights.. US Social 619726729</Title><Msg>I am stranded out of US and somecriminals misappropriatingmy hardearned wealth in WWWfor11years..Ihave only 3000Rs ..some locals in India are capturing what i am tippingtoFBI using cellphone. The misapropriators are creating hatred in me ..every hour they dosomething to irritate me..Esp these criminals show lookalikesof the 4 criminals who attacked me..they have to be arrested and punsihed ye these misappropriators havebribed kerala police..I am forced to stay with visalahsy atthe age of 42 and depend on her and she wantmre tobe portrayd as adisabled. SHedoes not have money but does notwant metoenjoy my money and want ittobe stolen by her relatives..Again i am forced to stay in a room where isuspect have been attacked..Walking does notcauespineproblems and foodpoison goes away..palakkad is a sickcorruptplace..she stayssecondflor and i wanted a way tolocksecnd floor from first flor as i do not acknowledge or talk toanyone in the first flor when i amforcedtostay with her..Everything iown is in a backpack.. Iallege the criminals in palakad preventing mefrom relating toanyone and these criminals have done itfor two decades..They want tosteal the value ofmy effort and show it as ancestralwealth and i want thesecriminals in aprison..I want monetary helpfrom Wellwishers of my work untilmy case with SUN/ORACLE and USImigration and uSSocialsecurity ends..and it has to end Now,today ortomorrow atthe earliest..Iam42 and does not have partner and children and i cannotbe an Uncle toanyone.the criminals in kerala wouldwant mmy money tofeed blood relatives and want me as disabled..i amalleging someone has entered my roomand harmed meandvisalakshy mnay be fearful..I suspect Balan andPrabha as they have done tome before..These shamelescriminals cannot confornt mealone..they have tocomein a gang..Iamnota gladiator tofight..i allege the kerala police attacked me in bangkok..somesecurity is gettuing paid from the value ofmy work..yet why i was attacked..this is crime..isuffered foradecade..i should ne in harbin hotpsprings area andenjoyingmy lifewith woman..Ido not knowanything more than the nameof my mothers relatives and they have delayed and distracted me from beingmyself and having a partner(s) andacommunity..</Msg><Username>pcaseagainstsun</Username><Timestamp>1347031587775</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347032286966-17</Id><Title>Debbie Washerwoman Schultz</Title><Msg>I thought she had stepped down or was booted from DNC chair. Media reports list her as still being chair. She's not doing the Dems any good by lying, then saying she was misquoted when it was on tape from the DNC. Now she'll probably say the tape was edited or worked. Is it just me or does anyone else think she's the only person who has 46 permanent teeth....... that she lies thru? Her molars take up half her head. I never saw anything like it.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1347032286966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:38:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347032931713-18</Id><Topic><Title>roads, bridges, schools, and runways</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1347030722069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come on seebe, he wants the working class to think he cares about those things. His base takes what he says to heart and teachers think he's pulling for them, no, he's pulling for their vote. Obama knows what to say where, he changes his rhetoric from town to town. Watch what he says in Pennsylvania.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1347032931713</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347035914060-19</Id><Title>anyone check out Jenifer Granholm last night</Title><Msg>pretty hilarious. Many leftist women are plain Janes. Granholm is gorgeous.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1347035914060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 12:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347038253812-20</Id><Topic><Title>anyone check out Jenifer Granholm last night</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1347035914060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 12:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bubble-headed insanity abounding... like the great majority of her convention audience! Terrifying that kool-aid drinkers like these would be determining the course of America!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1347038253812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 13:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347039862518-21</Id><Title>gop are such liars about the economy and how more bush taxcuts on top of bush tax cuts will get the trickle down going</Title><Msg>(The Greedy Old Party offers nothing but lies about how high taxes and regulation and supposedly "anti" business Obama are holding the economy back ....(corporate profits are at record highs is about as PRO busininess as possible) Of course the real problem with the economy is lack of demand..... ) ".........the effects of high taxes and regulation, the lack of confidence supposedly created by Mr. Obama’s failure to lavish enough praise on “job creators” (what I call the “Ma, he’s looking at me funny!” theory of our economic problems). ... there’s not a shred of evidence for the G.O.P. theory of what ails our economy, while there’s a lot of hard evidence for the view that a lack of demand, largely because of excessive household debt, is the real problem. And here’s the good news: The forces that have been holding the economy back seem likely to fade away in the years ahead. Housing starts have been at extremely low levels for years, so the overhang of excess construction from the bubble years is long past — and it looks as if a housing recovery has already begun. Household debt is still high by historical standards, but the ratio of debt to G.D.P. is way down from its peak, setting the stage for stronger consumer demand looking forward. And what about business investment? It has actually been recovering rapidly since late 2009, and there’s every reason to expect it to keep rising as businesses see rising demand for their products. So, as I said, the odds are that barring major mistakes, the next four years will be much better than the past four years. Does this mean that U.S. economic policy has done a good job? Not at all. Bill Clinton said of the problems Mr. Obama confronted on taking office, “No one could have fully repaired all the damage that he found in just four years.” If, by that, he meant the overhang of debt, that’s very much the case. But we should have had strong policies to mitigate the pain while households worked down their debt, as well as policies to help reduce the debt — above all, relief for underwater homeowners. The policies we actually got were far from adequate. Debt relief, in particular, has been a bust — and you can argue that this was, in large part, because the Obama administration never took it seriously. But, that said, Mr. Obama did push through policies — the auto bailout and the Recovery Act — that made the slump a lot less awful than it might have been. And despite Mitt Romney’s attempt to rewrite history on the bailout, the fact is that Republicans bitterly opposed both measures, as well as everything else the president has proposed. So Bill Clinton basically had it right: For all the pain America has suffered on his watch, Mr. Obama can fairly claim to have helped the country get through a very bad patch, from which it is starting to emerge. krugman</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347039862518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 13:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347041128513-22</Id><Topic><Title>Debbie Washerwoman Schultz</Title><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1347032286966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:38:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are such a #$%$ and "prostitute" as Rush would say, for spouting off your political ideas, You should only talk about motherhood and about how women do not deserve equal pay for equal work as per the gop. Even Ann coulter thinks that women should not even be allowed to vote and certainly the rightwing billionaire Theil says just that. nice, of you to denigrate the first Jewish Congresswoman ever elected from Florida, Debbie Wasserman Schultz ....... i bet you just hate it that 17% of the US Senate are women, for instance.........and nevermind that 51% of the USA are Women. If i was as scummy as a rush or a coulter i would wish that you and yours get raped often and pregnant each and every year and have to bear and raise each and every rapist's kid, and give them visitation rights and then they can rape you again and have more kids with you, all as per your slutty political ideas.</Msg><Username>granniefritz</Username><Timestamp>1347041128513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 14:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347042237121-23</Id><Topic><Title>Debbie Washerwoman Schultz</Title><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1347032286966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:38:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey theref fritzy, you ignorant GD Nazzi! Do the world a favor... eat shyt and die!!!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1347042237121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 14:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347043485714-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Kicks Another 368,000 People OUT of The Work Force!!</Title><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347021871885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 08:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The illusion that things are getting better. Uncle Ben keeps pumping up the stock market so Obama can sell the GM instead of losing $20 Billion of taxpayers money. Bush/Paulson's TARP bailouts of all the banks MADE money for taxpayers. QE1 along with Stimulus worked for a short time in 2009 into early 2010. Then, we started sliding backwards due to all the bank bashing by Obama and the Dems followed by Obamacare. Labor participation rate has been dropping almost every month since Obama took office to the lowest rate in 31 years. Drops in labor participate has been a major element in the drop in the official UE Rate. You can bet the UE report that comes out the Friday before election day will show UE rate at 7.9%. Obama and Biden will do a victory lap even though the real UE rate is 11.2% if labor participation now was the same as when Obama came into office. That's right. Fewer and fewer workers are in the total population -- job growth is not keeping up with population growth and immigration. That's why all illegal aliens need to get thrown out for stealing American citizen's jobs. We don't get fooled again!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1347043485714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 14:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347044568754-25</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bush tax cuts expired in 2010, they were extended by this guy Obama.</Msg><Username>tomuch2491</Username><Timestamp>1347044568754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347044709727-26</Id><Topic><Title>roads, bridges, schools, and runways</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1347030722069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incidently, roads, bridges, highways come under state maintenance funds. Is Obama going to take credit for those jobs? I still think states should keep a larger proportion of income tax revenue and the Feds less. What is earned in the state should stay in the state to benefit those who build those roads, bridges and highways.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1347044709727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347046141978-27</Id><Title>Obama: Another Bad Jobs Report...</Title><Msg>... and $12 Billion more debt piled onto the national debt during the 4-day run of the democratic national convention. I can't IMAGINE what this country is going to look like if we elect Obama to do the same thing to us over the next 4 years as he has over the LAST 4 years... ... No growth, High Un-employment and MASSIVE deficits. We won't survive 4 more years of this... another $5 trillion of debt will sink us, just like Greece. Every economist out there agrees that it would be catastrophic!</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1347046141978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:29:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347046253550-28</Id><Topic><Title>roads, bridges, schools, and runways</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1347030722069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tolls and fuel taxes account for far more revenue than is necessary to maintain the current infrastructure... The problem is that so many entities have their hand in the till and massive amounts of money are diverted elsewhere. The Bridge tolls in metro NY have over 75% of the revenue siphoned off to support the MTAs Busses subways and commuter rails Those that drive a car are being hosed on the tolls and fuel taxes that by law are supposed to maintain bridges and roads But the powers that be will not stop this practice because the inner city dwellers shouldn't have to pay a fare that equates to the costs involved in the trip So it is yet another example of wealth distribution... Surburban dwellers and truckers are supposed to pay a higher rate so the the inner city folk get a free (greatly reduced) ride... and now Obama want us to pay more taxes to pay for what we are already paid for</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1347046253550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 15:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347048625735-29</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: “We left him a total mess. He hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough. So fire him and put us back in.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347025246657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as I recall both parties were responsible for the debocle during the bush years. Why? Wall street gives tons of money to both sides. as for Reagan, his mess was brought on by inflation and crushing interest rates by paul Voekler to get a handle on inflation. Obama inherited deflation, disinflation and a credit crunch we havn't seen since the great depression. A far worse situation.</Msg><Username>caray11</Username><Timestamp>1347048625735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347051046796-30</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: “We left him a total mess. He hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough. So fire him and put us back in.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347025246657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Pig's Fantasy of history! !</Msg><Username>econ_meister</Username><Timestamp>1347051046796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347051412067-31</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: “We left him a total mess. He hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough. So fire him and put us back in.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347025246657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cleaned it up fast enough??? He hasn't cleaned it up at all! Left alone, the economy will slowly heal itself. Obama has prevented natural healing and will continue to prevent it as long as he is allowed to remain in office.</Msg><Username>uguyssuk</Username><Timestamp>1347051412067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347051564191-32</Id><Title>Donkey Convention</Title><Msg>The circus has ended The Bummer has spoke The problem now is Ourcountry is broke</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347051564191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347051715401-33</Id><Topic><Title>GOP: “We left him a total mess. He hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough. So fire him and put us back in.”</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347025246657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bummer is of the Harry Reid mode, a worthless POS.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347051715401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347051990405-34</Id><Title>Romney should run for prez of the Cayman Islands, where his money is</Title><Msg>"— Romney of Michigan/Massachusetts/New Hampshire/Utah/Zurich/Grand Cayman — this man who will not explain exactly how all his wealth was obtained, where he keeps it, or how much taxes he pays on it. He wants to turn the clock back to the '50s – the 1850s – and he refuses to offer any specific plan about what he'll do about anything. He wants to run the country like a corporation but he can't even control one 82-year-old actor on his own convention stage, a Hollywood legend who, in the matter of ten and a half minutes went from Good (walking onto the stage) to Bad (talking to a chair) and then to Ugly (the chair started … swearing?). It was better than the best cat-flushing-the-toilet video on YouTube and it was a gift to all of us who know that Romney is doomed come November." Moore</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347051990405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347052253644-35</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strange how I remember the Reagan years with admiration but libiots see it differently. Tremendous growth in GDP, tax revenues doubled in eight years, middle class growth a reality, housing market boomed, stock market grew, inflation tamed, minimal debt compared to GDP growth, employment numbers steady. My, my, my.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347052253644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347052693269-36</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"GOPers ranted and raved about the need for tax cuts for “job creators” but when the time came for a renewal of a payroll tax cut – which helped the middle class enormously but did almost nothing for the rich – the GOP fought it. When Obama proposed allowing the Bush tax cuts for the middle class to be renewed, the GOP refused, instead taking the proposal hostage in an attempt to force through tax cuts for the rich." Tax will have to be raised , no doubt about it. obama wanted to end the bush tax cuts for the rich and keep them for the middle class. That is wise. 1. the rich got most of the benefit in the first place. 2. the rich don't spend their tax cut, they just pile up more in the cayman islands, which helps he USA how? 3. the middleclass spend every cent just to get buy and they would have spent their tax cut , creating more demand and more jobs, goor for the economy, get the picture? but eventually the bush tax cuts should be ended, period. after all, they sure accomplised W's stated purpose of eliminating the projected $5.6 trillion in budget SURPLUSES.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347052693269</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347053752062-37</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Messsssssebird got his nuts in a twist with Federal Act of 1993 causing more ER visits and being a drain on the healthcare system. Well, if you believe the NCPA, the National Center for Policy Analysis, emergency room visits will increase with Obummercare across the board. Among the newly insured under age 18, ER visits will increase from 18 to 22 percent. For insured from ages 18 to 44, ER visits will increase from 21 to 28 percent. And insured patients from ages 45 to 64, visits will increase from 19 to 28 percent. So Obummercare will be more of a drain on our healthcare system will no physician increase in these ER's. And the dimwits who wrote this 2700 pages of dribble want you to believe it will not increase healthcare costs. CBO now realizing how costly this monstrosity will become.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347053752062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347054039537-38</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Bummer got his way with raising taxes on the top 1-2 percent of the most successful of Americans, it would probably add up to 50 billion a year. That would be 1/29 th of our debt for the year. What's the boy going to do about the other 29/30 th of the debt. Growing the economy is out of the question because he alienated business when elected, played to the 47 percent on govt assistance, and now finds himself boxed in. Proof that he is but a community organizer. Or maybe just a post turtle.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347054039537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347054192650-39</Id><Topic><Title>roads, bridges, schools, and runways</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1347030722069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bummer should have opted for planes, trains, and automobiles like Steve Martin and John Candy.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347054192650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347055793061-40</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes and the National Debt went from 800B to 4 trillion when the Gipper left office!</Msg><Username>michaelmars128</Username><Timestamp>1347055793061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 18:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347060841299-41</Id><Title>You have to hand it to Dems for desperate assaults.</Title><Msg>John Kerry rattling about Romney's foreign policy. Like Kerry even had one when he ran. And Obama has been a sterling example of how to win back our allies respect. Did anyone tell Kerry their platform was about jobs and God, not foreign policy. If foreign policy is more important than getting America fixed, they failed at both. Canada has it right. They closed the Iranian Embassy and kicked out the diplomats, accusing Iran as the greatest danger to the world. Ouch!</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1347060841299</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347063638605-42</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Bummer got his way with raising taxes on the top 1-2 percent of the most successful of Americans, it would probably add up to 50 billion a year. That would be 1/29 th of our debt for the year. What's the boy going to do about the other 29/30 th of the debt. Growing the economy is out of the question because he alienated business when elected, played to the 47 percent on govt assistance, and now finds himself boxed in. Proof that he is but a community organizer. Or maybe just a post turtle. *** Good point. Raising taxes on the top 1% is symbolic and really solves nothing initially. Of course, the 99% who don't get taxed more will support it. However, with Uncle Ben printing money like crazy, the dollar will continue to devalue, inflation will run rampant (that's the whole point... to stop deflation) and within 3 years the less than half the country that's working will be making 250K a year and they'll be taxed like millionaires. The 53% on the dole will allow Obama to changes laws to get himself re-elected for life (like Hugo Chavez.) Taxing capital gains like ordinary income should do wonders for the stock market. Facist #$%$ Obama apologist lemmings are easily manipulated. The history books were re-written by libs to cleanse the past to support the present like in 1984. Everything old is bad.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1347063638605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347067817537-43</Id><Topic><Title>Romulus and Ryanulus promise more Bush tax cuts on top of the previous bush tax cuts</Title><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1347023457307</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it was based on borrowed money doofus</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347067817537</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347072665181-44</Id><Title>Thank Goodness for the Voice of Republican Women</Title><Msg>Laura Ingraham and Michele Malkin are firey, no holds barred adversaries. Laura smacked down an immigration activist who kept repeating the Dems favorite buzz word, "comprehensive". "We need comprehensive immigration reform". What the flaming flamingos does that mean? Laura asked her why we should even close the border if the laws don't mean anything. "We need comprehensive immigration reform". But having no explanation for what that means or the details to make her point, Laura steamrolled her.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1347072665181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 22:51:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>