<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347768925539-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Let Us Down</Title><Username>darwinvoyagebeagerbil</Username><Timestamp>1347727028109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile, we are supposed to think that terrorists radicals are attacking American embassies all over the mi-east because of some YouTube video nobody ever watched. How much appeasement do you think Obama will grant to get "peace in our time?" Rumor is that he will release and pardon The Blind Sheik.</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1347768925539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 00:15:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347769349208-2</Id><Topic><Title>EGAN JONES DOWNGRADES US TO (AA-) ON QE-3, ALONE!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347733997394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 14:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, downgrade is because Big Ben's QE3 will allow for UNLIMITED printing of money. No end in sight! $40 BN per MONTH! And they plan to buy up those "toxic assets" that I thought were bought up and burned up back in 2008-2009.</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1347769349208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 00:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347794117764-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Let Us Down</Title><Username>darwinvoyagebeagerbil</Username><Timestamp>1347727028109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama and his re-election team marked the anniversary of the 9/11 terror attacks and events related to the killing of four Americans abroad that day with a slate of official and somber events. But they also took to Twitter for some campaign business on both days. "The election is in eight weeks. Sign up to volunteer," reads the first tweet, on Wednesday, the 11th anniversary of the deadly attacks, from @BarackObama. The tweet went out at 7:07 a.m. President Obama and first lady Michelle Obama then appeared on the White House South Lawn and bowed their heads at 8:46 a.m. -- the exact time the first hijacked plane struck the North Tower of the World Trade Center. The event was followed by the president and first lady laying a wreath at the Pentagon, where the third plane struck. The Obama campaign declined to comment Saturday for this story. The second tweet, about a sale of Obama apparel, was posted Friday, about 30 minutes before Obama arrived at Andrews Air Force Base to welcome home the bodies of the four Americans – including U.S. Ambassador Chris Stevens -- killed at the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi, Libya. "You would expect nothing less from a president whose priorities have been misplaced ever since he came to office," Paul Lindsay, communications director for the National Republican Congressional Committee, said Saturday. The second tweet read: "Winter is coming, but these sweatshirts are perfect for fall."</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1347794117764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347794273252-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Let Us Down</Title><Username>darwinvoyagebeagerbil</Username><Timestamp>1347727028109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Afghan inside attack kills 4 US troops: officials AP Last Updated: 6:44 AM, September 16, 2012 Posted: 6:10 AM, September 16, 2012 Share on email Share on facebook More Sharing ServicesMore Print KABUL, Afghanistan — At least one Afghan police officer turned his gun on NATO troops at a remote checkpoint in southern Afghanistan before dawn Sunday, killing four American service members before escaping, according to Afghan and international officials. It was the third attack by Afghan forces or insurgents disguised in military uniforms against international forces in as many days, killing eight troops in all. Recent months have seen a string of such insider attacks by Afghan forces against their international counterparts. The killings have imperiled the military partnership between Kabul and NATO, a working relationship that is key to the handover of security responsibilities to Afghan forces as international troops draw down. The most recent attacks also come amid an international uproar about an Internet video mocking the Prophet Muhammad that many fear could further aggravate Afghan-U.S. relations. The video has sparked protests throughout the Muslim world and the Afghan government blocked the YouTube site that hosts the video and its parent company, Google Inc., over the weekend in a move to prevent violent protests. So far, protests in Afghanistan have remained peaceful. Details of Sunday's attack were slow to come out because it took place in a remote area, said Jamie Graybeal, a spokesman for the international military in Afghanistan. He said the attacker was still at large but it was unclear if there were multiple assailants. "The attack took place in the vicinity of an outpost in southern Afghanistan. It is my understanding that it was a checkpoint," Graybeal said. International forces often work with Afghan police to man checkpoints as part of the effort to train and mentor the Afghan forces so that they can eventually operate on their own. The goal is to turn over all security responsibility for the country to the Afghans by the end of 2014, though numbers of NATO forces have already been reduced in many areas. Afghan officials said the checkpoint in Zabul province's Mizan district first came under attack from insurgents sometime around midnight. American forces came to help the Afghan police respond to the attack, said Ghulam Gilani, the deputy police chief of the province. It was not clear if some of the Afghan police turned on their American helpers in the middle of the battle with the insurgents, or afterward, or were somehow forced into attacking the American troops by the insurgents, Gilani said. "The checkpoint was attacked last night. Then the police started fighting with the Americans. Whether they attacked the Americans willingly we don't know," Gilani said. Taliban spokesman Qari Yousef Ahmadi said the police were not affiliated with the Taliban insurgency. "But they are Afghans and they know that Americans are our enemy," Ahmadi told The Associated Press. He said all four of the dead were American. A U.S. official speaking on anonymity because the information had not been officially released confirmed that the four killed were American. The coalition said in a statement that they were investigating what happened. There were also international troops wounded, Graybeal said. He said that early reports showed two were hurt and that they were receiving treatment. He did not say how serious the injuries were. So far this year, 51 international service members have died at the hands of Afghan soldiers or policemen or insurgents wearing their uniforms. At least 12 such attacks came in August alone, leaving 15 dead. On Saturday, a gunman in the uniform of a government-backed militia force shot dead two British soldiers in Helmand district in the southwest. Britain's defense minister said the two soldiers, from 3rd Battalion the Yorkshire Regiment, were killed at a checkpoint shooting in Nahri Sarraj district of Helmand province in southern Afghanistan, where the Taliban have their strongest roots. NATO said earlier that the gunman was wearing a uniform used by the Afghan Local Police, a village-level fighting force overseen by the central government. That strike came a day after insurgents wearing U.S. Army uniforms attacked a military base, killing two American Marines, wounding nine other people and destroying six Harrier fighter jets, military officials said. Fourteen insurgents were killed. The Taliban claimed responsibility for that attack and said that it was revenge for the video insulting Prophet Muhammad. In the capital on Sunday, several hundred university students chanted "Death to America!" and "Long life to Islam!" over several hours to protest the video. Riot police cordoned off the area and the protest ended without incident in the early afternoon. A smaller protest went forward in the western city of Herat.</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1347794273252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:17:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347794380986-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Let Us Down</Title><Username>darwinvoyagebeagerbil</Username><Timestamp>1347727028109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fed grilling filmmaker behind anti-Islam film ‘Innocence of Muslims’ By PEDRO OLIVEIRA JR. With POST WIRE SERVICES Last Updated: 6:24 AM, September 16, 2012 Posted: 12:22 AM, September 16, 2012 Share on email Share on facebook More Sharing ServicesMore Print Federal authorities yesterday grilled the filmmaker behind the controversial movie that sparked hellfire across the Muslim world for depicting prophet Mohammed as a womanizer and a pedophile, authorities said. Nakoula Basseley Nakoula, in hiding since the bloodshed erupted on Tuesday, was escorted shortly after midnight from his home in Cerritos, Calif., to a local sheriff’s station swaddled like the Invisible Man in a coat, hat, scarf and glasses. The disguise was Nakoula’s idea, cops said.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1347794380986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347800904164-6</Id><Title>nice work on bushraq , you lunatic neocons</Title><Msg>first Regean aided Saddam with billions in aid, then you lunatic meddlers charged off and replaced that dictator with Malaki who is friends with Iran and who is setting himself up to be a dictator. But thank god you saved us from the hordes of crazy angry poor muslims who were on the verge of invading the USA, their navy and landing craft were certainly a scary threat. It is so surprising that the hundreds of millions islamic people in the region don't appreciate how the USA has gone to great expense to look out for their interests by spending so much blood and treasure installing or supporting dicatators and monarchs in the reagion: Saddam, the Shah, the Saudi royals and by sending hundreds of billions to the Israelis. The one and only thing Ron paul got right is this: "they attack us because we've been over there"...."So right now we're building an embassy in Iraq that's bigger than the Vatican. What would we say here if China was doing this in our country or in the Gulf of Mexico? We would be objecting. We need to look at what we do from the perspective of what would happen if somebody else did it to us. "</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1347800904164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347804676948-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Has Let Us Down</Title><Username>darwinvoyagebeagerbil</Username><Timestamp>1347727028109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:37:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the capital on Sunday, several hundred university students chanted "Death to America!" and "Long life to Islam!" over several hours to protest the video. Riot police cordoned off the area and the protest ended without incident in the early afternoon. A smaller protest went forward in the western city of Herat. Obama says now that he is President, America is more respected in the world. Yeah right. Reduce the deficit by cutting off aide to these lunatics.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1347804676948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:11:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347804815161-8</Id><Topic><Title>QE3</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347762786744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 22:33:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because of Obama policies, we have become Japan. 20 years of stagnation. That'll get you out of bed to work in the morning. No matter how hard you try, things are going to continue to get worse because of Obama. Time of regime change in America. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1347804815161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347804973277-9</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to dumbbuttuuuuu?</Title><Username>wearelegion100000</Username><Timestamp>1347677413735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 22:50:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares. He posted the same S*T*F*U message for 4 years. Save a link to his previous posts so you can read it again when you feel like it.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1347804973277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347805134958-10</Id><Topic><Title>Can't wait for the presidential debate where</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347626390610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without a teleprompter, Obama sounds like: uhgggghhhhh blah blah blah blah ugggghhhhhhhhhhh He says four or five words and then uggggghhhhhhhhhhhh chuckle chuckle chuckle He's a clown.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1347805134958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:18:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347805499021-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama leads in OHIO poll by SEVEN</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347632417362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>North Carolina: Romney 51%, Obama 45% Ohio: Obama 47%, Romney 46% Florida: Obama 48%, Romney 46% Tight race with margin of error of the poll. Obama's going the wrong way. His approval index is back down to -13.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1347805499021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347805691395-12</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the campaign by Mittens Romney:</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347622804070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 07:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama lies. He's so fake. When is George Obama coming to the White House? Why won't Obama bring his own family in to visit the White House? What kinda bas*tud screwed up family is that!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1347805691395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 10:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347811291098-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama leads in OHIO poll by SEVEN</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347632417362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's problem is this: The more people know about him the less they like him So the more he campaigns the less support he draws good luck with that</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347811291098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 12:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347811345140-14</Id><Topic><Title>Can't wait for the presidential debate where</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347626390610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pure #$%$</Msg><Username>egik_egak_egoogimak</Username><Timestamp>1347811345140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 12:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347819556384-15</Id><Topic><Title>Can't wait for the presidential debate where</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347626390610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt Romney wins the election!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1347819556384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347820253074-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama leads in OHIO poll by SEVEN</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347632417362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**** The more people know about him the less they like him That's #$%$ The more you know about Mitt Romney the more you discover that he is one of the most decent and competent men to ever run for President! The Democrats complain about his tax rates and ignore the total tax dollars he pays, and ignore his CHARITY rate of 16%! Compare that to ANY Democrat and you will find that Democrats give almost NOTHING to charity. (Bill Clinton use to donate used underwear!) Meanwhile, Romney gives generously of his personal TIME in thoughtful and kind ways to personal individuals and families! And doesn't talk about it. Personal charity is a fundamental part of Mormon culture! Democrats think that high taxes and government subsidies are better than personal charity! These just create long term dependency. Which is why we have all time high numbers of people and percents of people in poverty and on poverty programs 44 pluse years after Lyndon Johnson's "Great Society" and "Wart on Poverty"! Mitty Romney definitely has the smarts, experience and competence to turn our economy around. The Democrats obviously do not have a clue!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1347820253074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347821071253-17</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the campaign by Mittens Romney:</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347622804070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 07:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a little quiz for you. When George Obama (Barack Obama's half brother who lives in a shack in Kenya) was in medical trouble and needed $1000 for an operation, who did he call? 1. Barack Obama 2. Joe Biden 3. Michelle Obama 4. Nancy Pelosi 5. Harry Reid 6. Dinesh D'Souza 7. Mitt Romney 8. Paul Ryan ANSWER: Dinesh D'Souza, who has been the ONLY person in America to care at all about him. Dinesh D'Souza gladly gave George Obama the money he needed.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1347821071253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347821624205-18</Id><Topic><Title>QE3</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347762786744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 22:33:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>QE's just juice for addiction of socialism.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347821624205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347821788357-19</Id><Topic><Title>Quote of the campaign by Mittens Romney:</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347622804070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 07:40:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bummer is proof of the saying, "How do you know he's lying. When his lips are moving".</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347821788357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 14:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347822264616-20</Id><Topic><Title>nice work on bushraq , you lunatic neocons</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1347800904164</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did they attack us when we were not there? You are just another libiotic appeaser who would make Neville Chemberlain proud. They hate us Bubba because we are Christian and successful. Hopefully they can keep blowing themselves up and do away with their ilk. The Mooslims are pathetic. We have to be tolerant of Allah but they can kill Christians at will. Get a clue.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347822264616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347822865172-21</Id><Topic><Title>EGAN JONES DOWNGRADES US TO (AA-) ON QE-3, ALONE!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347733997394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 14:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at that Stupid One-Star, he still tries to Out my posts! It don’t work anymore, STUPID! BARRACK IS A LOSER AND AN IMBECILE! WHAT I POSTED ABOVE IS ABSOLUTE!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347822865172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347823052701-22</Id><Topic><Title>QE3</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347762786744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 22:33:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, comrade, all QE3 is is a Cleaning of the Balance Sheets of JP morgan. The US Governemnt (taxpayers) are buying mortguage backed securities., ie, JUNK! This will help the Jp morgan BILLIONAIRS STAY SOLVENT at the EXPENSE OF THE US TAXPAYER. IT WILL ALSO DEVALUE YOUR DOLLAR, WHILE YOU GET ZERO ON YOUR SAVINGS. UNEMPLOYMENT UP, WAGES DOWN ... GDP DOWN , EARNINGS DOWN ... ALL THESE TRENDS WILL CONTINUE WITH QE3.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347823052701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347823166328-23</Id><Title>WAKE UP AND SMELL THE COFFEE ... EGAN JONES DOWNGRADED qe3 on its BIRTH!!!</Title><Msg>YOU REPUBS BETTER PICK UP THE STICK, because this is a blue-print for disaster!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347823166328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:19:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347824231741-24</Id><Title>In 1986</Title><Msg>When Reagan was president, Americans were killed in Libya. Then Reagan bombed their leaders house. For the next 25 years, they were quiet. Until someone apologized.n</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347824231741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347828249933-25</Id><Topic><Title>WAKE UP AND SMELL THE COFFEE ... EGAN JONES DOWNGRADED qe3 on its BIRTH!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347823166328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:19:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlimited money printing at a rate of $40 billion per month, to buy up "toxic assets" that shouldn't have existed in the first place, and should have been "marked to market" at ZERO dollars long ago. What could possibly go wrong?.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1347828249933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 16:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347828319680-26</Id><Topic><Title>QE3</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347762786744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 22:33:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think 10000% inflation will become a problem?</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1347828319680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 16:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347828395323-27</Id><Topic><Title>QE3</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1347762786744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 22:33:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I forgot, the 10000% inflation only applies to food and fuel! Nothing important!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1347828395323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 16:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347828880849-28</Id><Topic><Title>WAKE UP AND SMELL THE COFFEE ... EGAN JONES DOWNGRADED qe3 on its BIRTH!!!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1347823166328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:19:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard that the Russians are selling US$ &amp; Euros and buying gold. The Chinese are selling US$ &amp; Euros and buying gold. India is selling US$ &amp; Euros and buying gold. Other countries are selling US$ &amp; Euros and buying gold! George Soros is selling US$ &amp; Euros and buying gold! (Can you see a trend here?) MEANWHILE, the USA is printing an unlimited supply of US$ and buying Euros and selling gold. Meanwhile, the Euro has only existed as a currency since 1999 and many people think it will be a miracle if it still exists in 2019.</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1347828880849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 16:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347829154731-29</Id><Topic><Title>Obama leads in OHIO poll by SEVEN</Title><Username>whycantphiligetawoman</Username><Timestamp>1347632417362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:20:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We saw this before with Pres. Carter. The [liberal] polls all had Carter ahead, then Reagan won and the poll takers were all in shock!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1347829154731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 16:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347844612612-30</Id><Title>Second-Hand Software Sales Set to Soar on Oracle Ruling</Title><Msg>As chief of computer systems for Berliner Volksbank, Joerg Bauske has long been dismayed at the amount he spends on software. Now he says he’s found an easy way to cut costs dramatically: Buying used programs. Bauske plans to upgrade the regional savings bank’s copies of Microsoft Corp. (MSFT)’s Windows Server with second-hand copies purchased from a broker called Preo Software AG. The move was eased by a July ruling from the European Union’s highest court paving the way for sales of previously owned software. Bauske had some experience in the matter, having bought second-hand copies of Microsoft Office and Adobe Photoshop in 2006 and 2007, when the legality of such deals was less clear. “We’ve had to be certain that the savings outweigh the legal risks,” Bauske said. “Now there’s less reason to be concerned.” On July 3 the European Court of Justice ruled in a case brought by Oracle Corp. (ORCL) seeking to prevent Munich-based UsedSoft GmbH from reselling software licenses. The court said developers can’t forbid resale of programs and updates downloaded from the Internet, expanding earlier case law permitting the sale of second-hand software delivered on disk.</Msg><Username>the_competitor</Username><Timestamp>1347844612612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 21:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>