<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357310057756-1</Id><Title>LAST CHNACE TO BUY VUZI at this level - 100 Bagger</Title><Msg>Check it out</Msg><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1357310057756</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 09:34:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357310329395-2</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Increases and spankerdropkicks faiure to launch</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1357167460037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:57:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, there you go again, duck liar! As expected, you were incapable of performing the simple analysis requested. Whether you cannot read, cannot analyze, or both, your failure to make any effort just highlights your blind progressive allegiance. Hate on, idioso! Oh, here is another one for you --- what has been the Total Spending under Obama for 4 years? The Total Deficit under Obama for 4 years? Total Unemployment under Obama form4 years? You get the picture, dummy.</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1357310329395</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 09:38:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357310621684-3</Id><Title>The Goracle ---- just another hypocrite, Dem punk!</Title><Msg>The Goracle's moves of late highlight his hypocrisy (kinda like his Global Warming Theory #$%$). The clear facts: refused tp sell to Beck because of philosophy, than sold to big oil money and al jazeera (terrorist sympathizers), and tried to NOT payee "fair share" he was I skating the rest of us pay just a month earlier!</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1357310621684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 09:43:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357312747071-4</Id><Topic><Title>Isn't it time republicans admit bgroup tax cuts were the worst thing for the country and still are.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1357130865795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 07:47:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excess spending and deficit financing through the shysters that own the "Fed" is the problem. Most pols are enthralled by them or blackmailed into supporting this. It's how shysters gain control of whole nations and now they are going for the world. Don't worry though as it will soon come to a crashing halt.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1357312747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 10:19:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357313107302-5</Id><Topic><Title>George W Bush sells out to the Arabs (United Arab Emerates)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1357244100391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 15:15:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Igor" (Al Gore) just sold his network to Al Jazeera. He said; "They reflect my vakues". Need I remind you that Al Jazeera made excuses for the 9/11 group? Al Gore has no "values" except money. He and his father both were in bed with Armand Hammer in the oil business. Hammer worked closely with the Communists and his fortune was started with his dealings with them.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1357313107302</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 10:25:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357317587723-6</Id><Topic><Title>Personal message for bigpopcomingsoon</Title><Username>hurt.bigpop</Username><Timestamp>1339383496000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-06-10 22:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indeed... quite the amazing display of pointless jackassery! You were no schmoe yourself, Harry. Well actually you were :) I wonder what ever happened to nfny911, sparky and magneticguy (utter ungarla!).</Msg><Username>whojadaddy</Username><Timestamp>1357317587723</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 11:39:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357318554108-7</Id><Title>short ORCL</Title><Msg>as I just did. I think it's about time.</Msg><Username>markhwang2003</Username><Timestamp>1357318554108</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 11:55:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357318748775-8</Id><Topic><Title>Tax Increases and spankerdropkicks faiure to launch</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1357167460037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-02 17:57:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I get it now---- you are just ignorant! Adult illiteracy is such a tragedy. Have a local third grader read the numbers for you. The closest we came to balancing the budget inn the last 12 years was by Bush, and during the two wars and the unfunded drug program. This is just basic data and fact, man!</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1357318748775</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 11:59:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357320497635-9</Id><Title>It is the spending, stupid!</Title><Msg>Again, simple math. Go get a rededial course in addition &amp; subtraction, okay?</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1357320497635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 12:28:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357321594461-10</Id><Title>VUZI SMART GLASSES - last chance to buy at this level - breaking out 100 bagger</Title><Msg>check it out</Msg><Username>whattime0000</Username><Timestamp>1357321594461</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 12:46:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357322790188-11</Id><Topic><Title>Gore Sucks Up Oil Money Like A Pig On Slop!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1357255966365</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 18:32:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can never trust a Democrat Pig or any of their minions... hypocrites and liars all... !!!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1357322790188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 13:06:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357323458874-12</Id><Title>Biden tells new female Senator's hubby to spread his legs!</Title><Msg>While groping the new Senator (Secret Service should have given the hubby a gun to put sumthin in Bidens head) And Biden gets the women's vote Can't find a more disrespectful hypocrite anywhere And they wonder why republicans point out that those who vote democrat are ignorant</Msg><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1357323458874</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 13:17:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357325243414-13</Id><Topic><Title>balanced budget facts</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1357312882301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 10:21:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do so many pubbies on this board lie and ignore the facts?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1357325243414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 13:47:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357332425857-14</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore sells out to Al Jazeera</Title><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1357238876457</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 13:47:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying that Al Jazeera did not cheer on the September 11 2001 terrorist attacks? Naivete so becomes you douchebags</Msg><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1357332425857</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 15:47:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357334372433-15</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore sells out to Al Jazeera</Title><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1357238876457</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 13:47:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Al Jazeera actually issued editorials in support of the Sept 11 2001 attacks and Bin Laden They have even reiterated their support at least as recently as the 10 year anniversary They have even called your boy Obama a criminal for ordering the attack on Bin Laden Its a historical fact The ownership remains the same and Gore is a double hypocrite for taking those dirty oil dollars.... that every other day of the week he denounces</Msg><Username>howie_is_long</Username><Timestamp>1357334372433</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:19:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357345808030-16</Id><Title>Debt Ceiling: Will Obama Finally Cut Spending?..... Does a Cat Like to Swim?</Title><Msg>Obama won the other day... big new taxes and more government deficit spending, that's what an Obama victory means. Moody's, Fitch and S&amp;P all made it clear that U.S. sovereign debt downgrades were advanced by Obama's victory... for those American's astute enough to notice the happenings in Greece, that's important, but for Obama voters, it's not worth the time to stop watching Justin Bieber on TV and take notice. For the last 4 years, we piled on close to $5 Trillion in federal debt. Obama did it, but blamed Bush as he promoted new laws that would perpetuate those huge deficits. What can we do?... after all, Obama is popular and only wants to tax and spend. We can call our Senators and Congressment and show them some support, that's what. Over the next 4 years, Obama will be trying to do everything he can to bankrupt our country in an ocean of entitlements, and deficits... anyone who does not see him as the enemy of America simply doesn't have his/her eyes open. Then, in the 2014 midterm elections, vote for people who will stand UP against the bankruptcy of our country... who will stand UP to Obama and neutralize the cancer of rampant socialism that is Obama's dream for America. Stand up. Our $16 Trillion National debt and bankrupt entitlements shout that the final battle to save America is RIGHT NOW. We don't HAVE 4 years to stop Mr. Obama... if we don't do it now, then we WILL be Greece... ... every economic metric and trajectory tells us that... we're greece by 2016 unless we stop this President now. S</Msg><Username>bjspokanimal</Username><Timestamp>1357345808030</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 19:30:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357354052978-17</Id><Topic><Title>Personal message for bigpopcomingsoon</Title><Username>hurt.bigpop</Username><Timestamp>1339383496000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-06-10 22:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whojadaddy!!! Damn, son.. where have you been? Haha, I remember UNGARLA with smiles but NFNY was a little scary. The last post I remember from him was instructing bigpop to sell covered calls on his "truckload" of SEBL shares. Bigpop said he would look into it and then, in classic bigpop fashion cursed NFNY for "trying to steal" his shares. BTW, bigpop's latest claim is that he made a 7 figure profit on his original SEBL investment. Sparky was boring and forgotten although Yohoho_andabottleof might very well be him or bigpop. Of course, my only problem with you was you succeeded in driving bigpopcomingsoon off the board. (the guy who posted his SEBL trades on the yahoo message board but forgot to remove his name, Robert Taylor)... damn you for that, son!!! I hope you stick around. This guy, dropkick needs a serious Whojadaddy working over.</Msg><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1357354052978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 21:47:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>