<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368765300253-1</Id><Title>cal zero is sooooooooo full of corpiss dabien she claims obama went to un to push for international</Title><Msg>law to prohibit the slander of some people.. THAT IS FALSE and it's just the kinda garbage spewed by repubs constantly. Actually at UN he spoke in support of free speech. GO CHECK YOU DUMB UGLY stupid person.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368765300253</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 00:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368765411028-2</Id><Topic><Title>cal zero is sooooooooo full of corpiss dabien she claims obama went to un to push for international</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368765300253</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 00:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only right wing news claims Obama did that. I read entirety of what he said,,,something a dummy like you should do,, he supported FREE SPEECH repubs are crud of the earth and 90% of what they claim is FALSE!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368765411028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 00:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368765479254-3</Id><Title>Scratch that,, EVERYTHING repubs claim is FALSE</Title><Msg>They know nothing about truth and they repeat ANYTHING spewed by other ugly repubs, thank god I'm not a repub.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368765479254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 00:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368774485050-4</Id><Title>redf =the sina of india but only $3 over 0.1 billion register user same business as sina</Title><Msg>t</Msg><Username>peterli453</Username><Timestamp>1368774485050</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 03:08:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368785468828-5</Id><Title>it begs the question</Title><Msg>if the O admin can decide what orgs get tax exempt status based on political beliefs, can the O admin also deicde who gets medical treatment based on political beliefs? The woman at the IRS in charge of making tax exempt decisions is now in charge of the IRS office in charge of healthcare administration.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368785468828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 06:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368790157432-6</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats keep ignoring the truth about Benghazi Signed cal ZERO....what is the truth?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368759121241</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 22:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charles Krauthammer raises Watergate Charles Krauthammer is pictured. | John Shinkle/POLITICO 'The question is why didn’t [Obama] give a broad answer,' Krauthammer said. | John Shinkle/POLITICO By KEVIN CIRILLI | 5/17/13 7:05 AM EDT Charles Krauthammer says President Barack Obama left himself “wiggle room” by refusing to say the White House had no knowledge that IRS officials were unfairly targeting conservative groups who were seeking non-profit status and he raised the specter of Watergate and impeachment. Bloomberg reporter Julianna Goldman asked Obama at a press conference earlier this week whether the president could “assure the American people that nobody in the White House knew about the agency’s actions before your Counsel’s Office found out on April 22nd.” “I can assure you that I certainly did not know anything about the IG report before the IG report had been leaked through the press,” Obama answered. Krauthammer’s take: Obama dodged. “If he didn’t know anything about anything, why didn’t he say, ‘I didn’t know anything about anything?’ He is</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1368790157432</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 07:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368791911131-7</Id><Title>Charles Krauthammer raises Watergate...So????????? who the $%$*&amp;)(_*&amp; is HE? What crummy repub hasn;t?</Title><Msg>Again,..all repubs are full of corpiss dabien....Theres nothing good about any of you.. You've no right opening your mouths. Besides idiots,..you thought watergate was NUTHIN.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368791911131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 07:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368792191238-8</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Krauthammer raises Watergate...So????????? who the $%$*&amp;)(_*&amp; is HE? What crummy repub hasn;t?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368791911131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 07:58:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>,,and with this again,,, you repubs CAN;T think for yourselves! Other moron saying screw the pooch because some repub says it,..now this mention of this jerk.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368792191238</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368793445261-9</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Krauthammer raises Watergate...So????????? who the $%$*&amp;)(_*&amp; is HE? What crummy repub hasn;t?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368791911131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 07:58:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Raindrops wash away reeling O’s fake veneer By MICHAEL GOODWIN Last Updated: 7:18 AM, May 17, 2013 Posted: 1:25 AM, May 17, 2013 headshot Michael Goodwin Watching President Obama trying to dodge raindrops and responsibility yesterday reminded me of the moment when Dorothy pulls back the curtain and discovers that the Wizard of Oz is “just a man.” Stripped of his spell of mystery and power, the wizard is worse than mortal. He’s a fake. So it was with Obama in the Rose Garden. His performance was tired and trite, ordinary to the point of dull. His veneer of passion was so transparent that you could see him trying to summon his old-time magic by pushing the buttons and pulling the levers that got him out of tight spots before. “Folks” and “I” and “me” and “my” — stop! The magic is gone, his act thin enough to say, as he recently did about Benghazi, that “there’s no there there.” Standing under an umbrella held by a Marine, Obama looked simultaneously imperious and small, no match for the rising tide of scandals swamping his presidency. At a moment that demanded genuine resolve, his answers were evasive, especially about whether he knew the IRS was politically profiling conservative groups. His response, that “I can assure you that I certainly did not know anything about the [inspector general] report,” wasn’t even an artful dodge. Serious trouble could be ahead if the president can’t give a straight answer to “What did you know and when did you know it?” Similarly, his attempt to duck the Benghazi fallout by suggesting that Congress didn’t commit enough money for security, was, like his earlier bids to escape responsibility for the attack, preposterous and misleading. He doesn’t seem to understand it yet, but Fear &amp; Smear has run its course. The one-trick pony needs a second act to go with his second term. That’s no small order. And it’s not because the Benghazi terror attack, the IRS targeting and the Justice Department snooping on The Associated</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1368793445261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368793855137-10</Id><Topic><Title>Charles Krauthammer raises Watergate...So????????? who the $%$*&amp;)(_*&amp; is HE? What crummy repub hasn;t?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368791911131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 07:58:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALBANY — Gov. Cuomo Thursday demanded that pervy Democratic Assemblyman Vito Lopez resign or be thrown out of office by his colleagues for tormenting young female aides — but pulled his punches when it came to the actions of Assembly Speaker Sheldon Silver. A day after a pair of scathing investigations found Lopez subjected at least eight staffers to years of unwanted groping and creepy come-ons, Cuomo said the Assembly should give the Brooklyn Democrat the boot. “If he doesn’t resign . . . I think the body should expel him. I think they should make a statement that says we do not tolerate this in our house,” Cuomo said. The reports from the Joint Commission on Public Ethics and from Staten Island District Attorney Dan Donovan, a special prosecutor, were also critical of Assembly brass who bungled the initial reports of sexual harassment by Lopez, 71, and allowed him to prey on other women.</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1368793855137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368793907916-11</Id><Topic><Title>it begs the question</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368785468828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 06:11:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get a load of the Obama babe (Ms. Ingram) who will be in charge of IRS healthcare implementation. Her photo is on Drudge. One look at this babe and one knows for sure she's a lib. Frumpy, schoolmarmish, a pis*ed off scowl on her face. And she may be deciding who gets medical treatment based on political beliefs. I mean, she has already made decisions of what orgs get tax exemption based on political beliefs.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368793907916</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368793928909-12</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush’s Watch Without a Peep from Fox News</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368735218412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, pubs and fox news ignored 13 Benghazis and only became interested in embassy attacks after 2009 for some reason.......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368793928909</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368794520721-13</Id><Title>IRS is correct to target teaparty PAC as being tax cheats</Title><Msg>the fact is that it is doubtful that they meet the requirement of "social welfare" as they can't show any activity that IS NOT just political...... ha ha ha...... "The promotion of social welfare does not include direct or indirect participation or intervention in political campaigns on behalf of or in opposition to any candidate for public office. However, a section 501(c)(4) social welfare organization may engage in some political activities, so long as that is not its primary activity." from IRS Social Welfare Organizations To be tax-exempt as a social welfare organization described in Internal Revenue Code (IRC) section 501(c)(4), an organization must not be organized for profit and must be operated exclusively to promote social welfare. The earnings of a section 501(c)(4) organization may not inure to the benefit of any private shareholder or individual. If the organization engages in an excess benefit transaction with a person having substantial influence over the organization, an excise tax may be imposed on the person and any managers agreeing to the transaction. See Introduction to IRC 4958 for more information about this excise tax. For a more detailed discussion of the exemption requirements for section 501(c)(4) organizations, see IRC 501(c)(4) Organizations. For more information about applying for exemption, see Application for Recognition of Exemption. To be operated exclusively to promote social welfare, an organization must operate primarily to further the common good and general welfare of the people of the community (such as by bringing about civic betterment and social improvements). ,</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368794520721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368794839175-14</Id><Title>This is what you get with Liberal Government</Title><Msg>A malaise economy with low employment and high unemployment. High taxes, high deficits, high debt and no budget. Businesses leaving the country to more favorable distant shores. A disregard for our Constitution and a disregard for the rule of law. Corruption and scandal after scandal after scandal. And blame of others in all directions. It is the culmination of Liberal thinking.</Msg><Username>flightofthedoodoobird</Username><Timestamp>1368794839175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368795102808-15</Id><Title>tax...exempt....applicant.....teaparty dot org... is 100% potlical just check them out</Title><Msg>no doubt they think they are a "social welfare" organization and should be tax exempt, but they certainly do not fit the definition... they are 100% engaged in politics, they offer nothing but political blather and attacks on politicians they don't like.......... "The promotion of social welfare does not include direct or indirect participation or intervention in political campaigns on behalf of or in opposition to any candidate for public office. However, a section 501(c)(4) social welfare organization may engage in some political activities, so long as that is not its primary activity." obviously teaparty dot org is doing 100% politics and zero anything that would actually qualify them for tax exempt status...... no wonder they cry foul and don't want any questions about their application for tax exemption........ they are liars, cheats and bullies ......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368795102808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368796902908-16</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush’s Watch Without a Peep from Fox News</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368735218412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senior Democratic Sen. Max Baucus, who recently slapped Obamacare as a "train wreck," believes that the IRS scandal is just beginning and that "a lot more" damaging information will be revealed, likely at congressional hearings. "I have a hunch that a lot more is going to come out, frankly," Baucus, whose pending retirement seems to have freed him up to speak bluntly, told Bloomberg's "Capitol Gains" TV show. "It's broader than the current focus. And I think it's important that we have the hearings, and I think that will encourage other information to come out that has not yet come out. I suspect that we will learn more in the next several days, maybe the next couple three weeks which adds more context to all of this," added Baucus, chairman of the Senate Finance Committee.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1368796902908</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 09:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368797486890-17</Id><Topic><Title>it begs the question</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368785468828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 06:11:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservative Hispanic Groups Targeted In IRS Scandal By Andrew O'Reilly Published May 16, 2013</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1368797486890</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 09:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368799161144-18</Id><Title>This Obama administration is in deep doo-doo.</Title><Msg>From Peggy Noonan in today's paper: "We are in the midst of the worst Washington scandal since Watergate. The reputation of the Obama White House has, among conservatives, gone from sketchy to sinister, and, among liberals, from unsatisfying to dangerous. No one likes what they're seeing.  The Justice Department assault on the Associated Press and the ugly politicization of the Internal Revenue Service have left the administration's credibility deeply, probably irretrievably damaged. They don't look jerky now, they look dirty. The patina of high-mindedness the president enjoyed is gone."</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368799161144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 09:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368799262733-19</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi e-mails.... whats missing!</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1368727491588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 14:04:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's missing? In most cases, the emails have the "To" and "From" redacted.</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1368799262733</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 10:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368799443974-20</Id><Topic><Title>Really.....dropkick can't REALLY bt that stupid, can he? Screwed the pooch?</Title><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1368657529165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-15 18:38:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes he can, and he is.</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368799443974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 10:04:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368801348736-21</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi e-mails.... whats missing!</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1368727491588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 14:04:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jay Carney: I dismiss the idea that these are scandals May 17, 2013 | 7:28 am | Modified: May 17, 2013 at 8:30 am</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1368801348736</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 10:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368801520413-22</Id><Topic><Title>This is what you get with Liberal Government</Title><Username>flightofthedoodoobird</Username><Timestamp>1368794839175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:47:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By KATIE GLUECK | 5/16/13 2:22 PM EDT President Barack Obama has been warning this week of the dangers of a mistrusted and politicized IRS — but in 2009, he seemed to take the agency a little more lightly. “Now, before I begin, I’d just like to clear the air about that little controversy everybody was talking about a few weeks back,” he said in a commencement address that year at Arizona State University. “I have to tell you, I really thought this was much ado about nothing, but I do think we all learned an important lesson. I learned never again to pick another team over the Sun Devils in my NCAA bracket. It won’t happen again. President Crow and the Board of Regents will soon learn about being audited by the IRS.”</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1368801520413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 10:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368802712247-23</Id><Title>To believe Dems @ today's hearings, the IRS's night janitor is responsible for anything unsavory</Title><Msg>Certainly none of the appointees or managers or directors or supervisors.</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1368802712247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 10:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368803080236-24</Id><Title>Argentine ex-dictator Videla dies in prison</Title><Msg>Now if we could just arrange the same for Obama, OPelosi &amp; OReid!</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368803080236</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368803330394-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has most active scandals for any sitting President!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1368719861467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 11:57:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obama were a Republican he would have been impeached already! And the Republicans would have voted to get his corrupt butt out of office! But Democrat phonies will calim it is all because of racism.</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368803330394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368803471832-26</Id><Topic><Title>This is what you get with Liberal Government</Title><Username>flightofthedoodoobird</Username><Timestamp>1368794839175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 08:47:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats don't understand why Replicans are upset. The Democrats are FASCISTS!</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368803471832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368803550475-27</Id><Topic><Title>it begs the question</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368785468828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 06:11:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure Rush Limbaugh and every member of FoxNews will get fair &amp; balanced treatment! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368803550475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:12:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368803638828-28</Id><Topic><Title>it begs the question</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1368785468828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 06:11:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glenn Beck is reporting that he a several significant members of his staff were all audited. What a coincidence!</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368803638828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368803705971-29</Id><Topic><Title>To believe Dems @ today's hearings, the IRS's night janitor is responsible for anything unsavory</Title><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1368802712247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 10:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the night janitor was a Bush appointee! Don't forget that!</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368803705971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368803857002-30</Id><Topic><Title>This Obama administration is in deep doo-doo.</Title><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368799161144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 09:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "patina of high-mindedness" was only a delusion of the Drive By Media! What we are seeing now is Obama, &amp; his band of fascist thugs, for exactly what they are: fascist thugs!</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368803857002</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368804085148-31</Id><Title>The Truth about Benghazi is...</Title><Msg>..taht Obama took a sleeping pill and went nighty-night! Probably in his pink onesies! So much for that 3:00AM emergency call Hillary warned us about! Then he lied about it later!</Msg><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368804085148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368805351090-32</Id><Title>Cincinnati OHIO.... Ohio a battleground state!!!</Title><Msg>That the Obama administration poured $10s of millions into.... starting in starting in early 2011.. and it just so happens that the IRS under Obama worked to silence conservative groups free speech so that they could not get their message out in Ohio Yep Barack's hand look real dirty.... Chicago politics exported on a national basis</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1368805351090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368805360880-33</Id><Title>Bush's war in Iraq</Title><Msg>far from over.No WMDs found as yet.Bush lied,tens of thousands died!! Mosque, funeral bombings kill 47 in Iraq May 17, 11:18 AM (ET) By SAMEER N. YACOUB BAGHDAD (AP) - Twin explosions ripped through a crowd of Sunni worshippers in Baghdad on Friday, an attack which, combined with a second deadly bombing at a Sunni funeral just outside the city, deepened fears Iraq may be headed toward a new round of sectarian conflict. In the first attack, police said a bomb detonated just as the congregation was leaving Friday prayer services at a mosque in the Baqouba district. Another explosion went off shortly afterward as people gathered to help the wounded, leaving a total of at least 40 dead and 56 wounded. After the explosions, bloodied bodies lay strewn across the road outside the mosque. The violence was the latest to hit a Sunni Muslim house of worship, a trend that has been on the rise. About 30 mosques were attacked between mid-April to mid-May, killing at least 65 Sunni worshippers. Later in the day, a second bombing hit a Sunni funeral just south of the capital, killing seven and wounding 11, police said. Friday's attacks came after two days of violence mainly in #$%$ areas that left 50 dead. Two medical officials confirmed the casualties. All officials spoke on condition of anonymity because they are not authorized to brief reporters. Meanwhile, hundreds of Iraqis attended the Friday funeral in a southern city of two #$%$ fighters killed in Syria. Several such funerals have been held in recent months, the latest sign that that conflict has taken on a sectarian regional dimension. In oil-rich Basra, mourners carried the coffin of Mohammed Aboud, whom they say was killed by sniper fire near the shrine of Sayida Zeinab outside the Syrian capital Damascus five days earlier. They said Aboud went to Iran two months ago before flying to Syria i</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368805360880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368805391099-34</Id><Title>Start your DD on MISM ASAP</Title><Msg>MISM looks like it is about to run. Do some DD on it. We could see an easy double from these levels</Msg><Username>isaiahfuller872</Username><Timestamp>1368805391099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368805887444-35</Id><Topic><Title>This Obama administration is in deep doo-doo.</Title><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368799161144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 09:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IRS stalled conservative groups, but gave speedy approval to Obama foundation... 'IS THIS STILL AMERICA?' How You Can Tell If the IRS Is Eyeing You... IRS HID PROBE UNTIL AFTER ELECTION</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1368805887444</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368806582478-36</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth about Benghazi is...</Title><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368804085148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP ready to push Benghazi case into 2014, beyond May 11, 3:33 AM (ET) By CHARLES BABINGTON WASHINGTON (AP) - Steady drips of information about a horrific night in Libya are fueling Republican arguments and ads designed to fire up the conservative base and undercut the Democrats' early favorite for president in 2016. Democratic and Republican strategists sharply disagree on the issue's power to influence elections next year and beyond. But after eight months of trying, Democrats are still struggling to move past last September's terrorist attack on the U.S. diplomatic compound in Benghazi, which killed ambassador Chris Stevens and three other Americans. Democrats insist that an independent inquiry, the dismissal of several State Department officials, and nine congressional hearings leave little new to say on the matter. But Friday turned up the sort of nuggets that feed conservative activists' belief that a major scandal may still be at hand. Newly revealed communications show that senior State Department officials pressed for changes in the talking points that U.N. Ambassador Susan Rice used a few days after the Benghazi attacks. These senior officials expressed concerns that Congress might criticize the Obama administration for ignoring warnings of a growing threat in Libya. The White House has insisted that it made only stylistic changes to the intelligence agency talking points, in which Rice suggested that spontaneous protests over an anti-Islamic video set off the deadly attack. The new details suggest a greater degree of political sensitivity and involvement by the White House and State Department.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368806582478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 12:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368807214251-37</Id><Title>Nobody died at Watergate.</Title><Msg>Watergate was just a couple of spies who were mad at a radical muslim video. Unlike Benghazi nobody died at Watergate. Thousands of soldiers died in Obama's illegal war in Afghanistan aka the good war.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1368807214251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 12:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368808260018-38</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth about Benghazi is...</Title><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368804085148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not to be outdone by some aniversary of bush's "mission accomplished". it doesn't matter what gripes the GOP hangs onto, because the cost of Iraq will continue to mount for many years to come.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1368808260018</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 12:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368810292740-39</Id><Title>Making money on this piece of garbage</Title><Msg>Is anybody making money on this besides Larry Ellison? How?</Msg><Username>bbgach</Username><Timestamp>1368810292740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 13:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368810885428-40</Id><Title>Larry, ❤❤ DARA Biosciences ❤❤❤ MMs took out retail stops ❤❤❤❤❤</Title><Msg>.68 spec trade, looking for $1.00+</Msg><Username>pcyc_at57centswasa_pos</Username><Timestamp>1368810885428</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 13:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368811863615-41</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's war in Iraq</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368805360880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still wagging the donkey, phyllis? You really think it will upstage the recent scandals? Iraq "happened a long time ago". "What difference does it make now?" SMACK!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1368811863615</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 13:31:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368812594465-42</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's war in Iraq</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368805360880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's all needing to be said. Dropkick!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368812594465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 13:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368812903800-43</Id><Title>Watergate was just a couple of spies who were mad at BINGO! Ya see! RIGHT THERE! Repubs have never accepted</Title><Msg>the horror that was WG. They actually feel Nixon got a raw deal!!! Some haven't even stopped saying it.. Runners or some other dabien head here said it recently.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368812903800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 13:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368813943817-44</Id><Topic><Title>Watergate was just a couple of spies who were mad at BINGO! Ya see! RIGHT THERE! Repubs have never accepted</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368812903800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 13:48:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama says he isn't 'distracted by chasing every fleeting issue' By JENNIFER EPSTEIN | 5/17/13 1:40 PM EDT</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1368813943817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 14:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368815959494-45</Id><Title>George Will nails it.</Title><Msg>Jay Carney, Bummers press sec., said the IRS scandal was inappropriate. Will replies that using your salad fork on the entree is inappropriate. IRS fiasco was criminal.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1368815959494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 14:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368816061306-46</Id><Topic><Title>Watergate was just a couple of spies who were mad at BINGO! Ya see! RIGHT THERE! Repubs have never accepted</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368812903800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 13:48:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was simple theft. Using the IRS is criminal.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1368816061306</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 14:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368816233873-47</Id><Title>Thousands of soldiers died fighting Obama illegal war in AFghanistan, aka the "good" war.</Title><Msg>It is a shame that thousands of soldiers died because of Obama. Nobody died in Watergate. The radical leftist Dems were obsessed with the break in. The burglars were just mad at an anti muslim video.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1368816233873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 14:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368816330316-48</Id><Title>Dow hits new highs. Rs making money and most dems still live in ghettos. Who wins?</Title><Msg>Who wins now brotha?</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1368816330316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 14:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368816570911-49</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's war in Iraq</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368805360880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Bush was behind the mosque bombings? You're a riot, phyllis. You liberal goons see one side of everything. Let me educate you. You notice the attacks are against Sunnis? Saddam was a Sunni and killed thousands of Shias during his reign. Those factions have been killing each other for centuries. The Iran/Iraq war was Shias against Sunnis. Sunnis are still engaged in insurgent attacks in Iraq and won't accept a democratic government. We should blame Bush? The Shia are dominant now and as history shows with their culture, an eye for an eye. Killing other muslims is so "peaceful" and is not about religion, it's about dominance and power. World affairs are beyond your understanding, stick to same-sex marriage rights.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1368816570911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 14:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368817212751-50</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's war in Iraq</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368805360880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SEQUESTER JESTERS: WH announces another star-studded concert...</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1368817212751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368818449985-51</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth about Benghazi is...</Title><Username>dr_gloom_and_doom</Username><Timestamp>1368804085148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 11:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Bummer and his comrades in Congress took over that war in 2009 when his realm started and the idiots in America let the donkeys control Congress in it's entirety for two years. So that pig ain't gonna fly bubba.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1368818449985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 15:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368820997361-52</Id><Title>George Will nails it.. There goes repubsagain,..yesterday one of you JERKS says SCREWD a POOCH because some gay repub</Title><Msg>says it,..this morning you mention Kroithammer said THIS,, now it's George Will said this....... YOU MORONS can;t think for yourselves and you know it! GREAT DROPKICK PAUPER!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368820997361</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 16:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368821093081-53</Id><Title>not a single repub EVER even TRIES to make their own argument! THEY CAN;T</Title><Msg>They just await their talking points from am tv repub media.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368821093081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 16:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368821605709-54</Id><Title>The Truth about Benghazi is.... Yiy repbubs have no idea what is the truth and when you find out the truth ya won't</Title><Msg>like it... Truth and repubs have nothing in common.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368821605709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 16:13:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368826096249-55</Id><Title>repbs,, go #$%$ yourselves,,, you're never right, always wrong...you suck</Title><Msg>Nice dropkick pauper!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368826096249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 17:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368826194703-56</Id><Title>every day repubs wake up and check repub radio/tv so they know what to say</Title><Msg>You're despicable,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368826194703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 17:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368827416476-57</Id><Title>Obama admin makes it official: We're not liars, we're idiots" as told to CBS news</Title><Msg>Included admitting the administration deliberately stood the rescue teams.</Msg><Username>gr8d84f8</Username><Timestamp>1368827416476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 17:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368827546439-58</Id><Title>Incompetence, followed by cowardice then a cover up = Obama on Benghazi</Title><Msg>Just as bad with the IRS as stormtroopers, spying on the media, and having Sebelius strong arm corporations to pay for Obamacare advertising.</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368827546439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 17:52:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368828062621-59</Id><Title>Incompetence, followed by cowardice then a cover up RIGHT! Bgroup on 9/11/01 and for next 7 years!!!!</Title><Msg>DROPKICK PAUPER!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1368828062621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368829147938-60</Id><Title>Illegal bullying, breaking the Constitution, lying and feigning ignorance = Obama on IRS scandal</Title><Msg>Booyah! Aother step ito doo doo by the TelePrompter President. Survey says "pretend you first heard about it on the news", so voila!</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368829147938</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368829284076-61</Id><Title>Violate the 1st amendment, hide it as a homeland issue, and get indignant = Obama on AP scandal</Title><Msg>Clearly they used the timing to try and find out something else, and it is biting them in the behind. We already know the AP was given the go ahead, so the spying by Holder was intended to find something else.</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368829284076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368829353668-62</Id><Topic><Title>Incompetence, followed by cowardice then a cover up = Obama on Benghazi</Title><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368827546439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 17:52:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The news today about the deliberate stand down is unsettling. Every soldier now knows the country's promise of help is hollow.</Msg><Username>gr8d84f8</Username><Timestamp>1368829353668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:22:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368829717221-63</Id><Topic><Title>Nice technicals today</Title><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1368235519781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 21:25:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another 0.40 to close the gap down after last Q earnings. If it succeeds, we should be looking at new highs.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1368829717221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:28:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368839080937-64</Id><Topic><Title>Violate the 1st amendment, hide it as a homeland issue, and get indignant = Obama on AP scandal</Title><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1368829284076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 18:21:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IRS HID PROBE UNTIL AFTER ELECTION... Agency stalled conservative groups, but gave speedy approval to Obama foundation... Used 'planted' question to reveal scandal... 'Absolutely Not Illegal'... 'IS THIS STILL AMERICA?' Congressman Receives Standing Ovation After He Rips IRS Commissioner... IRS ASKED GROUP ABOUT 'CONTENT OF THEIR PRAYERS'</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1368839080937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 21:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368847932696-65</Id><Title>D R A I N T H E S W A M P !!!!!</Title><Msg>- Nancy Pelosi, 2006</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1368847932696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368848075255-66</Id><Title>The truth about Banghazi is~~~~</Title><Msg>People Died! Obama Lied!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1368848075255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368848181794-67</Id><Title>The content of their prayers...</Title><Msg>... and deliver us from Obama!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1368848181794</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:36:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368848578894-68</Id><Title>Yahoo says: Three ways to tell if someone's lying to you</Title><Msg>Their name is: 1. Barack Obama 2. Eric Holder 3. Harry Reid</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1368848578894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-17 23:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>