<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363522392927-1</Id><Title>Nixon TREASON</Title><Msg>Yup.another repub president letting US soldiers die(whata surprise) for political reasons like bush, ,,,,,,,,,and LBJ and HHH knew and didn't tell us. Again, in our lifetimes no US soldier has died for anything necessary. Ya wanna honor the troops? Don't send them to unnecessary wars. Stop pretending our soldiers are actually protecting us. All their lives are thrown away for nothing. Disgusting you are corpiss.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363522392927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:13:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363522772023-2</Id><Title>Oh btw, the UN idoes not have the power to override OUR constitution. Signed, idiot assbuckeroo</Title><Msg>No S???? Tell your repub friends that. But your repub friends say US Congress has already signed off on the idea and they say Hillary of course was involved and Obama wants it. You people are 100% disgusting.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363522772023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363522821264-3</Id><Topic><Title>Racism Talk At CPAC Derailed When Attendee Says Slaves Should Have Been Grateful</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363478463467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 20:01:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just disgusting repubs are.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363522821264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363523203617-4</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployed Americans under Obama maxed at over 15 million, Bush never came close to that!</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1363444510681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:35:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush DOUBLED the jobless, Obama lowered it.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363523203617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363523980923-5</Id><Title>A Decade later, Most are Critical of the U.S.-Led War in Iraq,, MOST ? Should be ALL!</Title><Msg>Critical of #$%$ bgroup! Just look at Nixon and Bush....they LET US SOLDIERS DIE for their political goals! We are NOT being well served by our presidents and flag waving db's never say anything. They never say stop having unnecesary wars and flag wavers claim to love the troops and yet let them die for nuthin.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363523980923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:39:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363524280986-6</Id><Topic><Title>A Decade later, Most are Critical of the U.S.-Led War in Iraq,, MOST ? Should be ALL!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363523980923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:39:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine ANYONE thinking Iraq was worth it??????????? That group would be made up mostly of repubs and they know if they don't like Iraq war they don't like bush. So they pretend Iraq was good.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363524280986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363524792087-7</Id><Title>Vet who saved many in Iraq couldn't escape demons</Title><Msg>Great example of what happens when republicans start unnecessary wars. Corpiss types pretend to care about the troops but the actions of corpiss types show anything but concern.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363524792087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363525016798-8</Id><Title>tymetokill,..right corpiss????</Title><Msg>That was your fake id back in the days leading up to unnecessary Iraq war and and you corpiss were totally into the unnecessary war.. So into it you made an id called .tymetokill!! Whata punk you were,..you are.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363525016798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363525731821-9</Id><Title>Outa the 100% of repubs,,,all of them either believe UN is gonna take our guns OR</Title><Msg>they refuse to tell the OTHER repubs it's not gonna happen...Bottom line.ALL repubs suck. Either they're part of the problem or they're all the problem.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363525731821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363526936201-10</Id><Title>There are two types of republicans</Title><Msg>Type ONE are those that believe the UN is taking away their guns.....and Type B(humour) are the rest of the repubs that know the UN ISN'T gonna takeaway the guns but won't tell the other repubs.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363526936201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363528202884-11</Id><Title>US population 2013 = 315 million, bush never came close to that!</Title><Msg>US population in 2000 was 281 million US population in 2013 is about 315 million. (and hey btw morons, and you know who you are, the highest unemployement rate % post ww2 was Ronald Reagan's 10.8%, and he tripled the nation's debts and grew the government with his stimulus effort to improve the UE....... and as #$%$ cheney pointed out "Reagan PROVED deficits don't matter".</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363528202884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363528963846-12</Id><Title>nice work pubs, you pumped Iraq invasion 100% &amp; you blew trillions on it (&amp; if as many pubs voted no as dems did,it wouldn't have happened</Title><Msg>"While the official calculations of the cost to the treasury are in the $800 billion range, Nobel laureate Joseph Stiglitz has put the cost to the U.S. economy at $3 trillion. That's why it's quite laughable now to listen to the Fox News crew blast President Obama over the budget deficit. They all cheered for Bush's dumb war, which he prosecuted while cutting taxes. But the most disastrous long-term consequence of the war may be its effect on Iran. The United States gave Saddam nominal support for years because he served as a check on Iran, his bitter enemy. Now Shiites run Iraq, as they do Iran, and Tehran has great influence in Baghdad. So how is it that so many cheered the invasion? Why did so few voice any dissent? Why was it that those who did argue against the war were vilified as traitors? I vividly recall the months leading to the war because I was among those who insisted at the outset that the drive to oust Saddam was foolish. (At first, I assumed Bush was merely posturing. Even he, I thought, wouldn't do something that stupid.) For my trouble, I was denounced as a fifth columnist, an appeaser, a liberal bed-wetter, etc. Among those attacking my anti-invasion stance were comfortable, affluent professionals whose sons and daughters would never have considered volunteering for military service. I was dumbfounded by the nonchalance -- and hypocrisy -- with which they endorsed a war that would be fought by young men and women largely from the working classes. I was also deeply disappointed -- taken aback, actually -- by the complicity of the major news media, whose supposedly intrepid journalists, instead of ferreting out official dishonesty, caved before it. The nation's best newspapers ran numerous front-page stories trumpeting the Bush administration's lies about Saddam, his alleged WMDs and his supposed collusion with Osama bin Laden. There were no similarly placed stories about the Project for the New American Century, the group of neo-cons who were</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363528963846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363531637052-13</Id><Topic><Title>tymetokill,..right corpiss????</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363525016798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't feel bad, bucky! I was thinking of you!! Comprende Pig!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1363531637052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363533829028-14</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle Corporation on MAD MONEY TODAY!!</Title><Username>efrain.mercer</Username><Timestamp>1362394647203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 05:57:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perfect</Msg><Username>hobert.stockton</Username><Timestamp>1363533829028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363537878941-15</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH ORCL Analyst Report .</Title><Username>zelmastafford</Username><Timestamp>1361112271314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice one</Msg><Username>jose.delmonte</Username><Timestamp>1363537878941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363547316085-16</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH ORCL Analyst Report .</Title><Username>zelmastafford</Username><Timestamp>1361112271314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-17 09:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks.</Msg><Username>haugpaul</Username><Timestamp>1363547316085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363548632812-17</Id><Topic><Title>There are two types of republicans</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363526936201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why it's become clear that Obama's White House is open to the rich and closed to the poor President Obama's pledges to open up the White House are going in reverse, says Mark McKinnon U.S. President Barack Obama speaks about the sequester after a meeting with congressional leaders at the White House in Washington March 1, 2013 Access for the few - Obama's White House Photo: REUTERS American Way: Mark McKinnon 12:30PM GMT 16 Mar 2013 Comments354 Comments Once, only nobles were granted an audience with the King. In America, we've prided ourselves on abandoning those privileges of class some 237 years ago, following that little uprising in the 13 colonies. And we again congratulated ourselves at 12:01 pm Eastern Time on January 20, 2009, just moments after Barack Obama was sworn in as the 44th president of the United States and as he committed to making his administration the most transparent and open in history. But more than four years later it is time to ask questions. The most transparent administration ever? The most transparently political, yes. The most open government? If you have the money to buy access, yes. Since last weekend, Mr and Mrs Regular Citizen have been denied the access people used to be granted to tour the White House, purportedly because of the clampdown on federal spending since the "sequester" that imposed cuts across the board.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1363548632812</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363557063445-18</Id><Topic><Title>There are two types of republicans</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363526936201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:28:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correct! Type ONE, that thinks Democrats are intelligent, rational human beings interested in the well-being of the entire country, trusts them to do so, tries to work with them, and always gets burned by them, and Type TWO, those that know the Democrats are none of the above and will always push a socialist dogma, at all costs, to the detriment of the entire country.</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1363557063445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363557173790-19</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployed Americans under Obama maxed at over 15 million, Bush never came close to that!</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1363444510681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:35:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True dat, coffer!</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1363557173790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363557344469-20</Id><Topic><Title>Waaaaaah! Liberal crybabies whine because Obama policies are a failure! Waaaaah!</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1363444733475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be an understatement to only call them a failure" An average 9% unemployment rate for 4 years A U6 still well over 14%.</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1363557344469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363557399593-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's U6 sits at 14.3% (was a high of 17.1%) ----- Bush never came close to that in 96 months</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1363443355347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's because Obama policies suck and he wants the economy to be crapola.</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1363557399593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363557540110-22</Id><Title>The problem with nutcase lefties like delucks is they prefer to lie and report lies</Title><Msg>From liberal websites (like al jazeera, delucks) then to do actual research</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1363557540110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:59:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363558818329-23</Id><Topic><Title>nice work pubs, you pumped Iraq invasion 100% &amp; you blew trillions on it (&amp; if as many pubs voted no as dems did,it wouldn't have happened</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363528963846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pubs and bags were all in , 100% for charging into Iraq, blowing trillions and turning the place over to the friends of Iran.... the very reason Reagan gave money and helped saddam in the first place was that he opposed Iran.... oh well, pubs and bags never make any sense. 60% of dems in the house were against giving the maniac bush war powers.... too bad a few pubs didn't help on that, but they were 100% for the lunatic invasion.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363558818329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363558863357-24</Id><Title>#$%$ repubs know theres no such thing as UN taking away guns BUT</Title><Msg>they're pleased their loon bothers DO believe it. DISGUSTING,..make me sick!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1363558863357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363558898349-25</Id><Topic><Title>US population 2013 = 315 million, bush never came close to that!</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363528202884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:50:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do keep in mind that Reagan has the record post ww2 UE number: 10.8% WOW!</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363558898349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363559046857-26</Id><Title>U.S. corporations’ after-tax profits have grown by 171 percent under Obama, more than under any president since World War II</Title><Msg>American business has never had it so good. U.S. corporations’ after-tax profits have grown by 171 percent under Obama, more than under any president since World War II, and are now at their highest level relative to the size of the economy since the government began keeping records in 1947, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Profits are more than twice as high as their peak during President Ronald Reagan’s administration and more than 50 percent greater than during the late-1990s Internet boom, measured by the size of the economy. US jobless aid applications fall to 5-year low UE is lower than where bush left it, Bin laden is dead, more people have health insurance , stocks are making money, the record corporate profits of 2011 were topped by all time record corporate profits of 2012, usa oil production is higher now than bush era, there is less illegal immigration; and lol Mittens went back to the cayman islands after losing big.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363559046857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:24:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363563520463-27</Id><Title>Bottom line- imbedded unemployment under Obama is the worse ever!</Title><Msg>Going on 5 years of dismal, imbedded unemployment. Where is Barry? Setting up another vacation, more golf withTiger, some B-ball with Alexi, keeping kids out of the Whitehouse...... Anywhere but where he could do some good formthe country by workng together to create some jobs.</Msg><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1363563520463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363572088132-28</Id><Title>Dems Deserting Ship</Title><Msg>Bill Maher disgusted with the new "rich" tax. "Calif might lose me. I pay 50% now. I'm all for paying my fair share but this is ridiculous.." Hahahahaha. A liberal goon suffering the effects of what he voted for. He'll move to a No State Tax State or maybe to the Cayman Islands with Romney. When Maher talks, liberals listen. . Too Funny. Maybe lluck will get the rest of Hollywood to follow.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1363572088132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363574150548-29</Id><Title>This will make your day</Title><Msg>Sales approximately doubled last year as did earnings and I expect huge gains this year. Perfect size company w/ only 600 mil sales. It has a p/e of 22 and should have one of 40 just to get to the price of a typical fast growing company. Not only should the price rise for a higher p/e but also it should rocket up with the expected fast rise in earnings. We could easily see the price triple in one year considering these items. The SYMBOL: (AL) - a high profit airline leasing business. Company has billions of dollars in new jets ordered from Boeing and Airbus so obviously they expect a lot more business. I have 20 years experience evaluating hundreds of companies, this is one of the top 3 company stocks I have ever found. The company reported great earnings again and also leased 2 - Boeing 777's, and ordered 10 more Boeing 777's. Symbol (AL) Another interesting but more speculative stock is (edap). The company is big into ultrasound and they finished a study showing ultrasound works on prostate cancer without side effects like chemotherapy. The company is applying for approval with the FDA and it is expected to go through on a fast track because of the excellent results. This undiscovered company is priced at only $4.</Msg><Username>emsggim</Username><Timestamp>1363574150548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>