<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372850405829-1</Id><Topic><Title>Pope Gives His Blessing to Solar Power – Vatican Solar Panels (the Vatican produces electricity)</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372772588368</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 09:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Pope has more brains than idiot Ronald Reagun, not hard to do.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372850405829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 07:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372853900114-2</Id><Title>Another Day</Title><Msg>Patiently watching the misguided clowns and losers. Accumulating more way thankfully too low share prices. While the clock is ticking away. It is the greatst show on earth frantic action coming up.</Msg><Username>g.garyl</Username><Timestamp>1372853900114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372854699668-3</Id><Title>. We smashed several creep parades flying Viet Cong flags Signed, ignorant ugly stinking piece of cor#$%$ dabien, RUNNERS</Title><Msg>YOU IDIOT! People just like you are to blame for the majority of US deaths in SE Asia! Jane Fonda a HEROINE,,.YOU an ugly coward!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1372854699668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372855152602-4</Id><Title>Rush Limbaugh Attacks Police and Firefighters for Contributing Nothing to the Economy</Title><Msg>He says teachers are the same.................When fat Tush. gets paid for spouting off lies and hatred and hypocrisy now that is a contribution!</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372855152602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372855562076-5</Id><Title>G.O.P. IGNORES CHILDREN ONCE THEY'RE OUTSIDE THE WOMB</Title><Msg>"......The [gop] proposed food stamp cuts are only one assault on the programs that assist less-fortunate children once they are born. Republicans have also trained their sights on Medicaid, the health insurance program for the poor. Paul Ryan, the GOP's relentless budget-cutter, wants to turn Medicaid into a block grant to the states, which almost certainly means that fewer people would be served. About half of Medicaid's beneficiaries are children. Still, GOP bigwigs get furious when they are accused of conducting a war on women. But what else is it? It's clearly not a great moral crusade to save children. Cynthia Tucker, winner of the 2007 Pulitzer Prize for commentary</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372855562076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372858564898-6</Id><Title>billionaire Mitten's charitable donations mostly went to the Mormon church</Title><Msg>According to IRS documents reviewed by The Huffington Post, Mitt and Ann Romney's charitable foundation gave $4,325,000 to the Mormon Church in three hefty installments in 2003, 2008 and 2009. That was 74 percent of their foundation's donations from 2002 to 2009, during which time the couple gave a total of $5,854,916 to charity. 7 years Mittens donated about $6 million to "charity"............... most went to the Mormon church.........who, one analysis shows give about 0.7% of what they get to actual charity... the rest for their church empire.....(the Economist says the American Catholic Church gives 2.7% of its spending to charity.............) all of which is OK and who cares except for the fact that conservatives brag that they are the most generous in taking care of the needy........but that is not true........ since most of what they call "charity" is not the needy.... it is their own congregation and it's expenses......... and btw.... since it has been revealed that Mittens hid his wealth and is actually a billionaire........... is his giving of $6 million in 7 years generous compared to his wealth?..................0.001% of his net worth a year?...heck, i do more than that, much more. and so do most Americans......</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372858564898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372860224691-7</Id><Topic><Title>billionaire Mitten's charitable donations mostly went to the Mormon church</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372858564898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AG Holder personally signed off on James Rosen warrant, illegally invading his privacy. Next thing you know, he will join Eddie in Russia. We have communists running our federal govt.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372860224691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372860813472-8</Id><Topic><Title>billionaire Mitten's charitable donations mostly went to the Mormon church</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372858564898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>darn straight, where is Joe McCarthy when he is needed the most. Criminal Communist that seem to get away with accessories to the murder of American Citizens.</Msg><Username>threedogfarmer</Username><Timestamp>1372860813472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372860875862-9</Id><Topic><Title>billionaire Mitten's charitable donations mostly went to the Mormon church</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372858564898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and every penny of Algore's $356 charitable contributions went directly to where it did the most good. It was a very efficacious donation as there were no administrative or operational expenses.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372860875862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372861747716-10</Id><Topic><Title>G.O.P. IGNORES CHILDREN ONCE THEY'RE OUTSIDE THE WOMB</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372855562076</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:46:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Personal responsibility is the GOP mantra. Book it. But I do give to my dastardly Catholic church every month to support those babies the libs have not slaughtered.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372861747716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372861801485-11</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh Attacks Police and Firefighters for Contributing Nothing to the Economy</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372855152602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Govt only consumes!!!!!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372861801485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:30:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372862108991-12</Id><Topic><Title>An Overview of Religious Financial Fraud: The $34 Billion Scandal</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372699204162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 13:20:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phoney leader. Phoney leader. Hell, he's a pauper compared to the Bummer. African trip alone cost 90-100 million just so he could visit his homeland. Not that's the definition of audacity.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372862108991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372863351214-13</Id><Title>tired of losing? check here now</Title><Msg>I haven’t missed with a stock since I followed their picks. They always skyrocket. Great FREE service. Join now. Text the word Alert without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>hoganaiden443</Username><Timestamp>1372863351214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 10:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372867432309-14</Id><Title>Oracle</Title><Msg>Just a reminder that this is a message board for Oracle which is a software company. I respect your opinions but you aren't changing any minds here. If all you want to do is blow off a little steam, go to town! If you are trying to create change, you may want to find something more effective.</Msg><Username>slope661</Username><Timestamp>1372867432309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372868376167-15</Id><Title>Buy NDLS - $400 stock</Title><Msg>better than Chipotle</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1372868376167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372868711050-16</Id><Title>ObamaCare On "Suicide Watch"!!</Title><Msg>Hilarious! What the GOP and Supreme Court could not do, frightened Democrats are doing for them... and US! Killing it quietly! This Monstrosity can only avoid a train wreck by Suicide!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1372868711050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372869024232-17</Id><Topic><Title>billionaire Mitten's charitable donations mostly went to the Mormon church</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372858564898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Communism" was a front for certain veryu wealthy individuals. Marx and Engels. Know anything about Engels? A wealthy clothing manufacturer who financed Marx. Jacob Schiff of Kuhn Loeb Bank in New York financed Trotsky (nee Bronstein) to the tune of 20 mil. from his personal fortune. I have a book put out by the "Soviet-American Chamber of Commerce in 1937. It has articles on all the big corporations banks and brokerage houses that aided and abetted the Comunist thugs while they murderd millions. Many of those names are still in business today. "Armand Hammer (Osmond Hommes) of Occidental Petroleum and "Igor's" mentor got his start fencing stolen art treasures from Russia to the West. If you were an egomaniacal thief which wouldyou rather own, a corporation? Or, a whole nation, maybe even the world?</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372869024232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372869306367-18</Id><Topic><Title>billionaire Mitten's charitable donations mostly went to the Mormon church</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372858564898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not LDS but I do know that the church does many charitable works, Most churches do. It is hard to do charity on your own so most people donate to those that specialize in it. Look out for those groups with a high overhead and huge salaries.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372869306367</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372869508412-19</Id><Topic><Title>ObamaCare On "Suicide Watch"!!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1372868711050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't it be interesting to know just who wrote this Obamanation? It didn't originate in the House as our laws are supposed to. None of them had read it yet they passed it into law. Wouldn't you say it was a little strange?</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372869508412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372870442798-20</Id><Topic><Title>ObamaCare On "Suicide Watch"!!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1372868711050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Obamacare was written years ago by many people with varied interests. Once written it was tucked away into a desk drawer where it waited and waited for the right time to spring it on the people. Had obama never been elected that plan would still be in that desk drawer waiting.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1372870442798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372871438736-21</Id><Title>stocks that are ready to fly!</Title><Msg>You want to look like an expert trader? Follow their picks. Simple as that. Text the word Alerts without quotes to FIVE FIVE FIVE EIGHT EIGHT EIGHT</Msg><Username>hoganaiden443</Username><Timestamp>1372871438736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372872081014-22</Id><Title>$36 million for a fake faith healers gulf stream jet is considered "charity" by the righties</Title><Msg>$36 million PLUS $600K a year to operate it.....jeez..... who cares, but the righties say they are more generous and there is no need for food stamps or tax help for the needy because THEY are such charitable people...... they take care of the poor at the church..................... but that is all just rightwing conceit and braggadocio and baloney..........................Take for example the billionaire Mittens..... he gave about a million a year for many years......nice, bully for him.. and who cares...... but can the righties brag about it or claim that is helping to take care of the poor? NO......is the answer........ great, mittens donated 0.001 % of his billion dollar net worth..... ( I do way more , most do too).......... BUT he , like most righties gave MOST of that to the Mormon church.............. and yes they help the poor with, per Bloomberg , 0.7% of what they take in,,,,0.7%...goes to real charity and the rest to the expenses of their empire..for comparison the Economist says the US catholic church gives 2.7% of what they SPEND to charity.......</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372872081014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872401656-23</Id><Topic><Title>ObamaCare On "Suicide Watch"!!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1372868711050</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another demessy dream in the crash and burn column. Dems have accomplished nothing with their hope and change platform, well nothing except spending us into twice the debt to save the economy. And don't forget the lavish vacations while Michelle tells Americans they have to give up more of their pie to let others have some. Little did we know that was what they meant by change. I work hard for my piece of the pie, what the he'll does she do?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1372872401656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872633171-24</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh Attacks Police and Firefighters for Contributing Nothing to the Economy</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372855152602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rush Limbaugh is very stupid. stupid and disgusting and dishonest. WSJ: Unemployment Rate Would Be Near 7.1 Percent Without Government Job Cuts. Wall Street Journal reporter Justin Lahart stated that, all things equal, "if there were as many people working in government as there were in December 2008, the unemployment rate in April would have been 7.1%, not 8.1%." Economist Scott Brown: Economy Would Likely Be Growing A Full Percentage Point Faster Without Drag From Government Job Losses. From a June 6, 2012 ABC News report Economist Joel Naroff: When The Public Sector Cuts Jobs, "The Private Sector Gets Affected." A September 2, 2011, U.S. News &amp; World Report article quoted economist Joel Naroff as saying that "the private sector gets affected" by public-sector job losses. From U.S. News &amp; World Report Economist Dean Baker: "A Dollar ... Has The Same Impact On Demand And Growth Whether It [Is] Spent By A Public Sector Worker Or" A Private-Sector Worker. In an email to Media Matters, Dean Baker, co-director of the Center for Economic and Policy Research, explained the impact of public-sector spending on the economy, writing: "But seriously, a dollar is a dollar. It has the same impact on demand and growth whether it [is] spent by a public sector worker or whether it is spent by someone employed in the private sector</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372872633171</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372872790431-25</Id><Topic><Title>Spank your wife for Jesus</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372768163378</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-02 08:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think this might actually be in the gop platform: •The husband is the head of the household, whilst the wife is submissive to her husband as if the Lord Himself was her husband. See Eph. 5:22-24.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372872790431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372873571049-26</Id><Topic><Title>billionaire Mitten's charitable donations mostly went to the Mormon church</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372858564898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Capitalism As A Religion) "The [Mormon church] business starts with mandatory 10 percent tithing if you want access to Temples. All that money – estimated at an annual $8 billion – goes directly to Salt Lake City to a group of powerful businessmen who are the people who run the Church. There is no transparency. Mormons are sometimes charged to go make money for the church in various enterprises (my favorite is a Hawaiian theme-park that pays no taxes because it is related to church activities and yet brings in $60 million a year). Some are even recruited to volunteer services for for-profit enterprises. And the notion of charity is a very Mormon one: A study co-written by Cragun and recently published in Free Inquiry estimates that the Mormon Church donates only about 0.7 percent of its annual income to charity; the United Methodist Church gives about 29 percent." Bloomberg's Businessweek</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372873571049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372873828877-27</Id><Title>$50 in 3 weeks</Title><Msg>Just a reminder folks - this will fly to $50 in a few weeks time. Trust Dr. Osso. Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372873828877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:50:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372874154812-28</Id><Topic><Title>$50 in 3 weeks</Title><Username>ossobucco20l2</Username><Timestamp>1372873828877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:50:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do you waste your time posting such idiotic projections? Do you really think anyone will listen to you? - you are ignored</Msg><Username>wall.street13</Username><Timestamp>1372874154812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 13:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372875640326-29</Id><Title>Mark Turd</Title><Msg>Mark sold 1000000 Shares. _Why ?</Msg><Username>stockpicker2012</Username><Timestamp>1372875640326</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372877912697-30</Id><Title>Egyptian President Democratically Overthrown!</Title><Msg>The Arab Street is a far better gauge of real democracy than the GD corrupt elections! So tell us Obama, how's that Arab Spring of yours going?? Right... there's nothing left... totally destroyed, everywhere!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1372877912697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372878272921-31</Id><Topic><Title>Egyptian President Democratically Overthrown!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1372877912697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everything Obama touches, within and without America, turns into a massive FUP! The guy is a Pariah! Everyone with any brains wants to stay clear and distant of anything he does or says!!!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1372878272921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 15:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372881726972-32</Id><Title>FISA warrants are issued by all gop appointed judges</Title><Msg>just saying. Is that why Snowden loves Russia or China or Cuba more than the USA? almost all FISA judges are gop appointees. "the panel’s current roster of 11 includes 10 judges who were appointed to their federal district court positions by Republican presidents....... " The Most Secretive Court in America May Also Be the Most Conservative By Bill Blum</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372881726972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372882519995-33</Id><Title>btw, your guy Bush created PRISM and says it is necessary....</Title><Msg>I know, now you would vote for Snowden and now you would have never been for Bush invasion of Iraq "Defending PRISM: In an interview with CNN on Monday, former President George W. Bush says the National Security Agency’s Internet spying program that began under his administration and was expanded by President Obama’s was necessary to aid in the fight against terrorism. “I think there needs to be a balance, and as the president explained, there is a proper balance,” he said. “I put that program in place to protect the country. One of the certainties was that civil liberties were guaranteed.”</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372882519995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372883963788-34</Id><Topic><Title>billionaire Mitten's charitable donations mostly went to the Mormon church</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372858564898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 09:36:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess the LDS have their own IRS.... you can't even go to their church unless you tithe 10%.....and they don't account for ho they spend it.............no transparency............but I bet they demand to know YOUR finances.... to make sure you ARE tithing 10%................ "The [Mormon church] business starts with mandatory 10 percent tithing if you want access to Temples. All that money – estimated at an annual $8 billion – goes directly to Salt Lake City to a group of powerful businessmen who are the people who run the Church. There is no transparency" Bloomberg</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372883963788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372887131457-35</Id><Title>"The American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists" denounces Texas war on women</Title><Msg>(pub politicians say they know what's best for women's health and never mind what doc's or women say......) "The American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (ACOG), a national group of women’s health experts, has come out against the harsh abortion restrictions that Texas lawmakers are attempting to force through a second special session. In a new statement, the coalition of OB-GYNs warns that the Texas bills are “over-reaching” and “set a dangerous precedent” for medical care. “The Texas bills set a dangerous precedent of a legislature telling doctors how to practice medicine and how to care for individual patients,” the group’s Executive Vice President, Dr. Hal C. Lawrence III, said in the statement. “ACOG opposes legislative interference, and strongly believes that decisions about medical care must be based on scientific evidence and made by licensed medical professionals, not the state or federal government.” Senate Bill 1 and House Bill 2 — formerly known as SB 5 during Texas’ last special session — would criminalize abortions after 20 weeks of pregnancy and shut down the vast majority of the women’s health clinics in Texas. The proposed measures threaten to restrict access to all types of reproductive care, since many women currently receive contraceptive services and cancer screenings at the clinics that will be forced to close their doors. ACOG’s Texas District Chair, Dr. Lisa M. Hollier, called the abortion-related proposals “a compilation of over-reaching measures” intended to police the circumstances under which women can receive reproductive care. “The bills are not based on sound science, despite our efforts to provide the legislature with the best available medical knowledge,” Hollier pointed out, warning that SB 1 and HB 2 will ultimately “erode women’s health.”</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372887131457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372891343983-36</Id><Topic><Title>"The American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists" denounces Texas war on women</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372887131457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 17:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>God doesn't care what these fascists think. Right is right and left supports killing of the unborn.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372891343983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372891487058-37</Id><Topic><Title>btw, your guy Bush created PRISM and says it is necessary....</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372882519995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:15:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hydroencephalogous, you seem to agree with many of our past and present great Republican leaders. Keep the faith, adulthood may be a reality for you some day.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372891487058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372891565784-38</Id><Topic><Title>FISA warrants are issued by all gop appointed judges</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372881726972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:02:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great that you like our Republican appointed judges.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372891565784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372891645807-39</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh Attacks Police and Firefighters for Contributing Nothing to the Economy</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372855152602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that's a fact Jack.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1372891645807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 18:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372903686576-40</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh Attacks Police and Firefighters for Contributing Nothing to the Economy</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372855152602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't know just what you are referring to but bet it was regarding governmrent unions. I've had enough personal experience with unions and some of the thugs that run them and support them to give a thumbs down on most of them. Employees of the company I retired from had better benefits vis a vis similar companies before union representation than afterr. Our "Fearless Leader" used dues money to support activities of his choosing that was against the wishes of most of the members.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372903686576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372903757256-41</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh Attacks Police and Firefighters for Contributing Nothing to the Economy</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372855152602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 08:39:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, sounds like a description of "Liver Lips".</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372903757256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372904144690-42</Id><Topic><Title>btw, your guy Bush created PRISM and says it is necessary....</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1372882519995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 16:15:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spying on Americans has gone on as far back as I can remeber. They spied on me under LBJ and even tried a frame job. I'm sure if you studied some you would find it went on in Washington's time too. Ther are ALWAYS corrupt individuals that will use info gathered this way for blackmail. Don't hold Bushie out for an example. He and his dad were as bad as they get. Both lied about Iraq and the "WMD's". They lied about many other things too. Just like LBJ and the Tonkin Gulf Incident.. Oh, almost forgot the coverup of the U.S.S. Liberty attack too. Plus many other lies told by all of our pols.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1372904144690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372904262530-43</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle</Title><Username>slope661</Username><Timestamp>1372867432309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 12:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you!</Msg><Username>wall.street13</Username><Timestamp>1372904262530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 22:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>