<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369023727270-1</Id><Topic><Title>More Crock From Our Biggest Leftwing Goon</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1368996705347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish you'd been a slave.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369023727270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:22:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369023954084-2</Id><Title>More Crock From Our Biggest Leftwing Goonby passthebuckaroo ////////// I'm hurt I'm not your choice!</Title><Msg>You're just a simpleton skmmmmmmmy racist like most or all you repubs here. Isn't there just one decent repub here????</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369023954084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:25:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369024637588-3</Id><Title>My mom and dad were Southern Democrats. They switched when "Rosie The Red",,,says IDIOT, SIMPLETON LYING FOOL RACIST</Title><Msg>jkrOFF runners......No one knows who you refer to, I would speculate. Rosie the red????????/ You're a dddddbg. BTW, TALK about an over reaction! THAT would be the reaction to COMMUNISM! By people like you. You're a McCarthyism supporter I'm sure. He was a greta guy right runners? You fake.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369024637588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369024996359-4</Id><Title>It was better than what they had in Africa Signed runners,..there ya go again!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! You SICKO MUTHA!</Title><Msg>You FAKE regilious MORON! No religion should be proud to have YOU! YOU SUCK! Whata piece of stinking garbage you are runners! Hey runners, how about crosses in military cementaries?????? God you make me SICK! Runners is saying slavory..not so bad! No wonder people of color hate you. No wonder they hate some white people SOME white people go way beyond deserving to be hated,, that'd be runners! If they hate white people it;s because of runners! Yeah runners I know,,, some of your friends are black. NONE of my friends are like YOU runners.. You are stinking dabien!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369024996359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 00:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369027798618-5</Id><Title>and the Pope is responsible for it all,</Title><Msg>ANOTHER DROPkick by mesa!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369027798618</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 01:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369045647564-6</Id><Title>Only the biggest most stinking racist sk um bag would say slaves had better lives than they</Title><Msg>would have had in Africa. That'd be runners and many other racist repubs. The amazingly disgusting nerve to even think that.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369045647564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369046556289-7</Id><Title>Very bad seebe recently,,,</Title><Msg>He's made several untrue posts in past few days. Seebe would be perfect to work Mitch McConnel/</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046556289</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369046832055-8</Id><Title>McConnell: ‘There is a culture of intimidation throughout the administration’ WHATAPUNK!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Could that idiot be the number one most f' ed up repub at the moment? I'd say yeah.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046832055</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369046902574-9</Id><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Msg>DROPKICK YOU BUMS!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369049389458-10</Id><Title>Another example illustrating that dems are soooooo much better and honest than repubs is..............</Title><Msg>The poll showing majority want to know more about Benghazi and that majority feel repub reaction is justified, That of course means some dems agree it's serious. If situation were reversed NO WAY would repubs feel same way. More dems want honestly.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369049389458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 07:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369053526743-11</Id><Title>They There Head-Kicked! Enjoying Your Morning Spew...</Title><Msg>of Pigshyt, senseless drivel and countless lies?? Come on... give us another dozen puke posts!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1369053526743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369053857194-12</Id><Title>Obamacare will Make Workers Cheaper to Insure</Title><Msg>Will Obamacare Actually Make Workers Cheaper to Insure? By Meghan Foley May 20, 2013 . The math provided by PricewaterhouseCoopers showed what the employer-sponsored insurance will mean for employers and for employees once Obamacare is implemented. As the firm explained, compensating workers will enable businesses to save money when they provide a combination of salary and health insurance because of the federal tax exclusions. For example, if a company provides coverage to a worker earning $52,000 per year in 2014, it will save $2,550.87 because of tax deductions from the insurance. When workers obtain health insurance through their employer, their take-home pay is higher. A family with a combined income of $92,000 in 2014 that has employer-sponsored coverage earns $3,097.50 more in pay by taking advantage of the federal tax exclusion for the insurance.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369053857194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369057279588-13</Id><Topic><Title>t black on white crime is never a hate crime. Ever notice that?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006316967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'OUT OF CONTROL': AP Chief Calls on Obama to 'Rein In' DOJ Investigation and Intimidation</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369057279588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369057726942-14</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah!! and Reagan did trade weapons to our enemy... Iran...... as opposed to the gop bs blather about the bush era program fast and furious that was done by ATF cowboys in Arizona into the Obama admin who stopped it........</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369057726942</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058040376-15</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HughAkston 9:46 AM EDT "I'M OUTRAGED!!!" said President Obama.......before promoting and awarding 6-figure bonuses to the perpetrators.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369058040376</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 09:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369058793819-16</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>broken record, you are. Always looking at some guy from the past to justify or explain what is happening now. It's the only way you have to defend O as he cannot stand on his own merits.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369058793819</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369059379919-17</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you are just too dense and dishonest to get it that Reagan ACTUALLY, personally was involved in ILLEGAL gun trading to Iran............................ that is NOT the same as BS gop whining about a bush ATF program that continued into Obama's admin.... that he stopped, and that he never had a darn thing to do with... geez</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369059379919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369059495296-18</Id><Topic><Title>let's analyze priest pedophiles for race statistics, shall we seaburgc?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369007369278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:49:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the Pope is responsible for it all, right seeburgc????? no such thing as rogue employees as you say about the IRS.??????</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369059495296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060384935-19</Id><Topic><Title>let's analyze priest pedophiles for race statistics, shall we seaburgc?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369007369278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:49:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's right Mesa. There were no rogue IRS employees targeting the tea party. It came from the top...HQ that is. Here it is from the Washington Post. I doubt you will believe this piece. You;ll dismiss it outright? A story in the Washington Post yesterday about the Internal Revenue Service’s Cincinnati office, which does most of the agency’s nonprofit auditing, clearly contradicted earlier reports that the agency’s targeting of Tea Party groups was the result of rogue agents. The Post story anonymously quoted a staffer in Cincinnati as saying they only operate on directives from headquarters: As could be expected, the folks in the determinations unit on Main Street have had trouble concentrating this week. Number crunchers, whose work is nonpolitical, don’t necessarily enjoy the spotlight, especially when the media and the public assume they’re engaged in partisan villainy. “We’re not political,’’ said one determinations staffer in khakis as he left work late Tuesday afternoon. “We people on the local level are doing what we are supposed to do. . . . That’s why there are so many people here who are flustered. Everything comes from the top. We don’t have any authority to make those decisions without someone signing off on them. There has to be a directive.” The staff member, who spoke on the condition of anonymity for fear of losing his job,</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369060384935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060459549-20</Id><Topic><Title>let's analyze priest pedophiles for race statistics, shall we seaburgc?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369007369278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:49:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those Popes are gone. How about we get rid of the Bummer. Good deal for all Americans, all the world. #$%$ go home. Sharia law be gone.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369060459549</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:34:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060670320-21</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan dealt to propagate democracy in Nicaraugua. No more, no less. Another good deal to prevent the spread of socialism/communism in the Americas. Learn from history, Hilary doesn't.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369060670320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369060708636-22</Id><Title>Public school teachers the biggest pedophiles</Title><Msg>and then their unions make sure they are protected and get paid</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1369060708636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369060976497-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will Make Workers Cheaper to Insure</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369053857194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In her dreams. Newest ploy has companies buying the cheapest of all insurance policies, with no hospitalization offered with the policy. Most companies will find ways to legally opt out of Obummercare.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369060976497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061168750-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gaining in popularity (ha ha ha ha, loser pubs have egg on their face)</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368978442100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 11:47:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consider the source. Remember things, race, perception, and ignorance. All in abundance among American voters, especially among low information voters.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369061168750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061373240-25</Id><Topic><Title>Public school teachers the biggest pedophiles</Title><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1369060708636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:38:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this true. Libiots should be able to verify this fact.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369061373240</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369061570803-26</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama Administration’s Two-Front War on Fox By John Fund The Washington Post is reporting that the Justice Department took extraordinary steps to investigate Fox News reporter James Rosen for possible leaks of classified information about North Korea:”It used security badge access records to track the reporter’s comings and goings from the State Department, according to a newly obtained court affidavit. They traced the timing of his calls with a State Department security adviser suspected of sharing the classified report. They obtained a search warrant for the reporter’s personal e-mails.” Context is everything. The very same month Justice’s probe into Rosen’s story began, the Obama administration’s war on Fox News began. As NRO’s Eliana Johnson has reported: In June of 2009, the president complained about a “certain cable network” devoted entirely to attacking his administration. Four months later, former White House communications director Anita Dunn in 2009 said of Fox, “We’re going to treat them the way we would treat an opponent,” adding, “We don’t need to pretend that this is the way that legitimate news organizations behave.” The administration went on to try to exclude Fox from the network pool that covers the White House, making a recent appointee — pay czar Kenneth Feinberg — available for interviews to every network but Fox. When the other networks refused to conduct the interview until Fox was included, the White House relented. But the verbal assault continued, with Obama telling Rolling Stone magazine in 2010 that the network represents a point of view that is “ultimately destructive for the long-term growth of a country that has a vibrant middle class and is competitive in the world.” The public war that the Obama administration waged against Fox News was ugly enough. Perhaps with the Washington Post story we are now seeing the tip of the iceberg regarding the administration’s private war against Fox New</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369061570803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 10:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369064420016-27</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This government regardless of which tweedle dee or tweedle dum runs it has ALWAYS been peddling arms to whatever tin horn dictator is in favor at the moment. Like Ike warned; "look out for the military-industrial complex." Ever see the picture of Rumsfeld in Baghdad shaking hands with Saddam? I forget which drug company he worked for at the time but it is oretty well known that he delivered germ warfare components to Saddam. We also gave him chemical weapons some of which were at an ammo dump in So. Iraq that we destryed in Gulf War I bearing our ordnance markings. We put him in power in the first place.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369064420016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:40:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369065092516-28</Id><Topic><Title>mob violence: white teens attack and murder</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369003266047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:41:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gotta go back two years to find an example of your inane gibberish. What a bozo!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369065092516</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 11:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369066565101-29</Id><Title>Why are Dems too lazy to work and support their kids?</Title><Msg>Afronomics always fails. You can not redistribute brains and work ethics. Lower class dEms will always be on the bottom.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1369066565101</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369067039447-30</Id><Topic><Title>let's analyze priest pedophiles for race statistics, shall we seaburgc?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369007369278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:49:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weren't the priest pedophiles all white , conservative men?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369067039447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369067406476-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare will Make Workers Cheaper to Insure</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369053857194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 08:44:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>moron, that was the word Price Waterhouse and Coopers , why do you refer to them as "her"... that's your typical gop misogyny ....... really goes with your racism and religious bigotry....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369067406476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369067646635-32</Id><Title>How many IRS audits were conducted on</Title><Msg>Democrats when the corrupt Bush administration were in power?I know they outed a CIA operative,which was treasonous.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369067646635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369067772597-33</Id><Topic><Title>let's analyze priest pedophiles for race statistics, shall we seaburgc?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369007369278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:49:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stupid , liar seaburg.......as ususal your BS phony anonymous quotes.... referring to the "top" the top of what, the office car pool?............... and mr dishonest...... what do YOU mean by the TOP, ?Do you mean Obama, as in Obama phoned up a somebody in Cincinnati and whispered "let's get the teaparty"..... jeez.... what a scummy liar you and your ilk are...........where is your evidence you liar.... are you still a pedophile by the way, you know, according to a little birdie?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369067772597</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369068050155-34</Id><Topic><Title>How many IRS audits were conducted on</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369067646635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this bs "scandal" is such a gop weinie fest...... not a single tea party group was denied their tax exemption.....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369068050155</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369068143344-35</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan "didn't know" "didn't recall" hundreds of times and repubs LOVED IT!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369046902574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 06:48:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha,,,, Ronnie's excuse was brain damage, alzhiemers.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369068143344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369068693101-36</Id><Title>"Actually, Tea Party Groups Gave the IRS Lots of Good Reasons to Be Interested"</Title><Msg>"Actually, Tea Party Groups Gave the IRS Lots of Good Reasons to Be Interested" details almost make you forgive the profiling.....one aspect that sets off triggers: "Other tea party leaders with tax problems include: Michael Patrick Leahy, a management consultant who organized the National Tea Party Coalition, had $150,000 worth of IRS tax liens and court judgments to his name. Judson Phillips, the founder of the (for-profit) Tea Party Nation filed for bankruptcy in 1999, and had $22,000 in federal tax liens in his past. After Tea Party Nation planned a July 2010 tea party convention in Las Vegas and then canceled due to lack of interest, the organization stiffed the Venetian Hotel for more than 1,500 rooms it had reserved. That resulted in a judge ordering the organization to repay the hotel nearly $750,000. And then there was tea partier Christine O'Donnell, the Senate candidate from Delaware whose IRS tax lien for nearly $12,000 came to light during her 2010 campaign. Conservatives now say there was a partisan motive behind the IRS targeting of tea party groups. (An Inspector General's report released Tuesday did not find any evidence to that effect.) As evidence, they point to a lack of similar scrutiny directed at liberal groups. But it is also true that the tea party movement does not have an equivalent on the left; the Occupy Wall Street movement, perhaps the closest parallel, did not receive financial support on the scale that tea party organizations did, nor did it spawn legions of aspiring tax-exempt groups. When Occupy groups did seek out formal structure, they tended to use the traditional charitable 501(c)(3) status, which bars all political activity. The tea partiers, on the other hand, went for the c(4) designation for political non-profit organizations, helping make them the focus, as we now know, of IRS staffers."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369068693101</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369069445210-37</Id><Title>Voice of Tea Party speaks.What a</Title><Msg>genius this one is. The Fine Print As the chair of the Tea Party Caucus, Rep. Michele Bachmann (R – Minn.) is railing against the IRS’s targeting of Tea Party groups, saying: “clearly, this had political implications…that would benefit President Obama.” “Over and over and over, the common thread is the Obama administration was too willing to use the government to advance their agenda, their political agenda,” Bachmann tells The Fine Print. Bachmann says individuals in the Tea Party have been voicing concerns to her about getting “ridiculous questions” from the IRS for quite some time and asserts that other groups, in addition to the Tea Party, were also targeted. “The IRS couldn't do enough to part the waters to make sure that every progressive, left-wing leaning organization got their new tax-exempt status,” she says. “So they were able to get a favorable tax treatment, while Christians, pro Israel, conservative, Tea Partiers, pro-growth, pro-job, pro-business, they were hurt.” The congresswoman says the recent controversy highlights her broader concerns that the IRS may gain access to people’s medical information under the Affordable Care Act. “When people realize that their most personal, sensitive, intimate, private healthcare information is in the hands of the IRS that's been willing to use people's tax information against political opponents of this administration, then people have pause and they pull back in horror,” Bachmann says. The Obama administration has refuted the claim that the IRS will handle people’s medical records, but Bachmann is not convinced. The long-time critic of the president’s health care plan led a vote in the House last week calling for the repeal of the Affordable Care Act. “Well the ball is in Harry Reid's court now, because the House of Representatives has done its part,” Bachmann says of the measure that passed the House, but is not expected to gain traction in the Senate.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369069445210</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:04:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369069497986-38</Id><Topic><Title>"Actually, Tea Party Groups Gave the IRS Lots of Good Reasons to Be Interested"</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369068693101</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 12:51:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1369069497986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369070926380-39</Id><Title>“You think Susan Rice gave bogus talking points about Benghazi?</Title><Msg>“You think Susan Rice gave bogus talking points about Benghazi? What about the #$%$ [BS]talking points the entire Republican Party has been spewing on climate change since the ’90s? I wanna see the emails to find who came up with the talking points that global warming is just a theory, and that it needs more study, and that climate change is a hoax. The Obama administration isn’t dirty. The air is.” He concluded, “The air is dirty because Republicans are taking dirty (dark) money. Until people connect the dots, and demand that special interest money be removed from our politics, our planet will continue to die. The Obama scandals are a smokescreen to cover up the fact that Republicans would rather destroy the planet to enrich the few.” bill maher</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369070926380</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369071315595-40</Id><Title>97% of peer reviewed scientists agree that " climate change is caused by human activity"</Title><Msg>The most ambitious survey ever on the causes of climate change - covering 11,994 peer-reviewed academic papers by 29,000 scientists over 20 years - has found that 97.1% agree climate change is caused by human activity, with dissenters representing a "vanishingly small proportion." Yet there is a "gaping chasm" between the scientific consensus and public perception with just 42% of Americans seeing that connection, largely due to industry lobbying. "Surveys of climate scientists have found strong agreement (97–98%) regarding AGW amongst publishing climate experts (Doran and Zimmerman 2009, Anderegg et al 2010). Repeated surveys of scientists found that scientific agreement about AGW steadily increased from 1996 to 2009 (Bray 2010). This is reflected in the increasingly definitive statements issued by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change on the attribution of recent GW (Houghton et al 1996, 2001, Solomon et al 2007). The peer-reviewed scientific literature provides a ground-level assessment of the degree of consensus among publishing scientists. An analysis of abstracts published from 1993–2003 matching the search 'global climate change' found that none of 928 papers disagreed with the consensus position on AGW (Oreskes 2004). This is consistent with an analysis of citation networks that found a consensus on AGW forming in the early 1990s (Shwed and Bearman 2010). Despite these independent indicators of a scientific consensus, the perception of the US public is that the scientific community still disagrees over the fundamental cause of GW. From 1997 to 2007, public opinion polls have indicated around 60% of the US public believes there is significant disagreement among scientists about whether GW was happening (Nisbet and Myers 2007). Similarly, 57% of the US public either disagreed or were unaware that scientists agree that the earth is very likely warming due to human activity (Pew 2012). Through analysis of climate-related papers published from 1991 to</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369071315595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369071981219-41</Id><Title>Obama Regime Fascists Targeting Reporters Who Won't Bow &amp; Kiss Their Feet!</Title><Msg>PC Liberal trash, Ivy League trash especially, always make the best Fascists! After all, they invented it! Mussolini, a Socialist before a Fascist, was always enamored with the writings, decisions and acts of Woodrow Wilson.... and claimed he simply followed what Wilson had already done! Btw, the Liberal establishment loved Mussolini!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1369071981219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369077443240-42</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Regime Fascists Targeting Reporters Who Won't Bow &amp; Kiss Their Feet!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1369071981219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad twitty, the gop signed off on the AP thing. Nope, no scandal behind that curtain either. Senate Republican Leader Mitch McConnell of Kentucky said the government needs to stop leaks by whatever means necessary. "This is an investigation that needs to happen because national security leaks, of course, can get our agents overseas killed," he said.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369077443240</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369078421726-43</Id><Title>gop demands finger printing at airports</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — Foreigners leaving the country through any of the nation's 30 busiest airports would undergo mandatory fingerprinting under an amendment senators added Monday to a sweeping immigration bill. Lawmakers called it a step toward a more expansive biometric system that would use identifiers such as fingerprints to keep track of immigrants and visitors exiting the U.S. Currently no such system is in place, something viewed as a security weakness, particularly because some 40 percent of the 11 million immigrants in the country illegally overstayed their visas and there's no good system for tracking them. "This is an agreement that we need to build toward a biometric visa exit system," said Sen. Jeff Flake, R-Ariz., who offered the amendment by Sen. Orrin Hatch, R-Utah, who was absent Monday. "Implementing this biometric exit system is long overdue." A full-fledged biometric entry-exit system is favored by many senators but was deemed too expensive and unworkable to include in the bill. Current law already requires such a system to be in place, but the Department of Homeland Security has not implemented it. Instead the bill seeks electronic scanning of photo IDs.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369078421726</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 15:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369080720516-44</Id><Title>Good dropkicks phil and mesa</Title><Msg>repubs got nuthin..just their complete dishonesty and lack of self awareness!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369080720516</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:12:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369080816536-45</Id><Title>Sorry dropkick, but Fast &amp; Furious occured under Obama, not Bush. Once again, UR wrong on</Title><Msg>...the facts.</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1369080816536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369080936495-46</Id><Title>Prediction: all of these growing scandals will cause 3-5 real Obamaites to resign by Sept 1st, and will</Title><Msg>tank the second term. Booyah! Boink! Slam-dunk! Ouch! That hurts, lefties!</Msg><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1369080936495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369082791322-47</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction: all of these growing scandals will cause 3-5 real Obamaites to resign by Sept 1st, and will</Title><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1369080936495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:15:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First Lady: ‘I Could Take Up A Whole Afternoon Talking About’ Obama’s Failures May 20, 2013 1:31 PM</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369082791322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369083772546-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Regime Fascists Targeting Reporters Who Won't Bow &amp; Kiss Their Feet!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1369071981219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, Putz...I was talking about James Rosen, at FOX News!! In any event, with respect to the AP McConnell signed on to an "Investigation" not a wholesale RAID on the 1st Amendment, going after records of 100 reporters! What they did to Rosen was far more flagrant... which even Pigs, save for the Fascists, can't defend!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1369083772546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369083909089-49</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction: all of these growing scandals will cause 3-5 real Obamaites to resign by Sept 1st, and will</Title><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1369080936495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 16:15:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 53% PC Loser Shytheads of America seem to like him even more... the more he lies and trashes the Constitution!!</Msg><Username>itsthepress_stupid</Username><Timestamp>1369083909089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369083932739-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Regime Fascists Targeting Reporters Who Won't Bow &amp; Kiss Their Feet!</Title><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1369071981219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 13:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as ususal, you bums would have whined if nothing was done about the AP loose lips leaks, and you whine when steps are taken to stop the leaks of national security info that could cost lives....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369083932739</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369084233200-51</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush’s Watch Without a Peep from Fox News</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368735218412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep 13 benghazis and the pubs then were fat and happy on vacation and reading "my pet goat" or whatever, not a peep from them, just a stream of "we are turning the corner" bs..... 13 fricken benghazis on W's watch.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369084233200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369084316353-52</Id><Topic><Title>gop "irs" ""scandal"" FIZZLES out as wet BS just like their other trumped up "scandals"</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1368896614405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-18 13:03:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loser pubs should go back to their birther drivel..... ha ha ha</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369084316353</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 17:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369091279827-53</Id><Title>I've gotta say.the tornados are even worse than repubs. Finally something is.</Title><Msg>I sure hope somehow the loss of life is little but it doesn't seem likely</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369091279827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369091493944-54</Id><Title>tornados have always been the most scary thing...next to republinism</Title><Msg>I lived in Ohio in early 70's storms,,, that was NUTHIN compared to this. Nothing was nothing compared to this.climate change??????</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369091493944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369091620098-55</Id><Title>GOP Lieutenant Governor Candidate in Va. Compares Planned Parenthood to KKK</Title><Msg>.and just when I think storms are worse than repubs////////////</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369091620098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369093290202-56</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Lieutenant Governor Candidate in Va. Compares Planned Parenthood to KKK</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369091620098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kinda cool. Reminds me of when the left often referred to Bush as Hitler, Turnabout is fair play.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369093290202</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369097973901-57</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Lieutenant Governor Candidate in Va. Compares Planned Parenthood to KKK</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369091620098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee... I thought they were more akin to the Khmer Rouge!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1369097973901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 20:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369101996773-58</Id><Topic><Title>More Crock From Our Biggest Leftwing Goon</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1368996705347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 16:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares?</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1369101996773</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369102033023-59</Id><Topic><Title>seebe,, just tell the black mobs that slavery wan't so bad!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369003494584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 18:44:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do tell us about your extensive experience with Africa. Know nothing big mouth.</Msg><Username>hotdoggitwiggie</Username><Timestamp>1369102033023</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369102949814-60</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Lieutenant Governor Candidate in Va. Compares Planned Parenthood to KKK</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369091620098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The scandals of the Obama administration seem to be hurting not just the White House but MSNBC as well while Fox News Channel scored its second-best week of the year. After double-digit gains during last year’s presidential election, May 13-17 saw the progressive-aligned “Lean Forward” news network hit new lows as the IRS scandal erupted and revelations that the Justice Department secretly obtained AP records became public. With 350,000 viewers on average and 94,000 among the adults 25-54 demo, MSNBC had its least-watched and lowest-rated total-day results of the year last week. That was also the lowest total-day demo result the network has had since the week of June 26-July 2, 2006, when MSNBC pulled in just 83,000 viewers among adults 25-54, according to Nielsen data.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369102949814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 22:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369106024945-61</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Lieutenant Governor Candidate in Va. Compares Planned Parenthood to KKK</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369091620098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 19:13:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you anti-Black? He's Black you know. He says planned parenthood has murdered over 30 million black babies. Gee, maybe YOU are a Que Kluxer. Well, the worshipers of Moloch and Baal have a come uppance very soon. It'll be fun to watch.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369106024945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369106651324-62</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush’s Watch Without a Peep from Fox News</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368735218412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The difference being that this admin. had time to send in armed forces and stop the killings. Everything else youi cite happened spontaneously without any warning and no time to react before the damage was done. Always nice to see apples and oranges compared by shills for this criminal gang running this country.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369106651324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369108254439-63</Id><Title>Are you anti-Black?</Title><Msg>I'm anti-------a wwwhole!........I'm anti-you for that same reason.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369108254439</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369108744333-64</Id><Title>Subway.........bad........</Title><Msg>Researchers from the University of California Los Angeles found that despite claims to the contrary, Subway is just as unhealthy as the oft-reviled golden arches of McDonald’s—which long had the most locations in the country of any fast-food chain until Subway surpassed it in 2011. ======================== FINALLY in the headlines. I've waited years for this. It's garbage except for spme of the vegs. The meats and other things come from factories.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369108744333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>