<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366457454980-1</Id><Title>why NOT read him his rights? They don't have a good enough case? I thought we have "the best system in the world"?</Title><Msg>In recent past it appears too many people don't think it's good enough/</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366457454980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:30:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366460271681-2</Id><Title>USA USA USA, they chanted.....I sure can understand their relief..I'm relieved. But//////////////////////</Title><Msg>If we saw a similar scene from another country where they'd just ended a several day bloody period of time where terrorists had done what these guys did,,, we'd possibly laugh and scratch our heads and say....those people are quite a bit worse off than they were a week prior yet they're acting as though they just won 100 gold medals in the Olympics. Is there really much to be happy about? Horrible week noting good to say about it. Hardly would I consider it a victory.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366460271681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366460870300-3</Id><Topic><Title>why NOT read him his rights? They don't have a good enough case? I thought we have "the best system in the world"?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366457454980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>* Authorities found multiple assembled pipe bombs in the brothers’ Cambridge apartment, where investigators planned to carry out a “controlled explosion” to make the residence safe to enter. They also found other explosives linked to the brothers elsewhere, including unexploded pipe bombs along the chase route. * It emerged that the FBI had interviewed Tamerlan about his “extremist views,” but then closed the case. Tamerlan was interviewed by the FBI in 2009 after authorities in Russia said he was a “radical,” according to sources. When G-men asked Tamerlan whether he was a radical, he replied “no,” a source said. * Their father, Anzor, was interviewed by the FBI in 2001 for taking pictures of the Manhattan skyline after the 9/11 attacks. * Their mother, Zubeidat, speaking from their native Russia, said, “My sons would never do this. It is a set-up” — and bizarrely claimed that Tamerlan “was controlled by the FBI . . . for three to five years.” * The brothers’ uncle Ruslan Tsarni, speaking on TV, called both the men “losers” of whom he was “ashamed,” and urged, “Dzhokhar, if you are alive, turn yourself in and ask for forgiveness.” Tsarni said the brothers struggled to adjust to American life during their decade living here, but ended up “just hating everyone.” * Authorities searched the West New York, NJ, apartment of one of the suspects’ sisters.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1366460870300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366461712385-4</Id><Topic><Title>Christie proposes measures to curb gun violence</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366428802389</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 23:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now that the bombing terrorists are behind us it's time to turn our attention to "pressure cooker" control. Mandatory background checks on anybody wanting to buy one, any that can hold more than 10 nailes or BB's are outlawed, and if you own one you have to register it. If we can save "just one life" it's something we have to do!!</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1366461712385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366462071059-5</Id><Topic><Title>why NOT read him his rights? They don't have a good enough case? I thought we have "the best system in the world"?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366457454980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still waiting for an apology from Obama, CNN, MSNBC and the other media outlets that are part of his ministry of propaganda for spending the past 3 days pointing fingers at the Tea Party and right wingers... and of course, being wrong again! One would think that it would get embarassing being made such fools of all the time!</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1366462071059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366462082747-6</Id><Topic><Title>why NOT read him his rights? They don't have a good enough case? I thought we have "the best system in the world"?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366457454980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A person wonders if this could have been prevented if Obama and Napolitano had been spending billions on tracking islamic fundamentalists instead of veterans, pro-lifers and teapartiers. These guys were sharing fundamentalists videos and making comments along that line which could have been tracked. Unfortunately, I believe Napolitano spends more time tracking people who like Ron Paul and Constitutionalists on Facebook and flying drones over the Midwest tracking rednecks then tracking the real criminals! But of course, thats part of the plan when you are trying to fundamentally change America isn't it?</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1366462082747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366462091303-7</Id><Title>can a non citizen own guns legally? You think thats a good idea?</Title><Msg>I look forward to this discussion</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366462091303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366462125703-8</Id><Topic><Title>how many libs in the Boston area....</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1366406220467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:17:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs would rather hide under their beds with a copy of strict gun laws to show the gun welding intruder he is breaking the law. Being stone stupid will save you every time. And what would you do you brain dead teabilly besides #$%$ your panties?</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1366462125703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366462194138-9</Id><Title>turn our attention to "pressure cooker" control db, they had GUNS,,how'd they get them? Should they have had them?</Title><Msg>NRA supports the rights of gun ownership for terrorists.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366462194138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366462293979-10</Id><Title>so right. Libs will do all they can to avoid the obvious connection. Yes, there is a connection but it's less of one</Title><Msg>than the connection between repubs and all our problems.+</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366462293979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366462621222-11</Id><Title>how many libs in the Boston area.....wish they had guns..................not many</Title><Msg>Go ahead, tell me where having guns in this case would have helped. Seriously. The cops that got shot/killed had guns,, the cops that chased them had guns etc.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366462621222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:57:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366468069180-12</Id><Title>crazy rightwinger who went on a murder spree to kill all libs (because his foodstamps were cut)</Title><Msg>Knoxville Unitarian Universalist church shooting liberals ruined he USA he raved, so he must KILL the, he also cited cuts to his food stamps as a reason ...... "Adkisson's rant also cited .......that his food stamps were being cut." “ During the interview Adkisson stated that he had targeted the church because of its liberal teachings and his belief that all liberals should be killed because they were ruining the country, and that he felt that the Democrats had tied his country's hands in the war on terror and they had ruined every institution in America with the aid of major media outlets......................</Msg><Username>thrustonhowl3rd</Username><Timestamp>1366468069180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468188440-13</Id><Topic><Title>how many libs in the Boston area.....wish they had guns..................not many</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366462621222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a fool.. and a complete fraud! Compende Bagboy! In the name of PC Trash Pigshyt, you try and dissuade, discourage and shame others from having the same weapons you have... solely for self-defense! When responsible sane people are faced with "kill or be killed", they all wish they had guns and knew how to use them... and that includes everyone of the teachers at Sandy Hook! Moreover, they would have wanted as large a magazine as reasonably possible... and several of them! The cops that got shot likely never had the chance to use their guns... the MIT officer was probably shot in the back, as is typical practice of Islamic Whack-job #$%$!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1366468188440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366469355435-14</Id><Title>After The Fact</Title><Msg>Now their doing background checks on these mad bombers and getting a profile that hints of problems. Does the INS check to see if immigrants applying for entry to the US have any criminal history in their own countries. What are we doing welcoming the radical arm of Izlam from several countries without as much as a raised eyebrow. Fools will pay.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366469355435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366470956951-15</Id><Topic><Title>After The Fact</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366469355435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:49:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All bush's fault...and yours.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366470956951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366471262003-16</Id><Title>you try and dissuade, discourage and shame others from having the same weapons you have,, signed fat-soh corpiss</Title><Msg>THEY DON'T WANT GUNS!@ They've a different mindset than we have. I don't quite understand it either. It;s YOU wanting to change them! My old friends in NJ,,.repub ones are as against guns as the dems. Saw Salmon Rusdie on tv last night. He said England offered him weapons and training back then,, he declined. I would not have had I been him. Of course he's a much thinner target than you corpiss,, hahahahha...dropkick.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366471262003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471367548-17</Id><Topic><Title>crazy rightwinger who went on a murder spree to kill all libs (because his foodstamps were cut)</Title><Username>thrustonhowl3rd</Username><Timestamp>1366468069180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:27:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know of a guy on federal assistyance and he calls obama a socialist and he complains he's not given enough and he's a fat repub.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366471367548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366471445448-18</Id><Title>come on repubs,,,should a non-citozen like the dead terrorist legally own guns?</Title><Msg>NRA says yes!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366471445448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471953272-19</Id><Topic><Title>come on repubs,,,should a non-citozen like the dead terrorist legally own guns?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366471445448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:24:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know you repubs are AFRAID to state how you feel about this!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366471953272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472574410-20</Id><Topic><Title>you try and dissuade, discourage and shame others from having the same weapons you have,, signed fat-soh corpiss</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366471262003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:21:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw corps,..as long as someone is totally responsible for that gun..up to MY standards,,, I support them having it. I don't see that too often.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366472574410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366475338375-21</Id><Title>Terrorist Plague</Title><Msg>I don't see any difference between a home grown terrorist or the acts of an anti-American foreign cult. These brothers had to be part of a larger conspiracy. They may have been just the drop off guys. FBI will check each part of the bomb fragments for fingerprints to determine if it was the two or that more were involved. I may be wrong but it seems unlikely that the two suspects had knowledge of putting together a bomb that would do that much damage.</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1366475338375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366475561587-22</Id><Topic><Title>how many libs in the Boston area.....wish they had guns..................not many</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366462621222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If early Bostonians had felt the same way good old King George would have robbed them of all they had. The same type thing is going on now. The country is in the hands of a gang of thieves that want to merge us into their world empire. They've been working on it for a long time. They know most will resist so they've hyped the anti-gun propaganda. There has to be a Hell for the likes of them or their is no justice in this universe.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366475561587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366475916065-23</Id><Topic><Title>Terrorist Plague</Title><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1366475338375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many places to get info on IED's and other weapons. There are explosives that can be made from common materials, i.e. black powder. Old time safe crackers would cook their own nitro. Dangerous but they did it. As in so many of these terrorist acts there are many unanswered questions. I suggest to all they do some reading on COINTELPRO. This was the FBI operation in the South during the 60's. Much of the crimes committed then had ties to this operation.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366475916065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366479610229-24</Id><Title>Terrorist Plague WHERE???????????????</Title><Msg>Ya think this is that huge of a deal? Think we need anothr "patriot" act? start another bgroup war?/You all always say it,..that's what happens in a free society..............this is nothing compared to how many people die from guns a year. Leave it to repubs to blow this outa proportion.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366479610229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366479686405-25</Id><Title>nra repubs should no citizens have guns?</Title><Msg>Afraid to answer aren't ya? Either yes or no from you and I'll dropkick ya!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366479686405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366485585470-26</Id><Title>domestic christian terror groups have done dozens of USA bombings and terror shootings.</Title><Msg>wsup with religion making people crazy enough to bomb and shoot innocent people? Christian terrorism From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia The goals of the KKK included, from an early time on, an intent to "reestablish Protestant Christian values in America by any means possible," and believe that "Jesus was the first Klansman."[66] Their cross-burnings were conducted not only to intimidate targets, but to demonstrate their respect and reverence for Jesus Christ, and the lighting ritual was steeped in Christian symbolism, including the saying of prayers and singing of Christian hymns.[67] Many modern Klan organizations, such as the Knights Party, USA, continue to focus on the Christian supremacist message, asserting that there is a "war" on to destroy "western Christian civilization." During the twentieth century, members of extremist groups such as the Army of God began executing attacks against abortion clinics and doctors across the United States.[.] A number of terrorist attacks were attributed to individuals and groups with ties to the Christian Identity and Christian Patriot movements, including the Lambs of Christ.[71] A group called Concerned Christians were deported from Israel on suspicion of planning to attack holy sites in Jerusalem at the end of 1999, believing that their deaths would "lead them to heaven."[72][73] The motive for anti-abortionist Scott Roeder murdering Wichita doctor George Tiller on May 31, 2009 was a belief that abortion is criminal and immoral, and that this belief went "hand in hand" with his religious beliefs.[74][75] The Centennial Olympic Park bombing in 1996, as well as subsequent attacks on an abortion clinic and a lesbian nightclub, were made by Eric Robert Rudolph; Hutaree was a Christian militia group based in Adrian, Michigan. In 2010, after an FBI agent infiltrated the group, nine of its members were indicted by a federal grand jury in Detroit on charges of seditious conspiracy to use of ieds, The Covenant, The Swo</Msg><Username>thrustonhowl3rd</Username><Timestamp>1366485585470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366487797760-27</Id><Title>Repubs don't want to prevent anyone from buying guns, hundreds of thousands of people are prevented from gun buying</Title><Msg>nra repubs,,,,,,,,,,,,,,, should non citizens have guns?.Afraid to answer aren't ya? Either yes or no from you and I'll dropkick ya! You believe the dead terrorist should have been legal to buy guns here?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366487797760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:56:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366488766906-28</Id><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.</Title><Msg>There is something unholy indeed about this demonic manifestation called: dropkick.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366488766906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366488974474-29</Id><Topic><Title>how many libs in the Boston area.....wish they had guns..................not many</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366462621222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dropkick, you fool. If one of those bombers had decided to take a hostage, the city of boston was an easy target. If nobody had guns then he could have easily broke into a house and took a hostage instead of hiding in a boat you GD fool. Shove Obama up your #$%$! Freak! Oh, and #$%$, it looks like your fool Obama exported the Saudi paymaster!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366488974474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366489186157-30</Id><Title>dropkick needs a psycological eval, Just look at this GD board!</Title><Msg>He claims he has or had a firearm in his possession. I believe the FBI should pay him a visit.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366489186157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:19:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366489274310-31</Id><Topic><Title>dropkick needs a psycological eval, Just look at this GD board!</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366489186157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:19:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops, that's psychological, I know.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366489274310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366489479504-32</Id><Title>Obama is a MURDERER! Illegal War Criminal ... HE IS #$%$!</Title><Msg>Obama democrats are all war criminals and are guilty of supporting obamas ethnic cleansing campaigns in the middle-east.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366489479504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494002119-33</Id><Topic><Title>how many libs in the Boston area.....wish they had guns..................not many</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366462621222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trump: 'Is the Boston Killer Eligible for Obama Care to Bring Him Back to Health?'</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1366494002119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366496059376-34</Id><Title>Boston Marathon bombing moves from solidarity to partisan politics</Title><Msg>,,,,,,,,,,,and GUESS which party is to blame!............REPUBS! Ya know what repubs want? They want NOITHING but tax cuts and people to sing patriotic NOTHING songs. They have no SUBSTANCE.. No DEPTH.. NO GRAVITAS! They're SHALLOW uncaring #$%$ beings.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366496059376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366496482768-35</Id><Title>Trump: 'Is the Boston Killer Eligible for Obama Care to Bring Him Back to Health?'</Title><Msg>Y athink it makes you look smart to post quotes from R eeeeeee trds? You've sunk to huge lows and for you to do that.that's SOMETHING!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366496482768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366497075951-36</Id><Topic><Title>Trump: 'Is the Boston Killer Eligible for Obama Care to Bring Him Back to Health?'</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366496482768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:21:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something else........we're all PAYIN for this terrorist to get care in a hospital and that's the case LONG before now. Repubs.YA GOT NUTHIN! As we're all payin for bgroup multi tril $'s of unnecessary war and the medicare trillions drug benefit bgroup pushed through along with reagUN tripleling debt and bgroup doubling it,,REPUBUBS GOT NUTHIN! EVER!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366497075951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366497201993-37</Id><Title>dropkick needs a psycological eval, Just look at this GD board!. Where you been db? Pretty funny and f UUUUUUUU</Title><Msg>I do what I want not what you repubs want....and when will carl give his take on Boston? Carl supports terror right? ?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366497201993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366497279834-38</Id><Title>Obama democrats are all war criminals and are guilty Signed carl.I guess that means carl is pro chechen terrorists</Title><Msg>RIGHT?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366497279834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366497356546-39</Id><Title>Obama democrats are all war criminals//bgroup repubs aren't also???</Title><Msg>come on carl you can do better than that! I missed ya db fatter-soh.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366497356546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366498086784-40</Id><Title>Where did the Boston terrorists get their guns? If they got them legally or not..repubs have MUCH explainin to do!</Title><Msg>DROPKICK! Finally people other than ME are asking... Good luck with that repubs.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366498086784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:48:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366499151564-41</Id><Topic><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366488766906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a hypocrite. A quick search on your posting history shows you post politics and not about ORCL. You and your gang should go find a proper politics discussion board instead of posting your political spamola here. Now GET LOST!</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1366499151564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366499675157-42</Id><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.. You stinking lying db! You've said that for years!</Title><Msg>Ypu're a funny f c kkk errrrrrrrrr</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366499675157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366499712489-43</Id><Topic><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.. You stinking lying db! You've said that for years!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366499675157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:14:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So,.how long will it take you to spew fire and brimstone? I bet.NOT LONG!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366499712489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366499800484-44</Id><Title>A quick search on your posting history shows..Oh boy carl.you've been quick searched.AGAIN!</Title><Msg>Time to spew fire and brim! You funny f k her.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366499800484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:16:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366501721091-45</Id><Title>Crazy terrorists who went on a murder spree to kill Libs in Boston.</Title><Msg>They complained they didn't understand Americans, well, hello, we aren't all libs.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366501721091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366508681904-46</Id><Topic><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.. You stinking lying db! You've said that for years!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366499675157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:14:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How long are you going to keep expressing your total lack of intellect? How long are you going to keep up your boring Obama slobber? How long are you going to support a murderer? You are not a funny fkr ... You are a Stupid FKR. dropkick!!!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366508681904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366508821190-47</Id><Topic><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366488766906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey, stupid, if the fed was not bailing out the stock market your GD orcl would be in the garbage can. You should not be in stocks, You are too GD stupid.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366508821190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366509024153-48</Id><Title>To: You gay and stupid quick search ... #$%$.</Title><Msg>Quick Search that!!!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366509024153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366509369873-49</Id><Topic><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366488766906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go suck one of your favorite politicians #$%$ you #$%$ of the earth</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1366509369873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366509371300-50</Id><Topic><Title>A quick search on your posting history shows..Oh boy carl.you've been quick searched.AGAIN!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366499800484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:16:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better use of metaphors and hyperbole then your illiterate Obama slobber! I like drama ... I have a brain and a personality. Unlike you Obama Drones ... total Dead Beats.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366509371300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366509472301-51</Id><Topic><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366488766906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know better then to like or trust politicians. I hate them all, they all lie.</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366509472301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366509668533-52</Id><Title>I put a curse on this board, a curse named dropkick.</Title><Msg>all of you fools are stuck with it, forever!</Msg><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366509668533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366509774648-53</Id><Topic><Title>I quit this stupid board, but I return and dropkick has desecrated it.</Title><Username>peterthegreat533</Username><Timestamp>1366488766906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't get it... I don't give #$%$ what you think about politicians... go take your drivel to a message board dedicated to the topic you want to discuss you shiathead.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1366509774648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366516689264-54</Id><Title>Safety rules limited for small fertilizer plants::: YEAH repubs,..lets have LESS govt regulations! Govt. stands in the way of business!</Title><Msg>Safety rules limited for small fertilizer plantsThere were no sprinklers. No firewalls. No water deluge systems. Safety inspections were rare at the fertilizer company in West, Texas, that exploded and -------------------------------- Five times as many peple killed in Tx. as Boston bacause republican owners of business didn't care.,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366516689264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>