<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371614511854-1</Id><Title>Keep swallowing the BS. sIGNED RUNNER</Title><Msg>RUNNER was HUGE supporter of nixon and Viet Nam,..he believed all that and wanted to attack anti war people who didn't fall for the garbage like runner did DROPKICK! He still thinks Jane Fonda was more to blame than nixon. Nice dropkick pauper!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371614511854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 00:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371640495675-2</Id><Title>seebe and repubs...........IRS repub 2nd one of them says tea baggers NOT singled out</Title><Msg>Snooping amd spying stopped 50 attacks!!!!!!! YA GOT NUTHIN! Oh.and Daryl Isaa.HUGE piece of corpiss dabien.dropkick 'em pauper!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371640495675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 07:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371645834546-3</Id><Title>White house petition wants Obama to ban creationism, intelligent design in schools</Title><Msg>just do it. Creationism is not science........ all the stuff about zeus, allah, chupecabra, yaweh, and the great watanka can be taught in a class on myth and comparative religion, perhaps, but don't pretend to push this nonsense as science.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371645834546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:43:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371646435782-4</Id><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Msg>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud . "Rep. Elijah Cummings, the top Democrat on the House Government Oversight Committee, delivers on his promise to call committee Chairman Darrell Issa's bluff: Democrats on the House Oversight Committee have just released a full transcript of testimony from a key witness in the investigation of IRS targeting of conservatives — and it appears to confirm that the initial targeting did originate with a low-level employee in the Cincinnati office. It also shows a key witness and IRS screening manager – a self described conservative Republican — denying any communication with the White House or senior IRS officials about the targeting. So now we know why Government Oversight Committee Chairman Darrell Issa didn't want to to release the full transcripts—they show everything he's been saying is bunk. You can read the transcripts here and here. "</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371646460400-5</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Rep. Cummings absolutely destroyed Issa’s conspiratorial claims that Obama was masterminding the IRS scandal: This interview transcript provides a detailed first-hand account of how these practices first originated, and it debunks conspiracy theories about how the IRS first started reviewing these cases. Answering questions from Committee staff for more than five hours, this official—who identified himself as a “conservative Republican”—denied that he or anyone on his team was directed by the White House to take these actions or that they were politically motivated. Instead, the Screening Group Manager explained that the very first case at issue in this investigation was initially flagged by one of his own screeners in February 2010. He told us he agreed that this case should be elevated to IRS employees in Washington because it was a “high profile” application in which the organization indicated that it would be engaging in political activity. He explained that he initiated the first effort to gather similar cases in order to ensure their consistent treatment, and that he took this action on his own, without any direction from his superiors, and without any political motivation. He also confirmed that one of his screeners developed terms subsequently identified by the Inspector General as “inappropriate,” such as “Patriot” and “9/12 project,” but that he did not become aware that his screener was using these terms until more than a year later."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646460400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371646528865-6</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"These statements from the Screening Group Manager directly contradict several serious and unsubstantiated accusations made by you and several other Republican Committee Chairmen over the past month. For example: • On May 14, 2013, you stated: “This was the targeting of the president’s political enemies effectively and lies about it during the election year, so that it wasn’t discovered until afterwards.” • On June 3, 2013, House Appropriations Committee Chairman Hal Rogers stated: “Of course, the enemies list out of the White House that IRS was engaged in shutting down or trying to shut down the conservative political viewpoint across the country—an enemies list that rivals that of another president some time ago.” • On June 12, 2013, Ways and Means Committee Chairman Dave Camp stated: “We know it didn’t originate in Cincinnati.” …. These facts are a far cry from accusations of a conspiracy orchestrated by the White House to target the President’s political enemies. At this point in the investigation, not one witness who has appeared before the Committee has identified any involvement by any White House officials in the identification or screening of Tea Party applicants for tax exempt status, and the Committee has obtained no documents indicating any such involvement."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646528865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371649578415-7</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Karzai furious with US over Taliban move, withdraws from talks... Taliban kills 4 US soldiers in rocket attack on base on same day Obama announces direct talks...</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1371649578415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 09:46:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371649859867-8</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Berlin Speech: 200,000 for Obama in 2008; Only 6,000 Today 9:18 AM, Jun 19, 2013 • By DANIEL HALPER Send to Kindle Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts The White House pool report reveals that only 6,000 will be in attendance for Obama's Berlin speech today: The stage for the president's speech is set up on the East side of the Brandenburg Gate, in the old East Berlin. The sun is pounding down and there are around 6,000 invited guests according to German authorities. There are bleachers set up either side of the square, with a big two storey riser facing the stage which has a row of bullet proof glass and 12 US, German and EU flags and the grand backdrop of the Gate. There is a large standing crowd between the bleachers. Last time around, when Obama delivered a speech in Berlin in the 2008 presidential campaign, when he was still a senator, 200,000 folks came out to see him. As the New York Times reports: The last time President Obama paid a visit here, as a candidate in 2008, he was cheered on by 200,000 Germans eager to see the back of George W. Bush and, as one member of that crowd recalled Tuesday, “full of wholly unrealistic expectations of what kind of miracles Obama could work.” When he arrived here on Tuesday evening ahead of a full day of talks — capped by a speech at the Brandenburg Gate — the reception was far more restrained. Almost five years later, Germans have undergone “a brutal sobering up” with regard to Mr. Obama, said Ralf #$%$, who heads the board of the Heinrich Böll Foundation, a nonprofit political organization in Berlin. It is, he said, as overdone as the euphoria of 2008, but also a bit alarming.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371649859867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 09:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371650698728-9</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SEQUESTER JESTERS: IRS to pay $70 MILLION in employee bonuses...</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1371650698728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 10:04:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371655457804-10</Id><Topic><Title>This is Rich</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371600063063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 20:01:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good enough for a sequel. Bump.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371655457804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 11:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371659828984-11</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitten's wanted more of this..... he was going to increase the military budget over it's already bloated fat cat astronomical amount: The Pentagon's Biggest Overrun: Way Too Many Generals The three- and four-star ranks have increased twice as fast as one- and two-star general and flag officers, three times as fast as the increase in all officers and almost ten times as fast as the increase in enlisted personnel. If you imagine it visually, the shape of U.S. military personnel has shifted from looking like a pyramid to beginning to look more like a skyscraper (i.e. higher ranks having fewer lower ranking personnel under them rather than more).... On average, there are now approximately 185 fewer enlisted personnel per general in the Air Force and 400 fewer enlisted per admiral in the Navy than there were just ten years ago. Similarly, there are more than 40 fewer officers per general or flag officer in both the Air Force and Navy today than there were in 2001.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371659828984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 12:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371662036060-12</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Matthews: Berlin Sun ‘Ruined’ Obama’s Speech By Andrew Johnson June 19, 2013 10:25 AM Comments 737 MSNBC host and Obama sycophant Chris Matthews blamed the sun for spoiling the president’s speech in Berlin today. “I think a lot of the problem he had today was the late afternoon sun in Berlin ruined his use of the teleprompter and so his usual dramatic windup was ruined,” Matthews said immediately after the speech. “I think he was really struggling with the text there.” Speaking behind a glass bulletproof shield, Obama appeared to be using the text of the speech rather than reading off of teleprompters.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371662036060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:13:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371663692719-13</Id><Topic><Title>doesn't anyone know about this?</Title><Username>breatesr</Username><Timestamp>1371531038007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 00:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks man im signing up</Msg><Username>coolerinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1371663692719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371663952928-14</Id><Topic><Title>what traders dont know!</Title><Username>rogerblack750</Username><Timestamp>1369796530470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks man im signing up</Msg><Username>coolerinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1371663952928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371665414789-15</Id><Topic><Title>White house petition wants Obama to ban creationism, intelligent design in schools</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371645834546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever do the mathematical numbers for even the smallest living thing to come into existence by chance? It's not that hard but doubt you're capable of it. As scripture says;"The fool hath said in his heart there is no God." That's the problem with the world now. It's run by fools and Satanists.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371665414789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 14:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371665714667-16</Id><Topic><Title>Keep swallowing the BS. sIGNED RUNNER</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371614511854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 00:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong again idiot. My friends and I opposed the war but we didn't think a gang of commies should be running loose in the streets flying Viet Cong flags and calling for their victory while they were killing our friends and relatives. I didn't support Bushie in either Iraq or Afghanistan but if some creeps were out in the streets calling for their victory I'd go after them today just as I did the creeps in the sixties.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371665714667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 14:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371666231781-17</Id><Topic><Title>White house petition wants Obama to ban creationism, intelligent design in schools</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371645834546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Ever do the mathematical numbers " for a super being to pop into existence and THEN go about creating bacteria and mosquitos and children with cancer?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371666231781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 14:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371666596126-18</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bush kept an aircraft carrier going in circles for days waiting until he could be flown in tail-hook style to brag "Mission Accomplished"...................Chris Matthews on MSNBC called Bush a "hero" and boomed, "He won the war. He was an effective commander. Everybody recognizes that, I believe, except a few critics." He added: "Women like a guy who's president. Check it out. The women like this war. I think we like having a hero as our president. It's simple."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371666596126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 14:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371668210108-19</Id><Topic><Title>NSA: 'Over 50' Terror Plots Foiled by Data Dragnets</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371580428392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-18 14:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You idiot, most of those foiled plots were by other countries who had a much better track record in profiling suspects. And speaking of preventable, how many did Clinton prevent? He didn't have the guts. He was more concerned about his oval office escapades than tracking and snooping on Al Queda. It was Bush who had to send out special ops to kill or capture Al Queda commanders. Facts don't lie, you gullible goon.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371668210108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 14:56:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371669717946-20</Id><Topic><Title>White house petition wants Obama to ban creationism, intelligent design in schools</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371645834546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama offends Catholics in the UK, says religious schools are divisive June 19, 2013 by Cheryl Carpenter Klimek 78 Comments The Catholic media is up in arms over comments President Obama made during a speech while in Northern Ireland for the G8 summit. Obama made what is described as “an alarming call for an end to Catholic education,” in spite of the fact that it is considered “a critical component of the Church.” In front of an audience of about 2,000 young people, including many Catholics, Obama claimed that Catholic education divides people and blocks peace, according to the Scottish Catholic Observer. “If towns remain divided—if Catholics have their schools and buildings and Protestants have theirs, if we can’t see ourselves in one another and fear or resentment are allowed to harden—that too encourages division and discourages cooperation,” Obama said.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1371669717946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 15:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371672625375-21</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's honeymoon with world over... Berlin Speech: 200,000 in 2008; Only 4,500 Today... Germans have undergone 'brutal sobering up'... Matthews: Sun 'Ruined' Speech Because Couldn't Use Teleprompter... Merkel lectures: Internet monitoring must have proper limits... Newspaper Removes 'Democrat' From Name...</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1371672625375</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 16:10:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371672642289-22</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's Turbulent European Vacation With vague pledges and backtalk from Merkel and Putin, the president shows how far America's standing with Europe has fallen. By Michael Hirsh June 19, 2013 | 3:40 p.m. President Obama delivers a speech in front of Brandenburg Gate, unseen, in Berlin Wednesday. (AP Photo/Michael Sohn) President Obama's honeymoon with the world is over. What was it, exactly, about Obama's controversy-marred trip to Germany and the G8 Summit in Northern Ireland that fell so flat? Ummm, how about … everything? There were the snarky words from Vladimir Putin, who expressed an almost Soviet-esque distance from Washington in his views about Syria. "Of course our opinions do not coincide," the Russian leader said bluntly. There was the coded warning from Chancellor Angela Merkel about spying on friends, and her and Obama's continuing frostiness over the issue of economic stimulus versus austerity. Above all, there was Obama's vague attempt at the Brandenburg Gate to capture some wisp of his past glory by pledging vague plans to cut nuclear arms and an even vaguer concept of "peace with justice." The "peace with justice" line was a quote from John F. Kennedy, Obama's attempt to steal just a little of JFK's thunder from 50 years before. He didn't come away with much, winning just a smattering of applause from a crowd that was one one-hundredth the size of JFK's. A crowd that, at about 4,500, was also much, much smaller than Obama drew as a candidate in 2008. Not only is the honeymoon long over, folks. The marriage is becoming deeply troubled and, increasingly, loveless.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371672642289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 16:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371673676608-23</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George and Laura Bush made 7 trips to Africa on the taxpayer' dime . Cost of Obama’s Trip is Dwarfed By George And Laura Bush’s Africa Spending Spree As conservatives rage about the cost of Obama’s Africa trip, it is important to remember that George and Laura Bush made a combined 7 trips to Africa all on the taxpayers’ dime. We’ve played this game before, but anytime the nation’s first black president spends more than a dollar, the right wing freaks out about Barack Obama “wasting taxpayer dollars.” Back in 2011, the right claimed that First Lady Obama’s Africa trip would cost taxpayers millions, but even if you use numbers that the White House disagrees with ($424,000), they weren’t even close. This time the right has whipped up the fake outrage over a leaked document showing that President Obama’s upcoming Africa trip could cost $60-$100 million. What these same people don’t tell is that George and Laura Bush loved to go to Africa on the taxpayers’ dime…a lot. During Bush’s second term alone, Laura Bush made five “goodwill” trips to Africa. President Bush made the trip twice during his presidency. Here is former First Lady Bush at an event the night before their trip in 2008, “Tomorrow, President Bush and I leave for what will be my fifth trip to Africa since 2001, and his second trip to Africa since 2001. I’ve seen the determination of the people across Africa — and the compassion of the people of the United States of America.” Wow, that’s a lot of trips to Africa. In 2007, Laura Bush also took her daughters with her, and they went on a safari. You know, the same kind of outing that President Obama just canceled. Not much was going right for George W. Bush. Even before the economy crashed, his legacy was 9/11, the unpopular Iraq invasion, and Hurricane Katrina. Back in 2003, Bush laid the groundwork for making aid to Africa his legacy. One of the areas where Bush drew praise was that he spent</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371673676608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 16:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371674030953-24</Id><Topic><Title>White house petition wants Obama to ban creationism, intelligent design in schools</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371645834546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Catholics in the UK.... ha ha ha ha....jeez... who cares..... Henry the 8th told the pope to kiss his #$%$..ha hah....jeez you are a whiny brat.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371674030953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 16:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371674787566-25</Id><Topic><Title>White house petition wants Obama to ban creationism, intelligent design in schools</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371645834546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Democrats Love To Spy On Americans Besides Senators Ron Wyden and Mark Udall, most Democrats abandoned their civil liberty positions during the age of Obama. With a new leak investigation looming, the Democrat leadership are now being forced to confront all the secrets they’ve tried to hide. posted on June 7, 2013 at 12:10pm EDT Michael Hastings BuzzFeed Staff Share Tweet Email NEW React with an animated GIF! React Image by Jeff Chiu / AP For most bigwig Democrats in Washington, D.C., the last 48 hours has delivered news of the worst kind — a flood of new information that has washed away any lingering doubts about where President Obama and his party stand on civil liberties, full stop. Glenn Greenwald’s exposure of the NSA’s massive domestic spy program has revealed the entire caste of current Democratic leaders as a gang of civil liberty opportunists, whose true passion, it seems, was in trolling George W. Bush for eight years on matters of national security. “Everyone should just calm down,” Senator Harry Reid said yesterday, inhaling slowly. That’s right: don’t panic. The very topic of Democratic two-facedness on civil liberties is one of the most important issues that Greenwald has covered. Many of those Dems — including the sitting President Barack Obama, Senator Carl Levin, and Sec. State John Kerry — have now become the stewards and enhancers of programs that appear to dwarf any of the spying scandals that broke during the Bush years, the very same scandals they used as wedge issues to win elections in the Congressional elections 2006 and the presidential primary of 2007-2008. Recall what Senator Levin told CNN in 2005, demanding to “urgently hold an inquiry” into what was supposedly President Bush’s domestic wiretap program.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371674787566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 16:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371676445353-26</Id><Topic><Title>White house petition wants Obama to ban creationism, intelligent design in schools</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371645834546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheney supports NSA wire-tapping.....mittens is all for it too. same as nearly the entire gop! They were even for doing it without warrants in the Bush administration and fox and friends thought it was the bee's knees!</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371676445353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371676838815-27</Id><Title>why hasn't Snowden denounced China's aggressive surveillance, hacking &amp; espionage programs?</Title><Msg>Snowden the traitor is a big wienie huh? ".... communiist Party officials do not want to make a big deal out of Snowden, lest it encourage debate about the government's own aggressive domestic programs. ......"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371676838815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371677193918-28</Id><Topic><Title>why hasn't Snowden denounced China's aggressive surveillance, hacking &amp; espionage programs?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371676838815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:20:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey snowden: "there are some two million Chinese spies working with the communist state’s security apparatus".... will you please whine about how unethical that is to them while you are there?......... "but many attacks originating in China are believed to come from special cyber units belonging to the Chinese military. A recent report by Mandiant, a northern Virginia cybersecurity firm, identified a Chinese military detachment known as Unit 61398 as one of the “most prolific” hacking groups in the world. The military link suggests China considers economic dominance a matter of national defense, raising the stakes for any western firms it targets..................... there are some two million Chinese spies working with the communist state’s security apparatus. The regime has countless agencies engaged in intelligence gathering, including the Ministry of State Security; various military intelligence agencies; multiple industrial, political, and economic espionage departments; and more. Hiding behind “diplomatic immunity” and using blackmail, bribery, special privileges, strategic “business” partnerships, cyber attacks, and a wide array of other methods, China’s spies have been extremely successful in their efforts.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371677193918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371677444701-29</Id><Title>The BIG LIE!! NSA "Foiled" Dozens of Terrorist Attacks!</Title><Msg>And naturally it comes from the Obama pumping American trash... who spew Pigshyt 24/7! The words used by Alexander about NSA's involvement were that its surveillance "led to disrupting or contributing to the disruption" of terrorist attacks! NOT FOILED! Never foiled! And even then.... the key words were "led to" and "contributing to"! NSA "Foiled" Jackshyt! NY Daily News... "He (Alexander) described the steps the government takes once it suspects a terrorist organization is about to act - all within the laws approved by Congress and under stringent oversight from the courts. He said the programs led to "disrupting or contributing to the disruption of terrorist attacks," but he did not give details on the terror plots."</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371677444701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371678299159-30</Id><Topic><Title>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371646435782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 08:53:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IRS scandal, another GOP fraud "Another week, another leak from Chairman Issa of cherry-picked excerpts that show no White House involvement whatsoever in the identification and screening of these cases," Cummings said in a statement. "By leaking transcript portions that omit key details from the accounts witnesses provided to the Committee, Chairman Issa has now drawn condemnation even from House Republicans working with him on this very investigation."</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1371678299159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371679930308-31</Id><Title>Alan West may offer primary challenge...</Title><Msg>to Marco Rubio. Wouldn't that be interesting? I salivate over that possibility.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371679930308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 18:12:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371683629627-32</Id><Title>repubs ya got nuthin and you know it.</Title><Msg>dropkickj</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371683629627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 19:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371684067765-33</Id><Title>Alan West may offer primary challenge...</Title><Msg>Ya getten a BONair over that? I've no idea why. Seebe ya got nuthin goin on.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371684067765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 19:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371684274328-34</Id><Title>corpisbigdumbfatppphck</Title><Msg>You believed EVERYTING from bgroup!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371684274328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 19:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371687708684-35</Id><Topic><Title>corpisbigdumbfatppphck</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371684274328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 19:24:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt... as usual!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371687708684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371688659497-36</Id><Title>Fox Contest for a Nickname for Obama</Title><Msg>They called Nixon, "tricky #$%$". Barak-a-crock was one someone sent in. Let's hear some from the gallery here. I thought of Obomber for his drone program.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371688659497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 20:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371690006350-37</Id><Topic><Title>Alan West may offer primary challenge...</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371684067765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 19:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep believing Big Bubba. He always tells the truth. Coming out now that flight 800 WAS shot down as anyone that read eye witness acounts said all along. A military pilot said he saw an exhaust trail from a rocket go up from the sound there and hit the plane. Oh no, says Big Bubba, you don't know what you saw. It was the other way around and was fuel spilled from the plane. Interesting list of passengers on that flight too. I'll go into that some other time. ALWAYS believe Big Bubba. He might sic the IRS or some other gang of slugs on you if you don't.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371690006350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 21:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371690339686-38</Id><Topic><Title>The BIG LIE!! NSA "Foiled" Dozens of Terrorist Attacks!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371677444701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 17:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know that two of the alledged 9'/11 plotters lived for a while in San Diego with an Islamic Imam. He was a fink for the FBI. I'm sure they didn't confide in him. After it came out that he was a fink he had to go into hiding in fear of his life. These government finks do all they can to entrap you. I knew two of them years ago. They were lucky someone didn't take them for a one way ride.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371690339686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 21:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371699960368-39</Id><Title>corpiss believed everything bgriup said esepcially about taaaarrrerism but now,not so much from obama.why</Title><Msg>is that?/////////////////////it's because corpiss is NOTHING but a stinking lying republican,,, that's all any repub is,,,stinking and lying....</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371699960368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 23:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371700109974-40</Id><Title>Keep believing Big Bubba. He always tells the truth says runner</Title><Msg>Like you believed nixon about Viet Nam...........you're so stupid you blamed and still blame Jane Fonda,,,Jane Fonda not the cause of ANY suffering in Viet Nam.YOU and Nixon are,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371700109974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 23:48:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371700311026-41</Id><Title>jeez you are a whiny brat.</Title><Msg>You said it. The repubs these days (and for about 35 years) are the worst ever.. Wrong and partisan about every single thing..</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371700311026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 23:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371700538624-42</Id><Title>They were lucky someone didn't take them for a one way ride. Says runners..</Title><Msg>WHAT an annoying storytelling loon weirdo runners is. In this post of his I think he's basically being critical of a "govt. fink" as he was trying to "fink" on 9/11 terrorists. YOU'RE one of the biggest dch bags ever runner..you're nothing but a lousy repub.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371700538624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 23:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371700662716-43</Id><Title>Fox Contest for a Nickname for Obama says assbukeroo</Title><Msg>Ya mean,..the organization that calls itself fair and balanced??? That fox??? You repubs are 100% skuuuuuuuuuuuuuu, of earth.DROPKICK pauper!@</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371700662716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 23:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>