<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370517561931-1</Id><Topic><Title>A republican says it, he hates democracy, and doesn't want black people to vote unless they vote his way</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370442829001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's NSA collecting phone records of millions daily... Secret court order requires VERIZON to hand over 'telephony metadata'... DHS: Laptops, phones can be searched based on hunches... FBI 'WANTS BACK DOOR TO ALL SOFTWARE'...</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1370517561931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370518494698-2</Id><Title>Oracle refuses to comment if it is in talks to buy VM Ware</Title><Msg>rumor says it is</Msg><Username>roxettewish</Username><Timestamp>1370518494698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370522299796-3</Id><Title>Obamacare cut even more costs</Title><Msg>.. New healthcare model cut even more costs in year two: insurer . By Sharon Begley NEW YORK (Reuters) - The nation's largest experiment in delivering medical care in an innovative way has reduced costs and improved the quality of care even more in its second year than in its first, according to the insurance company behind it. The nonprofit CareFirst BlueCross BlueShield launched its "Patient-Centered Medical Home" program in January 2011 among primary-care providers serving about one-third of its 3.4 million members in Maryland, Washington, D.C., and northern Virginia. Like other "accountable care organizations" (ACOs), which are centerpieces of President Barack Obama's healthcare reform, the medical home program ties insurance payments to healthcare providers to the quality of care they deliver.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370522299796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370523170358-4</Id><Title>You need to start your research on IOGA right away!</Title><Msg>IOGA looks pretty good at these levels. I bet after IOGA breaks resistance it will start to soar</Msg><Username>chanlevi481</Username><Timestamp>1370523170358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370523877289-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare cut even more costs</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370522299796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 08:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1370523877289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:04:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370525701394-6</Id><Title>2% Growth Rate Worst recovery since WWII!</Title><Msg>OH THANK, MR. PRESIDENT, OBAMA, SIR!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1370525701394</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370525875035-7</Id><Title>Top 20% Are Getting Richer! Because Federal Reserve is Pumping Stock Market!</Title><Msg>WORST RECOVERY IN HISTORY OF COUNTRY!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1370525875035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370526098512-8</Id><Title>Bush appointee Bernanke doing a good job.</Title><Msg>Bush: : "Unless money is loosened up the sucker could go down"</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526098512</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370526175094-9</Id><Title>Taylor Swifts Dancers Wave Red Commie Flags at CMT Awards!</Title><Msg>S H O C K I N G!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1370526175094</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370526563645-10</Id><Title>growth rate is getting hit by the gop austerity, GOP was hot to cut spending which will cut growth</Title><Msg>everyone knows how the gop causes a problem, and then they whine about it. The gop lying hypocrites can't have it both ways.... cut spending, which cuts jobs and cuts growth and then whine about job losses and the lower growth they caused.....jeez..... they are so slimy and such creeps...</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526563645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370526838833-11</Id><Title>gop, you were informed that your austerity would cut US growth in 2013 by HALF</Title><Msg>gop pumps austerity, and then whines about the effects , but they were told US growth would be cut in half to 1.5% in 2013..........as usual the lying gop wants hard times to whine about..and so they CREATE the hard times...... Sequester to halve U.S. 2013 growth: CBO Growth would be 1.5 percentage points higher absent tightening WASHINGTON (MarketWatch) — Fiscal tightening including the automatic budget cuts known as the sequester would cut U.S. growth in half in 2013 if allowed to go into effect, the Congressional Budget Office said Tuesday in a new budget and economic outlook.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526838833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370526929168-12</Id><Topic><Title>REAL torture is having to hear Obama talk at press conferences, interviews, etc.</Title><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1370442104741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 10:21:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cincinnati IRS Employee: I Was ‘Essentially a Front Person’ for Washington Wednesday, 05 Jun 2013 11:34 PM By Paul Scicchitano Carter Hull, an IRS Attorney in Washington, D.C. closely oversaw the agency’s scrutiny of tea party groups and other conservative organizations in an apparent contradiction of top agency officials, who insisted that low-level employees in Cincinnati were to blame for the now widening scandal. The Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday that Elizabeth Hofacre of the Cincinnati office told congressional investigators that she had limited autonomy to act on her own when it came to questioning conservative organizations. "I was essentially a front person, because I had no autonomy or no authority to act on [applications] without Carter Hull's influence or input," she said in transcripts of her interview, according to the Journal.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1370526929168</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370527683846-13</Id><Topic><Title>Romneycare Mittens said he woud take care of the pre-existing condition problem</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370466499005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-05 17:08:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pubs can't fix a problem.... they just whine, lie, and obstruct...... Obamacare fixed the preexisting condition problem. starting in 2014 insurers can't dump people for bs like that, and as Ca shows, they are doing that and the premium prices are reasonable.......... and who can forget that W didn't get bin laden..... he charged off into a costly and useless quagmire in Iraq........ Obama got bin laden and did it the way it should have been done in the first place... no invasions and no occupations......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370527683846</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370527943567-14</Id><Title>Obama fixes problems, the gop creates them</Title><Msg>......pubs can't fix a problem.... they just whine, lie, and obstruct...... Obamacare fixed the preexisting condition problem. .., and as Ca shows, they are doing that and the premium prices are reasonable.... ...... and who can forget that W didn't get bin laden..... he charged off into a costly and useless quagmire in Iraq........ Obama got bin laden and did it the way it should have been done in the first place... no invasions and no occupations and btw, regarding the pre-existing condition problem: Romneycare Mittens said he woud take care of the pre-existing condition problem . But Mittens was just lying: "Pre-existing conditions are covered under my plan." In the biggest whopper of the night, Romney suggested that his health care proposal would guarantee coverage to Americans with pre-existing conditions. This is just not true. Under Romney, if you have a pre-existing condition and have been unable to obtain insurance coverage or if you have had to drop coverage for more than 90 days because you lost your job or couldn't afford the premiums, you would be s..h..i...........t out of luck. Insurance companies could continue to discriminate and deny you coverage, as even Romney's top adviser conceded after the debate was over</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370527943567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370528920653-15</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle refuses to comment if it is in talks to buy VM Ware</Title><Username>roxettewish</Username><Timestamp>1370518494698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:34:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what rumor... the one you made up all by yourself?</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1370528920653</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370529209636-16</Id><Title>Sell off</Title><Msg>Going down on VMware talk or profit taking..newbie here</Msg><Username>babbizfriends</Username><Timestamp>1370529209636</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370529379206-17</Id><Topic><Title>growth rate is getting hit by the gop austerity, GOP was hot to cut spending which will cut growth</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526563645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, someone had to do something. The Dems only answer is to tax and spend. The fed budget can no longer handle this mentality. Cuts must originate somewhere. There are not enough current or future tax dollars alone to control our deficit or our budget.</Msg><Username>zing21042</Username><Timestamp>1370529379206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370529588156-18</Id><Topic><Title>growth rate is getting hit by the gop austerity, GOP was hot to cut spending which will cut growth</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526563645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mainstream Media Fail to Break Even One of Four Obama Scandals 710 0 95 Email Article Print Article Send a Tip by John Nolte 6 Jun 2013, 6:10 AM PDT 34 post a comment Well, if it is Thursday there must be a new Obama scandal. But one thing is for damn sure, whatever that scandal is, you can bet the American mainstream media will be playing catch up and not carrying the glory of breaking a story about a major White House scandal. Fact: Over the past few weeks, four major scandals have broken over the Obama administration, and it is a very sad (and frightening) truth that our pathetic, American, lapdog mainstream media is not responsible for breaking even a single one. Verizon? Nope, not our guys. That was the Brits over at The Guardian. IRS? Nope, not our guys. The IRS broke their own scandal with a planted question. The Justice Department's seizure of Associated Press phone records? Nope, not our guys. Believe it or not, the Associated Press didn’t even break that story. Like the IRS, we only found out because the Justice Department outted itself in a letter notifying the AP of what it had done. Benghazi? Are you kidding. With a couple of rare exceptions (Jake Tapper, Sharyl Attkisson) the media has spent the last 8 months attacking those seeking the truth (Congress, Fox News) not seeking the truth. It was the GOP congress that demanded the email exchanges around the shaping of the talking points, not the media.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1370529588156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370529781983-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama fixes problems, the gop creates them</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370527943567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"have to go to Kmart, definitely Kmart, get underwear, underwear, Kmart, Kmart"</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370529781983</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370529987172-20</Id><Title>Breaking News!The same analyst cut VMW from Hold to Sell and VMW is up $3.5 now.Check it out&amp;ORCL should go up now according</Title><Msg>to More than one analyst which are very bullish on orcl</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370529987172</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370530224535-21</Id><Topic><Title>growth rate is getting hit by the gop austerity, GOP was hot to cut spending which will cut growth</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526563645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What rubbish!! We saw how the stimulus created jobs and growth without cuts. Now we need to spend more to bail out the WH for insane policies? How is it possible to get dumber than buckwheat?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370530224535</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370530788688-22</Id><Topic><Title>what traders dont know!</Title><Username>rogerblack750</Username><Timestamp>1369796530470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i really like this site</Msg><Username>millionairestock</Username><Timestamp>1370530788688</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370530797914-23</Id><Title>Hey ORCL traders !Relax !the same analyst downgraded VMW to SELL and VMW is up +++$3.57 now and orcl should go up 1.5 now</Title><Msg>Iam telling you</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370530797914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370530877000-24</Id><Topic><Title>growth rate is getting hit by the gop austerity, GOP was hot to cut spending which will cut growth</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526563645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the maggots are turning on each other.... Democrats criticize NSA phone tracking By GINGER GIBSON and BURGESS EVERETT | 6/6/13 10:41 AM EDT Democratic lawmakers sounded off Thursday morning in the wake of a report that the Obama administration secretly obtained records for Verizon phone calls made in the United States. Senate Majority Whip #$%$ Durbin said he has been briefed on some of the information generally previously and “of course” he is troubled by it. “We’ve been unable to speak to it because it is classified,” Durbin said. Durbin said he hopes there will future votes examining the reach of government. “To say that every American’s records of phone conversations are now open to government scrutiny really goes to beyond that standard,” Durbin said. “This type of secret bulk data collection is an outrageous breach of Americans’ privacy. I have had significant concerns about the intelligence community over-collecting information about Americans’ telephone calls, emails, and other records,” Sen. Jeff Merkley (D-Ore.) said in a statement. Sen. Mark Udall (D-Colo.) said the report “concerns me." “The administration I think owes it to the American public to comment on what authorities it thinks it has and I’ll leave it there,” he told reporters Thursday.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1370530877000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370531203426-25</Id><Title>Bogus Downgrade Today</Title><Msg>Looks like Berenberg is loading up prior to earnings release. Never heard of Berenberg - surprised they could move it this much. Loading up by writing Jun 35 puts today.</Msg><Username>livermore923</Username><Timestamp>1370531203426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370531898476-26</Id><Title>Do some DD on IOGA. Looks ready to run.</Title><Msg>I am getting all the IOGA I can at these levels. Check their website and financials. This thing is so undervalued here.</Msg><Username>oliverkeith568</Username><Timestamp>1370531898476</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532106204-27</Id><Title>Last update: 6/6/2013 9:33:17 AM VMware Cut to Sell From Hold by Berenberg VMW &amp; is up $4 now.The same analyst downgraded ORCL</Title><Msg>Why ORCL is down?</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370532106204</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532257248-28</Id><Title>Judith Miller: Obama criminalizing news-gathering</Title><Msg>Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative journalist Judith Miller shared some sharp criticisms against the Obama administration’s “criminalization of news gathering” and the state of journalism at a Jerusalem Press Club lecture in the capital Wednesday evening. “Investigative reporting is dangerous and hasn’t been as bad as it is now with the Obama administratio since Watergate,” she said. “Obama has the worst record of civil liberties of any president since Nixon.” “Am I worried about what is going on in America?” she asked. “Yes. We have a president who is doing terrible things in the name of ‘national security.’” A member of The New York Times team that won a Pulitzer Prize for “explanatory reporting,” Miller, now a Fox News correspondent, may be most notable for her refusal to reveal her sources during the Valerie Plame Affair, when the identity of CIA operative Valerie Plame was exposed, compromising national security. “I have particular fury over what happened to James Rosen,” she said. “The Espionage Act has been used six times by Obama – he has used this act to criminalize reporting more than any other president in history and [he] gets away with it because he is a Democrat and African-American, which we’re proud of.” She also criticized the Justice Department’s handling of WikiLeaks publisher Julian Assange. The department accused Assange of aiding Osama Bin Laden in planning future attacks against the United States by releasing classified information. PS: The Obama Admin has accused people under the Espionage Act more that ALL the other Presidents since it was passed during the Woodrow Wilson era.</Msg><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370532257248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370532326746-29</Id><Topic><Title>Last update: 6/6/2013 9:33:17 AM VMware Cut to Sell From Hold by Berenberg VMW &amp; is up $4 now.The same analyst downgraded ORCL</Title><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370532106204</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:21:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right, didn't seem to work for VMW but is working for ORCL. Naturally, no reason was given. Buy to sell move is bogus. MMs driving down ORCL so that they can load up prior to earnings.</Msg><Username>livermore923</Username><Timestamp>1370532326746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532391139-30</Id><Title>Hey! What happened to my cute Avatar?</Title><Msg>Yahoo eneded use of cute Avatars.</Msg><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370532391139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370532393903-31</Id><Topic><Title>Bogus Downgrade Today</Title><Username>livermore923</Username><Timestamp>1370531203426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:06:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure signal to load up. Berenberg trying to be like GS?</Msg><Username>livermore923</Username><Timestamp>1370532393903</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532470681-32</Id><Title>Tire Sales down by 56%. Oil changes down 75%.</Title><Msg>People aren't driving anywhere. No job. No money. No place to go.</Msg><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370532470681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532525181-33</Id><Title>Hot News!Canaccord Genuity upgraded Oracle (NASDAQ: ORCL) from Hold to Buy with a price target of $42.00 (from $35.00).</Title><Msg>Canaccord Genuity upgraded Oracle (NASDAQ: ORCL) from Hold to Buy with a price target of $42.00 (from $35.00). Analyst Richard Davis said the firm is set up well to gain 20% this year. He expects Oracle deliver 9 to 11 percent EPS growth this year and thinks its multiple relative to peers IBM (NYSE: IBM) and SAP AG (NYSE: SAP) can expand given its current 10 to 25 percent discount valuation.</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370532525181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:28:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532672747-34</Id><Title>There ought to be a law</Title><Msg>There needs to be FULL disclosure of positions by banks that issue market calls like Berenberg did today. They go from BUY to SELL with a target to $28? What a farce!! What changed anyway to turn their opinion on a dime? Would anybody out there trust your money to this firm?</Msg><Username>livermore923</Username><Timestamp>1370532672747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370532677096-35</Id><Title>NYC Pension Plan protests 16 of 19 WalMart Directors of Board!</Title><Msg>NYC Council &amp; Unions will not allow WalMart into NYC but NYC Pension Plans own 1% of Walmart Stock. Making NYCs Unio9nized Public Employees rich!</Msg><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370532677096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:31:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370532766704-36</Id><Topic><Title>Tire Sales down by 56%. Oil changes down 75%.</Title><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370532470681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Must be the reason for the downgrade today, eh?</Msg><Username>livermore923</Username><Timestamp>1370532766704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370533440455-37</Id><Topic><Title>There ought to be a law</Title><Username>livermore923</Username><Timestamp>1370532672747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree however, ORCL has been pretty skittish since last earnings call and unfortunately clowns like this berenberg makes things worst</Msg><Username>mkoumaris</Username><Timestamp>1370533440455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370533972992-38</Id><Topic><Title>gop proves what lame whiny losers and blatherers they are, all talk, nothing but hot air.</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370269092953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 10:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you've NEVER been right about ANYTHING yet ....................................... wrong Phil. I am right about you. You're always so high on yourself.I wish that I could buy you for what you're worth and sell you for what you think you're worth,damn I'd make quite a profit.You're really just another rightwing IDIOT.Where's Mittens?You said he'd beat Obama,what happened Einstein?</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1370533972992</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370534092484-39</Id><Title>BMO Capital upgraded Oracle (NASDAQ: ORCL) from Market Perform to Outperform with a price target of $43.00 (from $36.00).</Title><Msg>BMO Capital upgraded Oracle (NASDAQ: ORCL) from Market Perform to Outperform with a price target of $43.00 (from $36.00).</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370534092484</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370534213368-40</Id><Topic><Title>Top 20% Are Getting Richer! Because Federal Reserve is Pumping Stock Market!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1370525875035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WORST RECOVERY IN HISTORY OF COUNTRY!</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1370534213368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370534236803-41</Id><Topic><Title>Tire Sales down by 56%. Oil changes down 75%.</Title><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370532470681</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People aren't driving anywhere. No job. No money. No place to go. It's a shame that you can't see just how silly you are,but apparently you haven't a clue.How old are you boy?</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1370534236803</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370534325869-42</Id><Topic><Title>gop proves what lame whiny losers and blatherers they are, all talk, nothing but hot air.</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370269092953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 10:18:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one is going to impeach Obama as long as Harry Reid, and anti-American, Democrat, is Senate Majority Leader.</Msg><Username>balongnieponey</Username><Timestamp>1370534325869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370534635989-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama fixes problems, the gop creates them</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370527943567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mesa... you are a complete fraud, phony and fool! Laughable! LOL!!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1370534635989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370535778685-44</Id><Topic><Title>Judith Miller: Obama criminalizing news-gathering</Title><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370532257248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:24:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Miller, now a Fox News correspondent, That clearly explains things right there.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1370535778685</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370535971190-45</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle refuses to comment if it is in talks to buy VM Ware</Title><Username>roxettewish</Username><Timestamp>1370518494698</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 07:34:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Market cap of VMW is too high for ORCL to take it over. Financials don't justify it and it would be very diluting to their performance metrics.</Msg><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1370535971190</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:26:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370536043321-46</Id><Topic><Title>growth rate is getting hit by the gop austerity, GOP was hot to cut spending which will cut growth</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526563645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big government spies on it's citizens, spies on the press, uses government agencies to attack political enemies. The founders of our nation would be shooting by now. And what country can preserve its liberties, if its rulers are not warned from time to time, that this people preserve the spirit of resistance? Let them take arms. The remedy is to set them right as to the facts, pardon and pacify them. What signify a few lives lost in a century or two? The tree of liberty must be refreshed from time to time, with the blood of patriots and tyrants. It is its natural manure." Thomas Jefferson</Msg><Username>infactidoknowitall</Username><Timestamp>1370536043321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370536262571-47</Id><Title>No, There Are No Intelligent Liberals in the House</Title><Msg>Ahh Phyllis, you never have a thoughtful counterpoint, you can't refute the truth, boy, just attack the messenger. Typical leftwing reply. You should post more often, I love the sound of squealing liberals.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370536262571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370538830167-48</Id><Topic><Title>growth rate is getting hit by the gop austerity, GOP was hot to cut spending which will cut growth</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526563645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Officials Mislead Lawmakers on Mass Collection of Phone Records? Report National Security Agency is collecting phone records of millions of US Verizon customers could contradict top officials who said the agency does not 'hold data on US citizens.'</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1370538830167</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370538964799-49</Id><Topic><Title>growth rate is getting hit by the gop austerity, GOP was hot to cut spending which will cut growth</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370526563645</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 09:49:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>last time schmucks like you took up arms Uncle Billy marched 3 columns , 20,000 men each, through the south and burned the rebellion to the ground................try to not forget, you stupid sob, that we live in a democracy, and not under a king George and the redcoats forced even to tithe to the church of England, no separation of church and state until Jefferson and others ended that despicable union.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370538964799</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370539228279-50</Id><Title>gop economic miracle in Wisconsin..... (making things worse is the gop's style)</Title><Msg>Scott Walker/Koch bros. "economic miracle" . Source: Milwaukee-Wisconsin Journal Sentinal In the latest economic indicator that casts Wisconsin in a negative light, the Badger state ranks 49th in the nation in the most recent index from the Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia. "Wisconsin clearly is not leading the recovery," said William Delwiche, an economist in Milwaukee at Robert W. Baird &amp; Co. The Philadelphia Fed data is from its monthly state-by-state index of leading economic growth indicators, and is meant to predict how the state's economy will grow in the next six months. The 50-state Leading Index report for April showed only five states with contraction, assigning Wisconsin an index rank of -0.74%. Wyoming, with a rank of -1.29%, is the only state with a lower index</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370539228279</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:20:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370539633270-51</Id><Title>Scott Walker kills growth in in Wi. Only 5 states are not making economic gains, all 5 are red states,btw</Title><Msg>The bad news keeps coming for Governor Scott Walker (R-WI), who ran as a conservative who was going to save the state and create 250,000 jobs. Instead, he’s thrown the state into what’s looking now like a long term economic contraction. In the latest numbers from the Philadelphia Fed, which is a monthly state-by-state index of leading economic growth indicators, Wisconsin ranks 49th in the nation. Out of the 50 states, only five are in contraction. Alaska, Louisiana, North Dakota, Wisconsin, and Wyoming are all projected to decrease growth, with Wisconsin second to last with an index of -.74%. These numbers shouldn’t be a huge shock, as Republican governors are associated with lower rates of growth, while state spending has a positive impact on growth. The other forty-five state indexes are projected to grow over the next six months. For comparison purposes, the Philadelphia Fed projects the US coincident index to grow 1.4 percent over the next six months.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370539633270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370539821572-52</Id><Title>Texas has most new jobs.</Title><Msg>Good job Republicans. Dems are still living in ghettos. Dems fail with Republican and Democratic leadership. They fail with every system.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1370539821572</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370539999735-53</Id><Title>GS analyst just upgraded ORCL to conviction buy from Buy and raised it price target to 45 dollars from 39</Title><Msg>orcl will cont to gain market share and execute real well</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370539999735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370540182349-54</Id><Title>Democrats still live in ghettos and Rs are stil making money. Dems lose again.</Title><Msg>Dems fail with every system. The only successful Dems are the handful of Dems who are capitalists and act like Republicans.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1370540182349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370541416982-55</Id><Topic><Title>Scott Walker kills growth in in Wi. Only 5 states are not making economic gains, all 5 are red states,btw</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370539633270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:27:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wrong way gop leads the race to the bottom.....jeez..... Out of the 50 states, only five are in contraction. Alaska, Louisiana, North Dakota, Wisconsin, and Wyoming are all projected to decrease growth, with Wisconsin second to last with an index of -.74%.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370541416982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370541724567-56</Id><Topic><Title>Scott Walker kills growth in in Wi. Only 5 states are not making economic gains, all 5 are red states,btw</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370539633270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:27:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The list is deceiving in that when states are so bad for so long eventually they recover. The five states have a common thread of coal and oil production. They were so good for so long that now you must consider they will slow some. And WI had a big industry of selling fracking sand to ND. Does not mean they will be real bad but that the growth is slowing. They are commodity states and commodities have cooled over past few months.</Msg><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1370541724567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370541798776-57</Id><Title>only 5 states are not growing their economy, red states..... Scott walker sure was full of shizer</Title><Msg>Walker has created a NEGATIVE growth rate in his state........ topped only by the larger NEGATVE growth in Wyoming...... and 3 other gop political correct hot air states are also NEGATIVE in growth.....what a SCANDAL, what a LIAR scott walker is.....he promised jobs and growth, but delivered economic losses, a ....</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370541798776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370542039494-58</Id><Title>ORCL (What do all the posts on this board have to do with ORCL)</Title><Msg>All you guys should post on some political boards and leave ORCL to ORCL news</Msg><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1370542039494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370542062225-59</Id><Title>Scott Walker delivers a negative growth rate for WI &amp; big tax cuts for cronies and corporations</Title><Msg>Governor Walker then lavished tax breaks on his friends, the corporations and wealthy who funded his election. What better way to pay them back for all their campaign contributions than to cut taxes on corporations and the wealthy by $2.3 billion over two years, forcing the burden of austerity on the Badger State’s working middle class.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370542062225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370542249822-60</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL (What do all the posts on this board have to do with ORCL)</Title><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1370542039494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:07:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed !!! Would be nice if these "message boards" discussed stocks instead of politics. There are other message boards for that.</Msg><Username>ericnliberty</Username><Timestamp>1370542249822</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370546442541-61</Id><Topic><Title>GS analyst just upgraded ORCL to conviction buy from Buy and raised it price target to 45 dollars from 39</Title><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370539999735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:33:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any link to your statement??</Msg><Username>rajesh_198911</Username><Timestamp>1370546442541</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370546502564-62</Id><Topic><Title>ORCL (What do all the posts on this board have to do with ORCL)</Title><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1370542039494</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:07:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ditto to both of you. I wonder if most of these people are invested in orcl.</Msg><Username>one_8t</Username><Timestamp>1370546502564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370546529331-63</Id><Topic><Title>Scott Walker delivers a negative growth rate for WI &amp; big tax cuts for cronies and corporations</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370542062225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Have to go to Kmart, get underwear, underwear, Kmart, definitely Kmart. That's exactly what Obama did for Goldman Sachs and the rest of his crony, wealthy, corporate supporters. You're not too bright, always bringing up what can be thrown back at you. but you persist. Keep wagging the donkey, SMACK!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370546529331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370547595435-64</Id><Topic><Title>Scott Walker delivers a negative growth rate for WI &amp; big tax cuts for cronies and corporations</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370542062225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeez, you are such a liar....... Bush was the one who gave tax cuts to the rich..... Obama wanted to end them..... the gop house saved the Bush tax cuts for those earning 250K to 400K and they saved the wall street bums carried interest tax break.... and Bush bailed out wall street: "unless money is loosened up the sucker could go down...... and he promptly bailed them out......... and the fact is, you dishonest moron....... stinking pubs like walker gave BILLIONs in tax cut to corporations and the wealth...... made up by the middleclass.......... and he lied saying this would create trickle down jobs and a growth economy........ well , the results are in and he walker is causing NEGATIVE growth and so are 5 OTHER RED STATES......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370547595435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370548061034-65</Id><Topic><Title>GS analyst just upgraded ORCL to conviction buy from Buy and raised it price target to 45 dollars from 39</Title><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1370539999735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:33:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ORCL has been downgraded to a price target of 28</Msg><Username>rajesh_198911</Username><Timestamp>1370548061034</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370548225316-66</Id><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Msg>Most yahoo stock boards are compromised now with political junk postings from morons. For a serious investor, these boards are useless, time for yahoo to control/ monitor postings here or better still close them!!!</Msg><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370550350708-67</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would that put you in Obama's camp that is in favor of censorship... violating free speech rights? If you haven't noticed... the politicians control everything and it is Fed policy that has ruled the markets.. The Fed cowtows to the politicians.. Does not Oracle's Ellison support Obama and the Dems with large contributions? So how then is politics not relevant?</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1370550350708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370550820249-68</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As an Oracle stock holder, I expect this board to be a platform to engage in discussion with other stock holders about the stock Is it too much to expect?. If you wish to engage in political discussions, why don't you use some other way to do it (like you can post on Yahoo itself under political stories, etc,)?</Msg><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370550820249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 16:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370555824746-69</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you don't like it leave! It's been this way for 10 years! When something significant happens with Oracle, you get to chat with your buddies. If Oracle is sleeping, you won't have any!! Seeya chump! No one cares #$%$ you "expect"!</Msg><Username>charlie59603</Username><Timestamp>1370555824746</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 17:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370556365248-70</Id><Title>Pope equates food waste to stealing from the poor</Title><Msg>The pontiff dedicated his weekly audience in St Peter’s Square to the United Nations World Environment Day to draw attention to the excesses of consumerism and food wastage. “This culture of waste has made us insensitive even to the waste and disposal of food, which is even more despicable when all over the world, unfortunately, many individuals and families are suffering from hunger and malnutrition,” the Pope said. ..................................................................................................................................................... Reminds me of when I was a kid my mother would say, "think of all the starving kids in India." Cripes, I think all moms said that.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1370556365248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370556552031-71</Id><Topic><Title>Scott Walker delivers a negative growth rate for WI &amp; big tax cuts for cronies and corporations</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370542062225</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone is a liar to you and you use it like you use racist, Obama gave Wall Street impunity in the mortgage mess even bailing them out for billions of dollars. He gave them breaks, dummy. What's the difference? You scuttle that when it was thee biggest reason for the economic crash that affected the whole country, There are just as many blue states with slow or absent growth, Calif for one. And Obama still can't figure how to fix it. But.....but if we keep spending, things will change. I don't lie, I put things into perspective, another word for reality which you seem to be absent from most of the time. SMACK!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370556552031</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370558890044-72</Id><Title>Who the #$%$ is Berenberg?</Title><Msg>Anyone???Berenberg downgraded a couple of tech heavy weight this morning citing future innovation concerns. The firm lowered its rating on Oracle (ORCL) and VMWare (VMW) to a sell rating, assigning a $28 price target to ORCL and a $57 price target to VMW. Shares of Oracle were lower by 2.3% today, while shares of VMWare were higher by over 6%</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1370558890044</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559166198-73</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They should add common politics keywords to the list of banned keywords like curses so they all come out looking like #$%$ said USA has #$%$ and the #$%$ responded by screwing the government dikks". I bet that would reduce the volume of non-stock related posts real quick.</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1370559166198</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559269270-74</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Yahoo forgot to ban the word #$%$ or #$%$s...</Msg><Username>blackoutbuzz</Username><Timestamp>1370559269270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:54:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559296787-75</Id><Topic><Title>Judith Miller: Obama criminalizing news-gathering</Title><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1370532257248</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 11:24:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By JESSICA MEYERS | 6/6/13 6:14 PM EDT The NSA and FBI have dug into the servers of nine major Internet companies and pulled everything from e-mails to video, according to a report in The Washington Post. The information has allowed analysts to track movements and contacts over an extended period of time. This marks the first time the classified program, nicknamed PRISM and established in 2008, has been made public. The disclosure comes on the same day as the Obama administration fielded charges that it secretly obtained records for millions of Verizon phone calls. The heavy-hitting companies — which knowingly participate in the program — include Microsoft, Yahoo, Google, Facebook, PalTalk, AOL, Skype, YouTube and Apple.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1370559296787</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559302452-76</Id><Topic><Title>only 5 states are not growing their economy, red states..... Scott walker sure was full of shizer</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370541798776</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 14:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wyoming BLM just killed Luca Technologies in Wyoming. Company had to claim bankruptcy and lay off about a hundred employees. It was an example of govt in action, or blackmail in action. In Mexico, it's pure payola. In Obummers America, it's govt blackmail. As for Wisconsin, it's early in the game. He brought the useless unions to their knees, just like the Bummer is doing to America.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370559302452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559463374-77</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats still live in ghettos and Rs are stil making money. Dems lose again.</Title><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1370540182349</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 13:36:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should blow up the cities, make everyone act in a civil manner. Detroit and Chicago could lead the way.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370559463374</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370559595300-78</Id><Title>New Monopoly game</Title><Msg>All the landing places are the crisis of the day for the last month. What a bozo. 57 states my #$%$.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370559595300</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559596816-79</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This has nothing to do with free speech. The topic of this board is Oracle.....not politics. Politics may impact the financial world....but that is much broader than any individual stock. The topic of this board is Oracle. Intelligent, informed and serious investors would appreciate an opportunity to share information, debate and discuss this stock. All others are wasting everyone's time. Please take your political opinions elsewhere....no one is interested in them here.</Msg><Username>ericnliberty</Username><Timestamp>1370559596816</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 18:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370559674196-80</Id><Topic><Title>No, There Are No Intelligent Liberals in the House</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370536262571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean no intelligent libiots in the world.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370559674196</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:01:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370560177613-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obama fixes problems, the gop creates them</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370527943567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. He fixed James Rosen. Got him mixed up with the Rosenbergs. Yep. He fixed the AP. Taught them a lesson. Yep. He fixed the fiasco at the IRS. Oops, he created that. My bad. Yep. He fixed Benghazi. Just lied about it. Then promoted Rice so she could live another day to lie. Yep. He fixed America by tapping their phones. Yep. He fixed the judicial system in America. Had Holder lie to three judges before he found a libiot judge to say okay, break the law. Yep. Curtailed the growth of energy in America so his Mooslim friends can continue to rip us off.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370560177613</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370560210571-82</Id><Topic><Title>Obama fixes problems, the gop creates them</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1370527943567</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 10:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, he's a fixer.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1370560210571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 19:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370568483921-83</Id><Title>Piers Morgan says we dont like Obama because he is black</Title><Msg>That's not true. We don't like Obama because he is a big cry baby who always wines about his blackness like its an excuse. We als don't like Obama because he is a godless, commie b #$%$ t u r d! 1. His alleged father could not legally have been married to his mother, because he was already married to some babe in Kenya. Therefore, Obama is for sure a b #$%$ t u rd! 2. Trinity United was not a proper Christian church: it was social-justice communism disguised as Christianty! And Obama says he is not a MUZZYWUZZY! Therefore he is GODLESS! 3. And he is a commie (socialist, e.g. Democrats.!) Therefore: PROVED! Barack Obama is a godless, commie ba sst urd!</Msg><Username>captain_cazo_schettino.the_brave</Username><Timestamp>1370568483921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370568617772-84</Id><Topic><Title>No, There Are No Intelligent Liberals in the House</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1370536262571</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 12:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, There Are No Intelligent Liberals [anywhere!]</Msg><Username>captain_cazo_schettino.the_brave</Username><Timestamp>1370568617772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370568718855-85</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is still an option to ignore a user. I will ignore you because you are a whiniy wussie!</Msg><Username>captain_cazo_schettino.the_brave</Username><Timestamp>1370568718855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 21:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370575844902-86</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should either monitor or close these boards!</Title><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1370548225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 15:50:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you agree then.... politics is relevant... you just don't want to talk about them and IF you believe that politics is not specifically relevant to Oracle... tell Larry to stop supporting Obama and the Democrat party with millions of dollars</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1370575844902</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-06 23:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>