<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366949220459-1</Id><Topic><Title>SYRIA Crosses Obama's "Red Line" and Obama Punts!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1366930780110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:59:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a fat ugly lying extreme republican piece of dabien. Ya wanna start another bgroup war ?? Ya want Obama to be a little dummy like you and your bush ? You make me sick and worse. You're nuthin but a stinking repub and theres nothing worse.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366949220459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 00:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366949381119-2</Id><Title>The guy won't take responibility for anything.,,bgroup never took any responsibility for 9/11,, nor did any repubs ever blame the bgroup for</Title><Msg>now did bgroup ever fire any bgroupers for allowing 9/11. Don't talk responsibilty through the stinking mouth of a repub.. it can';t be done!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366949381119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 00:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366952950968-3</Id><Title>Beck conspiracy theory: What's his evidence?</Title><Msg>Beck..........repubs still love him? toooooooooooo much...........beck and others are the reason repubs are repubs.........they believe and love anyone who hates democrats....repubs are the reason we are where we're at...they absolutely raised all this to the current level...they've no excuses being this way. You all are nothing but disgusting,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366952950968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 01:09:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366969885759-4</Id><Title>US won't allow Castro's daughter to visit Philly</Title><Msg>Bad Cub-Americans and bad Obama for not doing whats right.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366969885759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 05:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366982239899-5</Id><Topic><Title>SYRIA Crosses Obama's "Red Line" and Obama Punts!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1366930780110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:59:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Presidential Wheel Turns Disaffection for Bush gave us Obama. That explains the new affection for Bush. By PEGGY NOONAN Like this columnist Barack Obama was elected president in 2008 because he was not George W. Bush. In fact, he was elected because he was the farthest thing possible from Mr. Bush. On some level he knew this, which is why every time he got in trouble he'd say Bush's name. It's all his fault, you have no idea the mess I inherited. As long as Mr. Bush's memory was hovering like Boo Radley in the shadows, Mr. Obama would be OK. Related Video In an excerpt from a longer interview, former Florida Governor Jeb Bush is asked by Peter Robinson of the Hoover Institution whether he plans to run for president in 2016. "Uncommon Knowledge" is produced by the Hoover Institution for WSJ Live. This week something changed. George W. Bush is back, for the unveiling of his presidential library. His numbers are dramatically up. You know why? Because he's the farthest thing from Barack Obama. Obama fatigue has opened the way to Bush affection. *** In all his recent interviews Mr. Bush has been modest, humorous, proud but unassuming, and essentially philosophical: History will decide. No finger-pointing or scoring points. If he feels rancor or resentment he didn't show it. He didn't attempt to manipulate. His sheer normality seemed like a relief, an echo of an older age. And all this felt like an antidote to Obama—to the imperious I, to the inability to execute, to the endless interviews and the imperturbable drone, to the sense that he is trying to teach us, like an Ivy League instructor taken aback by the backwardness of his students. And there's the unconscious superiority. One thing Mr. Bush didn't think he was was superior. He thought he was luckily bo</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1366982239899</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366982292919-6</Id><Title>He us either a true wimp or a supporter of Muslim causes.</Title><Msg>HE caused the getting of bin Laden as your idiot dropped the ball,,,,HE has kicked out more illegals than anyone,........HE has kept us safe for these years except for a couple guys bgroup allowed in...........on and on you punk!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1366982292919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366984847720-7</Id><Title>heck, righties named our capital's airport for a guy who sold weapons to an Ayatollah terrorist</Title><Msg>just fact "...........the airport in our national capital is named for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini at a time the latter was on a terror watch list, and used the black money thus gained to support right wing death squads in Central America................." professor Juan Cole</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1366984847720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366985855260-8</Id><Title>over 20 million of them marched off to conquer the world saying God is with us</Title><Msg>just the Wehrmacht alone... over 20 million ..... Christians..... their motto was "god is with us", each had a belt buckle saying that "got mitt uns"........ they were still worked up over their celebration of Martin Luther's birthday: Kristallnacht.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1366985855260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366986099103-9</Id><Topic><Title>religious killing toll: Islam,2 million; Christianity, 100 million</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1366735609942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 12:46:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>most of our oil comes from Canada,so why continue to murder and meddle in the mid east, right? All Us troops home from the mid east and bushganistan...NOW!</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1366986099103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366986774844-10</Id><Topic><Title>Let's see -- Clinton committed a felony and lost his license to practice law.</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1366931376513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:09:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, who needs a license for a real job when you spend your whole life feeding off of the public trough! Now, he just collects $$$ from all his progressive buddies.</Msg><Username>say92liberals</Username><Timestamp>1366986774844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366986874461-11</Id><Topic><Title>SYRIA Crosses Obama's "Red Line" and Obama Punts!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1366930780110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:59:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will go with the latter.</Msg><Username>say92liberals</Username><Timestamp>1366986874461</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:34:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366987324380-12</Id><Topic><Title>SYRIA Crosses Obama's "Red Line" and Obama Punts!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1366930780110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:59:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This week something changed. George W. Bush is back, for the unveiling of his presidential library. His numbers are dramatically up. You know why? Because he's the farthest thing from Barack Obama. Obama fatigue has opened the way to Bush affection. In all his recent interviews Mr. Bush has been modest, humorous, proud but unassuming, and essentially philosophical: History will decide. No finger-pointing or scoring points. If he feels rancor or resentment he didn't show it. He didn't attempt to manipulate. His sheer normality seemed like a relief, an echo of an older age. And all this felt like an antidote to Obama—to the imperious I, to the inability to execute, to the endless interviews and the imperturbable drone, to the sense that he is trying to teach us, like an Ivy League instructor taken aback by the backwardness of his students. And there's the unconscious superiority." Obama is an incompetent shameless Ivy League fool in love with his own folly and endless Fups!</Msg><Username>itsthepress_stupid</Username><Timestamp>1366987324380</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366988243579-13</Id><Title>Obama Loves Immigrants</Title><Msg>The older Chechen was registered to vote because he was given citizenship. What is most enjoyable is heads are exploding over on BSNBC. Chris Matthews was sure the Boston bombing was a home grown white tea party member and each and every reporter on that vile network played it gleefully as if it was something to cheer. In fact it's Obama supporters who have committed the most crimes in this country, Chicago and LA at the front, but you would never hear that idiot Matthews claim it must have been a Black Panther thug or an ACORN pimp.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366988243579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:57:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366988661592-14</Id><Title>Everybody Sing</Title><Msg>Mama, don't let your babies grow up to be Jihads. Let 'em be lawyers or Pres and such</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366988661592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366989345383-15</Id><Topic><Title>Everybody Sing</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366988661592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:04:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which is worse? Can't tell the difference most times.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366989345383</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366989557116-16</Id><Topic><Title>Let's see -- Clinton committed a felony and lost his license to practice law.</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1366931376513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:09:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As with most drugs cocaine warps the brain. Never knew a druggie yet that wasn't psychotic in one way or another. Liver Lips admits to getting it from his "Father Figure" the card carrying commie Davis.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1366989557116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366990393195-17</Id><Topic><Title>Let's see -- Clinton committed a felony and lost his license to practice law.</Title><Username>indahouzza</Username><Timestamp>1366931376513</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 19:09:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why is Clinton a person you're upset with? The guy was a great President.....GREAT, followed by the worst.....WORST. And the funny thing is....they both did coke - only Bush did while evading Viet Nam as a pilot for the National Guard.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1366990393195</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366990668055-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Loves Immigrants</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366988243579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it McCain who is now behind the wheel of amnesty? for how many million? and wasn't it Bush that put down 'My Pet Goat' to make sure we had the lists of bad guys integrated between all the departments protecting us? All Bush did was add more layers to an already beuracratic intellegence gathering system.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1366990668055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366990948226-19</Id><Topic><Title>SYRIA Crosses Obama's "Red Line" and Obama Punts!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1366930780110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:59:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush numbers up? OMG LMFAO good luck ever EVER having Bush stump for anyone ever in his lifetime. It would be death to your campaign if that failure ever showed up in public to stump for anyone.</Msg><Username>kollesteral</Username><Timestamp>1366990948226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 11:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366993406848-20</Id><Topic><Title>SYRIA Crosses Obama's "Red Line" and Obama Punts!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1366930780110</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 18:59:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No greater "Failure" in American history than Barack Hussein Obama! The only thing he's good at is Pigshyting the gullible Mice of America and expanding his multitude of Losers and Government Leeches!! The sooner everything this POS stands for, top to bottom, is destroyed and wiped clean the better for America! And it will be!</Msg><Username>itsthepress_stupid</Username><Timestamp>1366993406848</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 12:23:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366995504281-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Loves Immigrants</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366988243579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And who began the wheel of amnesty? DA. And what about that intelligence gathering bureau who have made a joke of what it's aupposed to be doing. You think we should do away with the DHS and Napolitano? Isn't that what you're flapping about? If Bush had done nothing, you would still be wettting your pants. Just think, how many more of these Muslim brothers are in this country since Obama gave them a free ticket. We need immigration reform alright, start deporting those who are on "watch lists" and stop supporting them. They can start with you. btw, McCain is a bumbling idiot, always has been. Most Repubs have written him off. Keep up or shut up.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366995504281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 12:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366996422390-22</Id><Title>California High Speed Rail</Title><Msg>The are 38 million people in California. Studies show that only 41 million of them will have to use the high speed rail between LA &amp; San Francisco every year to make it economically viable. All of AMTRAK in the USA only services about 2.5 million passengers per year. 41 million passengers is 16.4 times higher than AMTRAK's total national ridership. Costs projections suggest it will cost $100 billion. So the project was cut back to "only" $68 billion. Outside of the Great Pyramid in Egypt, it will be the biggest government project in all of history.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1366996422390</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366996458028-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Loves Immigrants</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366988243579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama backs Planned Parenthood in political fight Associated WASHINGTON (AP) -- President Barack Obama vowed Friday to join Planned Parenthood in fighting against what he said were efforts across the country to turn women's health back to the 1950s. When babies were allowed to live. Obama's comments were the first by a sitting president before the abortion-rights group.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1366996458028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366996542365-24</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Loves Immigrants</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366988243579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Immigration bill to bring in at least 33 million people, says group 9:30 AM 04/26/2013 The pending Senate immigration bill would bring a minimum of 33 million people into the country during its first decade of operation, according to an analysis by NumbersUSA,. 95% of these illegals will vote Democrat. By 2024, the inflow would include an estimated 9.2 million illegal immigrants, plus 2.5 million illegals who arrived as children — dubbed ‘Dreamers’ — plus roughly 3.4 million company-sponsored employees with university degrees, said the unreleased analysis. The majority of the inflow, or roughly 17 million people, would consist of family members of illegals, recent immigrants and of company-sponsored workers, according to the NumbersUSA analysis provided to The</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1366996542365</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366996612491-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Loves Immigrants</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1366988243579</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A jury in South Bend, Indiana has found that fraud put President Obama and Hillary Clinton on the presidential primary ballot in Indiana in the 2008 election. Two Democratic political operatives were convicted Thursday night in the illegal scheme after only three hours of deliberations. They were found guilty on all counts. Former longtime St. Joseph County Democratic party Chairman Butch Morgan Jr. was found guilty of felony conspiracy counts to commit petition fraud and forgery, and former county Board of Elections worker Dustin Blythe was found guilty of felony forgery counts and falsely making a petition, after being accused of faking petitions that enabled Obama, then an Illinois Senator, to get on the presidential primary ballot for his first run for the White House.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1366996612491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366996849816-26</Id><Title>Obama Admin says high speed internet is a right!</Title><Msg>So that illiterate children from public schools can watch p o r n on the internet.</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1366996849816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366999261980-27</Id><Topic><Title>heck, righties named our capital's airport for a guy who sold weapons to an Ayatollah terrorist</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1366984847720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, Reagan sold weapons to a terrorist.... a big ayatollah......Ayatollah Khomeini......righties love terrorists I guess, more weapons get sold that way, so maybe that's the reason for their love of murder and meddling in the Mideast and bushghanistan</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1366999261980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 14:01:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367000994784-28</Id><Title>stuff we have done overseas is now brought back into our own front yards. America’s chickens are coming home to roost.”</Title><Msg>Ron Paul said the same thing.....blowback.......now Tom Brokaw is trying to wake you fools up......like Cronkite did for our SE Asia murder and meddling. Tom Brokaw’s appearance on “Meet the Press” last Sunday....he did a Cronkite on Blow back......time for the USA to wake up to the costs of our decades of murder and meddling in the mid east and bushghanistan. "Of course, Brokaw was merely stating the obvious: With America having killed thousands of civilians in its wars, we should be appalled by acts of terrorism—but we shouldn’t be surprised by them. We should know that violence will inevitably come from those like the Boston bombing suspect who, according to the Washington Post, “told interrogators that the American wars in Iraq and Afghanistan motivated him and his brother to carry out the attack.” Noting this is not to argue that such attacks are justified or that we deserve them. It is only to reiterate what Brokaw alluded to: Namely, that blowback should be expected in this age of Permanent War and that one way to potentially avert such blowback in the future is to try to de-escalate the cycle of violence. "</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1367000994784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 14:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367007313929-29</Id><Title>US Democrat Senator Max Baucus Calls ObamaCare "A Trainwreck"!</Title><Msg>Right... a well respected 6-term US Senator &amp; Senate Finance Chairman Max Baucus couldn't take the Regime BS any longer.! Enough! ObamaCare is a "Train Wreck"! Baucus, an ObamaCare architect and Chairman of the powerful Senate Finance Committee, announced Tuesday that he will not seek reelection.</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1367007313929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367008841724-30</Id><Title>Obama throws a little temper tantrum when everyone doesn't bow and say "Yes, sir!"</Title><Msg>Did you guys see  Obama throwing a tantrum (kicking a door, etc) when he was leaving a meeting with Congressional leaders after Cantor told the president "Republicans would not vote for his proposed tax hikes." As you can guess, it was not carried by the news media but did get caught on smartphones. He  displayed  his true lack of class and respect for the office. Just goes to show once again, that there is no fix,or excuse, for stupidity and ingrained ignorance, and complete lack of grace! Makes  you proud of your leader, yes?</Msg><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1367008841724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367009742340-31</Id><Title>Romney calls obamacare romenycare for all!!</Title><Msg>Romney said Romneycare with a mandates is the "responsible" way to go! and if it doesn't work out we can do single payer, medicare for all and just get rid of the thieving insurance cos. Romneycare, er... obamacare is the gop way of private insurance from free market exchanges......</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1367009742340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367012474654-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama throws a little temper tantrum when everyone doesn't bow and say "Yes, sir!"</Title><Username>gr8mkt</Username><Timestamp>1367008841724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:40:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking on the House floor yesterday, Representative Hank Johnson (D., Ga.) stood up for some of the most important victims of congressional gridlock: children’s birthday parties and comedians trying to make their voices high-pitched. Discussing a bill to continue the federal government’s sales from the National Helium Reserve, Johnson intoned, “Imagine, Mr. Speaker, a world without balloons.” In his pun-riddled push for the Responsible Helium Administration and Stewardship Act of 2013, he lamented, “today, the House has chosen to just simply float above it all.” “Too often lately, this body has sat deflated,” he said, but “not for a lack of hot air.” During a 2010 committee hearing regarding the U.S. military’s presence in Guam, Johnson voiced his concerns about the island “become so overly populated that it will tip over and capsize.”</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1367012474654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 17:41:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367013270502-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Admin says high speed internet is a right!</Title><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1366996849816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 13:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HOLDER: Citizenship for illegals a 'civil right'...</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1367013270502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 17:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367013637131-34</Id><Topic><Title>US Democrat Senator Max Baucus Calls ObamaCare "A Trainwreck"!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1367007313929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:15:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part of the landing gear from a passenger jet used in the Sept. 11 attacks was found behind the site of the controversial Ground Zero mosque, police said. The piece of gear was discovered Wednesday, wedged between the rear of 51Park Place, the mosque site, and the building behind it, 50 Murray Street. Police are treating the site as a crime scene. They will photograph the piece, and the Medical Examiner will check the area for human remains. The aircraft part has a clearly visible Boeing identification number, police said. Surveyors hired by the owner of 51 Park Place made the find this morning when they were working on the property. They called 911 at about 11 a.m. to report what they believed was damaged machinery, cops said. Hijackers flew two Boeing jets into the twin towers at the World Trade Center on the morning of September 11, 2001.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1367013637131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 18:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367014958906-35</Id><Title>Obama says living through an abortion does not give a childmthe right to life</Title><Msg>Speaks at, and 100% supports, Planned Parenthood</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1367014958906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 18:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367017751296-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says living through an abortion does not give a childmthe right to life</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1367014958906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 18:22:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pity he wasn't! America would be a far better nation!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1367017751296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 19:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367022374391-37</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says living through an abortion does not give a childmthe right to life</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1367014958906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 18:22:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Pity he wasn't" That goes for all far left liberal goons.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1367022374391</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367022900743-38</Id><Title>Boston Bombers</Title><Msg>They may have gained a place in history but their family will pay the price. They are saying now that their mother may have been instrumental in their radicalization. Peaceful</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1367022900743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367023151076-39</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Bombers</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1367022900743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somehow the above post was interrupted. I didn't click on post. Peaceful Muslims don't go to Al Queda websites to get inspired to make bombs. These brother were sacrificed in the name of religion, period.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1367023151076</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:39:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367024895083-40</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Bombers</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1367022900743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I always like George Patton's dictum. "You don't want to die for your cause, you want your enemy to die for his." Thes Muslim fanatics are stupid and will never win. Plus, they will burn in Hell for killing innocents.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1367024895083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 21:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367024984590-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says living through an abortion does not give a childmthe right to life</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1367014958906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 18:22:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another "liberal" worshiper of Moloch.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1367024984590</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 21:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367025247159-42</Id><Topic><Title>stuff we have done overseas is now brought back into our own front yards. America’s chickens are coming home to roost.”</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1367000994784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 14:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a book titled "Blowback". It details the many crimes the U.S. has committed all over the world. I met the man that wrote it and my copy is autographed. Look up "Operatiuon Phoenix" for one in 'Nam and No gun Ree in Korea for another among many. I could give a long list of what this country hasdone under the Satyanists that have ruled for a very long time.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1367025247159</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 21:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367026236167-43</Id><Topic><Title>heck, righties named our capital's airport for a guy who sold weapons to an Ayatollah terrorist</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1366984847720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. Pretty much everyone of the other losers on here besides you and me have an empty head and six fingers pointing back at them. I hate the birth defect FREAKS on this board, don't you..(??)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367026236167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 21:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367026272275-44</Id><Topic><Title>stuff we have done overseas is now brought back into our own front yards. America’s chickens are coming home to roost.”</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1367000994784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 14:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is my FAVORITE book..(!!). WOW. I would love to see the autographed copy (!!)</Msg><Username>zonbac89</Username><Timestamp>1367026272275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 21:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367027286245-45</Id><Topic><Title>Boston Bombers</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1367022900743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 20:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I mentioned before that they may have been part of a bigger operation and were just the drop off guys. The FBI is now saying the bombs were too intricate for these rookies to have assembled themselves.. So now what are we up against? Sporatic bombings and we don't know the enemy's whereabouts. .America use to be a great place to live, to prosper, to pursue happiness. Now we have foreign immigrants dissenting against us. And the government focuses on gun control. What about terrorists control?</Msg><Username>annieshenanigan</Username><Timestamp>1367027286245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 21:48:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>