<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371184789508-1</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal Mentality</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371173456443</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 21:30:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you should stop touching them then.</Msg><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1371184789508</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 00:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371184854194-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ain't wonderful!</Title><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371178297623</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 22:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent. Hopefully it keeps going up until you can no longer afford it and die alone of pneumonia. Slowly.</Msg><Username>echo.2165</Username><Timestamp>1371184854194</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 00:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371205385514-3</Id><Title>runner is one silly, ignorant, ugly, dumb, racist, Nixon loving mutha.</Title><Msg>How many times has he said what he'd do if someone did something to him????? COUNTLESS. I'd say that means he's an insecure old man with a macho complex he needs mental hearlth care quick.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371205385514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 06:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371207406582-4</Id><Topic><Title>They just look for any excuse to bash their black President. That's the real bottom line.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371180186691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 23:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No-Fly Zone... Syrian 'rebels' pledge loyalty to Al-Qaeda... Key to victories... Executed Teenager 2 Days Ago For Insulting Islam... ADMIN CONSIDERS RESETTLING THOUSANDS OF SYRIAN REFUGEES IN AMERICA... WAR: USA TO PROVIDE MILITARY SUPPORT TO SYRIA 'REBELS'</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371207406582</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 06:56:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371207426664-5</Id><Topic><Title>They just look for any excuse to bash their black President. That's the real bottom line.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371180186691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 23:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Introduced at WH Lesbian-Gay-Bisexual-Transgender Event -- By Third-Graders...</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1371207426664</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 06:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371209837208-6</Id><Topic><Title>They just look for any excuse to bash their black President. That's the real bottom line.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371180186691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 23:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who the Hell needs excuses!! Your Boy Obama is a complete fraud and liar... who F's up everything he touches! He pushes the FOOL BAR higher, and the Country lower, with every passing day, and watching his Nasty Little Pigs screw themselves into a thousand knots trying to defend him is hilarious!</Msg><Username>itsthepress_stupid</Username><Timestamp>1371209837208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 07:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371210860271-7</Id><Title>Our World-Class Chump Obama Now Backing al-Qaeda in Syria!!</Title><Msg>Who are running a big contingent, certainly the most successful, of the Syrian "Rebels"! YeeeeeHaaaaaaaaaaaaaa! Ain't that a kick in the azzs! And Why?? Because the butcher Assad "Crossed the Red Line"... and killed a100 or so people with Sarin gas! For Obama, the other 93,000 killed by this Butcher in 2 years meant Jackshyt... just collateral damage!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371210860271</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 07:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371211530057-8</Id><Title>NetSol Technologies, Inc. (NTWK)... Hiring like crazy</Title><Msg>watch it</Msg><Username>i_love_ntwk</Username><Timestamp>1371211530057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371213095184-9</Id><Topic><Title>Our World-Class Chump Obama Now Backing al-Qaeda in Syria!!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371210860271</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 07:54:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your past two losing pres candidates also back same,...ya got nuthing, ya never had anything and never will have anything dropkick!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371213095184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371213517724-10</Id><Topic><Title>Our World-Class Chump Obama Now Backing al-Qaeda in Syria!!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371210860271</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 07:54:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exaclly... Clinton and Carter were 1st Class Losers!! Gee baggerboy, you finally got one right!! From a guy who IS "Nothing", you spend way too much time pointing fingers!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371213517724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371214232884-11</Id><Topic><Title>Our World-Class Chump Obama Now Backing al-Qaeda in Syria!!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371210860271</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 07:54:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Al-Qaeda praises Allah every day for their good Buddy Barack Hussein Obama! He's been such a champion for their cause, especially his Killing Bin Laden!! Ever since Barack's personal hands-on slaying of Binny, for which Navy Seals were of little import, it's been sunny days and winds at their back for al-Qaeda!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371214232884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371214774885-12</Id><Topic><Title>Our World-Class Chump Obama Now Backing al-Qaeda in Syria!!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371210860271</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 07:54:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cops: Man Wearing Obama T-Shirt Exposed Self To Female Walmart Shopper Comments(43) Share A man wearing an “Obama 2008” t-shirt is being sought by Virginia police after allegedly exposing himself to a female shopper inside a Walmart. According to cops, the 21-year-old victim said that she was approached by an unknown man around 7:50 AM Tuesday in the Dumfries store. “During the encounter, the man exposed himself to the victim,” according to a Prince William County Police Department incident report. Investigators released the above surveillance photo (click to enlarge) of the suspect, who they described as a black male between the ages of 15 and 25. The 5’ 8”, 140-pound pervert wore glasses, green pajama pants, and “a white t-shirt” that was not further described by cops. The indecent exposure suspect left the Walmart in a “White, older model Honda Civic with black trim.”</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371214774885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371215101884-13</Id><Topic><Title>They just look for any excuse to bash their black President. That's the real bottom line.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371180186691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 23:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>way to go, it is so easy to get these baggies into a knee jerk panty wad... they just seemingly can't wait to throw up their skirts, take off their panties and wad them up...... ha ha ha it is true that no matter what Obama does they whine about it....they even whined about killing Bin Laden.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371215101884</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371215483718-14</Id><Title>PITY!! Poor John McCain Just Can't Live Without Another Useless Islamic WAR!</Title><Msg>To be fought largely by 20-something year old American kids... for Nothing! F Him!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371215483718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371215573679-15</Id><Topic><Title>PITY!! Poor John McCain Just Can't Live Without Another Useless Islamic WAR!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1371215483718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:11:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has already LOST Two and is now going for Three!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371215573679</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:12:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371217698397-16</Id><Topic><Title>They just look for any excuse to bash their black President. That's the real bottom line.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371180186691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 23:23:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oil above $97 a barrel amid Syrian war concerns, ahead of data on US industrial ... Washington Post - ‎26 minutes ago‎ The price of oil rose past $97 a barrel Friday amid concerns about a possible escalation in Syria's civil war while traders awaited the release of several reports on the U.S. economy. By early afternoon in Europe, benchmark oil for July delivery was up 36 cents ... Russia Hits Back at U.S. Over Syria Subscriber Article Preview MOSCOW—The Kremlin Friday dismissed as unconvincing evidence that U.S. officials provided of Syrian leader Bashar al-Assad’s alleged use of chemical weapons and criticized Washington’s decision to arm Syrian opposition fighters. The Kremlin believes the Obama Administration is taking this action now as a distraction for the many scandals plaguing his administration.</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1371217698397</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371221596226-17</Id><Title>Liberal mentality is another oxymoron.</Title><Msg>Now, liberal mental case is accurate.</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1371221596226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371221709171-18</Id><Title>poll: 57% think NSA data will be used against political opponents</Title><Msg>a valid concern given the stuff that goes on at the IRS.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371221709171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371221867983-19</Id><Topic><Title>poll: 57% think NSA data will be used against political opponents</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371221709171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>US to send weapons to Syrian rebels as Bill Clinton says Obama risks being a 'wussy' on the conflict Last Updated: 9:56 AM, June 14, 2013 Posted: 1:38 AM, June 14, 2013 WASHINGTON — The Obama administration will provide military aid to the Syrian rebels after finding conclusive evidence that dictator Bashar al-Assad killed as many as 150 of his own people with chemical weapons, the White House said yesterday. The sharp change in US policy came amid reports that the Pentagon was planning to arm the rebels and impose a no-fly zone — and that former President Bill Clinton said President Obama risked being remembered as a “wuss.” But as evidence about poison gas emerged earlier this year, the White House rejected a greater US role. At an unscheduled briefing last night, the White House said Assad had used outlawed chemical weapons “multiple times in the past year.” “The president has said that the use of chemical weapons would change his calculus, and it has,” Deputy National Security Adviser Ben Rhodes said. “Put simply, the Assad regime should know that its actions have led us to increase the scope and scale of assistance that we provide to the opposition,” he said. But the White House wasn’t saying how and how soon it would act. The US is stepping up assistance to the beleaguered rebels including aid that would have “direct military purposes on the ground,” Rhodes said. But he refused to say whether providing “military suppo</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1371221867983</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371222291106-20</Id><Topic><Title>poll: 57% think NSA data will be used against political opponents</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371221709171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure it will! Why else would they do it?? Certainly not to disrupt anything al-Qaeda may be doing! It won't have a single impact on al-Qaeda or any other terrorist... save for some clueless dumbazzs! Shyt.... it didn't even pick up any of the phone calls, or emails, or even #$%$ websites, of the GD Boston Bombers!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1371222291106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:04:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371223229067-21</Id><Title>The Beat Goes On........Upside the Head</Title><Msg>From audacity of hope to audacity of a dope. Like Eric Holder wasn't a bad enough pick, Obama appoints Susan Rice as Nat'l Security Advisor. Maybe they're having an affair. Obama on data mining: Listen, collecting everyone's phone info is no big deal. We make a record of the call but we don't actually listen to the content or do anything about it. Isn't that what got Ambassador Stevens and others killed?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371223229067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371223363742-22</Id><Topic><Title>poll: 57% think NSA data will be used against political opponents</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1371221709171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CBS News confirms multiple breaches of Sharyl Attkisson’s computer by the Obama NSA , Published: June 14, 2013 at 10:27 amE-mail the writer Sharyl Attkisson (John P. Filo/CBS News) CBS News reporter Sharyl Attkisson revealed in May that her computer had been compromised. When asked about the situation, CBS News responded with a statement that it was conducting an investigation. That investigation has reached the following conclusions, according to CBS News spokeswoman Sonya McNair: “A cyber security firm hired by CBS News has determined through forensic analysis that Sharyl Attkisson’s computer was accessed by an unauthorized, external, unknown party on multiple occasions late in 2012. Evidence suggests this party performed all access remotely using Attkisson’s accounts. While no malicious code was found, forensic analysis revealed an intruder had executed commands that appeared to involve search and exfiltration of data. This party also used sophisticated methods to remove all possible indications of unauthorized activity, and alter system times to cause further confusion. CBS News is taking steps to identify the responsible party and their method of access.” More to come on this.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1371223363742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371223547077-23</Id><Title>Government Data Mining Is A "Threat" Only To Innocent Americans!</Title><Msg>And to fascist wannabees, both Democrat and Republican, who want to use it! It damn well is not a Threat to al-Qaeda or to any other GD Islamic Terrorist... who have long since known that we were tracking their phones, emails, postings, internet activity, addresses and locations... and are a step ahead of the Dragnet! Shyt... all this Data Mining Drivel did absolutely Jackshyt on the attacks we know about including the Hasan slaughter at Fort Hood and the Boston Bombers, both of which were run by dumbazzes! It's a joke! If the Dragnet couldn't spot these Clowns it's useless! Anyone who believes all this BS from the 1984 Big Government Pumpers about all the "Threats this Dragnet has uncovered" is a Gullible Fool!!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1371223547077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371224152291-24</Id><Topic><Title>Government Data Mining Is A "Threat" Only To Innocent Americans!</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1371223547077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:25:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This country is full of "gullible fools". Has been for a long time. Try some door to door political work and find out for yourself. San Diego County had three corrupt tax assessors in a row. No one believed the people trying to expose them. The local rag vilified them and one lost his business because of a boycott. The truth finally came out and some low level go betweens got a slap on the wrist. The local rag was one of the beneficiaries of the rigging.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371224152291</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371224259928-25</Id><Topic><Title>runner is one silly, ignorant, ugly, dumb, racist, Nixon loving mutha.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371205385514</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 06:23:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make my day knowing how much I upset you. I just love upsetting phony "liberals."</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371224259928</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371225249511-26</Id><Topic><Title>ORACLE EARNINGS NEXT WEEK... WILL THEY MAKE THE FIGURES?</Title><Username>piakilm</Username><Timestamp>1371159295689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 17:34:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought a straddle. I think they are going to do good. I'm more optimistic than pessimistic.</Msg><Username>phogat_ajay</Username><Timestamp>1371225249511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371226210695-27</Id><Topic><Title>Huge get</Title><Username>abonner656</Username><Timestamp>1371130315319</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 09:31:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am buying this now</Msg><Username>mossalex731</Username><Timestamp>1371226210695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371226299334-28</Id><Title>Oh Oh, Obamacare costs worrying Congress</Title><Msg>Looks like the HC bill is not the cheap and do-able solution that it was pumped. Congress is putting up red flags. Maybe they should have read it. I don't know of anyone whose insurance rates have gone down. Another of Obama's magic wonders ready to crash and burn. We told you so.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371226299334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371226898013-29</Id><Topic><Title>ORACLE EARNINGS NEXT WEEK... WILL THEY MAKE THE FIGURES?</Title><Username>piakilm</Username><Timestamp>1371159295689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 17:34:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm very interested in your strategy. Can you share more detail on what you did with yours? Thanks so much</Msg><Username>mpk214</Username><Timestamp>1371226898013</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371229412237-30</Id><Title>Now Back To Our Regular Programming</Title><Msg>Liberals are all on board for spying on Americans who never have or never will be tied to a terror group. But profiling of illegals wherever, or suspicious foreigners at airports is cause for them to have conniptions. Is there ONE liberal in this country who has any sense?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371229412237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 13:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371229616331-31</Id><Title>Forget Gun Control</Title><Msg>They better ban butt enhancing injections. A woman in Fla died due to having her posterior plumped. I bet she was a liberal..</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371229616331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 13:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371231971207-32</Id><Title>stunning Fox and friends Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance</Title><Msg>Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance ( same as with many on this board) . (prism 2007 was to protect Americans they said, but prism in 2009 is unconstitutional..... well why didn't they say so in 2001 or 2005 or 2007?) Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance How does Sean Hannity feel about the federal government collecting information on millions of Americans? Well, that depends. According to clips compiled by Media Matters, the Fox News host’s position regarding government surveillance is evidently based entirely on who happens to be occupying the Oval Office at the time. For example, Hannity called the recent revelation about the extent of National Security Agency surveillance programs under Democratic President Barack Obama a “very clear violation of the Fourth Amendment.” But when President George W. Bush was in power, the conservative commentator seemed to have no problem with the NSA gathering data on Americans. In fact, he was a staunch defender of the practice during the Dubya years. L</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371231971207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 13:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371232638799-33</Id><Title>The stunning hypocricy is Obama's</Title><Msg>That's all one needs to know Obama will say anything to get elected</Msg><Username>central_scrutinizer_fz</Username><Timestamp>1371232638799</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 13:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371238565230-34</Id><Title>The stunning hypocricy is Obama's</Title><Msg>Most republicans say the leaker is a patriot.THAT'S all ya need to know about double talking hypocrites.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371238565230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371238848297-35</Id><Title>(prism 2007 was to protect Americans they said, but prism in 2009 is unconstitutional.....</Title><Msg>Bbbingo and dropkick.that's it,says it all! ya need to know.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371238848297</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371240129758-36</Id><Topic><Title>ORACLE EARNINGS NEXT WEEK... WILL THEY MAKE THE FIGURES?</Title><Username>piakilm</Username><Timestamp>1371159295689</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 17:34:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am thinking if you have positive outlook on the company to go ahead and sell many put options out of the money in the 30-31 range. Then to protect yourself buy an equal amount of 28-29 puts. This put spread would earn about .20 based on a 31/29 July contract. I am short a few shares but more positive on it at 31. Thinking of putting this on next week.</Msg><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1371240129758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:02:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371244302620-37</Id><Title>Obama Going For The Arab Spring Trifecta!!</Title><Msg>Egypt was their 1st major FUP, then Libya and now their headed straight for another debacle in Syria! And that says nothing about having lost 2 Wars in Iraq and Afghanistan!! This guy is just the most amazing Mass FUP in American history!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371244302620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371255851326-38</Id><Topic><Title>The stunning hypocricy is Obama's</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371238565230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:36:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Squeal, Squeal, Oink, Oink Most Repubs say he acted on conscience, something libs lack so they vilify him. The same thing Obama is doing with the Benghazi whistleblowers. If the leaker was a liberal goon from the same agency, you goons would be erecting a statue of him on the WH lawn. Do you understand what a hypocrite is? I didn't think so, you don't even know when you're being SMACKed. You just were. Hahahahahaha!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371255851326</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 20:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371262262071-39</Id><Topic><Title>The stunning hypocricy is Obama's</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371238565230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:36:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Dave Boyer The Washington Times Friday, June 14, 2013 The White House Friday defended the first family’s upcoming weeklong trip to Africa, which could cost taxpayers up to $100 million, as “great bang for our buck.” “There will be a great bang for our buck for being in Africa because when you travel to regions like Africa that don’t get a lot of presidential attention, you tend to have very longstanding and long-running impact from the visit,” said Ben Rhodes, a deputy national security adviser to President Obama. SEE RELATED: Report: Obama spent more hours golfing, vacationing than in economic meetings The Obamas’ trip, at a time of “sequestration” budget cuts, will take them to Senegal, Tanzania and South Africa from June 26 to July 3. Citing a conf</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1371262262071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371262707387-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Going For The Arab Spring Trifecta!!</Title><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1371244302620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:11:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The U.S. does nothing on it's on. It is simply a puppet state of those that run most of the world. They better make the most of it as their time is short.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371262707387</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371262851955-41</Id><Topic><Title>The stunning hypocricy is Obama's</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371238565230</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:36:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All you need to know about libs is that they don't believe in any restraints on their violations of law. Laws? We don't need no stinkin' laws.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371262851955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>