<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369728336894-1</Id><Topic><Title>Uh, the only scandal fading away is then where some thought our president was competent.</Title><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369711350014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 23:22:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a cute picture going around FB showing Obama, Biden &amp; Holder, with a caption saying, "If these guys are so clever, how come they don't know anything?"</Msg><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1369728336894</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 04:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369728638538-2</Id><Topic><Title>the trumped up pubbie 'scandals' have already faded away</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369689373045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason you can't see the original is because it's PRIVATE and Obumbles wont release it! Just like you private recxords at the IRS! That Lerner Lady, who took the Fifth, would NEVER release them with how much donations you gave to Republicans. Why that would be IMPROPER and she took the Fifth just to prove how much integrity she has! DRAIN THE SWAMP IN 2014!</Msg><Username>caliente.zorra</Username><Timestamp>1369728638538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 04:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369743186283-3</Id><Title>repubs,,,just shut up about taking 5th or lying on stand,,.reagan and ollie did it and you LOVED it..Your opinions</Title><Msg>mean nuthin and GREAT DROPKICK pauper!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369743186283</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 08:13:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369746458889-4</Id><Title>Is ORCL the real deal?</Title><Msg>Has anybody read in detail the articles being issued? Fascinating info that will help any investor or trader. Link:- tinyDOTcc/w5jhxw [ Remove DOT and Use . ]</Msg><Username>hoopeschad821</Username><Timestamp>1369746458889</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 09:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369754259915-5</Id><Title>Teach Your Kids About Taxes</Title><Msg>Eat 30% of their ice cream. Speaking of taxes, the people with authority to investigate tea party groups is the same crowd that abhors profiling at airports.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369754259915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369754441559-6</Id><Title>SMACK TIME</Title><Msg>Power mad Dems always seem to use an intimidating enforcement arm. That's right, like they used the Klan.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369754441559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369754709842-7</Id><Title>Overheard on the Golf Course</Title><Msg>Obama: Truthfully, can you see any obvious problem with my game? Caddy: Well, there's seems to be a clump of scht on the end of your club Obama starts to wipe the head of the club off with his hand towel. Caddy: No Sir, it's at the other end.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369754709842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369755601316-8</Id><Topic><Title>insiders SHORTING ??</Title><Username>trader_best</Username><Timestamp>1369445105215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 21:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im gonna do that!</Msg><Username>jeffdon234</Username><Timestamp>1369755601316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369758405116-9</Id><Topic><Title>Teach Your Kids About Taxes</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369754259915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt anyone really knows how much in direct and indirect taxes they pay. My first full time job of 48 hrs. per week, no time and a half at $1 per hour paid me $96 every two weeks. With income tax AND SS I paid about $7.50 and netted $88 and some change. Businesses figure taxes as a cost of doing business and add it to their prices. "Liberals" know this yet they keep hollering to "raise taxes on big business". These taxes also make our businesses less competitive on the world market. I think it is deliberate and meant to lower us down to the levels of the lesser countries.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369758405116</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369759024178-10</Id><Topic><Title>Teach Your Kids About Taxes</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369754259915</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:17:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In my case, our 26 year old son sells insurance. Straight commission. He doesn't even get a weekly draw. He is a 1099 employee which means he personally is responsible for everything. No one is more keenly aware of the taxes he pays than he an other 1099 employees. Matter of fact, the best way to get folks clamoring for more cost efficient gov is to make everyone responsible for their own tax. The pols will hear none of it because they know they'd be on losing end.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369759024178</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369759161610-11</Id><Title>The Pentagon Under Obama Has Become Garbage!</Title><Msg>It looks like Obama is targeting Jiminy Carter's staggering achievements as Commander In Chief!! Any 3 or 4 Star General worth their salt would resign rather than report to Captain Obama &amp; Sgt Hagel!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1369759161610</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369760966861-12</Id><Title>We had great schools before the Dems destroyed them with diversity.</Title><Msg>The Dems destroyed the schools with diversity.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1369760966861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369761670188-13</Id><Title>pub shizer storm hissie fit 'scandals' have faded away....ha ha ha</Title><Msg>no mention of them in the news for many days now.... and pub honchos like rand paul have already moved on... back to trying to blast obamacare but losing big on that too...... the low private insurer prices announced for Ca have blown away all the loser pub doom and gloom about Romneycare...er.... Obamacare.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761670188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369761741049-14</Id><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Msg>from Forbes: Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates Every now and again, a political pundit is required to stand up and admit to the world that he or she got it wrong. For me, this would be one of those moments. For quite some time, I have been predicting that Obamacare would likely mean higher insurance rates in the individual market for the “young immortals” and others under the age of 40. At the same time, my expectation was that those who fall into the older age ranges would benefit greatly as their premium charges would be lowered thanks to the Affordable Care Act. It is increasingly clear that I had it wrong. Yesterday, Covered California—the name given to the healthcare exchange created pursuant to the Affordable Care Act that will serve the largest population of insured citizens in the nation—released the premium rates submitted by participating health insurance companies for the four health insurance program categories (bronze, silver, gold and platinum) established by the Affordable Care Act, along with the catastrophic policy created for and available to those under the age of 30. Upon reviewing the data, I was indeed shocked by the proposed premium rates—but not in the way you might expect. The jolt that I was experiencing was not the result of the predicted out-of-control premium costs but the shock of rates far lower than what I expected—even at the lowest end of the age scale.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369765155051-15</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is it with you? You scour the internet for meaningless drivel from one side of the issue. You are compulsive to the point of disturbed. The Obamacare Insurance Exchange?? The government in the insurance business now?? Why not, LOL, they got into the car business. The bigger shock is when they get their rates raised every 4 or 5 years. The majority of 20 to 35 yr olds are less likely to have major medical problems and being they are forced to be covered, start with low rates. That's reasonable but as with private insurance, premiums will increase as they age. That is not going to change with Obamacare. And who the he'll wants the IRS involved in managing Obamacare? They might target conservatives as to what treatment or surgery they can or can't have and you will be required to pay a surgery tax before admittance.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369765155051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369765559744-16</Id><Title>Our Illustrious AG</Title><Msg>We know lawyers are seasoned liars but Holder takes the cake. This guy is so dumb he thinks he can fool Congress. Never saw anything like it. Oh wait, Hillary comes in second.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369765559744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369766254718-17</Id><Topic><Title>Our Illustrious AG</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369765559744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Washington launches four different investigations into IRS mess... Issa subpoenas State Dept. documents on Benghazi... REPORT: HOLDER WENT JUDGE SHOPPING TO OBTAIN FOX NEWS SUBPOENA... House Judiciary investigating whether Attorney General lied under oath... REPORT: Holder 'Beginning to Feel Creeping Sense of Personal Remorse'...</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369766254718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 14:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369767986261-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Pentagon Under Obama Has Become Garbage!</Title><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1369759161610</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 12:39:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A couple of TRILLION dollars in High End Department of Defense weapons systems and engineering designs hacked by the GD Chinese... and you can bet that Obama knew about it before the Election! Just more GD Lies, Incompetence and Cover-ups!! The Regime and it's Generals should be sacked!</Msg><Username>corpusamericana</Username><Timestamp>1369767986261</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369769500171-19</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeez you are stupid and dishonest, right now the CA exchange is offering better prices than I can get in my state, and fyi policies for young people are VERY cheap, VERY good and might even be free depending on income........whine all you want, you are just a loser. so far everyone thinks these exchanges are off to a good start and honest critics have changed their tune as shown by Forbes piece. Only a boob and a creep like you would be against this: "the entire idea of the exchanges is to require health insurance companies to compete openly with one another by offering identical coverage programs in the three created classes—each offering insurance coverage that actually delivers meaningful protection to customers—and then openly disclosing the price each insurance company will charge for that policy. Thus, shoppers can clearly see which company has the best price on an apples-to-apples basis."</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369769500171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369770981917-20</Id><Title>Obama &amp; Christie Together Again! Isn't It Just Wonderful!</Title><Msg>Tweedledee and Tweedledum!</Msg><Username>ivleeg_garbage</Username><Timestamp>1369770981917</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 15:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369771237718-21</Id><Title>Obama/Holder/Jarrett lies are catching up to them. They will fall on the scandals</Title><Msg>All of which are HUGE. Polls show 80% of Americans see them as big issues, and over 60% think the administration is covering crimes. Ouch!</Msg><Username>psychrelic</Username><Timestamp>1369771237718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369775469287-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama/Holder/Jarrett lies are catching up to them. They will fall on the scandals</Title><Username>psychrelic</Username><Timestamp>1369771237718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 16:00:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeez psychwrek, you are such a liar..... the truth is that Obama has GAINED in the polls since the phony pub hissy fit 'scandals' and everyone knows they are a crock of loser pub lies....... ha ha ha but sure, good luck with your wish. "Wish in one hand, #$%$ in the other. See which one gets filled first." ha ha ha ha</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369775469287</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369775898955-23</Id><Title>THE WEINER IS RISING!</Title><Msg>Here in NYC!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1369775898955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369776012716-24</Id><Topic><Title>Overheard on the Golf Course</Title><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369754709842</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 11:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! LOL! LOL!</Msg><Username>ourfirstpantroglodytepresident</Username><Timestamp>1369776012716</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 17:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369781218114-25</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not the one whining, You complain about everything from slavery to gay Repubs or about things you think everyone should support. I'm not against lower insurance rates for young people, you goon. I merely pointed out that the rates will rise as they age. Learn to read. Talk about stupid comments. People already shop around for the best price for coverage now. Private insurance can compete and do. I don't need Obamacare to get quality care. Obamacare is another option that puts insurance companies under the hand of government. For the cheapest coverage as you laud, patients will have deductibles, make co-pays and a percentage of hospital stays, did they elaborate on that? Now go scour the internet for some other meaningless tripe that agrees with your tripe.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369781218114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 18:46:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369782118712-26</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are 100% dishonest. THIS IS NOT the way the insurers operate without the ACA: : "the entire idea of the exchanges is to require health insurance companies to compete openly with one another by offering identical coverage programs in the three created classes—each offering insurance coverage that actually delivers meaningful protection to customers—and then openly disclosing the price each insurance company will charge for that policy. Thus, shoppers can clearly see which company has the best price on an apples-to-apples basis." in fact, without the ACA, they keep their accounting hidden. that is how they would only pay out 70 cents on the dollar in actual health benefits , WITH NO TRANSPARENCY or accounting for the rest , which they simply called overhead... NOW they must pay at least 85 cents in actual healthcare and account for the rest, FULL transparency..... and NOW you can get GOOD insurance at GOOD prices and not worry about getting DUMPED or worry about coverage... and I just just checked and for what my employer and I pay now, I could get on the Ca exchange for several hundred a month LESS even without any subsidy which I would not qualify for.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369782118712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 19:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369787299044-27</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I Had Kaiser in CA. with low co-pays. They took what Medi-Care paid and covered me and my wife with no additional payments. I recently moved to AZ. and I am paying $3,000 per year on top of Medi-Care plus large co-pays as high as $70. The insureance coimpanies get in bed with the pols of each state and pass laws making it almost impossible for competition to move in. I repeat, the insureance companies wrote "Obama Care" and will profit immensely from it. None of the thieves in Congress even read it before voting on it. It deserves to be called "Obama Care".</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369787299044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 20:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369789473403-28</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, Tell me what I was dishonest about. You won't, you can't. You accuse but have no rebuttal other than your usual blathering about what you think you know. You have no answer for what I brought to your attention, so you call me dishonest?? For someone who has all the answers, you are mighty ignorant about what Obamacare really entails. You should run for Congress, they have no idea either.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369789473403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369790670118-29</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are dishonest because you don't acknowledge the improvements that I pointed out. here , i'll show you again: THIS IS NOT the way the insurers operate without the ACA: : "the entire idea of the exchanges is to require health insurance companies to compete openly with one another by offering identical coverage programs in the three created classes—each offering insurance coverage that actually delivers meaningful protection to customers—and then openly disclosing the price each insurance company will charge for that policy. Thus, shoppers can clearly see which company has the best price on an apples-to-apples basis." in fact, without the ACA, they keep their accounting hidden. that is how they would only pay out 70 cents on the dollar in actual health benefits , WITH NO TRANSPARENCY or accounting for the rest , which they simply called overhead... NOW they must pay at least 85 cents in actual healthcare and account for the rest, FULL transparency..... and NOW you can get GOOD insurance at GOOD prices and not worry about getting DUMPED or worry about coverage... and I just just checked and for what my employer and I pay now, I could get on the Ca exchange for several hundred a month LESS even without any subsidy which I would not qualify for.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369790670118</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369792438438-30</Id><Topic><Title>pub shizer storm hissie fit 'scandals' have faded away....ha ha ha</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761670188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Early in the game Messybird. Look at SS and Medicare now. They are trillions in the red and totally unsustainable. The abyss is near.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369792438438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369792791689-31</Id><Topic><Title>the trumped up pubbie 'scandals' have already faded away</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369689373045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-27 17:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scandals are brewing like an early keg of wine just injected with more yeast. IRS scandal was described by Carney as inappropriate. George Will said using your salad fork with the entree is inappropriate. What this administration did was criminal. CRIMINAL.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369792791689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 21:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369792988326-32</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The loser would fit right in with this lying administration. They have perfected the "I don't know the answer to that" when questioned about anything they are responsible for.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369792988326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 22:03:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369796530470-33</Id><Title>what traders dont know!</Title><Msg>there is a easy way making doe! i subscribed to wallstreetotc a month ago and made over 25k! love this site! highly recommend it to any trader! always make over 300% gains</Msg><Username>rogerblack750</Username><Timestamp>1369796530470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>27</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369796873356-34</Id><Topic><Title>what traders dont know!</Title><Username>rogerblack750</Username><Timestamp>1369796530470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really? i like it i subscribed too</Msg><Username>traderporter</Username><Timestamp>1369796873356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369797239723-35</Id><Topic><Title>Unexpected Health Insurance Rate Shock-California Obamacare Insurance Exchange Announces Premium Rates</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369761741049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 13:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Posting this drivel once was enough. You think if you stayed up all night posting it a few dozen times, it would change my perspective? Doubt it, DA You want the IRS to manage your healthcare? Lots a luck, That old saying, "you get what you pay for" is true with insurance. Always has been. You think Obamacare will be the gold standard of health. Are you in for another shock.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369797239723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369798961980-36</Id><Topic><Title>insiders SHORTING ??</Title><Username>trader_best</Username><Timestamp>1369445105215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 21:25:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no way thats awesome</Msg><Username>traderporter</Username><Timestamp>1369798961980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-28 23:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>