<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369109491979-1</Id><Title>One Nugent less dumb</Title><Msg>Jeffrey Nugent Says Brother Ted Nugent Is Wrong On Background ... [May 19, 2013] Outspoken rocker Ted Nugent is now catching heat from his own brother on his uncompromising stance on gun rights. In a Washington Post op-ed published ... ( 2616</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369109491979</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 00:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369134011327-2</Id><Topic><Title>13 Benghazis That Occurred on Bush’s Watch Without a Peep from Fox News</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1368735218412</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-16 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New York State Assembly Speaker Sheldon Silver says 'I'm sorry' for his role in the Vito Lopez sex scandal coverup Silver faces growing pressure to quit leadership post, including from upstate Democratic Assemblyman Michael Kearns</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369134011327</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 07:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369137954648-3</Id><Title>Public Sharply Critical on IRS,</Title><Msg>They shouldn't be.. Ya gotta make sure these repub hate groups pay taxes. They won't unless forced to. People love taking money from but just don't like paying into..no one wants their programs to be cut and that's a fact. I wanna know how many repub hate groups were rejected for tax exempt status!!! A group put together just to hate Obama should not be tax exempt!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369137954648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369138556321-4</Id><Title>Killing of gay man in NYC draws protesters SEEBE! THIS has been on the increase!</Title><Msg>Repubs attacking and killing gay people, not your made up thing about black gangs,</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369138556321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369139028025-5</Id><Title>repubs claim they're terribly upset by "Obama leaks" yet when Obama does something to stop it repubs pretend to be upset.</Title><Msg>ANDDDDDDDDDDDDDD nothing Obama is doing isn't same as what repubs have done before!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369139028025</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369140372084-6</Id><Title>pubs now claims leaking classified national security info is a 1st ammendment right?</Title><Msg>spying is Ok, now I guess... too bad for the Rosenbergs who were executed for leaking USA abomb secrets to the Russians.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369140372084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369141004804-7</Id><Title>Fantastic Advancement for ORCL. Read Now!</Title><Msg>Has any one taken a look at the articles being released? Eye opening details that will help any investor or trader. alturlDotcom/i2seq</Msg><Username>jimmierobert</Username><Timestamp>1369141004804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369141382416-8</Id><Title>repubs will and do say ANYTHING</Title><Msg>On one hand they say Obama is a #$%$ and lets everyone do whatever they want..a minute later repubs say Obama is a tyrant breaking laws all the time....ever notice that ya do that repubs! ??? DROPKICK pauper</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369141382416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369141486388-9</Id><Topic><Title>Subway.........bad........</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369108744333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:59:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not much of a study, silly really. It only showed that you can eat say, 1,000 calories in a meal at both places. fact is though, a 1,000 calories of veggies are WAY better for you than a 1,000 calories of red meat, something the silly study didn't mention. Over consumption of red meat IS the primary cause of coronary heart disease. about zero percent is cause by a person's genes.....eating lots of saturated fat clogs up the arteries, it is as simple as that. and the only know cure is a vegan diet such as dr Ornish's.... which is scientifically proven to REVERSE coronary heart disease......“When you see the golden arches, you’re probably on the road to the pearly gates” Dr Castelli “A low-fat plant-based diet would not only lower the heart attack rate about 85%, but would lower the cancer rate 60%.” William Castelli, M .D . Director, Framingham Health Study; National Heart, Lung and Blood Institute</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369141486388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:04:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369142175364-10</Id><Topic><Title>Public Sharply Critical on IRS,</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369137954648</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:05:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democratic Senate panel OKs tax-welfare benefits for newly legal immigrants... SHOCK: Accused Fort Hood Shooter Paid $278,000 While Awaiting Trial...</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1369142175364</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369142263982-11</Id><Topic><Title>Subway.........bad........</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369108744333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:59:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you feel good about Subway and I kinda used to also. First thing that got me about the place was the stuff that comes in, made elsewhere,..egg whites,....guagamole(worst guac I've ever had) I recall that guy a few months ago protesting against them saying the meats are prepackaged at a factory in mid America. I can no longer consider their food to be "fresh". I think they have a far better reputation than they deserve. If ya tell them "everything" or let them put everything they'll put mayo and oil on a sandwhich to me it's one OR the other,..their sands taste only like onions pickles &amp; peppers,,..all their food is like vegetarian sands because that's all I can taste anyway no need to even have the meat,,.ever see the meat as they put it on? It looks like it came by truck from Iowa, preportioned, pre-sliced. You can get all veg sandwich anywhere. I'd think. 35 years ago I was making and eating out veg guacamole sands on whole wheat so I know ya don't need meat on a sandwhich to make it tasty but.I predict soon SW's reputaton will get worse. They're very lucky to have that healthy thing associated with them. I do like Jarrod though.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369142263982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369142317588-12</Id><Topic><Title>repubs will and do say ANYTHING</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369141382416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tornado kills at least 91 people.... Daily Show creator mocks: 'Tornado clearly targets conservatives'... Dem Senator uses deaths for rant over global warming... Flashback 1975 Democrats: Outbreaks Blamed On Global COOLING...</Msg><Username>onedinosaur</Username><Timestamp>1369142317588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369142419560-13</Id><Topic><Title>repubs will and do say ANYTHING</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369141382416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PJM EXCLUSIVE: Ex-Diplomats Report New Benghazi Whistleblowers with Info Devastating to Clinton and Obama May 21st, 2013 - 12:05 am More whistleblowers will emerge shortly in the escalating Benghazi scandal, according to two former U.S. diplomats who spoke with PJ Media Monday afternoon. These whistleblowers, colleagues of the former diplomats, are currently securing legal counsel because they work in areas not fully protected by the Whistleblower law. According to the diplomats, what these whistleblowers will say will be at least as explosive as what we have already learned about the scandal, including details about what really transpired in Benghazi that are potentially devastating to both Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton. The former diplomats inform PJM the new revelations concentrate in two areas — what Ambassador Chris Stevens was actually doing in Benghazi and the pressure put on General Carter Ham, then in command of U.S. Africa Command (AFRICOM) and therefore responsible for Libya, not to act to protect jeopardized U.S. personnel. Stevens’ mission in Benghazi, they will say, was to buy back Stinger missiles from al-Qaeda groups issued to them by the State Department, not by the CIA. Such a mission would usually be a CIA effort, but the intelligence agency had opposed the idea because of the high risk involved in arming “insurgents” with powerful weapons that endanger civilian aircraft. Hillary Clinton still wanted to proceed because, in part, as one of the diplomats said, she wanted “to overthrow Gaddafi on the cheap.” This left Stevens in the position of having to clean up the scandalous enterprise when it became clear that the “insurgents” actually were al-Qaeda – indeed, in the view of one of the diplomats, the same group that attacked the consulate and ended up killing Stevens.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369142419560</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369143046139-14</Id><Title>Ex-Diplomats Report New Benghazi Whistleblowers with Info Devastating to Clinton and Obama</Title><Msg>Wanna bet???????? You repubs always pretend things like this. Seebe always makes posts like that.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143046139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369143087824-15</Id><Topic><Title>t black on white crime is never a hate crime. Ever notice that?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006316967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the 'love' just oozes out of your posts.......</Msg><Username>newguy7001</Username><Timestamp>1369143087824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369143262543-16</Id><Topic><Title>Subway.........bad........</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369108744333</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-20 23:59:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just saying all the study proved is that a group of teens can get as unhealthy a meal at subway as they can at mcdonalds. However, the fact is the FOCUS of mcdonald's is red meat.... and American's hugely over consume red meat which is THE cause of coronary heart disease. at least at subway you can get a veggie sandwich on WHOLE wheat....... does mikey's even offer whole wheat? of course you can just eat a salad at mickeys.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369143262543</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369143273869-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ex-Diplomats Report New Benghazi Whistleblowers with Info Devastating to Clinton and Obama</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143046139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:30:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We haven't heard what the real scandal is yet. Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qeada through Benghazi. And THAT is the scandal Obama Admin is trying to keep hidden.</Msg><Username>goodgay000000001</Username><Timestamp>1369143273869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369143275260-18</Id><Title>PMJ news is REPUBLICAN</Title><Msg>of course they report repub lies.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143275260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369143283315-19</Id><Title>GDTK looks prime for a breakout</Title><Msg>With million in assets on their books (check their financials) it is amazing how GDTK is trading so low. Once this thing gets the attention it deserves everyone will be kicking themselves</Msg><Username>byersjoshua366</Username><Timestamp>1369143283315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369143369234-20</Id><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Msg>Repubs are soooooooooooooo full of corpis dabien!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369143726858-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ex-Diplomats Report New Benghazi Whistleblowers with Info Devastating to Clinton and Obama</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143046139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:30:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Tornado should clearly targets conservatives': Daily Show creator faces backlash over insensitive tweet PUBLISHED: 00:47 EST, 21 May 2013 | UPDATED: 02:21 EST, 21 May 2013</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1369143726858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369143857283-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ex-Diplomats Report New Benghazi Whistleblowers with Info Devastating to Clinton and Obama</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143046139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:30:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Administration pays accused Fort Hood Shooter Paid $278,000 While Awaiting Trial Injured soldier outraged suspected shooter receives salary while his family financially struggles in recovery Tuesday, May 21, 2013 | Updated 8:14 AM CDT The Department of Defense confirms to NBC 5 Investigates that accused Fort Hood shooter Major Nidal Hasan has been paid more than $278,000 since the Nov. 5, 2009 shooting that left 13 dead 32 injured.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1369143857283</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369144550006-23</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all part of a mau mau, madrassa, Weimar republic, UN globalization plot . Buy Gold NOW, it is your only hope.... you already have your guns and ammo, right?</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369144550006</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369144582838-24</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Indications are that the AP Wire Tapping scandal has deeper motives. There is another scandal the Obama Admin is trying to cover up and is afraid the public will learn about. We may learn in a few days.</Msg><Username>goodgay000000001</Username><Timestamp>1369144582838</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369144644563-25</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tornado Kills 24 Children at Elementary School, Many Missing. Democrats elated. Read Latest Breaking News</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369144644563</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369144751746-26</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice how quick I got TWO responses to my post. One refuting it and the other trying to burry it. Obama Minions are on the loose!</Msg><Username>goodgay000000001</Username><Timestamp>1369144751746</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:59:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369144840083-27</Id><Topic><Title>Ex-Diplomats Report New Benghazi Whistleblowers with Info Devastating to Clinton and Obama</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143046139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:30:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice the instant Obama Minion responses trying to burry this post!</Msg><Username>goodgay000000001</Username><Timestamp>1369144840083</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369144934470-28</Id><Topic><Title>PMJ news is REPUBLICAN</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143275260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PMJ = Postgraduate Medical Journal???</Msg><Username>goodgay000000001</Username><Timestamp>1369144934470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369145003050-29</Id><Topic><Title>Killing of gay man in NYC draws protesters SEEBE! THIS has been on the increase!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369138556321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Killing of Gay Man in NYC Draws Protesters NEW YORK May 21, 2013 (AP) "This happened in Midtown, during the day, with a ton of people around," one of the victims, Nick Porto, wrote in a Facebook posting. "... When are we safe?" 32-year-old Mark Carson was felled by a single gunshot to the head early Saturday near from the site of 1969 riots that helped give rise to the gay rights movement. Carson was killed Saturday as he walked with a companion through the Village. Police say a man charged with murder as a hate crime shot Carson in the heart of one of the city's most progressive neighborhoods. http://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/nypd-presence-bias-killing-gay-man-19219748</Msg><Username>goodgay000000001</Username><Timestamp>1369145003050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:03:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369147811233-30</Id><Title>the killers in NYC that dropkick reefs to were all Progressive Dems.</Title><Msg>Read the local paper.</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369147811233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369147879535-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ex-Diplomats Report New Benghazi Whistleblowers with Info Devastating to Clinton and Obama</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143046139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:30:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sandy Hook: Admin changed story to push banning automatic weapons. When the truth comes out, it will be the end of Barry.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1369147879535</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369147889082-32</Id><Topic><Title>Ex-Diplomats Report New Benghazi Whistleblowers with Info Devastating to Clinton and Obama</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143046139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:30:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There will eventually be jail time over Benghazi.</Msg><Username>gr8d84f8</Username><Timestamp>1369147889082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369147999137-33</Id><Topic><Title>t black on white crime is never a hate crime. Ever notice that?</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369006316967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-19 19:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON | Tue May 21, 2013 4:06am EDT (Reuters) - With the White House already reeling from three major controversies, some lawmakers lawmakers are zeroing in on what they perceive is another possible scandal tied to President Barack Obama's landmark health reform law just as it nears implementation. On top of the troubles the administration is facing over its handling of the attack on the Benghazi mission, the Internal Revenue Service's targeting of conservative groups, and the Justice Department's seizure of Associated Press phone records, lawmakers hope to target Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius. They are questioning her soliciting of funds on behalf of a non-profit group, called Enroll America, from two private entities, a practice which if not unprecedented is at the very least unusual. Federal law bars officials from soliciting any organization or individual with whom they do business or regulate.</Msg><Username>hikemanymiles</Username><Timestamp>1369147999137</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369148013598-34</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That. Is exactly what happened. Like burning down a house to hide a body, they used the timing of the AP snooping to try and dig out something else related to the admin.</Msg><Username>blackmesainterloper</Username><Timestamp>1369148013598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369148125465-35</Id><Title>All the 'love' just oozes out of your posts.......</Title><Msg>I USED not despise you muthas but you've CAUSED me to.,..because you all suck corpiss.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369148125465</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369148200549-36</Id><Title>GDTK is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>GDTK looking like it is ready to go. So undervalued here. Look at their site. They have some huge properties with proven reserves. Check it out</Msg><Username>hansenlevi299</Username><Timestamp>1369148200549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369148267126-37</Id><Title>Looks like I have found another winner. Check out GDTK</Title><Msg>GDTK is looking good here. They show some huge assets in their financials so the book value is atleast .50 cents per share. I am loading up</Msg><Username>hansenlevi299</Username><Timestamp>1369148267126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369148380919-38</Id><Title>Dropkick = a racist. Just read his posts and it becomes clear as a bell.</Title><Msg>He keeps bringing up lies from past centuries, just so he can sneak in racist references and comments and post epithets using symbols. You should be ashamed.</Msg><Username>psychrelic</Username><Timestamp>1369148380919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369150526497-39</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For $221k, July 4th Fireworks Show on National Mall in Washington Will Go On 7:27 AM, May 21, 2013 • By JERYL BIER Send to Kindle Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts The show will go on. Sequestration may have cost Washington D.C. tourists a chance to tour the White House, but the Independence Day fireworks will go off as planned. A contract was awarded yesterday to Garden State Fireworks of Millington, NJ for $221,819.77. The listing for bids on the typically business-like fbo.gov website contained this somewhat colorful solicitation: Provide supervision, labor, materials, supplies and equipment necessary to present an innovative, bounteous, dynamic and attractive fireworks display for Independence Day on the Grounds of the Washington Monument, Washington, D.C. on July 4, 2013.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369150526497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369152195970-40</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IRS targeted conservative college interns 10:36 PM 05/20/2013 5 The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) demanded information about conservative groups’ college-aged interns, prompting outrage from one of the country’s top conservative activist organizations and leading one former intern to wonder whether his family’s pizza parlor would be endangered. The IRS requested, in an audit, the names of the conservative Leadership Institute’s 2008 interns, as well as specific information about their internship work and where the interns were employed in 2012, according to a document request the IRS sent to the Leadership Institute, dated February 14, 2012.</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1369152195970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369152201945-41</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions are that the Obama Admin was doing gun running to Al Qaida</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369143369234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 09:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He’s No Nixon 8:00 AM, May 21, 2013 • By WILLIAM KRISTOL Send to Kindle Single Page Print Larger Text Smaller Text Alerts The thoughtful Carl Cannon has written a piece, "Richard Milhous Obama," concluding that our current president has more in common with our 37th than President Obama's partisans would like to acknowledge. The estimable Victor Davis Hansen has weighed in, defending against liberal dissents the proposition that "Nixon Is a Fair Comparison" with Obama. Nixon depart.png I protest. Will no one stand up for Richard Nixon? Richard Nixon was a combat veteran, a staunch and brave anti-Communist, a man who took on the liberal establishment and at times his own party's as well, a leader who often thought for himself and had the courage of his convictions, a president who assembled a first-rate Cabinet and one who—while flawed both in character and in policy judgment—usually tried to confront the real problems and deal with challenges of his times. Richard Nixon led neither the country nor his own administration from behind.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1369152201945</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369153844139-42</Id><Title>Global warming is a result of Obama's radical energy policy.</Title><Msg>Dems don't care about the environment. All they care about is welfare.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1369153844139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369154016280-43</Id><Topic><Title>pubs now claims leaking classified national security info is a 1st ammendment right?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369140372084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depends on whether the classification is to protect vital secrets or to cover up government crimes. In too many cases it is for the latter reason.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369154016280</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369154588031-44</Id><Title>I think GDTK is about to go to $1+</Title><Msg>I am getting all the GDTK I can at these levels. Check their website and financials. This thing is so undervalued here.</Msg><Username>hicksluke487</Username><Timestamp>1369154588031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369157183925-45</Id><Topic><Title>I think GDTK is about to go to $1+</Title><Username>hicksluke487</Username><Timestamp>1369154588031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 12:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are a GD JERK!</Msg><Username>turbotaxkid</Username><Timestamp>1369157183925</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369157287891-46</Id><Topic><Title>(IGXT)MCap $32 M/ Price 0.64 /NDA acceptance within 1 Week // TGT $2-4 before FDA decision</Title><Username>fdaplayer</Username><Timestamp>1369151683901</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 11:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you are a poopie head spammer!</Msg><Username>turbotaxkid</Username><Timestamp>1369157287891</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369157404278-47</Id><Topic><Title>pubs now claims leaking classified national security info is a 1st ammendment right?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369140372084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How could Obama commit a crime? Wasn't he of virgin birth? HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>turbotaxkid</Username><Timestamp>1369157404278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:30:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369158519791-48</Id><Title>IRS Not To Be Trusted</Title><Msg>What Steve Miller, IRS Commissioner said about the whole targeting of conservative groups thing, "Mistakes were made, but they were in no way made with a partisan motivation." Yeah, "Mistakes were made", try saying that when the IRS audits you. Obama knows this is going to have major repercussions and you know it's a bad subject when O is saying, "Hey, lets talk about Benghazi."</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369158519791</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369159139902-49</Id><Title>Wow! Start your DD on GDTK because I think it is about to soar.</Title><Msg>GDTK is looking good here. They show some huge assets in their financials so the book value is atleast .50 cents per share. I am loading up</Msg><Username>tdillard358</Username><Timestamp>1369159139902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369159177588-50</Id><Title>Check out GDTK right now! It is about to go on a massive run</Title><Msg>GDTK is the stock to watch. Financials show some huge assets along with proven mining properties. You need to start some research on GDTK, could be the next mining play to really make investors rich</Msg><Username>tdillard358</Username><Timestamp>1369159177588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 13:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369159308030-51</Id><Topic><Title>pubs now claims leaking classified national security info is a 1st ammendment right?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369140372084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just elated that the Bummer admin never leaked any classified info. They are too pure for that. LOSERS.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369159308030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369159535805-52</Id><Topic><Title>Killing of gay man in NYC draws protesters SEEBE! THIS has been on the increase!</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369138556321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminds me of the infamous Dr. who killed thousands of unborn and newly born babies in Philadelphia. Where are they safe?</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369159535805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369160068494-53</Id><Title>Rand Paul has it right.</Title><Msg>The Senate panel asking the questions of Tim Cook and his tax advisors should be the ones getting grilled for spending trillions beyond what they take in. Panel got it bass ackwards.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369160068494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369161877273-54</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul has it right.</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369160068494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The little punk is never right nor is other Ky sen.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369161877273</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369162449208-55</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul has it right.</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1369160068494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:14:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White House IRS timeline shifts again Jay Carney listens to a question during his daily news briefing at the White House in Washington, Wednesday, May 15, 2013. | AP Photo Carney said he had not been among the senior staff informed of the IRS actions. | AP Photo By REID J. EPSTEIN | 5/21/13 2:27 PM EDT The White House explanation of what it knew about the IRS story ahead of the first press reports on the controversy shifted once again Tuesday. Just a day after telling reporters that chief of staff Denis McDonough had learned of the situation about a month ago, press secretary Jay Carney revealed that White House officials had consulted with the IRS on how to initially present to the public the story that the agency had targeted conservative tax-exempt groups for extra scrutiny. Continue Reading There was “discussion about the possibility of a speech” by Lois Lerner, who oversaw the IRS’s work on tax-exempt groups, Carney said, and conversation about testimony by the acting commissioner of the agency and “what he would say” if asked about the issue. t</Msg><Username>atomicquark</Username><Timestamp>1369162449208</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 14:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369165538687-56</Id><Title>Dr. who killed thousands of unborn and newly born babies in</Title><Msg>We need millions more aborts!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369165538687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 15:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369165610059-57</Id><Title>Dr. who killed thousands of unborn BLOBS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Years after birth you're still a blob.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369165610059</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 15:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369171894596-58</Id><Title>More IRS dirt. Head of Exempt Division will take the fifth tomorrow</Title><Msg>...whichnbyndefinition means she was involved in a crime.</Msg><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1369171894596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 17:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369172044904-59</Id><Title>More IRS dirt part II - logs and IG report appear to link Obama directly to IRS story</Title><Msg>Inspector General report and WH logs show that IR Union Chief Met Colleen Kelly w/ Obama at WH  March 30/ 2010, next day IRS began targeting Teaparty and other Conservative groups. Hmmmm. Didn't he say he first learned about any IRS harassment from the news last Friday? Curious indeed. The empire is crumbling.</Msg><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1369172044904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 17:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369172241372-60</Id><Title>More IRS dirt, part duh! IG report and WH logs appear to show Obama with direct link to harassment.</Title><Msg>Inspector General report and WH logs show that IR Union Chief Met Colleen Kelly w/ Obama at WH  March 30/ 2010, next day IRS began targeting Teaparty and other Conservative groups. Hmmm. Didn't Obama saybhe first learned of any IRS harrassment in e news last Friday? Curious indeed. The evil starship begins to come apart.</Msg><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1369172241372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 17:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369172633433-61</Id><Topic><Title>More IRS dirt. Head of Exempt Division will take the fifth tomorrow</Title><Username>cockedlockedtorock</Username><Timestamp>1369171894596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 17:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Congress is smart, they will grant her complete immunity. Then if she takes the fifth, she will be in contempt and an be jailed.</Msg><Username>jomoredux</Username><Timestamp>1369172633433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 17:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369177661808-62</Id><Title>whichnbyndefinition means she was involved in a crime.</Title><Msg>Yup.just as it was when your hero Ollie North did it! NICE DROPKICK PAUPER! You repubs CAN'T say ANYTHING w/o it being super hypocritical! DOUBLE DROPKICK! YA GOT NUTHIN! Never had never will!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369177661808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369177805853-63</Id><Title>ABORTION IS GREAT!</Title><Msg>More abortions are even BETTER! DROPKICK! Ya wanna teach young kids about sex?.NO YA DON'T Then ya deserve aborts! You're to BLAME for aborts! Aborts go straight to heaven! Whats better than that ?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369177805853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369177860703-64</Id><Title>If Congress is smart, they will grant her complete immunity. Then if she takes the fifth, she will be in contempt and an be jailed.</Title><Msg>Just like OLLIE NORTH! Then repubs bailed him out! DROPKICK!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369177860703</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369177912020-65</Id><Title>Not to mention that POS DUMMY REAGAN who LIED under oath!</Title><Msg>YA GOT NUTHIN! TRIPLE DROPKICK PUNKS!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369177912020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:11:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369177960049-66</Id><Title>repubs are schhummm of earth</Title><Msg>and you KNOW IT! DROPKICK!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369177960049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369178188435-67</Id><Title>repubs,,,,,you can't say a single word w/o being hypocritical!</Title><Msg>TRY ME! DROPKICK!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369178188435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369179859781-68</Id><Title>....2 Moroccans tried for homosexuality get 4 months</Title><Msg>Hey repubs.......Moroccans are better than YOU! You'd want LIFE for them.or death</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369179859781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369180245411-69</Id><Title>in 2006, when tax officials threatened and persecuted liberal churches during the presidency of George W. Bush.</Title><Msg>yuuup</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369180245411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:50:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369180315689-70</Id><Title>repubs you're nuthing but corpiss dabien</Title><Msg>I can dropkick all of you in my sleep</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369180315689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369181603228-71</Id><Title>IRS official toplead the 5th</Title><Msg>The Los Angeles Times reported Tuesday afternoon that Lois Lerner, who heads up the Internal Revenue Service's tax-exempt division, plans to invoke the Fifth Amendment to the U.S. Constitution in a hearing Wednesday before the House Committee on Oversight and Government Affairs. ................................................................................................................................................................ perfectly constitutional and also suspicious as all 5th amendment pleas are.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369181603228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:13:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369182223319-72</Id><Topic><Title>IRS official toplead the 5th</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369181603228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:13:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like your hero Ollie North.what's your pernt?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369182223319</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369182501380-73</Id><Title>you suuucccummmmmms LOVED it when reagun lied claiming he couldn't recall and when PUNK Ollie North took the 5th1</Title><Msg>YOU LOVED IT! Now ya have a problem with it? Don't you IDIOTS EVER THINK before TRYING to post?</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369182501380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369182534155-74</Id><Topic><Title>you suuucccummmmmms LOVED it when reagun lied claiming he couldn't recall and when PUNK Ollie North took the 5th1</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369182501380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:28:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have dropkicked everyone of you all the time!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369182534155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369183450811-75</Id><Topic><Title>....2 Moroccans tried for homosexuality get 4 months</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369179859781</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 19:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The cape crusading goon strikes again. Here's buckwheat, all by himself , up on his soapbox with his pointless opinions. . I'll bite just to make a fool of you. Life or death? Hmmmmm. When have gays ever been tried in this country for being gay? Not a word about Moroccan justice. DA? But they are better than us. Maybe we should try it here. You think 4 months is enough? I'm always amazed at your fkd-up thinking. SMACK!</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1369183450811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369183643764-76</Id><Title>test</Title><Msg>eom</Msg><Username>xxxy453</Username><Timestamp>1369183643764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369185100669-77</Id><Topic><Title>pubs now claims leaking classified national security info is a 1st ammendment right?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369140372084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Commissioner knew more than year ago about IRS targeting conservatives... Ex-chief: Can't say how it happened... Conservative Group Waiting 3 Years For Approval Files Suit... IRS worker used government credit card for years-long AMAZON shopping spree... Top Dems blame scandal on tax code... MARCHING ORDERS: Liberal Pundits Gather in West Wing... GOP Sen. Launches Hotline for Reports of IRS Targeting... SCANDAL TIMELINE: Who knew what, when? TOP IRS OFFICIAL TO TAKE THE FIFTH</Msg><Username>liberals_plague_humanity</Username><Timestamp>1369185100669</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 21:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369186801662-78</Id><Topic><Title>pubs now claims leaking classified national security info is a 1st ammendment right?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1369140372084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 08:46:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, funny, he produces a "Birth Certificate". Experts say it is a forgery. The official records are STILL sealed. If the certificate was genuine then why are the records still sealed? "Liar, liar, pants on fire."</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369186801662</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 21:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369186959521-79</Id><Topic><Title>you suuucccummmmmms LOVED it when reagun lied claiming he couldn't recall and when PUNK Ollie North took the 5th1</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369182501380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:28:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever heard of Appendex IX? You and phony "Conservatives need to look up Reagan's record in it. He was no "Conservative". Just another leftist front man.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1369186959521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 21:42:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369191132845-80</Id><Title>There is no doubt that Obama has committed Treason!</Title><Msg>He has subverted the Constitution of the United States! He is a communist! And his (alleged) father was never legally married to his mother!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369191132845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 22:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369191334200-81</Id><Title>Patriotic Americans should waterboard Eric Holder until he confesses!</Title><Msg>Then torture him to death!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369191334200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 22:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369191618458-82</Id><Title>THEY WEREN'T 'BLOBS' YOU MORON!</Title><Msg>They were 27 week and older old babies in process! 26 week old babies, 6 months, can be saved if born premature! they are viable living humans! but you are a mindless 'blob' that should be terminated!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369191618458</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369192150526-83</Id><Title>OBAMA SAYS REPUBLICANS HAVE A 'WAR ON WOMEN"</Title><Msg>Because they prefer women whole, feminine, female, fertile and the happy mothers of living babies! But Democrats are the "protectors" of women because they want them, mutilated, androgenized, neutered, sterilized, and the bloody survivors of unsanitary abortion, with their murdered babies heaped in a plastic garbage cans! AND YOU 'USEFUL' IDIOTS VOTED THIS MAN TO A SECOND TERM!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369192150526</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:09:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369192369149-84</Id><Topic><Title>Patriotic Americans should waterboard Eric Holder until he confesses!</Title><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369191334200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 22:55:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's use impalement! It worked worked well when Vlad Tepes used it (against a certain Evil religious Group!)!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369192369149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:12:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369192651158-85</Id><Title>Chelsea Clinton is the New 'Multi-Faith Leader' at NYU</Title><Msg>WFT is a "Multi Faith Leader'? Can I hump Chelsea until she is pregnant? The Clintons should enjoy my child, their grand child! Jot To The World!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369192651158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:17:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369192773873-86</Id><Topic><Title>you suuucccummmmmms LOVED it when reagun lied claiming he couldn't recall and when PUNK Ollie North took the 5th1</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1369182501380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:28:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are incapable of intelligent thought so why should Republican posters think on your behalf? Total waste of time.</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369192773873</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369192848297-87</Id><Topic><Title>Chelsea Clinton is the New 'Multi-Faith Leader' at NYU</Title><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369192651158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chelsea is kind of cute, with her Mothers buck teeth. I would enjoy impregnating her!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369192848297</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369193081770-88</Id><Topic><Title>There is no doubt that Obama has committed Treason!</Title><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369191132845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 22:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been watching the Tudors. You #$%$ are so lucky I am not King! Machiavelli advised his Prince to exterminate all his enemies quickly then kill no more. The lemmings will accept that you had to kill your enemies and will be gratified that you had the self-control to stop. America need to exterminate about 20 million radicals.</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369193081770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369193251476-89</Id><Title>Teachers in Moore, OK sacrificed their bodies &amp; lives to protect children in their care!</Title><Msg>These people are great American Heroes and should each be awarded the Medal of Freedom. (Highest Honor a President can give to a civilian!)</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369193251476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369193314723-90</Id><Topic><Title>Chelsea Clinton is the New 'Multi-Faith Leader' at NYU</Title><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369192651158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh gawd! Chealsea baby! i'm c u m i n g! aaaaahhhhhh!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369193314723</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369193486775-91</Id><Topic><Title>IRS official toplead the 5th</Title><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1369181603228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 20:13:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Offer her a quick death if she confesses, or burn her at the stake. Your choice, Honey Pie!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369193486775</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369194068749-92</Id><Title>There was no practical reason for Alice Eve to appear in her lingerie in "Star Trek Into Darkness"</Title><Msg>That's true. She could have been totally naked! Or maybe tight-laced in just an exotic corset that exposed everything! WOW!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.obama</Username><Timestamp>1369194068749</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 23:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>