<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371880764643-1</Id><Title>with all that money...ellison sure got ripped off by the plastic surgeon.</Title><Msg>Now he looks like that guy who sold Intel that security software. Weird. He is going to get more wrinkles again if the stock acts like this.</Msg><Username>grgsvll</Username><Timestamp>1371880764643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 01:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371884627834-2</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted 10K at close today</Title><Username>bikahika</Username><Timestamp>1371845477610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The swing low last November was about 29.35, so there would be a lot of support there, since people who missed the bull move this spring would now get a chance to buy at the old low. People were buying at 30 in case it does not give them a chance lower such as at 29.35. So I think likely it can gap higher and bounce Monday even if the markets are not bouncing. To hedge I guess one could buy futures contracts Sunday night?</Msg><Username>paths_ca</Username><Timestamp>1371884627834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 03:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371899818441-3</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted 10K at close today</Title><Username>bikahika</Username><Timestamp>1371845477610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 16:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorted 7K two hours before close.</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1371899818441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:16:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371899892048-4</Id><Title>Shorted 7K before close.</Title><Msg>Cha ching!</Msg><Username>geraldmcginty</Username><Timestamp>1371899892048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371901335877-5</Id><Title>I love reading about these great stock traders here and their huge buys, sells and short sales.</Title><Msg>They always say they made the trade at right price AFTER..waaaaaaaay afterwards.. wanting others to believe they shorted at the high, went long at the low, sold at the high, bought more at the low again etc. I don't believe one of you and the ones claiming they bought $100k of ORCL as though it was a purchase of an EggaMuffin. Why are you all so full of it? Oh, one poster DID say he intended to buy a 100 shares at yesterdays open........thanks for your honesty.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371901335877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 07:42:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371905668476-6</Id><Title>"Goodhair" signs the ridiculous "Merry Christmas bill" into law</Title><Msg>Real Time's Bill Maher took Texas Gov. "Goodhair" Rick Perry to task for signing the ridiculous "Merry Christmas bill" into law, which is supposed to protect Christmas and "other holiday celebrations in Texas public schools from legal challenges." MAHER: New Rule: If you're thinking about the sanctity of Christmas in June, just stop. This week Texas Gov. Rick Perry signed the "Merry Christmas bill," protecting people who say "Merry Christmas" from the people who wish they'd say something else, who total somewhere between three and nobody. Come on. It's the first day of summer. Can’t we wait to do this until Christmas season really starts -- on the last day of summer? They're not going to stop with this stuff as long as they think it's scoring them points with their wingnut base</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371905668476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 08:54:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371909282800-7</Id><Topic><Title>"Goodhair" signs the ridiculous "Merry Christmas bill" into law</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371905668476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 08:54:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Billyboy Maher is nuttier than a squirrel's first sheet in the morning. Typical of most libiots in America. Liberalism simply a disease.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371909282800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 09:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371909813118-8</Id><Title>Need to talk with someone from the government</Title><Msg>Get on any phone, just say Osambo, conservative, Tea Party, or Republican and you will hear from them presently.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371909813118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 10:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371909992291-9</Id><Topic><Title>"Goodhair" signs the ridiculous "Merry Christmas bill" into law</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371905668476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 08:54:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about a law protecting the right to say "bah humbug"? or a law protecting the easter bunny or halloween witches and the right to demand "trick or treat" ? or a law protecting the right to wear green on st Patrick's day. or...........omg!!!...................fasting for Muslims during Ramadan typically includes the increased offering of salat (prayers) and recitation of the Quran........................................</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371909992291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 10:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371917369978-10</Id><Title>What is the 'Cloud'?</Title><Msg>The 'Cloud' is ethereal and scalable. It's somewhat abstract but it's free and and not prone to regulatory restricitions. Because anyone can use it, it is democratic. Outside of external controls it's a favorite of businesses and individuals and that is why corporations are employing it, though no one understands it (See Ellison, Larry). Business are going to the 'Cloud' because if you don't go there you will be 'Cloudless'-a conditon no one wants to be in-except maybe pilots. But put your stuff in the 'Clloud' at your own risk. Several people that I've read about have lost their stuff in the "Cloud'. Also once in the "Cloud' someone else might claim your stuff which, if you've worked on it for 10 years would be a bummer. This little essay may or may not go into the 'Cloud'-no one knows but if they do they are not telling.</Msg><Username>kip_castle</Username><Timestamp>1371917369978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 12:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371919460051-11</Id><Topic><Title>"Goodhair" signs the ridiculous "Merry Christmas bill" into law</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371905668476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 08:54:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give it time. Nut cases are always trying to ban something. Look at the freakazoid in NYC trying to ban large soft drinks. The only thing that really offends me are the thieves of the NWO that have their hands in my pocket. They run BOTH parties.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1371919460051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 12:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371922763061-12</Id><Topic><Title>"Goodhair" signs the ridiculous "Merry Christmas bill" into law</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371905668476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 08:54:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least the ban on large sugar drinks would do a good service..... fighting obesity.... USA did just fine before they began pushing supersize everything.... junk food pushers are like heroin and meth dealers in many ways......... [large sugar drink ban ] would address one of the fundamental causes of obesity—the growing portion size of sweetened drinks,” Dr. Y. Claire Wang, one of the researchers, said in a statement. The ban was originally proposed by Bloomberg last year. It was blocked by a judge in March and is back in appeals court this week. The U.S. leads the world in soda consumption as more and more American adults and children become obese.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371922763061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 13:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371924665274-13</Id><Title>Long Bet - I bought 150k of ORCL at 30.21. You will be kicking yourself if you sell here. Safe bet below</Title><Msg>Here is my long strategy --- I know Oracle can dip lower, but with a market cap this big, I'm in for 3 months with a trailing stop at 33.00. There is too much pressure on ORCL -- if sales continue to disappoint they will cut their prices and provide incentive to long term contracts. They will find a way to increase earnings. Look at their history of missing earnings 3 times in a row (NOT LIKELY) (and this last miss was an overreaction) An insider sold 85k at around 34.00 prior to earnings release. After these alliances with Salesforce and MSFT -- Im waiting for a tech rally that will get me 20-23% gain. We'll revisit this in three months, and I think I might be pleasantly surprised. I did this with Dell and had the same results. P/E is too low for it to fall lower than 29.58 unless something serious like Housing Sales (which can affect whole market) is poor on Tuesday or Bernanke steps in again and stops bond buying. Wont happen either. Get in while you can, at a minimum ORCL will continue raising its dividend. A great long term bet. Dont be scared by the drop, very similar to March. As Guns N roses says -- Patience</Msg><Username>jcapsom</Username><Timestamp>1371924665274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 14:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371926190608-14</Id><Topic><Title>The price is eright it time to buy now</Title><Username>raystock48079</Username><Timestamp>1363979299375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 15:08:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I took this stock down so we all could buy the shares real cheap. Now at 31.73 the shares are real cheap" Now they are even cheaper Raystock you sissy boy liar and loser</Msg><Username>artbell13</Username><Timestamp>1371926190608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 14:36:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371935578796-15</Id><Topic><Title>"Goodhair" signs the ridiculous "Merry Christmas bill" into law</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371905668476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 08:54:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those sound like liberal laws to come shortly. Hold your shorties on, they're coming.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371935578796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 17:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371935837773-16</Id><Title>One address in Atlanta, Ga.</Title><Msg>Had 23,000 checks sent there for a grand total of $46 million. Who sent all these checks to the one address? Yep, the same idiots who are going to run our healthcare. The ole IRS. America is in deep sheet girls and boys.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371935837773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 17:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371936649745-17</Id><Topic><Title>BUY rating intact - 52 week TARGET $38.00</Title><Username>stock2mm</Username><Timestamp>1371851994248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will but I am waiting for the sell off to stop before jumping in. Would rather miss a $1 or $2 up than down before this makes its move. Good trading and do your own homework and make your own decisions and take responsibility for both!</Msg><Username>ufgtor</Username><Timestamp>1371936649745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 17:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371939932141-18</Id><Title>America is in deep sheet girls and boys.</Title><Msg>But I LOVED how reagun, bush and bush did things!!!!!!!! Sgned,..nothing but a stinking repub.........</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371939932141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 18:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371940065667-19</Id><Title>repubs,..ya got NUTHIN!</Title><Msg>NUTHIN bad started with Obama. It was always there and ya LOVED IT! DROPKICK!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371940065667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 18:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371940301418-20</Id><Topic><Title>BUY rating intact - 52 week TARGET $38.00</Title><Username>stock2mm</Username><Timestamp>1371851994248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 17:59:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Company should pay more dividends. Not more pay to fat CEOs.</Msg><Username>mapp78</Username><Timestamp>1371940301418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 18:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371941282401-21</Id><Title>Could Someone Explain</Title><Msg>Why anyone in their right mind would reply to demessy? He's chained to his computer in a state of frenzy throwing out his current insidious, insipid opinion after scouring the news for something to slam. Nothing but anti-Christian, anti-Repub rhetoric. Baiting, taunting and deceit to get attention. Obnoxious to the point of disturbed. Why give him the opportunity to babble his nonsense? I no longer read his tripe, what is the point?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1371941282401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 18:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371942044241-22</Id><Title>Why anyone in their right mind would reply to demessy?</Title><Msg>To mesa? HE dropkiks you AND ALL THE REST OF YOU WITH EVERY POST.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371942044241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 19:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371942263169-23</Id><Title>Nothing but anti-Christian,</Title><Msg>You're all 100% INSECURE with your mythology and superstitions, You NEED everyone to agree and think as you do...TOO BAD! Less and less agree with you every day.Leave us alone or be dropkicked!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1371942263169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 19:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371951015447-24</Id><Topic><Title>One address in Atlanta, Ga.</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1371935837773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 17:17:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the IG report specifically mentioned that there are not enough IRS personnel to do the job properly and we know how you like to cut their budget, fire them and even whine when they ask questions........and sure rather than get the job done right you whine about having to pay taxes and bla bla bla</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371951015447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 21:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371951808525-25</Id><Title>Private insurers pay out tens of billions each year in fraudlulent claims</Title><Msg>and what do they care? They always hike your premium to cover all costs including fraud... "Coalition Against Insurance Fraud estimates that in 2006 a total of about $80 billion was lost in the United States due to insurance fraud.[4] According to estimates by the Insurance Information Institute, insurance fraud accounts for about 10 percent of the property/casualty insurance industry’s incurred losses and loss adjustment expenses.[5] The National Health Care Anti-Fraud Association estimates that 3% of the health care industry’s expenditures in the United States are due to fraudulent activities, amounting to a cost of about $51 billion.[6] Other estimates attribute as much as 10% of the total healthcare spending in the United States to fraud—about $115 billion annually................." (please stop being such white collar criminals you fraudsters!)</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371951808525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 21:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371952074251-26</Id><Title>Ratings agencies sold good ratings for cash (trillions in fraud....and people trust wall street?)</Title><Msg>Financial Crisis Smoking Gun - Ratings agencies sold good ratings for cash Matt Taibbi Reveals Financial Crisis Smoking Gun Ratings agencies sold good ratings for cash</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1371952074251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 21:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>