<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359305987338-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bigpopcomingsoon</Title><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1358884452649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 14:54:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? R YA SURE THAT YA TWO R NOT RELATED? HUH?</Msg><Username>nfny.the_hairy_schmuck</Username><Timestamp>1359305987338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:59:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359311178211-2</Id><Topic><Title>the climate scientist most quoted by AGW sceptics</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1359303320643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:15:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look up John Coleman. Founder of the Weather Channel and has a PHD in Climatology. He did a two hour special recently showing how the ones pushing Global Warming have doctored just about every input they used to support the BIG LIE.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1359311178211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 13:26:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359317143988-3</Id><Topic><Title>Global warming - the greatest progressive manipulation of data ever!</Title><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1359213356211</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:15:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are wrong on the math. It was conclusively proven the hockey stick was incorrect mat.</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1359317143988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 15:05:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359317373714-4</Id><Topic><Title>U6 is at 14.4% under Obama (avg almost 16% for 4 years)</Title><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1359212546803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 10:02:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems the progressive left likes unemployment this high. It allows them to give more "free stuff" to buy votes!</Msg><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1359317373714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 15:09:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359327439668-5</Id><Title>Undocumented Democrats.....</Title><Msg>.... Are a major part of Obama's immigration policy.</Msg><Username>dontmissthatplace</Username><Timestamp>1359327439668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 17:57:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359332245403-6</Id><Title>Imagine!! Some 2-Bit Black Chicago Politician Lecturing White Americans...</Title><Msg>on gun control, security and Government protections... as if he, his bubble-headed VP, their families, and all their buddies were not fully protected by thousands of cops and military, 24/7, which they are, as if the whack-jobs in Newtown, Aurora and Tucson were the typical American Killers, which they are not, as if Chicago were not the Murder Capitol of America, which it is, as if Chicago were not followed closely in Homicides by many other heavily Minority populated cities and communities, which it is, as if Blacks were not responsible for over 50% of all homicides in the Country, which they are, as if Murders by Blacks were not 8 times that of Whites, as if fewer guns in the hands of Good people (of all colors!) actually lowers the murder rate, which it doesn't, and finally, as if law enforcement routinely arrives to save and protect people before they get pillaged, raped and slaughtered by thugs, which they seldom do! Even worse... that 40% of White Americans would actually buy into this huge Pile of Obama-Biden-Democrat "US vs Them" Manure, like the gullible suicidal lemmings they are... especially as our current resident of the White House is easily the most divisive President in American history, gleefully pitting White against Black, Left against Right, Poor against Rich, Worker against Management/Owner, North against South, Gay against Straight, Youth against Old, Women against Men, Government against Real Americans... and it's only getting WORSE!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1359332245403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:17:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359338458234-7</Id><Topic><Title>Imagine!! Some 2-Bit Black Chicago Politician Lecturing White Americans...</Title><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1359332245403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 19:17:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The pot calling the kettle black, no pun intended. Did Mayor Rahm respond? Not on your life. He doesn't have the guts to offend his voter base. Just this week, 5 Obama supporters were gunned down in Chicago by other Obama supporters. Just your ordinary drive-by assailants with hand guns. I'm sure gun reform will fix that.</Msg><Username>yourmovepal</Username><Timestamp>1359338458234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 21:00:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>