<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373779417736-1</Id><Title>ZIMMERMAN ACQUITTED!</Title><Msg>Not Guilty of Second Degree Murder!</Msg><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1373779417736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:23:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373800158478-2</Id><Title>The Zimmerman-Martin Trial Just Goes To Show that...</Title><Msg>If we can keep PC Left-wing Nanny State Trash off of juries there's a good chance of getting Real Justice.... even with a pack of White Police State prosecutors, backed by their gestapo H00res in the Media and Government, trying to railroad a US Citizen into a 30 year jail sentence! Zimmerman was lucky enough to have a great lawyer who took it to the Naaa@zzzi wannabees and peeled away their Pigshyt race-baiting lies and 2-bit phony theories!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1373800158478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 07:09:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373806513401-3</Id><Title>Zimmerman-Martin Trial Just Goes To Show that...</Title><Msg>It shows repubs made it legal to murder here in Fl. and Jeb fat head claims that wasn't the intent.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373806513401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:55:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373806807404-4</Id><Topic><Title>ZIMMERMAN ACQUITTED!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1373779417736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not Guilty! Not Guilty! Acquitted of Second Degree Murder! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>trollingalongonmoonlightbay</Username><Timestamp>1373806807404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373808696342-5</Id><Title>Only a true racist could still think Zim was guilty of murder.</Title><Msg>Repubs,,, do shove your repub talking point claiming dems are the racists,,,just more corpis dabien from repub radio/tv. What they did and always do is.THEY say. THEY know THEY'RE the racist repubs......... how can we fight back, they ask??? I know! Lets tell THEM THEY are the racists! Dazzle them with our lying repub corpiss dabien! Whatever we are, they know we are, WE know we are,..lets just tell THEM,, THEY ARE and Carl Rve earned millions for that one.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373808696342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373808709831-6</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman-Martin Trial Just Goes To Show that...</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373806513401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:55:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drop the prosecution didn't make the case. In fact it didn't,t have a case. There was more than reasonable doubt..</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1373808709831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:31:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373808900681-7</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman-Martin Trial Just Goes To Show that...</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373806513401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:55:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's a clue, you ignorant race-baiting Democrat Pig..... killing someone in self-defense is not murder! But.... there are tens of thousands of Real Murders every year committed by young black thugs of other kids, both teens and pre-teens.... black and white! Indeed, your trouble-prone "ever so innocent" bad kid, Trayvon Martin, enjoyed posing for pictures of himself as a wannabee gangbanger, with gun in hand and a pile of jewelry by his side... and that says nothing of his decision to stalk and attack the "creepy#$%$@s-cracker" Zimmerman, punching him in the face and slamming his head on concrete.... all of which led directly to his death! Angela Corey should be jailed for life... for pimping a Pigshyt trial that never should have seen the light of day!</Msg><Username>moveon_moveoutnow</Username><Timestamp>1373808900681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:35:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809453732-8</Id><Topic><Title>Only a true racist could still think Zim was guilty of murder.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373808696342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ZIM caused this murder to happen and THAT is in the record.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373809453732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:44:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809671244-9</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman-Martin Trial Just Goes To Show that...</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373806513401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 08:55:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listening to talking heads this morning, I get the sense they would,t mind if riots start. Travis smiley, for example, said young black guys cannot stand their ground....when in fact this was not a stand your ground case. It was a self defense case</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1373809671244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373809897769-10</Id><Topic><Title>Only a true racist could still think Zim was guilty of murder.</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373808696342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:31:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Murder is not in the record. The record shows zim was acquitted. Now go start a riot or something.</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1373809897769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373810369766-11</Id><Title>Here's a clue, you ignorant race-baiting Democrat Pig..... another repub LIE.. They know THEY are the race baiters,, willie horton for examp</Title><Msg>but Carl Rove or someoneLIKE told repubs to call DEMS racebaiters in attempt to dazzle with their corpissdabien...NICE DROPKICK PAUPER!</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373810369766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373812011978-12</Id><Title>WAAAAAA! ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Msg>And the little black kid had the nerve to fight back. I won because I had a gun. And he didn't know it.</Msg><Username>coughingreddinkydick</Username><Timestamp>1373812011978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373815368266-13</Id><Topic><Title>Here's a clue, you ignorant race-baiting Democrat Pig..... another repub LIE.. They know THEY are the race baiters,, willie horton for examp</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373810369766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:59:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pigshyt!! Willie Horton was a poster child for a significant portion of Black society and culture... which has turned rotten to the core... thanks in large measure to their PC Left Nanny State Massa's in the Democrat Party, Black &amp; White.... who have enslaved them to Government handouts, give-me's, entitlement, ignorance, violence and criminality, all while destroying self-responsibility and discipline!!</Msg><Username>pt_bama_nation</Username><Timestamp>1373815368266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373816238924-14</Id><Topic><Title>Here's a clue, you ignorant race-baiting Democrat Pig..... another repub LIE.. They know THEY are the race baiters,, willie horton for examp</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373810369766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 09:59:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Years ago in San Diego there was a Black man that had a small chain of liquor stores. He wanted to sell them to another Black. He looked a long time and could find no one willing to take that responsibility. He finally sold them to an Iraqi immigrant. The few Blacks that do work hard to better themselves are made fun of by others as "Uncle Toms". These people usually associate with Whites as they find no friendship with their own people. Want some real "race baiting? Go to the joint. Interesting to is that the Mexicans will usually side with the Whites against Blacks.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1373816238924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373816372248-15</Id><Topic><Title>WAAAAAA! ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Username>coughingreddinkydick</Username><Timestamp>1373812011978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Fight back?" No, Zimmerman was attacked and HE fought back, with as gun. A fat, out of shape guy assaulted by a 175 lb. first string football player.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1373816372248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:39:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373817177450-16</Id><Title>Isn't that cute! Dropkick the puke, like the 9 yr old he is, resorts to "name calling" with my ID!</Title><Msg>No brains, no imagination, no ability to read &amp; comprehend. But, like all moronic liberals, he can act like a child. Bully taw!</Msg><Username>coughingredink</Username><Timestamp>1373817177450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 11:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373818155152-17</Id><Title>a cop's take on Zimmerman</Title><Msg>George Zimmerman: George fits into a special category that we will just term the perpetual wanna-be. He loves guns, he loves MMA, he watches cops. He fancies himself a criminal investigator in the making. He patrols and has a direct line into dispatch making his mind up that, sneaky perp wasn't going to get away from him this time. His GUN makes him do things that he shouldn't do because he is basically a coward. He follows, attacks, then is bested in a ground fight by a 17 year old boy that he outweighed by several pounds that he then decides to shoot at point black range. Even the fight scene that played out in Zimmermans mind was written like a urban contemporary movie with Treyvon's last words saying "you got me". (really?) As a police officer you are trained to use the necessary force to subdue the threat but if there is no longer a deadly threat, deadly force is no longer necessary or approved. Translation = Had this been a real police officer, his #$%$ would be in deep #$%$. The local police new he was a cheese ball. That's why they never hired him. They probably knew him by name. I think what we have in George Zimmerman is a person who very likely has tried to be a police officer many, many, many times but couldn't for some very good reasons. He has probably tried to apply to police departments and could not p#$%$ the entry requirements. Now from the surface you would say this is because of his size. You may surmise that he probably couldn't meet the weight or fitness standard. But I disagree. I would wager that Mr. Zimmerman has probably never gotten past the psyche evaluation. I'm sure laws prohibit the release of applicant information but I would bet that he has applied to at least 2 or more sheriff or police departments in the area and has been declined. You see its a relatively small community. Once you begin applying and fail a polygraph or fail a psych, that follows you. Chances are hes failed a few and has likely been blacklisted. Judg</Msg><Username>olderwisercrankier</Username><Timestamp>1373818155152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373820714866-18</Id><Title>I Wish Someone Would</Title><Msg>gag Al Sharpton with a yard of bubble wrap. Talk about race baiting, he's the master. Some black woman on HLN was upset the prosecution didn't show photos of Trayvon hugging his mother and riding a horse. As if that would exonerate him. Let's face it, there are a million young black men like Trayvon that have no chance at pro sports and have been easily influenced by the Hip Hop culture..... drugs, gangbanging, burglary, gold front teeth which is supposed to signal some kind of coolness and many dropping out of school. Did his parents just ignore his activities and what about his older brother, he looked like he would have been a role model for Trayvon but appearances can fool you. I can bet if this incident didn't happen, 5 years down the road Trayvon would be in prison for crimes he perpetrated. It's one less wanna be gangsta off the street.</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1373820714866</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373823241811-19</Id><Topic><Title>a cop's take on Zimmerman</Title><Username>olderwisercrankier</Username><Timestamp>1373818155152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 12:09:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't know Zimmerman, his background, nor his ambitions. You are speculating just as Obummer, the special prosecutor, and the three idiot prosecutors who thought the louder they talked the more impact they would have. O'Mara was right, the MSM is completely out of control. They edited tapes, slanted evidence, and showed pictures of Trayvon and Zimmerman that misrepresented the participants in this tragedy. Good to know that there are still people like you who have ESP and know that Zimmerman took any lie detector tests and failed them. You are a baiter of the worse kind. Maybe if I beat you about the head with my fists and a concrete sidewalk, you might think differently about the gibberish you wrote.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373823241811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373823364886-20</Id><Topic><Title>WAAAAAA! ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Username>coughingreddinkydick</Username><Timestamp>1373812011978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's the lesson all fathers need to teach their son. A few words by both would have probably defused the situation.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373823364886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373823607471-21</Id><Topic><Title>Zim did exactly what a normal person would do when attacked by someone bigger, stronger, younger,</Title><Username>siriusf8</Username><Timestamp>1373752218453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 17:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm for a beer summit like the one Obummer had with the professor. The Bummer, AG Holder, and Zimm.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373823607471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373823708255-22</Id><Topic><Title>The jury should know zim attacked his wife and the cops</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373755500749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 18:45:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both backgrounds should come out and you will see the true Trayvon and the true Zimmerman. Kickbird, it will be an eye opener.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373823708255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:41:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373823898871-23</Id><Topic><Title>"There is no reason in the world to carry a gun for Neighborhood Watch,"</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373746787572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 16:19:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thing he did, otherwise he would be dead or still in the hospital.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373823898871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373824140044-24</Id><Title>The three prosecutors and their idiot lady chief prosecutor</Title><Msg>Will probably have sanctions thrown at them. They withheld evidence and the judge seemed complicit in their shenanigans. Talk about zealots who cared not about the evidence, but just about being as loud as possible. They are of the Harry Dingy Reid model, worthless pieces of #$%$....</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373824140044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373824255017-25</Id><Topic><Title>The three prosecutors and their idiot lady chief prosecutor</Title><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373824140044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:49:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As O'Mara and West said, they should be ashamed along with the worthless MSM who care not a whit about the truth, they only care about ratings.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373824255017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373829826000-26</Id><Title>zimscum murdered the kid and there were no actual witnesses to clearly detail what happened</Title><Msg>so it's hard to convicit a murderer under these circumstances. I'm sure glad they tried though. The scumpunkzim followed Martin and caused entire thing to happen..He's a murderer but repubs changed the law in Fl making it hard to convict. No one saw OJ kill yet you #$%$ wanted conviction as with Casey Anthony....You're repub racists your records prove it.</Msg><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373829826000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373832812363-27</Id><Topic><Title>zimscum murdered the kid and there were no actual witnesses to clearly detail what happened</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373829826000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go cry in your Corona, butthead. The jury saw and heard the facts and decided the way the majority of Americans saw and heard it. Zimmerman did not intend to shoot until he was attacked, No one but Trayvon caused his own death thus the verdict came back as it did. This has nothing to do with Repubs, you slowwitted VVop This was a black vs hispanic crime but the media and that freak Al Sharpton pumped it as a white vs black crime stirring up racial dissent from all sides. Tell me why blacks aren't convulsing over blacks killing blacks in Chicago and Oakland? No fun if they can't riot, right?</Msg><Username>passthebuckaroo</Username><Timestamp>1373832812363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373834607943-28</Id><Topic><Title>ZIMMERMAN ACQUITTED!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1373779417736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and his evil commie-fascist-mooslime minions have spent six years propagandizing America and they STILL can't bring in a "guilty" verdict! ROTFLMFAO!</Msg><Username>barakthemagicnegroe</Username><Timestamp>1373834607943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373835543680-29</Id><Title>affirmative action now applied to justice system</Title><Msg>well done, obama</Msg><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1373835543680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373835658376-30</Id><Title>A Drunk, Racist Got Knocked Out by black man standing his ground</Title><Msg>A Drunk, Racist Got Knocked Out There was an altercation between a drunk, racist, well-dressed white man and a black couple in New York's Greenwich Village on Friday. It did not end well for the white man, who is now in critical condition after he was knocked out and his head hit the pavement. The drunken white man hurled racial slurs at the couple who were, up until this point, privately enjoying some Mexican food. "You n-----s are why I lost my job," the unidentified drunk said, witnesses told the Daily News. "This n----r wants to fight me!" he yelled, police told the Post.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373835658376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373837944332-31</Id><Title>Oracle software sucks</Title><Msg>Oracle is like IBM and Microsoft. Their products sucked but they knew how to sell. Oracle's database is one of the most user-hostile POS around, but it doesn't matter as Oracle is able to push their products onto customers.</Msg><Username>maxkissime</Username><Timestamp>1373837944332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373839704142-32</Id><Topic><Title>A Drunk, Racist Got Knocked Out by black man standing his ground</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373835658376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No problem. Al, Jesse, Holder and his boys will probably sue for .........they will think of something.</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373839704142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373840037652-33</Id><Title>America has spoken. Trayvon is guilty.</Title><Msg>Isn't immigration reform wonderful?</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1373840037652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373840102388-34</Id><Topic><Title>affirmative action now applied to justice system</Title><Username>harryschmoe</Username><Timestamp>1373835543680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's destroyed just about everything else, why not our system of justice in America. He is a true failure. No, make that FAILURE!</Msg><Username>vanzinf</Username><Timestamp>1373840102388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:15:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373840178733-35</Id><Title>Now we can concentrate on the thousands of blacks who commit murder each year.</Title><Msg>Blacks destroy schools and neighborhoods with crime.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1373840178733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373840677670-36</Id><Topic><Title>A Drunk, Racist Got Knocked Out by black man standing his ground</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373835658376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ainte diversity wonderful? Maybe you should stay in your own neighborhoods.</Msg><Username>crombola19040</Username><Timestamp>1373840677670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373841662860-37</Id><Topic><Title>A Drunk, Racist Got Knocked Out by black man standing his ground</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373835658376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>News said Feds are considering civil rights charges against Zimmerman. No doubt that will happen especially under a holder doj</Msg><Username>seeburgc</Username><Timestamp>1373841662860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373845552846-38</Id><Topic><Title>zimscum murdered the kid and there were no actual witnesses to clearly detail what happened</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373829826000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny, I watched an eyewitness testify that Zimmerman was assaulted and was being straddled by Trayvon who was beating his head on the ground. You are a liar!</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1373845552846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373845792828-39</Id><Topic><Title>zimscum murdered the kid and there were no actual witnesses to clearly detail what happened</Title><Username>dropkickpubs4321</Username><Timestamp>1373829826000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had lots of fights with Blacks in school. The only time I lost was when 2 or more were on my back. I retaliated a day after one fight with three on my back by catching one in the gym shower. I walked up and laid him out cold. They were going to arrest me and do nothing to the three. I was in with the cops still sporting bruises from being kicked. This due to White "liberal" #$%$.</Msg><Username>lewcor</Username><Timestamp>1373845792828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 19:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373848894712-40</Id><Topic><Title>Oracle software sucks</Title><Username>maxkissime</Username><Timestamp>1373837944332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 17:39:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really ???</Msg><Username>arthates</Username><Timestamp>1373848894712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373848994159-41</Id><Topic><Title>Transferring to NYSE : Mondays PPS prediction</Title><Username>garrettklein87</Username><Timestamp>1373744776680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 15:46:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, is this called UPLISTING ? Should be good.</Msg><Username>arthates</Username><Timestamp>1373848994159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373851670655-42</Id><Title>Hey, racist Dems --- One man was violently attacked by another, and the attacker was unfortunatel killed</Title><Msg>End of argument.</Msg><Username>cykdelic</Username><Timestamp>1373851670655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373854994714-43</Id><Topic><Title>ZIMMERMAN ACQUITTED!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1373779417736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All Hail Kommrade Obama!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1373854994714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373855107725-44</Id><Title>ALL HAIL COMMRADE OBAMA!</Title><Msg>And his beloved Empress, Michelle!</Msg><Username>bullwinkle.themoose</Username><Timestamp>1373855107725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:25:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373858514511-45</Id><Topic><Title>ZIMMERMAN ACQUITTED!</Title><Username>beelzebufo_ampinga_10048</Username><Timestamp>1373779417736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 01:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Justice Department Explores Possible Federal Charges in Zimmerman Case AP DOJ says it will determine if prosecutors will file criminal civil rights charges in death of Trayvon Martin after Florida jury finds Zimmerman 'not guilty' on all counts, just days after department was accused by watchdog of supporting anti-Zimmerman protests after shooting.</Msg><Username>hillary_is_sewage</Username><Timestamp>1373858514511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 23:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>